<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 04:48:43 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Uwerx (WERX) Keeps Breaking New Heights As Stellar (XLM) And Stacks (STX) Rally]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/uwerx-werx-keeps-breaking-new-heights-as-stellar-xlm-and-stacks-stx-rally</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-10-at-192149.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-10-at-192149.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-10-at-192149.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 19:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/uwerx-werx-keeps-breaking-new-heights-as-stellar-xlm-and-stacks-stx-rally</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s5">Despite the promise of a bullish season, the crypto market has persisted with a bearish trend, causing many tokens to experience huge reductions in their total market capitalizations. Hence, tokens like Stellar (XLM) and Stacks (STX) struggle to stay in the game.</p>
<p class="s5">Uwerx has breezed through many successful presale stages, rapidly selling out and reaching new heights daily.</p>
Stacks (STX) Launches Stacks 2.1
<p class="s5">Stacks (STX) aims to create a more secure, decentralized internet owned by users. The Layer-2 blockchain provides a scalable infrastructure for building decentralized applications (dApps) and performing decentralized finance (DeFi) transactions on the Bitcoin (BTC) blockchain.</p>
<p class="s5">The Stacks (STX) platform improves the base protocol by introducing smart contract functionality for Bitcoin (BTC) users. Furthermore, it enables users to create and trade valuable non-fungible tokens (NFTs) on popular digital marketplaces.</p>
<p class="s5">Moreover, Stacks (STX) also provides the underbanked access to vital financial services, like micropayments and loans, without interference from governments or other intermediaries.</p>
<p class="s5">The blockchain recently released a significant upgrade in March 2023. Stacks (STX) launched the Stacks 2.1 upgrade to improve the speed and volume of DeFi transactions. The launch caused the STX token's price to surge 14% in less than 24hrs, reaching $1.27.</p>
<p class="s5">However, the token has steadily declined since March after reaching more than $1.5. STX stayed at $0.9 since April but has now fallen even more, trading at $0.6 currently.</p>
Stellar (XLM) Partners With Anchain.ai
<p class="s5">Stellar (XLM) is a decentralized payment system based on the Stellar Consensus Protocol. The blockchain enables the exchange of traditional crypto coins and fiat money across international borders.</p>
<p class="s5">Furthermore, Stellar (XLM) recently partnered with an AI-powered security company, Anchain.ai. This integration is aimed at enhancing cross-border payment security. Stellar (XLM) seeks to provide more accessible security tools to create a secure developer ecosystem.</p>
<p class="s5">The XLM token has been on a constant decline since March after it reached $0.13. The coin took a significant fall to settle at $0.7 in April.</p>
<p class="s5">Stellar (XLM) is experiencing a decline in Q2 2023, making only very minuscule backward and forward leaps. The XLM token has been stuck in the $0.8 range since last week. Holders are looking wide-eyed for appreciation, while investors are watching and wondering if now would be an excellent time to get in the game.</p>
<p class="s5">However, experts are predicting an exaggerated dip, even with the steadiness of the token.</p>
Uwerx (WERX) Presale Is Breaking New Heights
<p class="s5">This new crypto project focuses on the freelancer economy. With freelancing becoming widely adopted, even by big companies like Google, the project is on the right track. The project has undergone vetting and auditing by SolidProof and InterFi Network to ensure transparency.</p>
<p class="s5">Uwerx aims to provide a secure, fast, and accessible platform for freelancers and their clients. Uwerx charges a low transaction fee of 1%, while other freelancing platforms, such as Upwork and Fiverr, charge 10%-20%.</p>
<p class="s5">The project is in its fifth funding stage and has a 72.5 million token allocation, with WERX priced at $0.0315 per token. The total presale token allocation increased to 57% from 45%, creating more opportunities for early supporters. The hard cap presale will occur on 31st July 2023.</p>
<p class="s5">Uwerx recently announced preparations to transition to the Beta version to enable users to start testing. The Alpha version of the platform was launched last week. The launch came with Landing Page and Sign-Up Page. However, the platform has been recently updated with more pages, including the Login, Forgot Password, Freelancer or Client Initiation, Job Creation Process, My Activity, and Initial Step of Job Creation and Initial Step Of Finding Talent pages. Users can also send helpful feedback to Uwerx through an email, feedback@uwerx.network.</p>
<p class="s5">Uwerx provides a Uwerx Vault to help secure users' tokens. Users can store their tokens for a specified time and earn rewards using the Vault.</p>
<p class="s5">Moreover, the team has locked the developer's liquidity, which was set for 25 years after the presale. The lock happened after 82.8% of the community voted on an instant lock. Also, 92.8% of the community voted for a test airdrop to enable users to validate their wallet addresses.</p>
<p class="s5">The project has an excellent presale run, and with that, the developers have reduced the token allocation from 8% to 7%, increasing investor confidence in the project.</p>
<p class="s5">The Uwerx developers utilized an agile methodology approach to achieve presale success. The approach uses rapid development and accelerated deployment through feedback.</p>
<p class="s5">Stellar (XLM) and Stacks (STX) give holders much anxiety with their current standings as the tokens seem to be rolling downhill.</p>
<p class="s5">Fortunately, Uwerx is pushing a very successful presale run. Uwerx presents better features and investment potential and has shown a clean record to investors with a successful presale and increased value of the WERX token.Take advantage of Uwerx's current discounted price of $0.047725 with a purchase bonus of 15%. However, be aware that the price will rise to $0.05245 by today (Monday 10th) at 18:00 UTC. It is recommended to act quickly and make your WERX token purchase today.</p>
Follow the links below to enjoy the 15% bonus:
<p class="s5">Website: https://www.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s5">Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s5">Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network &nbsp;</p>
<p class="s5">Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s5">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s5">Despite the promise of a bullish season, the crypto market has persisted with a bearish trend, causing many tokens to experience huge reductions in their total market capitalizations. Hence, tokens like Stellar (XLM) and Stacks (STX) struggle to stay in the game.</p>
<p class="s5">Uwerx has breezed through many successful presale stages, rapidly selling out and reaching new heights daily.</p>
Stacks (STX) Launches Stacks 2.1
<p class="s5">Stacks (STX) aims to create a more secure, decentralized internet owned by users. The Layer-2 blockchain provides a scalable infrastructure for building decentralized applications (dApps) and performing decentralized finance (DeFi) transactions on the Bitcoin (BTC) blockchain.</p>
<p class="s5">The Stacks (STX) platform improves the base protocol by introducing smart contract functionality for Bitcoin (BTC) users. Furthermore, it enables users to create and trade valuable non-fungible tokens (NFTs) on popular digital marketplaces.</p>
<p class="s5">Moreover, Stacks (STX) also provides the underbanked access to vital financial services, like micropayments and loans, without interference from governments or other intermediaries.</p>
<p class="s5">The blockchain recently released a significant upgrade in March 2023. Stacks (STX) launched the Stacks 2.1 upgrade to improve the speed and volume of DeFi transactions. The launch caused the STX token's price to surge 14% in less than 24hrs, reaching $1.27.</p>
<p class="s5">However, the token has steadily declined since March after reaching more than $1.5. STX stayed at $0.9 since April but has now fallen even more, trading at $0.6 currently.</p>
Stellar (XLM) Partners With Anchain.ai
<p class="s5">Stellar (XLM) is a decentralized payment system based on the Stellar Consensus Protocol. The blockchain enables the exchange of traditional crypto coins and fiat money across international borders.</p>
<p class="s5">Furthermore, Stellar (XLM) recently partnered with an AI-powered security company, Anchain.ai. This integration is aimed at enhancing cross-border payment security. Stellar (XLM) seeks to provide more accessible security tools to create a secure developer ecosystem.</p>
<p class="s5">The XLM token has been on a constant decline since March after it reached $0.13. The coin took a significant fall to settle at $0.7 in April.</p>
<p class="s5">Stellar (XLM) is experiencing a decline in Q2 2023, making only very minuscule backward and forward leaps. The XLM token has been stuck in the $0.8 range since last week. Holders are looking wide-eyed for appreciation, while investors are watching and wondering if now would be an excellent time to get in the game.</p>
<p class="s5">However, experts are predicting an exaggerated dip, even with the steadiness of the token.</p>
Uwerx (WERX) Presale Is Breaking New Heights
<p class="s5">This new crypto project focuses on the freelancer economy. With freelancing becoming widely adopted, even by big companies like Google, the project is on the right track. The project has undergone vetting and auditing by SolidProof and InterFi Network to ensure transparency.</p>
<p class="s5">Uwerx aims to provide a secure, fast, and accessible platform for freelancers and their clients. Uwerx charges a low transaction fee of 1%, while other freelancing platforms, such as Upwork and Fiverr, charge 10%-20%.</p>
<p class="s5">The project is in its fifth funding stage and has a 72.5 million token allocation, with WERX priced at $0.0315 per token. The total presale token allocation increased to 57% from 45%, creating more opportunities for early supporters. The hard cap presale will occur on 31st July 2023.</p>
<p class="s5">Uwerx recently announced preparations to transition to the Beta version to enable users to start testing. The Alpha version of the platform was launched last week. The launch came with Landing Page and Sign-Up Page. However, the platform has been recently updated with more pages, including the Login, Forgot Password, Freelancer or Client Initiation, Job Creation Process, My Activity, and Initial Step of Job Creation and Initial Step Of Finding Talent pages. Users can also send helpful feedback to Uwerx through an email, feedback@uwerx.network.</p>
<p class="s5">Uwerx provides a Uwerx Vault to help secure users' tokens. Users can store their tokens for a specified time and earn rewards using the Vault.</p>
<p class="s5">Moreover, the team has locked the developer's liquidity, which was set for 25 years after the presale. The lock happened after 82.8% of the community voted on an instant lock. Also, 92.8% of the community voted for a test airdrop to enable users to validate their wallet addresses.</p>
<p class="s5">The project has an excellent presale run, and with that, the developers have reduced the token allocation from 8% to 7%, increasing investor confidence in the project.</p>
<p class="s5">The Uwerx developers utilized an agile methodology approach to achieve presale success. The approach uses rapid development and accelerated deployment through feedback.</p>
<p class="s5">Stellar (XLM) and Stacks (STX) give holders much anxiety with their current standings as the tokens seem to be rolling downhill.</p>
<p class="s5">Fortunately, Uwerx is pushing a very successful presale run. Uwerx presents better features and investment potential and has shown a clean record to investors with a successful presale and increased value of the WERX token.Take advantage of Uwerx's current discounted price of $0.047725 with a purchase bonus of 15%. However, be aware that the price will rise to $0.05245 by today (Monday 10th) at 18:00 UTC. It is recommended to act quickly and make your WERX token purchase today.</p>
Follow the links below to enjoy the 15% bonus:
<p class="s5">Website: https://www.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s5">Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s5">Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network &nbsp;</p>
<p class="s5">Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s5">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Wasn’t crypto supposed to be for retail investors?]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/wasnt-crypto-supposed-to-be-for-retail-investors</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bit-54.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bit-54.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bit-54.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 17:57:43 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/wasnt-crypto-supposed-to-be-for-retail-investors</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>As retail investors leave crypto in droves, is institutional money coming in to quietly buy the cream of the cryptocurrencies?</p>
Sell and perhaps get in lower?
<p>Bitcoin is at a critical juncture. A narrative going around social media platforms such as Twitter suggests that with the backdrop of the SEC enforcement actions against Coinbase and Binance, the liquidity and investor interest that would normally propel the next bitcoin bull market just isn&rsquo;t there.</p>
<p>Bitcoin is going sideways and downwards, and certain influencers and analysts believe that the latest rejection from the $31,000 price level is the start of a fairly large pullback that could be in the range of 30% for bitcoin and up to 50% for the altcoins.</p>
<p>In this sort of very uncertain environment weak hands are going to sell and even stronger hands might be thinking to do the same thing with a view to improving their position a lot lower down.</p>
Fickle retail money vs institutional know-how
<p>So we perhaps have the perfect scenario for an institutional take over of cryptocurrencies that have been in the hands of retail investors ever since they came onto the scene.</p>
<p>It must be wondered though just how fickle retail is. It is hardly any time at all since Larry Fink, CEO of Blackrock, the largest asset management firm in the world, said on national TV in the US that bitcoin was an &ldquo;international asset&rdquo; and &ldquo;digitised gold&rdquo;.</p>
<p>Obviously, it&rsquo;s not at all sure that the Blackrock filing for a Spot Bitcoin ETF will be approved, especially given Gensler and the SEC&rsquo;s extremely negative stance on crypto. Be that as it may, Blackrock isn&rsquo;t just any company. It is a behemoth, and has untold influence in Washington and across the world. It will surely get the business done at some point.</p>
<p>A Washington Post article published on Saturday posits that the &ldquo;tech-focused investors&rdquo; have moved on from crypto and are now much more interested in artificial intelligence, and that the once crazy amounts of venture capital that used to be thrown at crypto has &ldquo;slowed to a trickle&rdquo;.</p>
<p>When this kind of narrative becomes this strong, and the bitcoin halving only 280 days away, it&rsquo;s a perfect time for big money to slowly start coming into the crypto space. It cannot be argued that crypto will provide the solutions for many issues, especially in finance, and therefore now could be a good time for entry.</p>
The narrative is established
<p>When Satoshi Nakamoto launched bitcoin in the time of the Great Financial Crisis of 2008, he meant for bitcoin to be bought by the people in order to save them from the next, probably even worse crisis.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The average retail investor is scared though. Mainstream media has done its work, and so has the Biden administration, central banks across the world, and regulatory agencies such as the SEC. As this next financial crisis looms larger, retail needs to be brave and hang on in there. The alternative can be so much worse.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As retail investors leave crypto in droves, is institutional money coming in to quietly buy the cream of the cryptocurrencies?</p>
Sell and perhaps get in lower?
<p>Bitcoin is at a critical juncture. A narrative going around social media platforms such as Twitter suggests that with the backdrop of the SEC enforcement actions against Coinbase and Binance, the liquidity and investor interest that would normally propel the next bitcoin bull market just isn&rsquo;t there.</p>
<p>Bitcoin is going sideways and downwards, and certain influencers and analysts believe that the latest rejection from the $31,000 price level is the start of a fairly large pullback that could be in the range of 30% for bitcoin and up to 50% for the altcoins.</p>
<p>In this sort of very uncertain environment weak hands are going to sell and even stronger hands might be thinking to do the same thing with a view to improving their position a lot lower down.</p>
Fickle retail money vs institutional know-how
<p>So we perhaps have the perfect scenario for an institutional take over of cryptocurrencies that have been in the hands of retail investors ever since they came onto the scene.</p>
<p>It must be wondered though just how fickle retail is. It is hardly any time at all since Larry Fink, CEO of Blackrock, the largest asset management firm in the world, said on national TV in the US that bitcoin was an &ldquo;international asset&rdquo; and &ldquo;digitised gold&rdquo;.</p>
<p>Obviously, it&rsquo;s not at all sure that the Blackrock filing for a Spot Bitcoin ETF will be approved, especially given Gensler and the SEC&rsquo;s extremely negative stance on crypto. Be that as it may, Blackrock isn&rsquo;t just any company. It is a behemoth, and has untold influence in Washington and across the world. It will surely get the business done at some point.</p>
<p>A Washington Post article published on Saturday posits that the &ldquo;tech-focused investors&rdquo; have moved on from crypto and are now much more interested in artificial intelligence, and that the once crazy amounts of venture capital that used to be thrown at crypto has &ldquo;slowed to a trickle&rdquo;.</p>
<p>When this kind of narrative becomes this strong, and the bitcoin halving only 280 days away, it&rsquo;s a perfect time for big money to slowly start coming into the crypto space. It cannot be argued that crypto will provide the solutions for many issues, especially in finance, and therefore now could be a good time for entry.</p>
The narrative is established
<p>When Satoshi Nakamoto launched bitcoin in the time of the Great Financial Crisis of 2008, he meant for bitcoin to be bought by the people in order to save them from the next, probably even worse crisis.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The average retail investor is scared though. Mainstream media has done its work, and so has the Biden administration, central banks across the world, and regulatory agencies such as the SEC. As this next financial crisis looms larger, retail needs to be brave and hang on in there. The alternative can be so much worse.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Standard Chartered Projects Bitcoin $BTC To Reach $120K by 2024]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/standard-chartered-projects-bitcoin-btc-to-reach-120k-by-2024</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/standard-chartered-btc-prediction-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/standard-chartered-btc-prediction-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/standard-chartered-btc-prediction-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 17:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/standard-chartered-projects-bitcoin-btc-to-reach-120k-by-2024</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">In its latest research report, Standard Chartered Bank has presented an optimistic forecast for Bitcoin, suggesting that the leading cryptocurrency could touch the $50,000 milestone by the end of 2021, and climb to an impressive $120,000 by 2024's close.</p>
Mining Economics Fueling Bitcoin's Potential Ascend
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Driving this prediction is a key factor: the growing profitability of Bitcoin miners. As Geoff Kendrick, the head of FX and digital assets research at Standard Chartered, explained in the report, miners play a vital role in determining the net supply of the newly minted cryptocurrency, on top of their responsibility of maintaining the Bitcoin ledger.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"Increased miner profitability per BTC (bitcoin) mined means they can sell less while maintaining cash inflows, reducing net BTC supply and pushing BTC prices higher," Kendrick stated.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to Standard Chartered's report, the primary driving force behind its predicted Bitcoin price surge involves Bitcoin miners. These miners create approximately 900 new Bitcoins globally every day. The costs they incur, predominantly power expenses for high-performance computers, are currently being offset by selling 100% of these freshly minted coins, as per the bank's estimation.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">However, should Bitcoin's value climb to $50,000, Standard Chartered believes miners would only need to sell between 20% and 30% of their new coins to cover their costs. This reduction in the number of new coins entering the market could potentially limit the available supply, thereby driving prices up.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">A surge in miner profitability per Bitcoin mined means miners are under less pressure to sell their output. This shift allows miners to retain their earnings while simultaneously decreasing the net Bitcoin supply, creating a favorable environment for Bitcoin prices to rise.</p>
Forecast Revision, Shifting Market Conditions
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This recent revision is a significant upgrade from the bank's previous forecast in April, which projected Bitcoin hitting $100,000. According to Standard Chartered, this initial prediction, influenced by several factors including a banking-sector crisis, now appears "too conservative."</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Since then, the market conditions have shifted notably. Bitcoin has experienced an 80% increase from the start of 2021 and is currently trading around $30,100, triggering the bank's reconsideration of its initial forecast.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In light of the revised projection, it's clear that financial institutions are adapting their strategies and outlooks in response to the highly dynamic cryptocurrency market, underscored by the recent flurry of institutional interest and significant price movements.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">As the sector continues to transform, these expert forecasts offer valuable insights into potential trends and fluctuations. However, investors and market observers should approach these predictions with a keen awareness of the broader context &mdash; the cryptocurrency market's intrinsic volatility and unpredictability.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">At the time of writing, the current trading price of Bitcoin, at around $30,200, represents an 80% increase since the start of 2021, which is an important consideration when gauging the potential future trajectory of this premier cryptocurrency.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">In its latest research report, Standard Chartered Bank has presented an optimistic forecast for Bitcoin, suggesting that the leading cryptocurrency could touch the $50,000 milestone by the end of 2021, and climb to an impressive $120,000 by 2024's close.</p>
Mining Economics Fueling Bitcoin's Potential Ascend
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Driving this prediction is a key factor: the growing profitability of Bitcoin miners. As Geoff Kendrick, the head of FX and digital assets research at Standard Chartered, explained in the report, miners play a vital role in determining the net supply of the newly minted cryptocurrency, on top of their responsibility of maintaining the Bitcoin ledger.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"Increased miner profitability per BTC (bitcoin) mined means they can sell less while maintaining cash inflows, reducing net BTC supply and pushing BTC prices higher," Kendrick stated.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to Standard Chartered's report, the primary driving force behind its predicted Bitcoin price surge involves Bitcoin miners. These miners create approximately 900 new Bitcoins globally every day. The costs they incur, predominantly power expenses for high-performance computers, are currently being offset by selling 100% of these freshly minted coins, as per the bank's estimation.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">However, should Bitcoin's value climb to $50,000, Standard Chartered believes miners would only need to sell between 20% and 30% of their new coins to cover their costs. This reduction in the number of new coins entering the market could potentially limit the available supply, thereby driving prices up.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">A surge in miner profitability per Bitcoin mined means miners are under less pressure to sell their output. This shift allows miners to retain their earnings while simultaneously decreasing the net Bitcoin supply, creating a favorable environment for Bitcoin prices to rise.</p>
Forecast Revision, Shifting Market Conditions
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This recent revision is a significant upgrade from the bank's previous forecast in April, which projected Bitcoin hitting $100,000. According to Standard Chartered, this initial prediction, influenced by several factors including a banking-sector crisis, now appears "too conservative."</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Since then, the market conditions have shifted notably. Bitcoin has experienced an 80% increase from the start of 2021 and is currently trading around $30,100, triggering the bank's reconsideration of its initial forecast.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In light of the revised projection, it's clear that financial institutions are adapting their strategies and outlooks in response to the highly dynamic cryptocurrency market, underscored by the recent flurry of institutional interest and significant price movements.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">As the sector continues to transform, these expert forecasts offer valuable insights into potential trends and fluctuations. However, investors and market observers should approach these predictions with a keen awareness of the broader context &mdash; the cryptocurrency market's intrinsic volatility and unpredictability.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">At the time of writing, the current trading price of Bitcoin, at around $30,200, represents an 80% increase since the start of 2021, which is an important consideration when gauging the potential future trajectory of this premier cryptocurrency.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  29998 Support Tested - 11 July 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-29998-support-tested-11-july-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-10-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-10-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-10-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 16:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-29998-support-tested-11-july-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD 29998 Support Tested:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 11 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) remained dominated by short-term technical levels early in the Asian session as the pair encountered buying pressure around the 29996.74 level, representing a test of the 61.8% retracement of the recent appreciating range from 29715.87 to 30456.&nbsp; Traders pushed BTC/USD higher to the 30282.09 area, representing a test of the 23.6% retracement of the same appreciating range.&nbsp; Recent selling pressure expanded around the 31142.38 area and this increases the risk of another test of the 29427 area, representing the 38.2% retracement of the broader appreciating range from 26165.98 to 31443.67.&nbsp; &nbsp;Below that area, the 28604.83 level represents the 50% retracement of that appreciating range.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives include the 31737, 32125, and 33569 areas.&nbsp; Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 31674, 32043, 34531, and 34658 areas.</p>
<p>Following recent selling pressure, areas of potential technical support and buying pressure include the 29427, 28886, 28804, 28182, 28096, and 27306 areas.&nbsp; &nbsp;Technicians will closely monitor trading activity around the 28095.44 area, representing the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 30475.07 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 30227.33.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD 29998 Support Tested:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 11 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) remained dominated by short-term technical levels early in the Asian session as the pair encountered buying pressure around the 29996.74 level, representing a test of the 61.8% retracement of the recent appreciating range from 29715.87 to 30456.&nbsp; Traders pushed BTC/USD higher to the 30282.09 area, representing a test of the 23.6% retracement of the same appreciating range.&nbsp; Recent selling pressure expanded around the 31142.38 area and this increases the risk of another test of the 29427 area, representing the 38.2% retracement of the broader appreciating range from 26165.98 to 31443.67.&nbsp; &nbsp;Below that area, the 28604.83 level represents the 50% retracement of that appreciating range.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives include the 31737, 32125, and 33569 areas.&nbsp; Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 31674, 32043, 34531, and 34658 areas.</p>
<p>Following recent selling pressure, areas of potential technical support and buying pressure include the 29427, 28886, 28804, 28182, 28096, and 27306 areas.&nbsp; &nbsp;Technicians will closely monitor trading activity around the 28095.44 area, representing the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 30475.07 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 30227.33.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Earn Crypto Rewards Through LFi One Smartphone]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/earn-crypto-rewards-through-lfi-one-smartphone</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/lfi-1920x1080.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/lfi-1920x1080.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/lfi-1920x1080.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 14:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Adrian Barkley]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/earn-crypto-rewards-through-lfi-one-smartphone</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>LFi One is a revolutionary smartphone that not only boasts cutting-edge features comparable to leading smartphones in the market but also serves as a unique minting hardware. Unlike other mobile devices, LFi One has embedded powerful software that enables it to mint tokens and generate rewards for its users.</p>
<p>All you need to do is make sure that your LFi One is connected to the internet. Once it is online, the phone will start minting LFi tokens and you will receive crypto rewards in return. The price of an LFi token is currently $1. And, as the LFi ecosystem continues to develop, the price of LFi tokens has the potential to go up in the coming years.</p>
Here are some of the benefits of using LFi One:
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Mint tokens: LFi One is built to support token minting. This gives users the opportunity to earn crypto rewards by simply using their phone.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Top-of-the-line features: LFi One has features that can compete with the leading smartphones in the market. This makes it a great choice for users who want a powerful and versatile device.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Potential for price appreciation: The price of LFi tokens has the potential to go up in the coming years. This means that users who mint LFi tokens now could potentially see their portfolio grow in value.</li>
</ul>
Understanding Minting&nbsp;
<p>Crypto minting is the process of creating new units of a cryptocurrency without the need for computational work. It is an important part of the process by which new cryptocurrency units are created and added to the market.</p>
<p>There are a variety of different mechanisms through which crypto minting can occur, depending on the specific cryptocurrency being minted. In some cases, crypto minting can occur through a process called staking. Staking involves holding a certain amount of a cryptocurrency in a wallet or on a particular blockchain network. Stakers are then rewarded with newly minted units of the cryptocurrency, based on the amount they hold and the length of time they have held it.</p>
Here are some of the most common mechanisms to generate crypto units:
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Proof-of-work (PoW): PoW is the most common mechanism for crypto mining. It involves using powerful computers to solve complex mathematical problems in order to verify transactions and add them to the blockchain. The first miner to solve a problem is rewarded with newly minted units of the cryptocurrency.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Proof-of-stake (PoS): PoS is a more energy-efficient alternative to PoW. It involves locking up a certain amount of cryptocurrency in a wallet in order to become a validator. Validators are then randomly selected to verify transactions and add them to the blockchain. They are rewarded with newly minted units of the cryptocurrency for their services.</li>
</ul>
<p>Crypto minting is an important part of the cryptocurrency ecosystem. It allows for the creation of new units of cryptocurrency, which helps to keep the market liquid and growing. The different mechanisms for crypto minting offer a variety of options for users, depending on their preferences and resources.</p>
<p>Order your LFi One at: https://lyotechlabs.com/lfi-build-your-independence/</p>
<p>Website: lfi.io</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LFi One is a revolutionary smartphone that not only boasts cutting-edge features comparable to leading smartphones in the market but also serves as a unique minting hardware. Unlike other mobile devices, LFi One has embedded powerful software that enables it to mint tokens and generate rewards for its users.</p>
<p>All you need to do is make sure that your LFi One is connected to the internet. Once it is online, the phone will start minting LFi tokens and you will receive crypto rewards in return. The price of an LFi token is currently $1. And, as the LFi ecosystem continues to develop, the price of LFi tokens has the potential to go up in the coming years.</p>
Here are some of the benefits of using LFi One:
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Mint tokens: LFi One is built to support token minting. This gives users the opportunity to earn crypto rewards by simply using their phone.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Top-of-the-line features: LFi One has features that can compete with the leading smartphones in the market. This makes it a great choice for users who want a powerful and versatile device.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Potential for price appreciation: The price of LFi tokens has the potential to go up in the coming years. This means that users who mint LFi tokens now could potentially see their portfolio grow in value.</li>
</ul>
Understanding Minting&nbsp;
<p>Crypto minting is the process of creating new units of a cryptocurrency without the need for computational work. It is an important part of the process by which new cryptocurrency units are created and added to the market.</p>
<p>There are a variety of different mechanisms through which crypto minting can occur, depending on the specific cryptocurrency being minted. In some cases, crypto minting can occur through a process called staking. Staking involves holding a certain amount of a cryptocurrency in a wallet or on a particular blockchain network. Stakers are then rewarded with newly minted units of the cryptocurrency, based on the amount they hold and the length of time they have held it.</p>
Here are some of the most common mechanisms to generate crypto units:
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Proof-of-work (PoW): PoW is the most common mechanism for crypto mining. It involves using powerful computers to solve complex mathematical problems in order to verify transactions and add them to the blockchain. The first miner to solve a problem is rewarded with newly minted units of the cryptocurrency.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Proof-of-stake (PoS): PoS is a more energy-efficient alternative to PoW. It involves locking up a certain amount of cryptocurrency in a wallet in order to become a validator. Validators are then randomly selected to verify transactions and add them to the blockchain. They are rewarded with newly minted units of the cryptocurrency for their services.</li>
</ul>
<p>Crypto minting is an important part of the cryptocurrency ecosystem. It allows for the creation of new units of cryptocurrency, which helps to keep the market liquid and growing. The different mechanisms for crypto minting offer a variety of options for users, depending on their preferences and resources.</p>
<p>Order your LFi One at: https://lyotechlabs.com/lfi-build-your-independence/</p>
<p>Website: lfi.io</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[DeFi Platform Arcadia Finance Hacked for $455K]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/defi-platform-arcadia-finance-hacked-for-455k</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/arcadia.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/arcadia.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/arcadia.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 13:56:25 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/defi-platform-arcadia-finance-hacked-for-455k</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Another day, another DeFi hack. Arcadia Finance has reportedly been the victim of an exploit which allowed hackers to drain roughly $455,000. </p>
<p>Decentralised finance (DeFi) platform Arcadia Finance has reportedly become the latest victim of a hack. Blockchain investigating firm PeckShields reported the exploit and said it was due to &ldquo;the lack of untrusted input validation.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">#PeckShieldAlert Our community contributor has detected that @ArcadiaFi has been exploited on both #Ethereum and #Optimism for ~$455KThe exploiter on #Ethereum was frontrun by 0x5C75e94dD0Ab9c10BFd1B8073DafEF031D3c050dhttps://t.co/blGx5IEAkkThe exploiter on #optimism&hellip; pic.twitter.com/WDzF0XVcmL</p>
&mdash; PeckShieldAlert (@PeckShieldAlert) July 10, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>PeckShields alerted about a code vulnerability that allowed a hacker to drain funds worth about $455,000 from Ethereum (darcWETH) and Optimism (darcUSDC) vaults. According to the firm, the code vulnerability lacked a validation mechanism to cross-check unverified inputs. It added, &ldquo;There is a lack of reentrancy protection, which allows for the instant liquidation to bypass the internal vault health check.&rdquo;</p>
<p>PeckShields also reported the exploiter transferred roughly 179 ETH by bridging 148 ETH and swapping 59,000 USDC to crypto mixer Tornado Cash.</p>
Arcadia TVL Drops 76%
<p>Following the hack, DeFiLlama reported that Arcadia&rsquo;s Total Value Locked (TVL) dropped by a staggering 76%, from $605,000 to $145,000.</p>
<p>The exploit on Arcadia Finance comes only days after a $130 million hack on Multichain&rsquo;s MPC bridge platform.</p>
<p>Observers noted $102 million worth of crypto was withdrawn from the Multichain Fantom bridge on the Ethereum side. $666,000 worth of Dogecoin (DOGE) and $5 million from Moonriver were also removed. An additional 7214 Wrapped Ether tokens, 1024 Wrapped Bitcoin, and $58 million worth of USDC tokens were drained from the Fantom bridge&rsquo;s Ethereum smart contract.</p>
Arcadia Acknowledges Exploit
<p>Arcadia Finance acknowledged the exploit on their protocol but has yet to provide further information.</p>
<p>The platform informed its users this morning that it had contacted the hacker.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We have initiated contact with the attacker. https://t.co/dh74gG90n6 https://t.co/O39Slsc1z5We will continue to work with our security partners, law enforcement, and the broader community to resolve this as best we can. Our number one priority is recovering funds for Arcadia&hellip;</p>
&mdash; Arcadia Finance (@ArcadiaFi) July 10, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Another day, another DeFi hack. Arcadia Finance has reportedly been the victim of an exploit which allowed hackers to drain roughly $455,000. </p>
<p>Decentralised finance (DeFi) platform Arcadia Finance has reportedly become the latest victim of a hack. Blockchain investigating firm PeckShields reported the exploit and said it was due to &ldquo;the lack of untrusted input validation.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">#PeckShieldAlert Our community contributor has detected that @ArcadiaFi has been exploited on both #Ethereum and #Optimism for ~$455KThe exploiter on #Ethereum was frontrun by 0x5C75e94dD0Ab9c10BFd1B8073DafEF031D3c050dhttps://t.co/blGx5IEAkkThe exploiter on #optimism&hellip; pic.twitter.com/WDzF0XVcmL</p>
&mdash; PeckShieldAlert (@PeckShieldAlert) July 10, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>PeckShields alerted about a code vulnerability that allowed a hacker to drain funds worth about $455,000 from Ethereum (darcWETH) and Optimism (darcUSDC) vaults. According to the firm, the code vulnerability lacked a validation mechanism to cross-check unverified inputs. It added, &ldquo;There is a lack of reentrancy protection, which allows for the instant liquidation to bypass the internal vault health check.&rdquo;</p>
<p>PeckShields also reported the exploiter transferred roughly 179 ETH by bridging 148 ETH and swapping 59,000 USDC to crypto mixer Tornado Cash.</p>
Arcadia TVL Drops 76%
<p>Following the hack, DeFiLlama reported that Arcadia&rsquo;s Total Value Locked (TVL) dropped by a staggering 76%, from $605,000 to $145,000.</p>
<p>The exploit on Arcadia Finance comes only days after a $130 million hack on Multichain&rsquo;s MPC bridge platform.</p>
<p>Observers noted $102 million worth of crypto was withdrawn from the Multichain Fantom bridge on the Ethereum side. $666,000 worth of Dogecoin (DOGE) and $5 million from Moonriver were also removed. An additional 7214 Wrapped Ether tokens, 1024 Wrapped Bitcoin, and $58 million worth of USDC tokens were drained from the Fantom bridge&rsquo;s Ethereum smart contract.</p>
Arcadia Acknowledges Exploit
<p>Arcadia Finance acknowledged the exploit on their protocol but has yet to provide further information.</p>
<p>The platform informed its users this morning that it had contacted the hacker.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We have initiated contact with the attacker. https://t.co/dh74gG90n6 https://t.co/O39Slsc1z5We will continue to work with our security partners, law enforcement, and the broader community to resolve this as best we can. Our number one priority is recovering funds for Arcadia&hellip;</p>
&mdash; Arcadia Finance (@ArcadiaFi) July 10, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[SEC Responds To Coinbase In Ongoing Legal Battle]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/sec-responds-to-coinbase-in-ongoing-legal-battle</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/sec-15.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/sec-15.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/sec-15.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 12:55:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/sec-responds-to-coinbase-in-ongoing-legal-battle</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>According to the SEC, Coinbase was aware of securities law violations and even warned some of its shareholders about the risk.&nbsp;</p>
SEC Claps Back At Coinbase
<p>The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has finally responded to Coinbase&rsquo;s claims that the former lacks the jurisdiction to regulate the crypto exchange&rsquo;s activities.</p>
<p>It all started on June 6, 2023, when the US regulatory body filed charges against Coinbase, claiming that the crypto exchange had offered investors unregistered securities since 2019. The &ldquo;unregistered securities,&rdquo; in this case, were several cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>In the SEC&rsquo;s recent letter, the organization addressed a district judge and argued that Coinbase, as a "multi-billion-dollar entity advised by sophisticated legal counsel," intentionally disregarded decades of established legal precedent, specifically the landmark Howey test, in an attempt to create its own criteria for determining what constitutes an investment contract.</p>
Coinbase Acknowledged Securities Law?&nbsp;
<p>The response from the SEC highlighted Coinbase's own acknowledgment of the risk that assets traded on its platform could be classified as securities. The regulator quoted from Coinbase's public statements since becoming a publicly traded company, emphasizing that the company had consistently informed shareholders about the potential violation of federal securities laws resulting from its conduct.</p>
<p>The SEC also presented evidence that the crypto firm was well aware of the federal securities laws and how they could be applied to the exchange&rsquo;s activities. The letter also claimed that the Coinbase team had even gone as far as communicating the potential securities laws violations and the associated risks to its shareholders.&nbsp;</p>
<p>An excerpt from the letter reads.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Since becoming a public company, Coinbase has repeatedly informed its shareholders of the risk that the crypto assets traded on its platform could be deemed securities and therefore that its conduct could violate the federal securities laws.&rdquo;</p>

Coinbase Claims Lack Of Jurisdiction
<p>This letter from the SEC is in direct response to a previous filing made by Coinbase on June 28, where the latter appealed to the court to dismiss the case on grounds of lack of jurisdiction and its claims that the SEC did not follow due process.</p>
<p>Coinbase had referenced a statement allegedly made by SEC Chair Gary Gensler during his appearance before Congress, where he reportedly claimed that market regulation of crypto exchanges was outside the scope of the SEC's authority and that only Congress could confer such regulatory power.</p>
<p>Coinbase also pointed out that despite being a public company for two years, it was only recently that the SEC brought charges against the exchange for activities that had been thoroughly described to the regulator and the public.</p>
<p>The outcome of this case will have significant implications for the regulation of cryptocurrencies and how they are traded within the United States. As the legal battle between Coinbase and the SEC continues, market participants eagerly await a resolution that could shape the future of the crypto industry.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to the SEC, Coinbase was aware of securities law violations and even warned some of its shareholders about the risk.&nbsp;</p>
SEC Claps Back At Coinbase
<p>The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has finally responded to Coinbase&rsquo;s claims that the former lacks the jurisdiction to regulate the crypto exchange&rsquo;s activities.</p>
<p>It all started on June 6, 2023, when the US regulatory body filed charges against Coinbase, claiming that the crypto exchange had offered investors unregistered securities since 2019. The &ldquo;unregistered securities,&rdquo; in this case, were several cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>In the SEC&rsquo;s recent letter, the organization addressed a district judge and argued that Coinbase, as a "multi-billion-dollar entity advised by sophisticated legal counsel," intentionally disregarded decades of established legal precedent, specifically the landmark Howey test, in an attempt to create its own criteria for determining what constitutes an investment contract.</p>
Coinbase Acknowledged Securities Law?&nbsp;
<p>The response from the SEC highlighted Coinbase's own acknowledgment of the risk that assets traded on its platform could be classified as securities. The regulator quoted from Coinbase's public statements since becoming a publicly traded company, emphasizing that the company had consistently informed shareholders about the potential violation of federal securities laws resulting from its conduct.</p>
<p>The SEC also presented evidence that the crypto firm was well aware of the federal securities laws and how they could be applied to the exchange&rsquo;s activities. The letter also claimed that the Coinbase team had even gone as far as communicating the potential securities laws violations and the associated risks to its shareholders.&nbsp;</p>
<p>An excerpt from the letter reads.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Since becoming a public company, Coinbase has repeatedly informed its shareholders of the risk that the crypto assets traded on its platform could be deemed securities and therefore that its conduct could violate the federal securities laws.&rdquo;</p>

Coinbase Claims Lack Of Jurisdiction
<p>This letter from the SEC is in direct response to a previous filing made by Coinbase on June 28, where the latter appealed to the court to dismiss the case on grounds of lack of jurisdiction and its claims that the SEC did not follow due process.</p>
<p>Coinbase had referenced a statement allegedly made by SEC Chair Gary Gensler during his appearance before Congress, where he reportedly claimed that market regulation of crypto exchanges was outside the scope of the SEC's authority and that only Congress could confer such regulatory power.</p>
<p>Coinbase also pointed out that despite being a public company for two years, it was only recently that the SEC brought charges against the exchange for activities that had been thoroughly described to the regulator and the public.</p>
<p>The outcome of this case will have significant implications for the regulation of cryptocurrencies and how they are traded within the United States. As the legal battle between Coinbase and the SEC continues, market participants eagerly await a resolution that could shape the future of the crypto industry.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin big move gets closer]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-big-move-gets-closer</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bit-53.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bit-53.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bit-53.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 10:54:28 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-big-move-gets-closer</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>As bitcoin continues to trade sideways in a range, the next sharp move is not far from happening.</p>
Becalmed, but not for long
<p>Bitcoin looks to be reasonably comfortable as it sits on support at around $30,000. Not the heights of over $31,000 and a chance at breaking resistance, but a respectable sideways price action that could break soon.</p>
<p>In fact, it&rsquo;s only 5 days since bitcoin made a new high for the year, when it rose to $31,500 and looked as though it might break the strongest resistance it&rsquo;s likely to meet in this bull market.</p>
Strong support below
<p>However, gravity took its toll and bitcoin has returned back down to $30,000. Should this break further to the downside, there is very strong support at around $29,300 and then down to $28,800. After that there is massive support at $25,000 which would also be bolstered by the 200 MA, plus the upward trendline that started at the beginning of the year.</p>
Dark economic clouds gather
<p>Things are still incredibly uncertain from an economic perspective. The lower inflation sequence could be about to be broken in the US, while remaining very persistent worldwide, particularly in countries in Europe and especially in the UK.</p>
<p>On the horizon in August there is the BRICS summit, where a new rival reserve currency to the dollar could potentially be announced. The lack of decent Western mainstream coverage of such an earth-shattering economic event does not bode well for proper preparation from the West.</p>
<p>Housing crises are also drawing near in many Western countries. UK mortgage holders are getting to the end of their fixed rate mortgages and will need to renegotiate them, facing a potential rise of at least 300% on their current payments.</p>
<p>In addition, when the Summer comes to an end and Winter begins to demand vastly higher energy bills, an entry into recession will have been all but assured.</p>
Bitcoin about to prove its worth
<p>How bitcoin will perform in such an economic quagmire is really the million dollar question. So far it hasn&rsquo;t become that inflation hedge that all were hoping for, but this could change.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Money printing in the West is likely to start getting ramped up again as these economies desperately fight to get themselves through the Winter. Bitcoin, the scarcest asset in the world, and out of the reach of government manipulation, will have the chance to prove that it is a haven of safety. Those able to buy bitcoin, gold, or silver may want to do so before fiat debasement makes it so much more difficult.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As bitcoin continues to trade sideways in a range, the next sharp move is not far from happening.</p>
Becalmed, but not for long
<p>Bitcoin looks to be reasonably comfortable as it sits on support at around $30,000. Not the heights of over $31,000 and a chance at breaking resistance, but a respectable sideways price action that could break soon.</p>
<p>In fact, it&rsquo;s only 5 days since bitcoin made a new high for the year, when it rose to $31,500 and looked as though it might break the strongest resistance it&rsquo;s likely to meet in this bull market.</p>
Strong support below
<p>However, gravity took its toll and bitcoin has returned back down to $30,000. Should this break further to the downside, there is very strong support at around $29,300 and then down to $28,800. After that there is massive support at $25,000 which would also be bolstered by the 200 MA, plus the upward trendline that started at the beginning of the year.</p>
Dark economic clouds gather
<p>Things are still incredibly uncertain from an economic perspective. The lower inflation sequence could be about to be broken in the US, while remaining very persistent worldwide, particularly in countries in Europe and especially in the UK.</p>
<p>On the horizon in August there is the BRICS summit, where a new rival reserve currency to the dollar could potentially be announced. The lack of decent Western mainstream coverage of such an earth-shattering economic event does not bode well for proper preparation from the West.</p>
<p>Housing crises are also drawing near in many Western countries. UK mortgage holders are getting to the end of their fixed rate mortgages and will need to renegotiate them, facing a potential rise of at least 300% on their current payments.</p>
<p>In addition, when the Summer comes to an end and Winter begins to demand vastly higher energy bills, an entry into recession will have been all but assured.</p>
Bitcoin about to prove its worth
<p>How bitcoin will perform in such an economic quagmire is really the million dollar question. So far it hasn&rsquo;t become that inflation hedge that all were hoping for, but this could change.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Money printing in the West is likely to start getting ramped up again as these economies desperately fight to get themselves through the Winter. Bitcoin, the scarcest asset in the world, and out of the reach of government manipulation, will have the chance to prove that it is a haven of safety. Those able to buy bitcoin, gold, or silver may want to do so before fiat debasement makes it so much more difficult.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Revoke Introduces New Feature As Users Report Fake Approval Scam]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/revoke-introduces-new-feature-as-users-report-fake-approval-scam</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/revoke.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/revoke.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/revoke.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 10:08:30 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/revoke-introduces-new-feature-as-users-report-fake-approval-scam</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Approval management platform Revoke introduced a new feature to combat a new crypto scam. Users reported receiving "fake approval" requests leaving users with exuberant transaction fees.</p>
<p>Revoke, an approval management platform that helps users practice safer crypto wallet behaviour was forced to issue a fix after users reported a new crypto scam.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Yesterday, we received reports of people seeing unknown approval transactions in their transaction history.It turns out that this is a new scam where scammers use so-called gas tokens to steal money when victims revoke these "fake approvals". pic.twitter.com/vpY2sGIv0T</p>
&mdash; Revoke.cash (@RevokeCash) July 9, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Revoke.com received complaints over the weekend of a new crypto scam which baits users into revoking "fake approvals," leaving them with excessively high transaction fees. The platform posted on Twitter that it had received reports of users seeing unknown approvals in the transaction history.</p>
Scammers Are Creating Fake Gas Tokens
<p>Revoke explained the scam involves scammers using so-called "gas tokens" to steal funds when victims revoke so-called "fake approvals." Gas tokens were developed after Ethereum network fees began increasing, allowing users to store "cheap gas" when network demand is low.</p>
<p>Revoke explained this feature allows users "to mint gas tokens when fees were low and burn them when fees were high, effectively "locking in" the lower fee." The platform explained the scam operates by scammers creating fake gas tokens, which they airdrop with fake approvals to users, tricking them into thinking there are requests they need to revoke.</p>
<p>The scammer's fake tokens are programmed to generate a lot of gas during the revoked transactions. The newly minted tokens are sent to scammers, leaving victims with high transaction fees.</p>
<p>Revoke said:</p>

<p>But the scammers programmed these fake tokens so that it mints a lot of gas tokens during a revoke transaction. These gas tokens are then sent to the scammers, who can sell them. This is scary because your wallet popup will not show that you're sending funds, just a high fee.</p>

Revoke Introduces Fix to Mitigate Scam
<p>Revoke acts as a tool to help users practice safer wallet behaviour. The platform manages or revokes active approvals such as those no longer required by decentralised finance protocols.</p>
<p>In an effort to mitigate the fallout from the scam, Revoke added a check that disables revoking approvals if the gas fees are excessive, and urged users to ignore fake approvals. Revoke explained:</p>

<p>Best thing to do with these fake approvals / fake tokens is to ignore them. As long as you don't interact with them, they can't steal your funds.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Approval management platform Revoke introduced a new feature to combat a new crypto scam. Users reported receiving "fake approval" requests leaving users with exuberant transaction fees.</p>
<p>Revoke, an approval management platform that helps users practice safer crypto wallet behaviour was forced to issue a fix after users reported a new crypto scam.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Yesterday, we received reports of people seeing unknown approval transactions in their transaction history.It turns out that this is a new scam where scammers use so-called gas tokens to steal money when victims revoke these "fake approvals". pic.twitter.com/vpY2sGIv0T</p>
&mdash; Revoke.cash (@RevokeCash) July 9, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Revoke.com received complaints over the weekend of a new crypto scam which baits users into revoking "fake approvals," leaving them with excessively high transaction fees. The platform posted on Twitter that it had received reports of users seeing unknown approvals in the transaction history.</p>
Scammers Are Creating Fake Gas Tokens
<p>Revoke explained the scam involves scammers using so-called "gas tokens" to steal funds when victims revoke so-called "fake approvals." Gas tokens were developed after Ethereum network fees began increasing, allowing users to store "cheap gas" when network demand is low.</p>
<p>Revoke explained this feature allows users "to mint gas tokens when fees were low and burn them when fees were high, effectively "locking in" the lower fee." The platform explained the scam operates by scammers creating fake gas tokens, which they airdrop with fake approvals to users, tricking them into thinking there are requests they need to revoke.</p>
<p>The scammer's fake tokens are programmed to generate a lot of gas during the revoked transactions. The newly minted tokens are sent to scammers, leaving victims with high transaction fees.</p>
<p>Revoke said:</p>

<p>But the scammers programmed these fake tokens so that it mints a lot of gas tokens during a revoke transaction. These gas tokens are then sent to the scammers, who can sell them. This is scary because your wallet popup will not show that you're sending funds, just a high fee.</p>

Revoke Introduces Fix to Mitigate Scam
<p>Revoke acts as a tool to help users practice safer wallet behaviour. The platform manages or revokes active approvals such as those no longer required by decentralised finance protocols.</p>
<p>In an effort to mitigate the fallout from the scam, Revoke added a check that disables revoking approvals if the gas fees are excessive, and urged users to ignore fake approvals. Revoke explained:</p>

<p>Best thing to do with these fake approvals / fake tokens is to ignore them. As long as you don't interact with them, they can't steal your funds.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Swaap v2 Launches: Revolutionizing DeFi Market Making with Secure, Autopilot Strategies]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/swaap-v2-launches-revolutionizing-defi-market-making-with-secure-autopilot-strategies</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/photo_2023-07-07_14-48-53_1688730550VLuucVVVfS.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/photo_2023-07-07_14-48-53_1688730550VLuucVVVfS.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/photo_2023-07-07_14-48-53_1688730550VLuucVVVfS.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 10:03:38 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/swaap-v2-launches-revolutionizing-defi-market-making-with-secure-autopilot-strategies</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Paris, France, July 10th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Leveraging its successful $4.5m fundraising, Swaap launches its v2 protocol, bringing easy-to-use and powerful market-making strategies to the global DeFi community. Swaap v2 is unique in addressing key challenges such as impermanent loss which have plagued Liquidity Providers.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Swaap, the cutting-edge market-making protocol for blue-chip crypto assets, is thrilled to announce the launch of its v2 protocol. With an emphasis on ease of use, state-of-the-art strategies, strong security, and solutions to impermanent loss, Swaap v2 is poised to democratize access to advanced market-making tools for the global DeFi community.</p><p>What Sets Swaap v2 Apart: Making Market Making Effortless</p><p class="ql-align-justify">For the first time ever, Swaap v2 offers anyone - from institutions to individuals - a seamless way to engage in advanced market-making strategies. The protocol uses mathematically optimized strategies, which means it intelligently adjusts fees and asset holdings to maximize returns while minimizing risks, all on autopilot. Importantly, Swaap v2 addresses impermanent loss, a problem that has deterred many from participating as liquidity providers.</p>Stanislas Barth&eacute;l&eacute;mi, an early user of Swaap v2, shares: &ldquo;As someone who was an LP in traditional Automated Market Makers but was burned by Impermanent Loss, Swaap v2 has been a game-changer for me. It's like having an expert trader working for you around the clock.&rdquo;<p>The Tech Behind Swaap v2</p><p class="ql-align-justify">With models built in collaboration with the Louis Bachelier Institute, a leading financial research institute, Swaap v2 brings the best of traditional financial market-making models to DeFi. It incorporates strategies that intuitively adapt to market conditions, safeguarding funds while optimizing returns. Moreover, liquidity providers can effortlessly engage with a wide array of assets across the Polygon and the Ethereum ecosystems.</p><p>Launch Partners Powering Swaap v2</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Swaap v2 is backed by notable launch partners to ensure robust functionality and support. Chainlink provides critical price feeds for on-chain defensive mechanisms and safeguards, further reinforcing security for Liquidity Providers.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Additionally, Paraswap, Odos, and Open Ocean are onboard as aggregators, which already ensures significant volumes on the Swaap platform.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">FRAX, a leading stablecoin protocol, has approved a proposal to incentivize liquidity on a FRAX-ETH pool on Swaap v2 to reinforce its role as a connector token in DeFi.</p><p>Built with Security at its Core</p><p class="ql-align-justify">In the world of DeFi, security is paramount. Swaap v2 has undergone rigorous audits by ChainSecurity &amp; Quantstamp. Furthermore, Swaap v2 pioneers defensive modules and on-chain protections that offer users additional peace of mind.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Swaap is celebrating the launch by offering Swaap tokens to the first wave of liquidity providers, seamlessly integrating them into the governance ecosystem.</p>&ldquo;With Swaap v2, we&rsquo;re not just launching a product; we&rsquo;re catalyzing a movement to empower people globally through decentralized financial tools. Our goal is to ensure that anyone, anywhere, has access to sophisticated market-making strategies that were once reserved for high-net-worth individuals and established financial institutions,&rdquo; says Cyrille Pastour, co-founder of Swaap.&ldquo;Swaap v2 is an eloquent example of what happens when innovation meets expertise. We believe Swaap is on the verge of redefining how DeFi engages with market-making, and we are thrilled to be part of this transformative journey.", says Nikolai Lambsdorff, from Signature Ventures.<p class="ql-align-justify">Liquidity Deposits to Secure Launch NFT</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Swapp invites users to deposit liquidity in Swaap v2 to not only unlock the full potential of their assets but also to secure exclusive launch NFT. This uniquely designed digital asset is Swapp's way of acknowledging users early participation and commitment to the evolution of DeFi.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Users who want to deposit liquidity to secure their piece of blockchain history and join the frontlines of DeFi innovation can visit this link.</p><p>About Swaap</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Swaap is an innovative market-making protocol specializing in blue-chip crypto assets. Through pioneering models developed in collaboration with leading institutions, Swaap is revolutionizing DeFi market-making by providing liquidity providers with effortless and superior market-making strategies.</p>ContactHead of MarketingDavid CostelloSwaapdavid.costello@swaap.finance]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Paris, France, July 10th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Leveraging its successful $4.5m fundraising, Swaap launches its v2 protocol, bringing easy-to-use and powerful market-making strategies to the global DeFi community. Swaap v2 is unique in addressing key challenges such as impermanent loss which have plagued Liquidity Providers.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Swaap, the cutting-edge market-making protocol for blue-chip crypto assets, is thrilled to announce the launch of its v2 protocol. With an emphasis on ease of use, state-of-the-art strategies, strong security, and solutions to impermanent loss, Swaap v2 is poised to democratize access to advanced market-making tools for the global DeFi community.</p><p>What Sets Swaap v2 Apart: Making Market Making Effortless</p><p class="ql-align-justify">For the first time ever, Swaap v2 offers anyone - from institutions to individuals - a seamless way to engage in advanced market-making strategies. The protocol uses mathematically optimized strategies, which means it intelligently adjusts fees and asset holdings to maximize returns while minimizing risks, all on autopilot. Importantly, Swaap v2 addresses impermanent loss, a problem that has deterred many from participating as liquidity providers.</p>Stanislas Barth&eacute;l&eacute;mi, an early user of Swaap v2, shares: &ldquo;As someone who was an LP in traditional Automated Market Makers but was burned by Impermanent Loss, Swaap v2 has been a game-changer for me. It's like having an expert trader working for you around the clock.&rdquo;<p>The Tech Behind Swaap v2</p><p class="ql-align-justify">With models built in collaboration with the Louis Bachelier Institute, a leading financial research institute, Swaap v2 brings the best of traditional financial market-making models to DeFi. It incorporates strategies that intuitively adapt to market conditions, safeguarding funds while optimizing returns. Moreover, liquidity providers can effortlessly engage with a wide array of assets across the Polygon and the Ethereum ecosystems.</p><p>Launch Partners Powering Swaap v2</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Swaap v2 is backed by notable launch partners to ensure robust functionality and support. Chainlink provides critical price feeds for on-chain defensive mechanisms and safeguards, further reinforcing security for Liquidity Providers.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Additionally, Paraswap, Odos, and Open Ocean are onboard as aggregators, which already ensures significant volumes on the Swaap platform.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">FRAX, a leading stablecoin protocol, has approved a proposal to incentivize liquidity on a FRAX-ETH pool on Swaap v2 to reinforce its role as a connector token in DeFi.</p><p>Built with Security at its Core</p><p class="ql-align-justify">In the world of DeFi, security is paramount. Swaap v2 has undergone rigorous audits by ChainSecurity &amp; Quantstamp. Furthermore, Swaap v2 pioneers defensive modules and on-chain protections that offer users additional peace of mind.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Swaap is celebrating the launch by offering Swaap tokens to the first wave of liquidity providers, seamlessly integrating them into the governance ecosystem.</p>&ldquo;With Swaap v2, we&rsquo;re not just launching a product; we&rsquo;re catalyzing a movement to empower people globally through decentralized financial tools. Our goal is to ensure that anyone, anywhere, has access to sophisticated market-making strategies that were once reserved for high-net-worth individuals and established financial institutions,&rdquo; says Cyrille Pastour, co-founder of Swaap.&ldquo;Swaap v2 is an eloquent example of what happens when innovation meets expertise. We believe Swaap is on the verge of redefining how DeFi engages with market-making, and we are thrilled to be part of this transformative journey.", says Nikolai Lambsdorff, from Signature Ventures.<p class="ql-align-justify">Liquidity Deposits to Secure Launch NFT</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Swapp invites users to deposit liquidity in Swaap v2 to not only unlock the full potential of their assets but also to secure exclusive launch NFT. This uniquely designed digital asset is Swapp's way of acknowledging users early participation and commitment to the evolution of DeFi.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Users who want to deposit liquidity to secure their piece of blockchain history and join the frontlines of DeFi innovation can visit this link.</p><p>About Swaap</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Swaap is an innovative market-making protocol specializing in blue-chip crypto assets. Through pioneering models developed in collaboration with leading institutions, Swaap is revolutionizing DeFi market-making by providing liquidity providers with effortless and superior market-making strategies.</p>ContactHead of MarketingDavid CostelloSwaapdavid.costello@swaap.finance]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[RFK Jr. Says He Is Not A Bitcoin Investor, Records Show Otherwise]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/rfk-jr-says-he-is-not-a-bitcoin-investor-records-show-otherwise</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/kennedy.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/kennedy.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/kennedy.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 09:05:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/rfk-jr-says-he-is-not-a-bitcoin-investor-records-show-otherwise</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Democratic presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr had recently stated during a May conference that he has not invested in Bitcoin. However, financial records have shown that he is indeed invested in the cryptocurrency.&nbsp;</p>
Robert F. Kennedy Jr&rsquo;s Bitcoin Investment&nbsp;
<p>The Democratic presidential candidate had, during his appearance at the Bitcoin conference in Miami, told conference attendees that he was not an investor in Bitcoin, and neither was he in a position to give investment advice. However, he had stated that he was open to accepting campaign donations in Bitcoin. However, June&rsquo;s financial documents showed otherwise, revealing that a brokerage account he held had between $100,000 and $250,000 worth of Bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Just hours after the information came to light, the Kennedy camp went into damage control, with campaign manager and former Democratic Rep Dennis Kucinich stating that the Bitcoin investment was made after the Miami conference speech and the June 30th filing deadline. According to the chief ethics counsel for the watchdog group Citizens for Responsibility and Ethics in Washington, Virginia Canter, the situation could represent a conflict of interest. This is because Kennedy appeared to be touting Bitcoin on the campaign trail while his immediate family invested in the cryptocurrency. However, the Kennedy campaign has stated that there are no grounds for a conflict of interest.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m really concerned that he&rsquo;s speaking at this conference, touting this investment to potential voters while the family has a history of owning Bitcoin. It&rsquo;s like he could do the same thing for Procter and Gamble.&rdquo;</p>

Details Of The Filing&nbsp;
<p>According to the filing, the Bitcoin holding in question made less than $201 as income. However, it does not specify when it was purchased and also does not reveal how much was spent on the original investment. It is also unclear whether the Bitcoin holding has been sold. The holding is listed under a section on the form that includes assets that could belong to spouses or dependent children and is intended to disclose holdings from the preceding calendar year to the current filing date.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Hours after the story about the holdings broke, the Kennedy campaign stated that the investment was that of his wife and that Kennedy was not involved in business and investment decisions taken by his wife. However, they did not state when the asset was purchased and for how long it was held. However, the campaign later issued another statement, saying that the investment indeed belonged to Kennedy.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I was mistaken in my last communication. Mr. Kennedy does hold a Bitcoin investment, but it came later. At the time of the bitcoin speech, he had no cryptocurrency holdings.&rdquo;</p>

Pro Crypto Stance&nbsp;
<p>Robert F. Kennedy Jr is part of a growing list of pro-crypto candidates, which also includes Republican Senator Ted Cruz and others such as Florida governor and presidential hopeful Ron DeSantis. Highlighting his support for Bitcoin and crypto in general, Kennedy had stated in a tweet,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Bitcoin is not only a bulwark against totalitarianism and the manipulation of our money supply; it points the way toward a future in which government institutions are more transparent and more democratic.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>The tweet also included a video of a part of his speech at the Miami Bitcoin conference, where he described how he would be a pro-Bitcoin president. As a result, the Kennedy campaign has garnered considerable support from several wealthy supporters, even though he remains far behind President Joe Biden in the Democratic primary polls. These include billionaire Jack Dorsey and others such as Chamath Palihapitiya, Omeed Malik, and David Sacks. According to surveys, Biden has 70% support among Democrats and Democratic-leaning voters, while Kennedy has support among 17%.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, while Kennedy has adopted a pro-Bitcoin stance, the Biden administration has taken an aggressive approach towards crypto. The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), under current chair Gary Gensler, has gone after several prominent entities in the crypto space, including Binance and Coinbase.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Democratic presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr had recently stated during a May conference that he has not invested in Bitcoin. However, financial records have shown that he is indeed invested in the cryptocurrency.&nbsp;</p>
Robert F. Kennedy Jr&rsquo;s Bitcoin Investment&nbsp;
<p>The Democratic presidential candidate had, during his appearance at the Bitcoin conference in Miami, told conference attendees that he was not an investor in Bitcoin, and neither was he in a position to give investment advice. However, he had stated that he was open to accepting campaign donations in Bitcoin. However, June&rsquo;s financial documents showed otherwise, revealing that a brokerage account he held had between $100,000 and $250,000 worth of Bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Just hours after the information came to light, the Kennedy camp went into damage control, with campaign manager and former Democratic Rep Dennis Kucinich stating that the Bitcoin investment was made after the Miami conference speech and the June 30th filing deadline. According to the chief ethics counsel for the watchdog group Citizens for Responsibility and Ethics in Washington, Virginia Canter, the situation could represent a conflict of interest. This is because Kennedy appeared to be touting Bitcoin on the campaign trail while his immediate family invested in the cryptocurrency. However, the Kennedy campaign has stated that there are no grounds for a conflict of interest.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m really concerned that he&rsquo;s speaking at this conference, touting this investment to potential voters while the family has a history of owning Bitcoin. It&rsquo;s like he could do the same thing for Procter and Gamble.&rdquo;</p>

Details Of The Filing&nbsp;
<p>According to the filing, the Bitcoin holding in question made less than $201 as income. However, it does not specify when it was purchased and also does not reveal how much was spent on the original investment. It is also unclear whether the Bitcoin holding has been sold. The holding is listed under a section on the form that includes assets that could belong to spouses or dependent children and is intended to disclose holdings from the preceding calendar year to the current filing date.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Hours after the story about the holdings broke, the Kennedy campaign stated that the investment was that of his wife and that Kennedy was not involved in business and investment decisions taken by his wife. However, they did not state when the asset was purchased and for how long it was held. However, the campaign later issued another statement, saying that the investment indeed belonged to Kennedy.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I was mistaken in my last communication. Mr. Kennedy does hold a Bitcoin investment, but it came later. At the time of the bitcoin speech, he had no cryptocurrency holdings.&rdquo;</p>

Pro Crypto Stance&nbsp;
<p>Robert F. Kennedy Jr is part of a growing list of pro-crypto candidates, which also includes Republican Senator Ted Cruz and others such as Florida governor and presidential hopeful Ron DeSantis. Highlighting his support for Bitcoin and crypto in general, Kennedy had stated in a tweet,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Bitcoin is not only a bulwark against totalitarianism and the manipulation of our money supply; it points the way toward a future in which government institutions are more transparent and more democratic.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>The tweet also included a video of a part of his speech at the Miami Bitcoin conference, where he described how he would be a pro-Bitcoin president. As a result, the Kennedy campaign has garnered considerable support from several wealthy supporters, even though he remains far behind President Joe Biden in the Democratic primary polls. These include billionaire Jack Dorsey and others such as Chamath Palihapitiya, Omeed Malik, and David Sacks. According to surveys, Biden has 70% support among Democrats and Democratic-leaning voters, while Kennedy has support among 17%.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, while Kennedy has adopted a pro-Bitcoin stance, the Biden administration has taken an aggressive approach towards crypto. The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), under current chair Gary Gensler, has gone after several prominent entities in the crypto space, including Binance and Coinbase.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Will Polygon (MATIC) Price Go to Zero as the SEC Begins To Clamp Down on Crypto?]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/will-polygon-matic-price-go-to-zero-as-the-sec-begins-to-clamp-down-on-crypto</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-09-at-195104.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-09-at-195104.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-09-at-195104.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/will-polygon-matic-price-go-to-zero-as-the-sec-begins-to-clamp-down-on-crypto</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Recently, crypto experts and analysts have raised questions on whether Polygon (MATIC) price could plummet to zero amidst the SEC's tightening regulations on the crypto industry. </p>
<p>Amidst the uncertainty, seize the opportunity to participate in Uwerx presale bonuses, offering enticing rewards for early investors. </p>
<p>This article provides a comprehensive overview to help you navigate the evolving crypto community and make informed investment decisions.</p>
Polygon (MATIC) Price Prediction
<p>Polygon (MATIC) is a &nbsp;crypto and blockchain platform built on top of the Ethereum (ETH) network. Polygon (MATIC) aims to address the limitations of the Ethereum blockchain by providing faster transaction processing and lower fees. </p>
<p>Polygon (MATIC) achieves this through a combination of technologies, including sidechains, plasma chains, and a decentralized network of validators.</p>
<p>Polygon (MATIC) holds a value of $0.6339, boasting a market capitalization of $6B and a 24-hour trading volume of $552M. Market experts project a promising trajectory for Polygon (MATIC), anticipating a rise to $2.05 by the first quarter of 2025.</p>
Disrupting the Industry: Uwerx's (WERX) Low Transaction Fee Sets it Apart from Traditional Platforms.
<p>Uwerx is revolutionizing the freelancer marketplace with its array of innovative features. One notable highlight is its customized matching system, which optimizes connections between freelancers and clients based on their specific requirements, skills, and budget.</p>
<p>Upon its launch on centralized exchanges, Uwerx plans to renounce contracts, cementing its disruptive approach. A significant aspect of this disruption is the platform's transaction fee, set at a mere 1%. This starkly contrasts the excessive charges imposed by traditional platforms like Upwork and Fiverr, making Uwerx a highly appealing choice for freelancers and clients.</p>
<p>Its latest feature&mdash;the Uwerx Vault&mdash;adds another layer of innovation for token holders. Users can earn rewards based on platform variables by staking their WERX tokens in the vault, enhancing their engagement and potential benefits.</p>
<p>Uwerx prioritizes security and reliability, evident in the rigorous audits conducted by reputable firms such as SolidProof and InterFi Network. These audits provide users with a sense of confidence and trust in the platform's integrity.</p>
<p>Uwerx's achievements have garnered recognition, leading to its listing on CoinSniper. Moreover, it is set to be listed on Uniswap, a major decentralized exchange, on August 1st. These listings further enhance Uwerx's accessibility, liquidity, and overall standing in the crypto market.</p>
Uwerx (WERX) Test Airdrop and Long-Term Stability Measures: Exciting Opportunities and Trust for Token Holders
<p>Uwerx recently launched the initial version of its Alpha platform, providing users with a glimpse into its functionality and user experience. The platform is now preparing to transition from Alpha to the eagerly awaited Beta phase, bringing further improvements and enhanced features for a smoother user journey.</p>
<p>Uwerx has made a comprehensive update available as a PDF document to demonstrate its commitment to transparency and user support. This update covers essential aspects such as sign-up, login, password recovery, freelancer and client roles, job creation, talent discovery, and key pages like activity tracking and the hiring dashboard.</p>
<p>Uwerx's progress in shaping the future of freelancing is undeniable, driven by innovation, lower fees, and user-centric features. The platform highly values user feedback, encouraging individuals to share their insights at feedback@uwerx.network to actively contribute to its evolution.</p>
<p>Exciting times lie ahead as Uwerx prepares for a Test Airdrop scheduled at the end of the presale on July 31st. This presents an excellent opportunity for participants to experience the platform's capabilities personally.</p>
<p>To ensure stability and trust for token holders, Uwerx has implemented a nine-month lock on team tokens and plans to extend the token liquidity lock for 25 years after the presale. These long-term commitments showcase Uwerx's dedication to maintaining a secure and reliable environment.</p>
<p>The rapid growth of the Uwerx platform, with over 5,500 sign-ups and a substantial presence on Twitter and Telegram, reflects its appeal to freelancers and clients seeking cutting-edge solutions.</p>
<p class="s7">Uwerx (WERX) Presale Success: Breaking Records and Reaching New Heights</p>
<p>Uwerx achieved outstanding success during its presale by swiftly completing stages 1 to 4. In the Stage 5 presale, Uwerx tokens are available at an attractive price of $0.047725 per token, accompanied by a tempting 15% bonus on each purchase. &nbsp;</p>
<p>The price is set to rise to $0.05245 on Monday, July 10th at 18:00 UTC.</p>
<p>This week, there will be a release of a clickable prototype for the presale, which will include pages for freelancer registration and client registration. Furthermore, the Uwerx Vault feature will be unveiled next week, and a poll will be conducted to determine the date of the test airdrop.</p>
<p>This presents a remarkable opportunity to acquire tokens at a favorable value. Market analysts anticipate a promising trajectory for Uwerx, projecting a price of $1.33 by Q4 2023.</p>
<p>Remaining responsive to community demands, the Uwerx team demonstrates flexibility by adjusting token allocations in light of the rapid speed of the presale.</p>
<p>Don&rsquo;t Miss Out on the 15% Bonus; Buy WERX tokens today: </p>
<p>Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Recently, crypto experts and analysts have raised questions on whether Polygon (MATIC) price could plummet to zero amidst the SEC's tightening regulations on the crypto industry. </p>
<p>Amidst the uncertainty, seize the opportunity to participate in Uwerx presale bonuses, offering enticing rewards for early investors. </p>
<p>This article provides a comprehensive overview to help you navigate the evolving crypto community and make informed investment decisions.</p>
Polygon (MATIC) Price Prediction
<p>Polygon (MATIC) is a &nbsp;crypto and blockchain platform built on top of the Ethereum (ETH) network. Polygon (MATIC) aims to address the limitations of the Ethereum blockchain by providing faster transaction processing and lower fees. </p>
<p>Polygon (MATIC) achieves this through a combination of technologies, including sidechains, plasma chains, and a decentralized network of validators.</p>
<p>Polygon (MATIC) holds a value of $0.6339, boasting a market capitalization of $6B and a 24-hour trading volume of $552M. Market experts project a promising trajectory for Polygon (MATIC), anticipating a rise to $2.05 by the first quarter of 2025.</p>
Disrupting the Industry: Uwerx's (WERX) Low Transaction Fee Sets it Apart from Traditional Platforms.
<p>Uwerx is revolutionizing the freelancer marketplace with its array of innovative features. One notable highlight is its customized matching system, which optimizes connections between freelancers and clients based on their specific requirements, skills, and budget.</p>
<p>Upon its launch on centralized exchanges, Uwerx plans to renounce contracts, cementing its disruptive approach. A significant aspect of this disruption is the platform's transaction fee, set at a mere 1%. This starkly contrasts the excessive charges imposed by traditional platforms like Upwork and Fiverr, making Uwerx a highly appealing choice for freelancers and clients.</p>
<p>Its latest feature&mdash;the Uwerx Vault&mdash;adds another layer of innovation for token holders. Users can earn rewards based on platform variables by staking their WERX tokens in the vault, enhancing their engagement and potential benefits.</p>
<p>Uwerx prioritizes security and reliability, evident in the rigorous audits conducted by reputable firms such as SolidProof and InterFi Network. These audits provide users with a sense of confidence and trust in the platform's integrity.</p>
<p>Uwerx's achievements have garnered recognition, leading to its listing on CoinSniper. Moreover, it is set to be listed on Uniswap, a major decentralized exchange, on August 1st. These listings further enhance Uwerx's accessibility, liquidity, and overall standing in the crypto market.</p>
Uwerx (WERX) Test Airdrop and Long-Term Stability Measures: Exciting Opportunities and Trust for Token Holders
<p>Uwerx recently launched the initial version of its Alpha platform, providing users with a glimpse into its functionality and user experience. The platform is now preparing to transition from Alpha to the eagerly awaited Beta phase, bringing further improvements and enhanced features for a smoother user journey.</p>
<p>Uwerx has made a comprehensive update available as a PDF document to demonstrate its commitment to transparency and user support. This update covers essential aspects such as sign-up, login, password recovery, freelancer and client roles, job creation, talent discovery, and key pages like activity tracking and the hiring dashboard.</p>
<p>Uwerx's progress in shaping the future of freelancing is undeniable, driven by innovation, lower fees, and user-centric features. The platform highly values user feedback, encouraging individuals to share their insights at feedback@uwerx.network to actively contribute to its evolution.</p>
<p>Exciting times lie ahead as Uwerx prepares for a Test Airdrop scheduled at the end of the presale on July 31st. This presents an excellent opportunity for participants to experience the platform's capabilities personally.</p>
<p>To ensure stability and trust for token holders, Uwerx has implemented a nine-month lock on team tokens and plans to extend the token liquidity lock for 25 years after the presale. These long-term commitments showcase Uwerx's dedication to maintaining a secure and reliable environment.</p>
<p>The rapid growth of the Uwerx platform, with over 5,500 sign-ups and a substantial presence on Twitter and Telegram, reflects its appeal to freelancers and clients seeking cutting-edge solutions.</p>
<p class="s7">Uwerx (WERX) Presale Success: Breaking Records and Reaching New Heights</p>
<p>Uwerx achieved outstanding success during its presale by swiftly completing stages 1 to 4. In the Stage 5 presale, Uwerx tokens are available at an attractive price of $0.047725 per token, accompanied by a tempting 15% bonus on each purchase. &nbsp;</p>
<p>The price is set to rise to $0.05245 on Monday, July 10th at 18:00 UTC.</p>
<p>This week, there will be a release of a clickable prototype for the presale, which will include pages for freelancer registration and client registration. Furthermore, the Uwerx Vault feature will be unveiled next week, and a poll will be conducted to determine the date of the test airdrop.</p>
<p>This presents a remarkable opportunity to acquire tokens at a favorable value. Market analysts anticipate a promising trajectory for Uwerx, projecting a price of $1.33 by Q4 2023.</p>
<p>Remaining responsive to community demands, the Uwerx team demonstrates flexibility by adjusting token allocations in light of the rapid speed of the presale.</p>
<p>Don&rsquo;t Miss Out on the 15% Bonus; Buy WERX tokens today: </p>
<p>Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Decentraland shows green on the weekly chart, Tradecurve hits milestone with 13K users]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/decentraland-shows-green-on-the-weekly-chart-tradecurve-hits-milestone-with-13k-users</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-92.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-92.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-92.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/decentraland-shows-green-on-the-weekly-chart-tradecurve-hits-milestone-with-13k-users</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Decentraland, one of the most well-known virtual worlds, has seen a surge in the value of its native token, MANA. However, it's not the only cryptocurrency to achieve major milestones, as the upcoming Tradecurve exchange has surged in user count and reached a total of 13,000 sign-ups even before launch. We will go over both projects to see why this has been the case.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
Decentraland (MANA) Heads Into The Green Zone According to Weekly Chart
<p>Decentraland celebrated Metaverse Pride 23, an event that was held with Polygon Mind. Decentraland also saw numerous developments, where they introduced new profile updates, where users could swap names, modify their bio, add links and other information, and manage their wallets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As of July 4, 2023, the Decentraland cryptocurrency traded at $0.404545. During the past week, Decentraland saw its high point of value at $0.358488, with its low point at a value of $0.416113. Within the last two weeks, the total price increase of Decentraland was by 20.8%.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In addition, within the past seven days, Decentraland climbed by 4%. This indicates that on its weekly chart, Decentraland has maintained its green zone and is heading upward in value.</p>
<p></p>
Tradecurve Hits 13,000 User Milestone
<p>However, Decentraland was not the only project to reach a significant milestone. Tradecurve is an upcoming hybrid exchange that focuses on privacy and anonymity. In addition, it's not locked to just crypto trading, as anyone can also trade bonds, US and European equity CFDs, ETFs, forex, indices, commodities, and options. As a result, 13,000 people have already signed up for the exchange even before its launch.</p>
TCRV Increased by 80% in Value
<p>During Stage 4 of the presale, TCRV trades at $0.018, indicating that the cryptocurrency has surged in value by 80% since the beginning giving solid ROI for early investors. In addition, it will surge by an additional 40% at Stage 5, meaning that investors who want to make the most significant ROI will want to get into it early.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Analysts are also predicting that based on its feature sets, such as high leverage at 500:1, negative balance protection, and the VIP account system, TCRV can spike in value even further.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
Analysts Predict a 100x Jump In value When Tradecurve Launches
<p>Current market experts predict that the growth of the TCRV token will be by 100x, fueled by its future listing on Tier-1 exchanges and on Uniswap, and due to the introduction of Proof of Reserves (PoR) that will bolster transparency in the exchange.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In addition, true borderless access appeals to millions of people, and the team estimates that they can onboard 100,000 users at launch. They've already raised $2.8 million out of the estimated $20 million, and the presale has seen significant appeal from investors and whales.&nbsp;</p>
For more information about the Tradecurve presale:
<p>Click Here For Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Decentraland, one of the most well-known virtual worlds, has seen a surge in the value of its native token, MANA. However, it's not the only cryptocurrency to achieve major milestones, as the upcoming Tradecurve exchange has surged in user count and reached a total of 13,000 sign-ups even before launch. We will go over both projects to see why this has been the case.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
Decentraland (MANA) Heads Into The Green Zone According to Weekly Chart
<p>Decentraland celebrated Metaverse Pride 23, an event that was held with Polygon Mind. Decentraland also saw numerous developments, where they introduced new profile updates, where users could swap names, modify their bio, add links and other information, and manage their wallets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As of July 4, 2023, the Decentraland cryptocurrency traded at $0.404545. During the past week, Decentraland saw its high point of value at $0.358488, with its low point at a value of $0.416113. Within the last two weeks, the total price increase of Decentraland was by 20.8%.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In addition, within the past seven days, Decentraland climbed by 4%. This indicates that on its weekly chart, Decentraland has maintained its green zone and is heading upward in value.</p>
<p></p>
Tradecurve Hits 13,000 User Milestone
<p>However, Decentraland was not the only project to reach a significant milestone. Tradecurve is an upcoming hybrid exchange that focuses on privacy and anonymity. In addition, it's not locked to just crypto trading, as anyone can also trade bonds, US and European equity CFDs, ETFs, forex, indices, commodities, and options. As a result, 13,000 people have already signed up for the exchange even before its launch.</p>
TCRV Increased by 80% in Value
<p>During Stage 4 of the presale, TCRV trades at $0.018, indicating that the cryptocurrency has surged in value by 80% since the beginning giving solid ROI for early investors. In addition, it will surge by an additional 40% at Stage 5, meaning that investors who want to make the most significant ROI will want to get into it early.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Analysts are also predicting that based on its feature sets, such as high leverage at 500:1, negative balance protection, and the VIP account system, TCRV can spike in value even further.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
Analysts Predict a 100x Jump In value When Tradecurve Launches
<p>Current market experts predict that the growth of the TCRV token will be by 100x, fueled by its future listing on Tier-1 exchanges and on Uniswap, and due to the introduction of Proof of Reserves (PoR) that will bolster transparency in the exchange.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In addition, true borderless access appeals to millions of people, and the team estimates that they can onboard 100,000 users at launch. They've already raised $2.8 million out of the estimated $20 million, and the presale has seen significant appeal from investors and whales.&nbsp;</p>
For more information about the Tradecurve presale:
<p>Click Here For Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Orbiting 30281 Tightly - 10 July 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-orbiting-30281-tightly-10-july-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-9-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-9-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-9-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-orbiting-30281-tightly-10-july-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Orbiting 30281 Tightly:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 10 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) awaited fresh technical guidance early in the Asian session as the pair tightly orbited the 30281.33 area, representing the 23.6% retracement of the recent appreciating range from 29715.87 to 30456.&nbsp; &nbsp;Selling activity recently reversed around the 30148.60 area, representing a test of the 23.6% retracement of the depreciating range from 31525.10 to 29715.87.&nbsp; Earlier selling pressure recently intensified around the 31142.38 area and this increases the risk of another test of the 29427 area, representing the 38.2% retracement of the broader appreciating range from 26165.98 to 31443.67.&nbsp; &nbsp;Below that area, the 28604.83 level represents the 50% retracement of that appreciating range.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives include the 31737, 32125, and 33569 areas.&nbsp; Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 31674, 32043, 34531, and 34658 areas.</p>
<p>Following recent selling pressure, areas of potential technical support and buying pressure include the 29427, 28886, 28804, 28182, 28096, and 27306 areas.&nbsp; &nbsp;Technicians are closely watching to see how much technical support develops around the 28095.44 area, representing the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 30465.99 and the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 30403.73.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Orbiting 30281 Tightly:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 10 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) awaited fresh technical guidance early in the Asian session as the pair tightly orbited the 30281.33 area, representing the 23.6% retracement of the recent appreciating range from 29715.87 to 30456.&nbsp; &nbsp;Selling activity recently reversed around the 30148.60 area, representing a test of the 23.6% retracement of the depreciating range from 31525.10 to 29715.87.&nbsp; Earlier selling pressure recently intensified around the 31142.38 area and this increases the risk of another test of the 29427 area, representing the 38.2% retracement of the broader appreciating range from 26165.98 to 31443.67.&nbsp; &nbsp;Below that area, the 28604.83 level represents the 50% retracement of that appreciating range.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives include the 31737, 32125, and 33569 areas.&nbsp; Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 31674, 32043, 34531, and 34658 areas.</p>
<p>Following recent selling pressure, areas of potential technical support and buying pressure include the 29427, 28886, 28804, 28182, 28096, and 27306 areas.&nbsp; &nbsp;Technicians are closely watching to see how much technical support develops around the 28095.44 area, representing the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 30465.99 and the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 30403.73.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto Weekly Roundup: Gemini Sues DCG And More]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/crypto-weekly-roundup-gemini-sues-dcg-and-more</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-weekly-roundup-new.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-weekly-roundup-new.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-weekly-roundup-new.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 12:35:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/crypto-weekly-roundup-gemini-sues-dcg-and-more</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Looks like Cameron Winklevoss made good on his promise of pursuing legal action against DCG CEO Barry Silbert after the latter failed to meet his final offer payment of $1.47 million. Let&rsquo;s find out more.&nbsp;</p>
Bitcoin&nbsp;
<p>Google Cloud's recently announced a partnership with infrastructure provider Voltage, unveiling a new trajectory for the tech giant's Bitcoin and Lightning ambitions.</p>
<p>Lightning Labs, the primary Bitcoin Lightning Network development firm, has rolled out a revolutionary set of tools designed for AI applications.</p>
<p>A recent report by JP Morgan looks to play down the effect that the approval of a Spot Bitcoin ETF might bring to the crypto sector.</p>
<p>Bitcoin miners have raked in an impressive revenue of $184 million in the second quarter of 2023, breaking previous records.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Perhaps because of incredibly bullish statements by Blackrock CEO Larry Fink, Bitcoin has set a new yearly high with expectations of going much higher.</p>
Ethereum
<p>Ethereum Name Service Labs has announced plans to introduce Layer 2 interoperability for its ENS domains during a community call on June 28.</p>
DeFi
<p>In the wake of a series of high-profile security breaches plaguing the DeFi space, a group of Ethereum community members has put forth a new standard, ERC 7265, aiming to enhance the security of DeFi protocols.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The latest statement from the Uniswap Foundation has claimed that the launch of version 4 of the protocol depends on Ethereum&rsquo;s upcoming Cancun upgrade.&nbsp;</p>
Altcoins
<p>The Multichain MPC bridge platform has seen abnormally large outflows, fueling concerns that the platform could be a target for a multi-million dollar exploit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Binance no longer supports deposits and withdrawals for several cross-chain bridge tokens linked with the Multichain project.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Ethereum founder Vitalik Buterin has expressed his sympathy and concerns for Solana and other cryptocurrencies in the context of the SEC&rsquo;s crackdown on the crypto markets.&nbsp;</p>
Technology
<p>The Open Network (TON) has announced the release of an on-chain encrypted messaging feature, allowing private messages between TON users.&nbsp;</p>
Business
<p>After Cameron Winklevoss penned an open letter threatening litigation against Barry Silbert over the latter&rsquo;s role in the Gemini Earn Program, cryptocurrency exchange Gemini is suing DCG, the parent company of bankrupt crypto broker Genesis.</p>
<p>A new currency pegged to commodities, particularly gold, will be announced at the BRICS summit on August 22.</p>
<p>Crypto Exchange Bitfinex has announced that it has recovered some of the stolen assets from the 2016 Bitcoin hack but stated that a considerable number of assets are still yet to be recovered.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Indian government has partnered with Polygon and Airchains in order to develop a blockchain-based land ownership system.&nbsp;</p>
<p>McDermott Will &amp; Emery, the law firm representing Voyager&rsquo;s committee of unsecured creditors, has sent the group a staggering bill of over $5 million for the work it has done between March and May.</p>
<p>Co-founders of bankrupt crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital plan to donate their future earnings from their new venture to creditors who lost money.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Cryptocurrency exchange LBank has announced the launch of the first unlimited crypto credit card.</p>
Regulation
<p>Israel is considering a bill that would exempt foreign residents from capital gains tax on the sale of digital assets and reduce tax on crypto options from 50% to about 25%.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Investigators from the United States Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) have concluded that Celsius and its former CEO, Alex Mashinsky broke several US laws.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The UK parliament has passed a bill that could help the authorities seize and freeze cryptocurrencies used for crime.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to a recent report by the FATF, more than half of all UN member countries still need to implement the Travel Rule.</p>
<p>South Africa&rsquo;s financial regulator has ordered crypto exchanges in the country to apply for licenses before the end of the year to continue operating.</p>
<p>In an attempt to combat fraud, Belarus is looking to put an end to peer-to-peer crypto exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
NFT
<p>Blur founder, Pacman, defends his NFT marketplace against accusations that the platform&rsquo;s strategies crashed the NFT market as the floor price of the Bored Ape Yacht Club NFT collection has dropped to the lowest in the last 20 months.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Members of the Azuki decentralized autonomous organization have initiated a Snapshot proposal to hold the project&rsquo;s founder accountable over allegations of misconduct.&nbsp;</p>
Security
<p>The Poly Network has fallen victim to another exploit after hackers manipulated a smart contract function on the cross-chain bridge protocol. According to security analysts, hackers allegedly leveraged a vulnerability in the smart contract system to mint an unlimited amount of tokens.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice. </p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Looks like Cameron Winklevoss made good on his promise of pursuing legal action against DCG CEO Barry Silbert after the latter failed to meet his final offer payment of $1.47 million. Let&rsquo;s find out more.&nbsp;</p>
Bitcoin&nbsp;
<p>Google Cloud's recently announced a partnership with infrastructure provider Voltage, unveiling a new trajectory for the tech giant's Bitcoin and Lightning ambitions.</p>
<p>Lightning Labs, the primary Bitcoin Lightning Network development firm, has rolled out a revolutionary set of tools designed for AI applications.</p>
<p>A recent report by JP Morgan looks to play down the effect that the approval of a Spot Bitcoin ETF might bring to the crypto sector.</p>
<p>Bitcoin miners have raked in an impressive revenue of $184 million in the second quarter of 2023, breaking previous records.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Perhaps because of incredibly bullish statements by Blackrock CEO Larry Fink, Bitcoin has set a new yearly high with expectations of going much higher.</p>
Ethereum
<p>Ethereum Name Service Labs has announced plans to introduce Layer 2 interoperability for its ENS domains during a community call on June 28.</p>
DeFi
<p>In the wake of a series of high-profile security breaches plaguing the DeFi space, a group of Ethereum community members has put forth a new standard, ERC 7265, aiming to enhance the security of DeFi protocols.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The latest statement from the Uniswap Foundation has claimed that the launch of version 4 of the protocol depends on Ethereum&rsquo;s upcoming Cancun upgrade.&nbsp;</p>
Altcoins
<p>The Multichain MPC bridge platform has seen abnormally large outflows, fueling concerns that the platform could be a target for a multi-million dollar exploit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Binance no longer supports deposits and withdrawals for several cross-chain bridge tokens linked with the Multichain project.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Ethereum founder Vitalik Buterin has expressed his sympathy and concerns for Solana and other cryptocurrencies in the context of the SEC&rsquo;s crackdown on the crypto markets.&nbsp;</p>
Technology
<p>The Open Network (TON) has announced the release of an on-chain encrypted messaging feature, allowing private messages between TON users.&nbsp;</p>
Business
<p>After Cameron Winklevoss penned an open letter threatening litigation against Barry Silbert over the latter&rsquo;s role in the Gemini Earn Program, cryptocurrency exchange Gemini is suing DCG, the parent company of bankrupt crypto broker Genesis.</p>
<p>A new currency pegged to commodities, particularly gold, will be announced at the BRICS summit on August 22.</p>
<p>Crypto Exchange Bitfinex has announced that it has recovered some of the stolen assets from the 2016 Bitcoin hack but stated that a considerable number of assets are still yet to be recovered.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Indian government has partnered with Polygon and Airchains in order to develop a blockchain-based land ownership system.&nbsp;</p>
<p>McDermott Will &amp; Emery, the law firm representing Voyager&rsquo;s committee of unsecured creditors, has sent the group a staggering bill of over $5 million for the work it has done between March and May.</p>
<p>Co-founders of bankrupt crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital plan to donate their future earnings from their new venture to creditors who lost money.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Cryptocurrency exchange LBank has announced the launch of the first unlimited crypto credit card.</p>
Regulation
<p>Israel is considering a bill that would exempt foreign residents from capital gains tax on the sale of digital assets and reduce tax on crypto options from 50% to about 25%.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Investigators from the United States Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) have concluded that Celsius and its former CEO, Alex Mashinsky broke several US laws.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The UK parliament has passed a bill that could help the authorities seize and freeze cryptocurrencies used for crime.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to a recent report by the FATF, more than half of all UN member countries still need to implement the Travel Rule.</p>
<p>South Africa&rsquo;s financial regulator has ordered crypto exchanges in the country to apply for licenses before the end of the year to continue operating.</p>
<p>In an attempt to combat fraud, Belarus is looking to put an end to peer-to-peer crypto exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
NFT
<p>Blur founder, Pacman, defends his NFT marketplace against accusations that the platform&rsquo;s strategies crashed the NFT market as the floor price of the Bored Ape Yacht Club NFT collection has dropped to the lowest in the last 20 months.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Members of the Azuki decentralized autonomous organization have initiated a Snapshot proposal to hold the project&rsquo;s founder accountable over allegations of misconduct.&nbsp;</p>
Security
<p>The Poly Network has fallen victim to another exploit after hackers manipulated a smart contract function on the cross-chain bridge protocol. According to security analysts, hackers allegedly leveraged a vulnerability in the smart contract system to mint an unlimited amount of tokens.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice. </p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[USDT Stablecoin Is Flowing To Exchanges, Experts Say It Is More Profitable To Hold Tradecurve]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/usdt-stablecoin-is-flowing-to-exchanges-experts-say-it-is-more-profitable-to-hold-tradecurve</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-91.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-91.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-91.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 20:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/usdt-stablecoin-is-flowing-to-exchanges-experts-say-it-is-more-profitable-to-hold-tradecurve</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Over the past month, thousands of investors have moved their Tether (USDT) stablecoin to exchanges, in an effort to hedge against price fluctuations. At its peak in June, USDT was experiencing a daily trading volume of $33 billion, making USDT the number one most traded cryptocurrency in the world.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, with the U.S. economy struggling and several banks collapsing, some investors believe that stablecoins may not be as safe as first perceived. As a result, many investors are now choosing to diversify their portfolios with new altcoins like Tradecurve, which is on track to hit a 125% ROI in July.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;Register For The Tradecurve Presale&lt;&lt;&nbsp;</p>
USDT Experiences A Surge In Tokens On Exchanges
<p>Throughout June, a total of 13.4 billion USDT was sent to cryptocurrency exchanges. This mass movement has been triggered by a recent SEC lawsuit against Binance and Coinbase, as well as 55 new cryptocurrencies being added to the SEC&rsquo;s list of securities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>An increase in USDT being sent to exchanges could suggest that many investors are looking to buy altcoins and other cryptocurrencies, which is good news for the market. This would imply that the market is turning bearish, which will likely drive up the value of projects.</p>
<p>However, an increase in USDT transactions could also suggest that investors want to minimize losses. This could explain the current increase in USDT transactions, as many projects have decreased in value by over 30%&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
Tradecurve&rsquo;s Stage 4 Presale Starts With A Big Win
<p>Although USDT is pegged to the USD, which in theory makes it more stable, Tradecurve is providing investors with significantly higher returns. Tradecurve started its presale at $0.01 and has already increased to $0.018, an 80% ROI for bullish investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Now the project is on track to increase to $0.0215, taking its token returns to 125%. While these returns sound high, experts predict that Tradecurve could surge by 50x during its presale, meaning there are still plenty of opportunities for investors to profit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Tradecurve has been able to thrive during the recent market conditions due to its unique new hybrid exchange. The Tradecurve exchange will combine the best of decentralized exchanges, including anonymous trading, with the best of centralized exchanges, such as the opportunity to trade traditional assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This all-in-one exchange is the perfect solution to current market trends and will open up thousands of opportunities for investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Another benefit of Tradecurve is its unique educational features. As part of Tradecurves ecosystem, investors will be able to profit from AI trading bots with a proven track record, as well as copy trading subscriptions. Copy trading will allow experienced investors to generate an income, while providing new investors with the opportunity to learn from the market's most experienced veterans.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In addition, Tradecurve has also developed a lucrative metaverse trading academy designed for traders of all levels. Just four stages into its presale Tradecurve has raised $2.8 million and is being compared to the Binance ICO.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Stage four tokens are currently selling out fast, with crypto whales buying at record rates to maximize their returns in one of the market's highest potential projects.&nbsp;</p>
<p>For more information about $TCRV presale tokens:</p>
<p>Website: https://tradecurve.io/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Buy presale: https://app.tradecurve.io/sign-up&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/Tradecurveapp&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/tradecurve_official&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Over the past month, thousands of investors have moved their Tether (USDT) stablecoin to exchanges, in an effort to hedge against price fluctuations. At its peak in June, USDT was experiencing a daily trading volume of $33 billion, making USDT the number one most traded cryptocurrency in the world.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, with the U.S. economy struggling and several banks collapsing, some investors believe that stablecoins may not be as safe as first perceived. As a result, many investors are now choosing to diversify their portfolios with new altcoins like Tradecurve, which is on track to hit a 125% ROI in July.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;Register For The Tradecurve Presale&lt;&lt;&nbsp;</p>
USDT Experiences A Surge In Tokens On Exchanges
<p>Throughout June, a total of 13.4 billion USDT was sent to cryptocurrency exchanges. This mass movement has been triggered by a recent SEC lawsuit against Binance and Coinbase, as well as 55 new cryptocurrencies being added to the SEC&rsquo;s list of securities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>An increase in USDT being sent to exchanges could suggest that many investors are looking to buy altcoins and other cryptocurrencies, which is good news for the market. This would imply that the market is turning bearish, which will likely drive up the value of projects.</p>
<p>However, an increase in USDT transactions could also suggest that investors want to minimize losses. This could explain the current increase in USDT transactions, as many projects have decreased in value by over 30%&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
Tradecurve&rsquo;s Stage 4 Presale Starts With A Big Win
<p>Although USDT is pegged to the USD, which in theory makes it more stable, Tradecurve is providing investors with significantly higher returns. Tradecurve started its presale at $0.01 and has already increased to $0.018, an 80% ROI for bullish investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Now the project is on track to increase to $0.0215, taking its token returns to 125%. While these returns sound high, experts predict that Tradecurve could surge by 50x during its presale, meaning there are still plenty of opportunities for investors to profit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Tradecurve has been able to thrive during the recent market conditions due to its unique new hybrid exchange. The Tradecurve exchange will combine the best of decentralized exchanges, including anonymous trading, with the best of centralized exchanges, such as the opportunity to trade traditional assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This all-in-one exchange is the perfect solution to current market trends and will open up thousands of opportunities for investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Another benefit of Tradecurve is its unique educational features. As part of Tradecurves ecosystem, investors will be able to profit from AI trading bots with a proven track record, as well as copy trading subscriptions. Copy trading will allow experienced investors to generate an income, while providing new investors with the opportunity to learn from the market's most experienced veterans.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In addition, Tradecurve has also developed a lucrative metaverse trading academy designed for traders of all levels. Just four stages into its presale Tradecurve has raised $2.8 million and is being compared to the Binance ICO.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Stage four tokens are currently selling out fast, with crypto whales buying at record rates to maximize their returns in one of the market's highest potential projects.&nbsp;</p>
<p>For more information about $TCRV presale tokens:</p>
<p>Website: https://tradecurve.io/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Buy presale: https://app.tradecurve.io/sign-up&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/Tradecurveapp&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/tradecurve_official&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Slowed by 30142 Technicals - 9 July 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-slowed-by-30142-technicals-9-july-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-8-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-8-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-8-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-slowed-by-30142-technicals-9-july-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Bears Slowed by 30142:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 9 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) continued to suffer from bearish sentiment early in the Asian session as the pair failed to sustain a break of the 30407 level, representing the 38.2% retracement of the recent depreciating range from 31525.10 to 29715.87.&nbsp; Selling activity reversed around the 30148.60 area, representing a test of the 23.6% retracement of the same depreciating range.&nbsp; Earlier selling pressure recently intensified around the 31142.38 area and this increases the risk of another test of the 29427 area, representing the 38.2% retracement of the broader appreciating range from 26165.98 to 31443.67.&nbsp; &nbsp;Below that area, the 28604.83 level represents the 50% retracement of that appreciating range.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives include the 31737, 32125, and 33569 areas.&nbsp; Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 31674, 32043, 34531, and 34658 areas.</p>
<p>Following recent selling pressure, areas of potential technical support and buying pressure include the 29427, 28886, 28804, 28182, 28096, and 27306 areas.&nbsp; &nbsp;Technicians are closely watching to see how much technical support develops around the 28095.44 area, representing the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 30422.49 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 30234.43.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Bears Slowed by 30142:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 9 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) continued to suffer from bearish sentiment early in the Asian session as the pair failed to sustain a break of the 30407 level, representing the 38.2% retracement of the recent depreciating range from 31525.10 to 29715.87.&nbsp; Selling activity reversed around the 30148.60 area, representing a test of the 23.6% retracement of the same depreciating range.&nbsp; Earlier selling pressure recently intensified around the 31142.38 area and this increases the risk of another test of the 29427 area, representing the 38.2% retracement of the broader appreciating range from 26165.98 to 31443.67.&nbsp; &nbsp;Below that area, the 28604.83 level represents the 50% retracement of that appreciating range.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives include the 31737, 32125, and 33569 areas.&nbsp; Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 31674, 32043, 34531, and 34658 areas.</p>
<p>Following recent selling pressure, areas of potential technical support and buying pressure include the 29427, 28886, 28804, 28182, 28096, and 27306 areas.&nbsp; &nbsp;Technicians are closely watching to see how much technical support develops around the 28095.44 area, representing the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 30422.49 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 30234.43.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Price Prediction: ADA’s Team Responds to SEC's Claims of Unregistered Security]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/cardano-ada-price-prediction-adas-team-responds-to-secs-claims-of-unregistered-security</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-08-at-195829.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-08-at-195829.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-08-at-195829.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/cardano-ada-price-prediction-adas-team-responds-to-secs-claims-of-unregistered-security</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Cardano (ADA) and Uwerx are making headlines with significant updates in the ever-evolving realm of cryptocurrencies. Cardano (ADA)'s team responds to the SEC's allegations of being unregistered security, shedding light on their regulatory compliance efforts. </p>
<p>Meanwhile, Uwerx's presale is nearing its sell-out, captivating investors with its innovative platform for freelancers. </p>
<p>This article delves into the latest developments and examines the potential price prediction for Cardano (ADA), offering insights into the dynamic and promising opportunities Uwerx presents. Stay informed and discover the exciting prospects that await in the crypto world.</p>
Cardano (ADA): Empowering the Future of Blockchain Technology
<p>Cardano (ADA) is a testament to successfully implementing a power-efficient Proof-of-Stake (PoS) consensus mechanism, positioning itself among the most extensive networks to achieve this remarkable feat. </p>
<p>By leveraging intelligent contracts and the Cardano (ADA) token, the platform empowers users to actively engage in network operations, fostering a society prioritizing security, transparency, and fairness.</p>
<p>Priced at $0.3537, Cardano (ADA) presents an enticing opportunity for investors and enthusiasts alike. In-depth analysis and diligent market observation suggest a projected value of $0.90 by Q2 2024, highlighting the platform's potential for growth and its undeniable appeal in innovative blockchain technology. </p>
<p>As Cardano (ADA) continues to advance, it remains a compelling force driving transformation within the industry. Stay tuned to witness the ongoing evolution of Cardano (ADA) as it forges ahead, revolutionizing the blockchain landscape and redefining the possibilities of decentralized technology.</p>
Uwerx (WERX): Redefining Freelancing with Cutting-Edge Solutions
<p>Uwerx is making waves in the freelance industry by introducing a revolutionary platform that leverages blockchain technology to empower freelancers and clients. With its focus on innovation, transparency, and user-centric features, Uwerx is poised to disrupt traditional freelance platforms and create a more efficient and rewarding ecosystem.</p>
<p>To ensure the long-term stability of the project, Uwerx has implemented a groundbreaking token lock mechanism. The team's tokens will remain locked for an impressive nine months, demonstrating their commitment to the project's success. Also, WERX tokens will be on a 25-year liquidity lock starting after the presale.</p>
<p>Uwerx has strongly emphasized security, subjecting its intelligent contracts to thorough audits by renowned firms such as SolidProof and InterFi Network. These audits provide an extra layer of assurance to users.</p>
<p>With its listing on CoinSniper and upcoming listing on Uniswap by August 1st, Uwerx is expanding its reach and enhancing liquidity for WERX tokens. These listings will offer increased trading opportunities, further bolstering the token's value and market accessibility.</p>
<p>A key differentiator for Uwerx is its transaction fee of just 1%. This fee reduction positions Uwerx as a cost-effective alternative to industry giants like Upwork and Fiverr, who charge 10-20%, enabling freelancers to retain more earnings and fostering greater participation on the platform.</p>
<p>The introduction of the Uwerx Vault adds an exciting dimension to the platform. Freelancers can securely store their WERX tokens in the vault, taking advantage of staking opportunities and earning rewards based on platform variables. </p>
Uwerx (WERX): Continuous Community Growth
<p>This week, a clickable prototype will be launched during the presale, featuring registration pages for both freelancers and clients. Furthermore, the upcoming week will witness the introduction of the Uwerx Vault feature, alongside a poll to determine the test airdrop's date.</p>
<p>The recent launch of the Alpha platform showcases Uwerx's commitment to delivering a robust user interface and a long last experience for users. This initial version includes signing up, logging in, job creation, talent sourcing, and activity monitoring. The team is actively working toward the Beta version, which will introduce additional enhancements and further streamline the platform's capabilities.</p>
<p>The success of Uwerx's presale has been astounding, with each stage surpassing expectations. In Stage 5, the presale allows investors to secure WERX tokens for $0.047725 per token, with an additional 15% bonus on every purchase. The overwhelming response underscores the market's confidence in Uwerx's vision and potential. </p>
<p>The price is set to rise to $0.05245 on Monday, July 10th at 18:00 UTC.</p>
<p>After the presale concludes on July 31st, token holders can look forward to a 6-week vesting period. Tokens will be gradually distributed during this period according to a predetermined schedule, ensuring a balanced and controlled release.</p>
<p>Seize the chance to join this extraordinary adventure and contribute to shaping the future of freelance work. Uwerx values your invaluable feedback, so don't hesitate to share it at feedback@uwerx.network and let us know what you think.</p>
Stay ahead of the Uwerx presale by using the links below:
<p>Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cardano (ADA) and Uwerx are making headlines with significant updates in the ever-evolving realm of cryptocurrencies. Cardano (ADA)'s team responds to the SEC's allegations of being unregistered security, shedding light on their regulatory compliance efforts. </p>
<p>Meanwhile, Uwerx's presale is nearing its sell-out, captivating investors with its innovative platform for freelancers. </p>
<p>This article delves into the latest developments and examines the potential price prediction for Cardano (ADA), offering insights into the dynamic and promising opportunities Uwerx presents. Stay informed and discover the exciting prospects that await in the crypto world.</p>
Cardano (ADA): Empowering the Future of Blockchain Technology
<p>Cardano (ADA) is a testament to successfully implementing a power-efficient Proof-of-Stake (PoS) consensus mechanism, positioning itself among the most extensive networks to achieve this remarkable feat. </p>
<p>By leveraging intelligent contracts and the Cardano (ADA) token, the platform empowers users to actively engage in network operations, fostering a society prioritizing security, transparency, and fairness.</p>
<p>Priced at $0.3537, Cardano (ADA) presents an enticing opportunity for investors and enthusiasts alike. In-depth analysis and diligent market observation suggest a projected value of $0.90 by Q2 2024, highlighting the platform's potential for growth and its undeniable appeal in innovative blockchain technology. </p>
<p>As Cardano (ADA) continues to advance, it remains a compelling force driving transformation within the industry. Stay tuned to witness the ongoing evolution of Cardano (ADA) as it forges ahead, revolutionizing the blockchain landscape and redefining the possibilities of decentralized technology.</p>
Uwerx (WERX): Redefining Freelancing with Cutting-Edge Solutions
<p>Uwerx is making waves in the freelance industry by introducing a revolutionary platform that leverages blockchain technology to empower freelancers and clients. With its focus on innovation, transparency, and user-centric features, Uwerx is poised to disrupt traditional freelance platforms and create a more efficient and rewarding ecosystem.</p>
<p>To ensure the long-term stability of the project, Uwerx has implemented a groundbreaking token lock mechanism. The team's tokens will remain locked for an impressive nine months, demonstrating their commitment to the project's success. Also, WERX tokens will be on a 25-year liquidity lock starting after the presale.</p>
<p>Uwerx has strongly emphasized security, subjecting its intelligent contracts to thorough audits by renowned firms such as SolidProof and InterFi Network. These audits provide an extra layer of assurance to users.</p>
<p>With its listing on CoinSniper and upcoming listing on Uniswap by August 1st, Uwerx is expanding its reach and enhancing liquidity for WERX tokens. These listings will offer increased trading opportunities, further bolstering the token's value and market accessibility.</p>
<p>A key differentiator for Uwerx is its transaction fee of just 1%. This fee reduction positions Uwerx as a cost-effective alternative to industry giants like Upwork and Fiverr, who charge 10-20%, enabling freelancers to retain more earnings and fostering greater participation on the platform.</p>
<p>The introduction of the Uwerx Vault adds an exciting dimension to the platform. Freelancers can securely store their WERX tokens in the vault, taking advantage of staking opportunities and earning rewards based on platform variables. </p>
Uwerx (WERX): Continuous Community Growth
<p>This week, a clickable prototype will be launched during the presale, featuring registration pages for both freelancers and clients. Furthermore, the upcoming week will witness the introduction of the Uwerx Vault feature, alongside a poll to determine the test airdrop's date.</p>
<p>The recent launch of the Alpha platform showcases Uwerx's commitment to delivering a robust user interface and a long last experience for users. This initial version includes signing up, logging in, job creation, talent sourcing, and activity monitoring. The team is actively working toward the Beta version, which will introduce additional enhancements and further streamline the platform's capabilities.</p>
<p>The success of Uwerx's presale has been astounding, with each stage surpassing expectations. In Stage 5, the presale allows investors to secure WERX tokens for $0.047725 per token, with an additional 15% bonus on every purchase. The overwhelming response underscores the market's confidence in Uwerx's vision and potential. </p>
<p>The price is set to rise to $0.05245 on Monday, July 10th at 18:00 UTC.</p>
<p>After the presale concludes on July 31st, token holders can look forward to a 6-week vesting period. Tokens will be gradually distributed during this period according to a predetermined schedule, ensuring a balanced and controlled release.</p>
<p>Seize the chance to join this extraordinary adventure and contribute to shaping the future of freelance work. Uwerx values your invaluable feedback, so don't hesitate to share it at feedback@uwerx.network and let us know what you think.</p>
Stay ahead of the Uwerx presale by using the links below:
<p>Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[XRP’s Regulatory Hurdles Will Not Stifle InQubeta (QUBE) and Cardano (ADA) as Growth Surges]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/xrps-regulatory-hurdles-will-not-stifle-inqubeta-qube-and-cardano-ada-as-growth-surges</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-08-at-200531.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-08-at-200531.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-08-at-200531.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/xrps-regulatory-hurdles-will-not-stifle-inqubeta-qube-and-cardano-ada-as-growth-surges</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s5">The crypto market has recently experienced a bearish trend that has concerned many investors. This downturn can largely be attributed to the SEC lawsuits against major exchanges such as Binance and Coinbase, which have caused significant uncertainty.</p>
<p class="s5">Additionally, the classification of several tokens as securities has raised concerns about the future of established cryptocurrencies. However, despite these challenges, both InQubeta (QUBE) and Cardano (ADA) have defied the odds and continued their upward growth trajectory. Let's take a closer look at these two tokens and explore their features and growth potential.</p>
InQubeta (QUBE): Dominating the AI Crypto Sector
<p class="s5">InQubeta (QUBE) has garnered significant attention for its advancements in the AI crypto sector. Here are some notable features that make QUBE a promising investment:</p>
<p class="s5">1. AI Integration: InQubeta harnesses the power of artificial intelligence within its blockchain ecosystem. This integration allows for enhanced automation, data analysis, and decision-making processes, positioning QUBE at the forefront of innovation in the AI space.</p>
<p class="s5">2. Diverse Utility: QUBE serves as a utility token within the InQubeta ecosystem, providing access to a wide range of AI-based services and products. These include AI-powered investment strategies, predictive analytics, and personalized recommendations, creating value for token holders.</p>
<p class="s5">3. Strong Community Support: InQubeta has built a vibrant community of supporters and contributors who actively participate in the project's development. The community's collective knowledge and expertise contribute to the ecosystem's ongoing growth and success.</p>
Don't Miss the InQubeta Presale
<p class="s5">Investors should not overlook the ongoing InQubeta (QUBE) presale, as it presents an excellent opportunity to get involved in this promising project. Here are some essential details about the presale:</p>
<p class="s5">- Successful Presale: The InQubeta presale has already raised over $850,000 within a few weeks of its launch, highlighting the strong interest in the project.</p>
<p class="s5">- Multiple Payment Options: The presale accepts various payment systems, including popular cryptocurrencies like BTC, USDT, ETH, BNB, and more. This flexibility ensures accessibility and convenience for a wide range of investors.</p>
<p class="s5">- Inclusive Entry Fee: The presale welcomes participants with a minimum entry fee of $50, making it an inclusive opportunity and promoting decentralized token distribution.</p>
<p class="s5">- Growth Potential: Experts have predicted that InQubeta (QUBE) has the potential to increase its value by up to 50 times before the end of 2023, making it an enticing investment option for long-term gains.</p>
<p></p>
Cardano (ADA): A Must-Have in Every Investor's Portfolio
<p class="s5">Cardano (ADA) is a top cryptocurrency offering unique features and robust fundamentals. Here are some reasons why ADA should be considered a valuable addition to any investor's portfolio:</p>
<p class="s5">1. Proof-of-Stake (PoS) Protocol: Cardano operates on a PoS consensus mechanism, which ensures scalability, energy efficiency, and security. This approach sets Cardano apart from other cryptocurrencies and positions it for long-term success.</p>
<p class="s5">2. Smart Contract Capabilities: Cardano is actively developing its smart contract capabilities, which will enable the creation and execution of decentralized applications (dApps) on its blockchain. This positions ADA to compete with established smart contract platforms.</p>
<p class="s5">3. Robust Ecosystem: Cardano has fostered a vibrant ecosystem with numerous projects, partnerships, and community initiatives. This ecosystem offers a fertile ground for innovation and collaboration, increasing the potential for growth and adoption of ADA.</p>
Conclusion
<p class="s5">Despite the regulatory challenges faced by the crypto market, both InQubeta (QUBE) and Cardano (ADA) have demonstrated resilience and continued their growth trajectory. InQubeta'sdominance in the AI crypto sector, its promising features, and its ongoing presale success position it as an attractive investment option. Cardano's solid fundamentals and active ecosystem make ADA a valuable addition to any investor's portfolio. As the crypto market evolves, these tokens showcase their potential for long-term gains and underline the importance of diversification in the ever-changing landscape of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p class="s10">Visit InQubeta Presale</p>
<p class="s14">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s5">The crypto market has recently experienced a bearish trend that has concerned many investors. This downturn can largely be attributed to the SEC lawsuits against major exchanges such as Binance and Coinbase, which have caused significant uncertainty.</p>
<p class="s5">Additionally, the classification of several tokens as securities has raised concerns about the future of established cryptocurrencies. However, despite these challenges, both InQubeta (QUBE) and Cardano (ADA) have defied the odds and continued their upward growth trajectory. Let's take a closer look at these two tokens and explore their features and growth potential.</p>
InQubeta (QUBE): Dominating the AI Crypto Sector
<p class="s5">InQubeta (QUBE) has garnered significant attention for its advancements in the AI crypto sector. Here are some notable features that make QUBE a promising investment:</p>
<p class="s5">1. AI Integration: InQubeta harnesses the power of artificial intelligence within its blockchain ecosystem. This integration allows for enhanced automation, data analysis, and decision-making processes, positioning QUBE at the forefront of innovation in the AI space.</p>
<p class="s5">2. Diverse Utility: QUBE serves as a utility token within the InQubeta ecosystem, providing access to a wide range of AI-based services and products. These include AI-powered investment strategies, predictive analytics, and personalized recommendations, creating value for token holders.</p>
<p class="s5">3. Strong Community Support: InQubeta has built a vibrant community of supporters and contributors who actively participate in the project's development. The community's collective knowledge and expertise contribute to the ecosystem's ongoing growth and success.</p>
Don't Miss the InQubeta Presale
<p class="s5">Investors should not overlook the ongoing InQubeta (QUBE) presale, as it presents an excellent opportunity to get involved in this promising project. Here are some essential details about the presale:</p>
<p class="s5">- Successful Presale: The InQubeta presale has already raised over $850,000 within a few weeks of its launch, highlighting the strong interest in the project.</p>
<p class="s5">- Multiple Payment Options: The presale accepts various payment systems, including popular cryptocurrencies like BTC, USDT, ETH, BNB, and more. This flexibility ensures accessibility and convenience for a wide range of investors.</p>
<p class="s5">- Inclusive Entry Fee: The presale welcomes participants with a minimum entry fee of $50, making it an inclusive opportunity and promoting decentralized token distribution.</p>
<p class="s5">- Growth Potential: Experts have predicted that InQubeta (QUBE) has the potential to increase its value by up to 50 times before the end of 2023, making it an enticing investment option for long-term gains.</p>
<p></p>
Cardano (ADA): A Must-Have in Every Investor's Portfolio
<p class="s5">Cardano (ADA) is a top cryptocurrency offering unique features and robust fundamentals. Here are some reasons why ADA should be considered a valuable addition to any investor's portfolio:</p>
<p class="s5">1. Proof-of-Stake (PoS) Protocol: Cardano operates on a PoS consensus mechanism, which ensures scalability, energy efficiency, and security. This approach sets Cardano apart from other cryptocurrencies and positions it for long-term success.</p>
<p class="s5">2. Smart Contract Capabilities: Cardano is actively developing its smart contract capabilities, which will enable the creation and execution of decentralized applications (dApps) on its blockchain. This positions ADA to compete with established smart contract platforms.</p>
<p class="s5">3. Robust Ecosystem: Cardano has fostered a vibrant ecosystem with numerous projects, partnerships, and community initiatives. This ecosystem offers a fertile ground for innovation and collaboration, increasing the potential for growth and adoption of ADA.</p>
Conclusion
<p class="s5">Despite the regulatory challenges faced by the crypto market, both InQubeta (QUBE) and Cardano (ADA) have demonstrated resilience and continued their growth trajectory. InQubeta'sdominance in the AI crypto sector, its promising features, and its ongoing presale success position it as an attractive investment option. Cardano's solid fundamentals and active ecosystem make ADA a valuable addition to any investor's portfolio. As the crypto market evolves, these tokens showcase their potential for long-term gains and underline the importance of diversification in the ever-changing landscape of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p class="s10">Visit InQubeta Presale</p>
<p class="s14">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Britanniacoin's Official Pre-release: introducing a unique vision for the future]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/britanniacoins-official-pre-release-introducing-a-unique-vision-for-the-future</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/main_2_1683669032Sm2XnMEnqv.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/main_2_1683669032Sm2XnMEnqv.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/main_2_1683669032Sm2XnMEnqv.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 15:05:10 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/britanniacoins-official-pre-release-introducing-a-unique-vision-for-the-future</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>London, United Kingdom, July 8th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Aptius Ltd, a British financial enterprise, has developed a new cryptocurrency called BritanniaCoin which will be available for pre-sale from June 18th onwards, ahead of its launch later this year. BritanniaCoin is a British-built blockchain that introduces real-world applications while honouring British cultural heritage.</p><p>The pre-release contains 316,000 coins for sale, fixed at 6 USD per coin, in honour of the official unification of England and Scotland in 1707, 316 years ago. The pre-release presents an opportunity to purchase BritanniaCoin before its launch on exchanges at 8 USD per coin. BritanniaCoin is also launching a software wallet for the public, downloadable on the Apple App Store and Google Play. As part of BritanniaCoin's commitment to charitable causes, 10% of the proceeds from the pre-sale will be donated to charity, as listed on the BritanniaCoin website.</p><p>During its pre-sale this summer, BritanniaCoin intends to give away 125,000 coins. BritanniaCoin is 100% self-funded and developed with no silent partners, as detailed in the white paper. These initiatives aim to foster an ecosystem that represents British values, integrates historic cultural legacy with technological innovation, and supports charitable organizations such as Hearts of Gold to improve the lives of vulnerable people.</p><p>BritanniaCoin introduces a proprietary blockchain with zero fees and a 20% faster block confirmation time than Bitcoin.</p><p>After the 1st round pre-release for commercial customers started in September 2022, BritanniaCoin launched its own bespoke hardware infrastructure. This hardware wallet platform&nbsp;intends to facilitate customer&nbsp;security, anonymity, and technological innovation. This exclusive hardware wallet is currently available to private investors and commercial clients who get in touch via their website. Moreover, the prospect of providing customers of the planned NFT project with access to hardware wallets in the future is something that is currently being considered. Following the completion of its 2nd stage ICO, BritanniaCoin intends to center its blockchain ecosystem, brand identity, and community on this hardware technology basis.</p><p>BritanniaCoin pursues multiple long-term goals, including expanding its community and improving the user experience. In addition, BritanniaCoin has its own British-themed NFT&nbsp;project that provides holders unique advantages, offering access to airdrops, special discounts, voting rights, an active role in selecting which charity institutions to support and signature events, such as their recent pre-release party held at the East India Club.</p><p class="ql-align-justify"></p><p>In the aftermath of the ICO,&nbsp;BritanniaCoin intends to launch BritanniaPay, consisting of their software wallet compatible with iOS and Android and connected with the company's current hardware wallet network. BritanniaPay is an innovative new initiative that prioritizes British brands and businesses by integrating blockchain technology into its own payment system. Users can pay for their purchases at various UK and international retailers with BritanniaCoin alongside Bitcoin, Ethereum and other established cryptocurrencies.</p><p>BritanniaCoin unites a diverse team, as the Co-founder and CEO Daniel M. Ashworth brings over five years of experience in the cryptocurrency sector and co-founded Aptius in 2018, a Crypto and Forex trading company. Co-founder and CTO Jonathan Peters has 10 years of programming experience, including blockchain architecture, network infrastructures, and algorithmic trading software. COO Demetri Georgiev has over 10 years of experience in logistics operations and supports the project's day-to-day operations. Events Manager Mark Turley has acquired over 18 years of experience arranging entertainment events and manages the project's unique range of events in magnificent venues, such as the East India club. Charities Co-ordinator Mary Johnston has over 30 years of experience in sales and marketing and is actively involved in Hearts of Gold, the nominated charitable foundation supported by BritanninaCoin.</p><p>For more details about BritanniaCoin, access the project&rsquo;s website.</p><p>About BritanniaCoin</p><p class="ql-align-justify">BritanniaCoin is a cryptocurrency that deploys real-world utilities developed by Aptius Ltd, a British financial organization. Available for pre-sale from June 18th, BritanniaCoin intends to celebrate British cultural heritage.</p>ContactDaniel M. AshworthBritanniacoin Ltdinfo@britanniacoin.org]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>London, United Kingdom, July 8th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Aptius Ltd, a British financial enterprise, has developed a new cryptocurrency called BritanniaCoin which will be available for pre-sale from June 18th onwards, ahead of its launch later this year. BritanniaCoin is a British-built blockchain that introduces real-world applications while honouring British cultural heritage.</p><p>The pre-release contains 316,000 coins for sale, fixed at 6 USD per coin, in honour of the official unification of England and Scotland in 1707, 316 years ago. The pre-release presents an opportunity to purchase BritanniaCoin before its launch on exchanges at 8 USD per coin. BritanniaCoin is also launching a software wallet for the public, downloadable on the Apple App Store and Google Play. As part of BritanniaCoin's commitment to charitable causes, 10% of the proceeds from the pre-sale will be donated to charity, as listed on the BritanniaCoin website.</p><p>During its pre-sale this summer, BritanniaCoin intends to give away 125,000 coins. BritanniaCoin is 100% self-funded and developed with no silent partners, as detailed in the white paper. These initiatives aim to foster an ecosystem that represents British values, integrates historic cultural legacy with technological innovation, and supports charitable organizations such as Hearts of Gold to improve the lives of vulnerable people.</p><p>BritanniaCoin introduces a proprietary blockchain with zero fees and a 20% faster block confirmation time than Bitcoin.</p><p>After the 1st round pre-release for commercial customers started in September 2022, BritanniaCoin launched its own bespoke hardware infrastructure. This hardware wallet platform&nbsp;intends to facilitate customer&nbsp;security, anonymity, and technological innovation. This exclusive hardware wallet is currently available to private investors and commercial clients who get in touch via their website. Moreover, the prospect of providing customers of the planned NFT project with access to hardware wallets in the future is something that is currently being considered. Following the completion of its 2nd stage ICO, BritanniaCoin intends to center its blockchain ecosystem, brand identity, and community on this hardware technology basis.</p><p>BritanniaCoin pursues multiple long-term goals, including expanding its community and improving the user experience. In addition, BritanniaCoin has its own British-themed NFT&nbsp;project that provides holders unique advantages, offering access to airdrops, special discounts, voting rights, an active role in selecting which charity institutions to support and signature events, such as their recent pre-release party held at the East India Club.</p><p class="ql-align-justify"></p><p>In the aftermath of the ICO,&nbsp;BritanniaCoin intends to launch BritanniaPay, consisting of their software wallet compatible with iOS and Android and connected with the company's current hardware wallet network. BritanniaPay is an innovative new initiative that prioritizes British brands and businesses by integrating blockchain technology into its own payment system. Users can pay for their purchases at various UK and international retailers with BritanniaCoin alongside Bitcoin, Ethereum and other established cryptocurrencies.</p><p>BritanniaCoin unites a diverse team, as the Co-founder and CEO Daniel M. Ashworth brings over five years of experience in the cryptocurrency sector and co-founded Aptius in 2018, a Crypto and Forex trading company. Co-founder and CTO Jonathan Peters has 10 years of programming experience, including blockchain architecture, network infrastructures, and algorithmic trading software. COO Demetri Georgiev has over 10 years of experience in logistics operations and supports the project's day-to-day operations. Events Manager Mark Turley has acquired over 18 years of experience arranging entertainment events and manages the project's unique range of events in magnificent venues, such as the East India club. Charities Co-ordinator Mary Johnston has over 30 years of experience in sales and marketing and is actively involved in Hearts of Gold, the nominated charitable foundation supported by BritanninaCoin.</p><p>For more details about BritanniaCoin, access the project&rsquo;s website.</p><p>About BritanniaCoin</p><p class="ql-align-justify">BritanniaCoin is a cryptocurrency that deploys real-world utilities developed by Aptius Ltd, a British financial organization. Available for pre-sale from June 18th, BritanniaCoin intends to celebrate British cultural heritage.</p>ContactDaniel M. AshworthBritanniacoin Ltdinfo@britanniacoin.org]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
