<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Russia’s Ministry of Energy Pushes to Legalize Crypto Mining</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/russias-ministry-of-energy-pushes-legalize-crypto-mining.htm</link><description>Russia’s Ministry of Energy is pushing for the legalization of industrial crypto mining, and wants lawmakers to press ahead with a much-anticipated mining-related bill. &lt;br /&gt;
Per the Russian news agency Tass, the ministry made the comments at the weekend, during the St. Petersburg International Economic Forum....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russias-ministry-of-energy-pushes-legalize-crypto-mining.htm"&gt;Read More: Russia’s Ministry of Energy Pushes to Legalize Crypto Mining&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Russia</category><category>Crypto Mining</category><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/russias-ministry-of-energy-pushes-legalize-crypto-mining.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117295/313636/russia-1906.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="707795"/></item><item><title>IMF Is Working Hard on a Global CBDC Concept, Director Georgieva Said: Bloomberg News</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/imf-working-hard-global-cbdc-concept-director-georgieva-said-bloomberg-news.htm</link><description>International Monetary Fund Managing Director Kristalina Georgieva said that the agency is “working hard on a concept of global infrastructure” to make sure there is interoperability of settlements between digital currencies that are issued by national central banks, according to Bloomberg News. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/imf-working-hard-global-cbdc-concept-director-georgieva-said-bloomberg-news.htm"&gt;Read More: IMF Is Working Hard on a Global CBDC Concept, Director Georgieva Said: Bloomberg News&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>IMF</category><category>CBDC</category><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 00:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/imf-working-hard-global-cbdc-concept-director-georgieva-said-bloomberg-news.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117377/313794/adobestock-310268103-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="351968"/></item><item><title>Washington DC Home Linked to Former FTX CEO May Have Been Sold</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/washington-dc-home-linked-former-ftx-ceo-may-been-sold.htm</link><description>A Victorian brownstone in Washington DC linked to former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried may have been sold.  &lt;br /&gt;
The four-bedroom home near Capitol Hill was listed on Realtor.com as “contingent,” meaning that an offer has been made and accepted, but some additional criteria needs to be met.  &lt;br /&gt;
Cointelegraph reported the news earlier on Monday....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/washington-dc-home-linked-former-ftx-ceo-may-been-sold.htm"&gt;Read More: Washington DC Home Linked to Former FTX CEO May Have Been Sold&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>FTX</category><category>SBF</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 19:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/washington-dc-home-linked-former-ftx-ceo-may-been-sold.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117374/313793/screen-shot-2023-05-12-at.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="515770"/></item><item><title>Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: June 19, 2023</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-delisting-announcements-june-19-2023.htm</link><description>Here is our weekly collection of digital asset listing and delisting, trading pair-related announcements by crypto exchanges that we found last week and today. &lt;br /&gt;
Have we missed something? Do you have information about new listings and/or delistings? Let us know here. &lt;br /&gt;
_________________________________________ &lt;br /&gt;
AscendEXListings:Wall Street Baby (WSB)Spiral Tower (STS) &lt;br /&gt;
BitForexListings: VNX (VNX)WAGMI Games (WAGMIGAMES)UC Finance  (UCF)...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-delisting-announcements-june-19-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: June 19, 2023&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Altcoins</category><category>Exchange</category><category>Trading</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-delisting-announcements-june-19-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117327/313688/listings-and-delisting.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="293198"/></item><item><title>School Kids Reportedly Phishing Millions in NFTs for Roblox Skins</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/school-kids-reportedly-phishing-millions-nfts-for-roblox-skins.htm</link><description>Phishing attacks in the world of non-fungible tokens (NFTs) have taken a concerning turn as school children allegedly steal millions of dollars' worth of NFTs to splurge on coveted Roblox skins. &lt;br /&gt;
The new and disturbing trend was highlighted by The Block in an article this weekend, which said a growing number of exploits using compromised Discord servers and Twitter accounts have been orchestrated by young people....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/school-kids-reportedly-phishing-millions-nfts-for-roblox-skins.htm"&gt;Read More: School Kids Reportedly Phishing Millions in NFTs for Roblox Skins&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><category>Scam</category><category>NFT</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 18:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/school-kids-reportedly-phishing-millions-nfts-for-roblox-skins.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117368/313773/scammer.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="238905"/></item><item><title>Binance.US Sees Sharp Market Share Decline Following SEC Lawsuit</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binanceus-sees-sharp-market-share-decline-following-sec-lawsuit.htm</link><description>Binance’s US-based exchange, Binance.US, has seen a sharp decline in its share of the trading volume among exchanges that support USD-to-crypto trading. &lt;br /&gt;
The dwindling market share held by Binance.US was clearly visible on data analyzed by The Block, which showed that the exchange now holds a market share of just 4.35%, down from more than 16% in April....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binanceus-sees-sharp-market-share-decline-following-sec-lawsuit.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance.US Sees Sharp Market Share Decline Following SEC Lawsuit&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><category>SEC</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binanceus-sees-sharp-market-share-decline-following-sec-lawsuit.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117364/313768/binance-us-and-sec.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="90677"/></item><item><title>JPMorgan Report: Hinman Documents in SEC-Ripple Case Strengthen Ether</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/jpmorgan-report-hinman-documents-in-sec-ripple-case-strengthen-ether.htm</link><description>JPMorgan believes the release of the Hinman documents in the ongoing legal battle between Ripple and the US Securities and Exchange Commission could benefit ethereum (ETH).  &lt;br /&gt;
In a Thursday research report, JPMorgan analyst Nikolaos Panigirtzoglou wrote that the internal SEC messages related to a 2018 speech by former Director William Hinman suggest ether did not look like a security....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/jpmorgan-report-hinman-documents-in-sec-ripple-case-strengthen-ether.htm"&gt;Read More: JPMorgan Report: Hinman Documents in SEC-Ripple Case Strengthen Ether&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>JPMorgan</category><category>SEC</category><category>Securities and Exchange Commission</category><category>Security</category><category>Ethereum</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/jpmorgan-report-hinman-documents-in-sec-ripple-case-strengthen-ether.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117365/313769/jpmorgan-media-library-or.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="67947"/></item><item><title>Crypto Lawyer Kyle Roche Was the 'Victim of an Elaborate International Set Up' – Here's What Happened</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-lawyer-kyle-roche-was-victim-of-an-elaborate-international-set-up-heres-what-happened.htm</link><description>Disgraced crypto lawyer Kyle Roche fell “victim to an elaborate international setup” that caused him to expose himself as corruptly beholden to Avalanche founder Ava Labs, reported the New York Times on Sunday.  &lt;br /&gt;
The setup, which destroyed Roche’s career as one of the biggest lawyers in cryptocurrency litigation, began in December 2021 when Roche received an email from a trusted peer introducing him to a businessman named Mauricio Andres Villavicencio de Aguilar....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-lawyer-kyle-roche-was-victim-of-an-elaborate-international-set-up-heres-what-happened.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Lawyer Kyle Roche Was the 'Victim of an Elaborate International Set Up' – Here's What Happened&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-lawyer-kyle-roche-was-victim-of-an-elaborate-international-set-up-heres-what-happened.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117358/313752/adobestock-369214601.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="178398"/></item><item><title>Coinbase Condemns SEC's 'Evasive Response' to Court Mandate</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-condemns-secs-evasive-response-court-mandate.htm</link><description>The US Securities and Exchange Commission was recently heavily criticized by a Coinbase executive after it provided rather evasive responses to questions from the US federal court.  &lt;br /&gt;
The exchange’s Chief Legal Officer, Paul Grewal, commented on the regulator’s behavior in a series of tweets. &lt;br /&gt;
According to Grewal, the exchange could not wait for its deadline this week to address the SEC’s response to the June 6 order from the Third Circuit.  &lt;br /&gt;
He pointed out that:...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-condemns-secs-evasive-response-court-mandate.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase Condemns SEC's 'Evasive Response' to Court Mandate&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-condemns-secs-evasive-response-court-mandate.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117333/313749/adobestock-427978506-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="202005"/></item><item><title>Binance Takes Legal Action Against Fraudulent Nigerian Entity – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-takes-legal-action-against-fraudulent-nigerian-entity.htm</link><description>Crypto giant Binance has issued a cease and desist notice against Binance Nigeria Limited, a “scam entity.” purporting to be associated with Binance. &lt;br /&gt;
On June 9, the Nigerian Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) ordered Binance to halt its operations of the local entity in the African country.  &lt;br /&gt;
The SEC said in its circular that the exchange was courting local investors through an illegal website. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-takes-legal-action-against-fraudulent-nigerian-entity.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Takes Legal Action Against Fraudulent Nigerian Entity – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><category>Changpeng Zhao</category><category>US SEC</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-takes-legal-action-against-fraudulent-nigerian-entity.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117348/313732/binance-nigeria.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="101011"/></item><item><title>Binance Subsidiary Cancels Registration With UK Regulator</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-subsidiary-cancels-registration-with-uk-regulator.htm</link><description>Binance Markets Limited, a UK subsidiary of Binance, has canceled its registration with a UK regulator.  &lt;br /&gt;
That came in a June 7 update from the Financial Conduct Authority that said the subsidiary is not allowed to “undertake any regulated activity in the UK.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-subsidiary-cancels-registration-with-uk-regulator.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Subsidiary Cancels Registration With UK Regulator&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><category>FCA</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 15:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-subsidiary-cancels-registration-with-uk-regulator.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117355/313743/adobestock-494313732-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="247808"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: IMF Will 'Pursue Relentlessly' CBDC Development, France Supports Global DeFi Rules, Crypto.com Operating Internal Proprietary Trading &amp; Market-Making Teams, Wyre Set to Shut Down</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/briefs.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/briefs.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: IMF Will 'Pursue Relentlessly' CBDC Development, France Supports Global DeFi Rules, Crypto.com Operating Internal Proprietary Trading &amp; Market-Making Teams, Wyre Set to Shut Down&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>CBDC</category><category>IMF</category><category>Central Bank</category><category>Regulation</category><category>France</category><category>DeFi</category><category>Crypto.com</category><category>Binance</category><category>UK</category><category>FCA</category><category>Wyre</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Staking</category><category>Web3</category><category>Hong Kong</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/briefs.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117323/313722/adobestock-kristina-blokhin-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="323639"/></item><item><title>Nike Hints at NFT Integration with Fortnite Game</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/nike-hints-at-nft-integration-with-fortnite-game.htm</link><description>Popular sports brand Nike has hinted at the possibility of launching a collection of sneaker-themed non-fungible tokens (NFTs) within the popular game Fortnite. &lt;br /&gt;
In a June 16 announcement from Nike, it was revealed that the "ultimate Sneakerhunt" would begin on June 20, with a video featuring the logos of Fortnite's Air Max and Nike's Web3 platform, .Swoosh....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/nike-hints-at-nft-integration-with-fortnite-game.htm"&gt;Read More: Nike Hints at NFT Integration with Fortnite Game&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><category>Nike</category><category>NFT</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 14:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/nike-hints-at-nft-integration-with-fortnite-game.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117347/313723/nft-sneakers.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="93961"/></item><item><title>Terraform Labs Co-Founder Do Kwon Found Guilty of Using False Passports in Montenegro Court</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terraform-labs-co-founder-do-kwon-found-guilty-of-using-false-passports-in-montenegro-court.htm</link><description>Terraform Labs co-founder Do Kwon was found guilty of using fake passports in a court in Montenegro on Monday.  &lt;br /&gt;
Kwon along with Terraform Labs’ former Chief Financial Officer Han Chong-joon will serve four months in prison each, according to a statement released by the Podgorica Basic Court. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terraform-labs-co-founder-do-kwon-found-guilty-of-using-false-passports-in-montenegro-court.htm"&gt;Read More: Terraform Labs Co-Founder Do Kwon Found Guilty of Using False Passports in Montenegro Court&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Do Kwon</category><category>Terra</category><category>Montenegro</category><category>SEC</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 14:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terraform-labs-co-founder-do-kwon-found-guilty-of-using-false-passports-in-montenegro-court.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117345/313720/screen-shot-2023-05-11-at.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="637793"/></item><item><title>Crypto.com Internal Trading Teams Prompt Concerns Over Conflicts of Interest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cryptocom-internal-trading-teams-prompt-concerns-over-conflicts-of-interest.htm</link><description>Major cryptocurrency exchange Crypto.com has come under scrutiny for deploying internal teams to trade tokens for profit.  &lt;br /&gt;
The Singapore-based group reportedly operates proprietary trading and market-making teams, which has raised concerns about potential conflicts of interest, the Financial Times reported, citing people familiar with the matter. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cryptocom-internal-trading-teams-prompt-concerns-over-conflicts-of-interest.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto.com Internal Trading Teams Prompt Concerns Over Conflicts of Interest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Crypto.com</category><category>Crypto Exchange</category><category>Conflict</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/cryptocom-internal-trading-teams-prompt-concerns-over-conflicts-of-interest.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117328/313689/adobestock-piter2121-1-1-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="110615"/></item><item><title>Spanish Crypto Exchange Bit2Me Raises $15 Million for Expansion in Spain and Latin America</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/spanish-crypto-exchange-bit2me-raises-15-million-for-expansion-spain-latin-america.htm</link><description>Bit2Me, a prominent crypto exchange based in Spain, has successfully raised €14 million in funding to strengthen its position within the Spanish market and expand its operations into Latin America. &lt;br /&gt;
The exchange announced the news on its blog, sharing that the funding round was led by Investcorp, a global manager of alternative investment products for private and institutional clients with more than $50 billion in assets under management. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/spanish-crypto-exchange-bit2me-raises-15-million-for-expansion-spain-latin-america.htm"&gt;Read More: Spanish Crypto Exchange Bit2Me Raises $15 Million for Expansion in Spain and Latin America&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Bit2Me</category><category>Spain</category><category>Latin America</category><category>Investment</category><category>Cardano</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/spanish-crypto-exchange-bit2me-raises-15-million-for-expansion-spain-latin-america.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117300/313663/brand-img-b2m-app.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="604680"/></item><item><title>Elon Musk's 'Scam Crypto' Claim Leads to Suspension of AI Bot on Twitter – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/elon-musks-scam-crypto-claim-leads-suspension-of-ai-bot-twitter-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>Twitter has suspended the account of a popular meme coin-linked AI bot "Explain This Bob" after Elon Musk called it a "scam." &lt;br /&gt;
"This sure looks like a scam crypto account. If so, it will be suspended," Musk said in response to a tweet by the bot.  &lt;br /&gt;
The account appears to have been suspended soon after Musk's tweet. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/elon-musks-scam-crypto-claim-leads-suspension-of-ai-bot-twitter-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: Elon Musk's 'Scam Crypto' Claim Leads to Suspension of AI Bot on Twitter – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Twitter</category><category>Twitter scam</category><category>Elon Musk</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 09:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/elon-musks-scam-crypto-claim-leads-suspension-of-ai-bot-twitter-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117304/313652/adobestock-612427354.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="257239"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC Maintains Stability Below $27,000; Latest Market Updates</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-maintains-stability-below-27000-latest-market-updates.htm</link><description>In the ever-evolving world of Bitcoin, the current price remains stable below the $27,000 mark. As investors eagerly monitor the price action, let's delve into the latest market updates that are influencing Bitcoin's trajectory.  &lt;br /&gt;
Notably, Goldman Sachs predicts that US inflation will decline slower than the market expects, introducing a new layer of uncertainty....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-maintains-stability-below-27000-latest-market-updates.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC Maintains Stability Below $27,000; Latest Market Updates&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 09:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-maintains-stability-below-27000-latest-market-updates.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117284/313641/19-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="526628"/></item><item><title>Terra’s Do Kwon Blames ‘Chinese-named Agency’ for ‘Fake Passports’</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terras-do-kwon-blames-chinese-named-agency-for-fake-passports.htm</link><description>Do Kwon, the Terraform Labs founder and CEO, has told a Montenegro court that he did not know the “fake” travel documents he was allegedly trying to leave the country with were forged – and blamed a “Chinese-named agency.” &lt;br /&gt;
Per the South Korean media outlets Segye Ilbo and MBN, Kwon told a District Court in Podgorica, Montenegro, that he had received all of his reportedly forged travel documents, including a Costa Rica passport, through “agencies.” &lt;br /&gt;
He said:...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terras-do-kwon-blames-chinese-named-agency-for-fake-passports.htm"&gt;Read More: Terra’s Do Kwon Blames ‘Chinese-named Agency’ for ‘Fake Passports’&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Do Kwon</category><category>Terra</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terras-do-kwon-blames-chinese-named-agency-for-fake-passports.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117270/313601/adobestock-317605927.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="654380"/></item><item><title>New Coin Listing to Watch - AiDoge to List on MEXC &amp; Uniswap Tomorrow</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-coin-listing-to-watch-aidoge-to-list-on-mexc-monday-19-june.htm</link><description>New cryptocurrency AiDoge (AI) is set to be listed on its first crypto exchanges tomorrow, on MEXC and Uniswap DEX - both at 9am UTC on Monday, June 19th.  &lt;br /&gt;
Token claim for presale buyers also takes place at the same time, 09:00 UTC. &lt;br /&gt;
As MEXC already has a token listed with the ticker symbol $AI (AICoin), AiDoge will be listed on the exchange under the ticker $AI2. &lt;br /&gt;
View the AiDoge contract on Etherscan here....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-coin-listing-to-watch-aidoge-to-list-on-mexc-monday-19-june.htm"&gt;Read More: New Coin Listing to Watch - AiDoge to List on MEXC &amp; Uniswap Tomorrow&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>ICO news</category><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 21:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-coin-listing-to-watch-aidoge-to-list-on-mexc-monday-19-june.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117275/313608/new-coin-listing-aidoge-mexc.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="521529"/></item></channel></rss>
