<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 16:40:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Institutions Are Not Interested in Crypto, Says JPMorgan Senior Strategist</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/institutions-are-not-interested-in-crypto-says-jpmorgan-senior-strategist/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 01:22:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Institutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[JP Morgan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230237</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/JPMorgan.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/JPMorgan.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Institutional investors feel relieved they stayed away from crypto, said Jared Gross.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite the massive bull market in 2020 and 2021, institutions have remained on the crypto sidelines and feel relieved about it.</p>
<p>This is what a JPMorgan senior investment strategist argued recently, indicating that the interest in the asset class from such investors is &#8220;effectively nonexistent.&#8221;</p>
<ul>
<li>The most notable bull run in the cryptocurrency market started at the end of 2020 and lasted for about a year, seeing prices explode to new highs. Bitcoin, for one, went from under $10,000 to $69,000 within that timeframe, becoming a trillion-dollar asset at the time.</li>
<li>There were multiple reports during this cycle that large individual investors, as well as institutions, are getting on the bandwagon, including <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/100-million-worth-of-bitcoin-bought-by-us-giant-massmutual-insurance-company/" data-wpel-link="internal">MassMutual</a>, One River, and others.</li>
<li>However, JPM&#8217;s senior investment analyst &#8211; Jared Gross &#8211; believes this interest has either disappeared or has never been at the scene at all.</li>
<li>He blamed it on the enhanced volatility and argued that most institutions are relieved that they missed out on last year&#8217;s rally because of everything that happened in 2022 and the massive price declines.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;As an asset class, crypto is effectively nonexistent for most large institutional investors. The volatility is too high, and the lack of an intrinsic return that you can point to makes it very challenging. Most institutional investors probably are breathing a sigh of relief that they didn’t jump into that market and are probably not going to be doing so anytime soon.&#8221; &#8211; he said during a <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/crypto-is-effectively-nonexistent-for-big-institutions-jpmorgan-s-gross-says-1.1863055#:~:text=Crypto%20Is%20&#039;Effectively%20Nonexistent&#039;%20for%20Big%20Institutions%2C%20JPMorgan&#039;s%20Gross%20Says,-Vildana%20Hajric%20and&amp;text=(Bloomberg)%20%2D%2D%20Money%20managers%20who,strategist%20at%20JPMorgan%20Asset%20Management." data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">podcast</a> with Bloomberg.</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>It&#8217;s worth noting that JPM has always had a controversial relationship with the crypto industry. In fact, it almost seems like it uses the bull markets to ramp up the market, which was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/jp-morgan-more-institutions-could-buy-bitcoin-following-massmutuals-100m-purchase/" data-wpel-link="internal">the case</a> following MassMutual&#8217;s purchase, and the bear cycles to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/jpmorgan-thinks-bitcoin-could-plunge-to-13k-following-the-ftx-crisis/" data-wpel-link="internal">predict</a> even gloomier developments.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/institutions-are-not-interested-in-crypto-says-jpmorgan-senior-strategist/" rel="nofollow">Institutions Are Not Interested in Crypto, Says JPMorgan Senior Strategist</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Billionaire Investor Bill Miller Sees Fresh Opportunities for Bitcoin Amid Sell-off</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/billionaire-investor-bill-miller-sees-fresh-opportunities-for-bitcoin-amid-sell-off/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 22:44:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230086</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Bill_Miller1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Bill_Miller1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Miller was surprised to see Bitcoin did not slash half of its current price following the FTX implosion. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Legendary investor Bill Miller continues to be bullish on Bitcoin despite the crypto asset being hit by a brutal sell-off this year.</p>
<p>The Baltimore investing giant rose to prominence by outperforming the S&amp;P 500 annually from 1991 to 2005. He subsequently served as the chairman and chief investment officer of Miller Value Partners, which had $1.9 billion in assets under management at the end of August 2022.</p>
<p>Despite announcing his retirement recently, Bitcoin remains one of his signature bets.</p>
<ul>
<li>In an <a href="https://www.barrons.com/articles/bill-miller-interview-bullish-on-bitcoin-amazon-51671661918" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">interview</a> with Barron&#8217;s, the 72-year-old billionaire reiterated his optimistic stance and said Bitcoin remains one of his top personal holdings.</li>
<li>Miller sees the cryptocurrency as a potential store of value, much like digital gold but clarified that other digital assets do not excite him and can be &#8220;lumped together in the category of venture speculation.&#8221;</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Most of them, like most venture investments, will fail. But I’ve never heard a good argument that you shouldn’t put at least 1% of your net worth into Bitcoin. Anybody can afford to lose 1%.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>The <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX bankruptcy</a> caused severe disruption in the market and proved to be a catalyzing agent for the crypto winter.</li>
<li>Miller, for one, said he is surprised that Bitcoin &#8220;is not at half of its current price&#8221; given the high-profile implosion. He considers the asset&#8217;s price hovering near $17,000 to be &#8220;remarkable,&#8221; considering many players have &#8220;fled&#8221; the scene to recover from the losses.</li>
<li>The fund manager further projected that the flagship crypto-asset would likely perform better once the Federal Reserve slows down on its monetary policy.</li>
<li>Bitcoin took a massive beating this year, and veteran crypto analyst Nicholas Merten <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/3-things-to-watch-to-identify-bitcoins-breaking-point-datadash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">predicts</a> more pain ahead.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/billionaire-investor-bill-miller-sees-fresh-opportunities-for-bitcoin-amid-sell-off/" rel="nofollow">Billionaire Investor Bill Miller Sees Fresh Opportunities for Bitcoin Amid Sell-off</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>White Hat Hackers Crack the Code: Over $65M in Crypto Bug Bounties Since 2020</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/white-hat-hackers-crack-the-code-over-65m-in-crypto-bug-bounties-since-2020/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 20:15:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230018</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/White_Hat_Hacker.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/White_Hat_Hacker.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The white hat hackers were rewarded for safeguarding over $25 billion in crypto assets.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Immunefi, a leading bug bounty platform for the cryptocurrency industry, has paid out a total of $65 million to white hat hackers since its founding in 2020.</p>
<p class="p2">These ethical hackers search for vulnerabilities in smart contracts and blockchain projects and are rewarded for reporting them to Immunefi. This helps to secure users&#8217; assets and prevent bad actors from stealing funds.</p>
<h2 class="p3">Smart Contract Bugs Account for Majority of Paid Reports</h2>
<p class="p2"><a href="https://assets.ctfassets.net/t3wqy70tc3bv/5OSuz2VWs1hSCdpkMNXxwu/59bc28b8395816429a765061f1072c03/Immunefi_Top_Crypto_Bounty_and_Ransom_Payments_Report.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">According</a> to Immunefi, 58.3% of the paid reports were for smart contract vulnerabilities, with 728 submissions. There were 488 submissions for cases in the Websites and Applications category, making up 39.1% of the total, and 32, or 2.6%, for Distributed Ledger Technology/Blockchain cases.</p>
<p class="p2">However, while Websites and Applications had the second highest number of submissions, they only accounted for 2.9% of the payouts, while smart contract bugs represented 89.6% of the payments.</p>
<p class="p2">Some projects have paid out more in bounties than others. Aurora, Wormhole, Optimism, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/polygon-dodges-a-bullet-patches-a-bug-that-put-24-billion-worth-of-matic-at-risk/" data-wpel-link="internal">Polygon</a>, and an unnamed company offered $30.2 million in payments through their bounty programs in 2021, with an average payout of $52,800 and a median payout of $2,000.</p>
<h2 class="p3">Over $52M Paid This Year</h2>
<p class="p2">In 2022, Immunefi facilitated over $52 million in payments to white hat hackers due to the increase in <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/hacktober-finished-with-657-million-losses-from-crypto-exploits/" data-wpel-link="internal">crypto hacks</a> that resulted in a loss of over $3 billion in assets.</p>
<p class="p2">The highest paid bounty of the year was a $10 million reward for a vulnerability discovered in the Wormhole decentralized messaging protocol, and another $6 million was paid for a bug found in the Aurora Ethereum-compatible layer-two scaling solution.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>Web3 Bug Bounties Higher Than Those for Web2</b></h2>
<p class="p2">Web3 bug bounties tend to be larger than those for Web2, due to the large amounts of capital held in smart contracts.</p>
<blockquote>
<p class="p2">As Immunefi explains, &#8220;A $5,000 bounty payout for a critical vulnerability may work in the web2 world, but it does not work in the web3 world. If the direct loss of funds for a web3 vulnerability could be up to $50 million, then it makes sense to offer a much larger bounty size to incentivize good behavior.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<p class="p2">Interestingly, the Wormhole bounty alone is larger than the $8.7 million <a href="https://security.googleblog.com/2022/02/vulnerability-reward-program-2021-year.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">paid</a> out by Google&#8217;s Vulnerability Reward Programs in the past year.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/white-hat-hackers-crack-the-code-over-65m-in-crypto-bug-bounties-since-2020/" rel="nofollow">White Hat Hackers Crack the Code: Over $65M in Crypto Bug Bounties Since 2020</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum&#8217;s History: From Whitepaper to Hardforks and the ETH Merge</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ethereums-history-from-whitepaper-to-hardforks-and-the-eth-merge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 17:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Editorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum 2.0]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228881</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ethereum_history_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ethereum_history_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[A closer look at how it all started, the major hard forks, and where Ethereum is headed next.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum, the second largest cryptocurrency, is the home of smart contracts and decentralized applications (dApps), holding a major share of the total value locked in the sector. Ethereum&#8217;s dominance in the dApp market was up to 90% before other rival platforms were created.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, Ethereum is still the undisputed king of dApps. Despite its high fees, the platform is still the first choice for different applications, ranging from finance, exchanges, and storage to gaming, non-fungible tokens (NFTs), and governance. This shows how far it has come since its whitepaper was published in 2013.</p>
<p>This article highlights the timeline of major events that made Ethereum a favorite decentralized blockchain network for dApp developers and its journey to Proof-of-Stake.</p>
<h2>2013: The Conception of Ethereum</h2>
<p>Ethereum, like all things, began with an idea. And the idea, which the Russian-born Canadian computer programmer Vitalik Buterin conceived, was to leverage blockchain technology to develop decentralized applications, unlike Bitcoin, which was strictly created for financial use.</p>
<p>Ethereum&#8217;s introductory paper was published in late 2013 by Buterin, the co-founder of Bitcoin Magazine. The <a href="https://ethereum.org/en/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">whitepaper</a> explained the concept of the new technology, its fundamental principles, and its possible use cases. But the project wouldn&#8217;t launch until two years later.</p>
<p>On January 23, 2014, Buterin officially <a href="https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=428589.0" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">announced</a> the start of the Ethereum ecosystem, calling on volunteers, developers, investors, and evangelists to join the project. The programmer revealed that he was working with Gavin Wood and Jeffrey Wilcke as primary core developers to build the platform. Other founding team members include Anthony Di Iorio, Joseph Lubin, and Charles Hoskinson.</p>
<p>Buterin also noted that his team&#8217;s goal was to provide a &#8220;platform for decentralized applications &#8211; an android of the cryptocurrency world, where all efforts can share a common set of APIs, trustless interactions and no compromises.&#8221;</p>
<p>Three months later, Wood published the project&#8217;s &#8220;<a href="http://gavwood.com/paper.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Yellow Paper</a>,&#8221; which provided a detailed definition and specification of the Ethereum ecosystem, including Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM), fee rewards for miners, and smart contracts. He also played a crucial role in creating Ethereum&#8217;s prototype by helping to code the project&#8217;s first functional implementation into seven programming languages.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/ethereum_cover-2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-218871" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/ethereum_cover-2.jpg" alt="ethereum_cover (2)" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/ethereum_cover-2.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/ethereum_cover-2-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/ethereum_cover-2-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/ethereum_cover-2-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/ethereum_cover-2-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>2014&#8217;s Crowdfunding: $18M Worth of BTC Funded Ethereum</h2>
<p>Ethereum developers needed large funding to build the project. So the team decided to raise capital from public investors through an initial coin offering (ICO) that lasted for 42 days, from July 20 to September 2, 2014.</p>
<p>In June 2014, the project established the Ethereum Foundation, a Swiss-based non-profit organization, to manage the legal and marketing efforts of the ICO campaign. The Foundation created a total of 60 million ether (ETH), the native cryptocurrency of the Ethereum ecosystem, for public sale. The company sold 2,000 ether per bitcoin (BTC) for the first two weeks of the ICO and 1,399 ETH per BTC for the remainder of the token sale event.</p>
<p>Interestingly, the Foundation sold over 50 million tokens within the first 14 days of the crowdfunding, and by the end of the campaign, the project raised a total of 31,531 BTC, worth more than $18 million. This made Ethereum&#8217;s crowdfunding the fifth most successful ICO in crypto history (back then).</p>
<p>The non-profit also created another 12 million ETH, bringing the total amount of minted ether to 72 million. The company said the additional tokens would be used for marketing and other developmental activities.</p>
<h2>2015: The Birth of Ethereum</h2>
<p>About two months after the crowdfunding, ETH DEV organized Ethereum&#8217;s first event, dubbed DEVCON-0, which hosted Ethereum developers worldwide to discuss the protocol&#8217;s security and scalability.</p>
<p>In April 2015, the Foundation launched its first grant program, DEVgrant, to support the best projects on the Ethereum ecosystem ahead of the platform&#8217;s pre-launch, and the program is still running to date.</p>
<p>On May 2015, the Ethereum development team released Olympic, a test version of the network, which focused on four areas &#8211; transaction activity, virtual machine usage for smart contract execution, mining prowess, and stress testing. The Foundation rewarded testers with 2,500 ETH and other prizes in each category of the testing stage.</p>
<h3><strong>Frontier</strong></h3>
<p>After the Olympic testing phase, Ethereum officially went live on July 30, 2015, nearly two years after Buterin published the project&#8217;s whitepaper. The project&#8217;s first public release, known as Frontier and aimed at developers and technical users, marked a significant milestone for the team. It was the birth of a new blockchain ecosystem for decentralized applications of all kinds, even though the protocol would later undergo a series of upgrades as it matured.</p>
<p>Like Bitcoin, the newly launched protocol adopted a proof-of-work (PoW) consensus mechanism. Ethereum created its first block (genesis block) through Frontier, and the block contained 8,893 ether transactions to different wallets, with a block reward of 5 ETH. Ether had no value during this period as there was no market for it yet. Investors who participated in ICO were still HODLing their tokens.</p>
<h3><strong>Ethereum&#8217;s Ice Age </strong></h3>
<p>The Ethereum development team introduced the Ice Age and, with it &#8211; the difficulty bomb on September 7, 2015, at block 200,000. It is a difficulty adjustment scheme designed to increase mining difficulty on the network after every 100,000 blocks, thus making it impossible for miners to keep up with the increasing difficulty level. This would make the network freeze over time, hence the name &#8220;Ice Age.&#8221;</p>
<p>The feature was implemented to ensure there would be consensus in the ecosystem on future upgrades that would transition Ethereum to a proof-of-stake (PoS) consensus network.</p>
<h3><strong>Homestead</strong></h3>
<p>On March 14, 2016, at block 1150000, the team launched an upgrade dubbed &#8220;Homestead,&#8221; nearly a year after Frontier went live. The new release came with GUI, thus making the platform useful for non-technical users.</p>
<p>The fork also enhanced the platform with Ethereum Improvement Proposals (EIP), which ensured the platform could run future upgrades.</p>
<h2>The DAO Attack of 2016: 3,600,000 ETH Stolen</h2>
<p>On April 30, 2016, a Decentralized Anonymous Organization (DAO) was created on Ethereum at block 1428757. The DAO raised $150 million worth of ether from over 11,000 investors, but little did anyone know the success wouldn&#8217;t last.</p>
<p>A <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-dao/" data-wpel-link="internal">decentralized autonomous organization (DAO)</a> is similar to a company&#8217;s board of directors, except that DAO members are anonymous, and their voting rights are determined by the number of tokens vested.</p>
<p>Barely three months after its launch, the DAO was hacked because its developer deployed the project without careful auditing. The attacker moved about 3.6M ETH, worth $60 million at that time, from the platform, which led to a controversial forking of the Ethereum network to recover the stolen assets.</p>
<p>The incident gave Ethereum its first real existential threat since DAO&#8217;s failure would have devastating consequences for the budding blockchain network in addition to financial losses for investors because the DAO had become one of the biggest projects on Ethereum.</p>
<p>The Ethereum community attempted a soft fork to avoid making permanent changes to the blockchain, but that didn&#8217;t work. A hard fork was then implemented, and the funds were restored and returned to investors.</p>
<p>A hard fork means permanently deviating from a blockchain&#8217;s latest version to upgrade or orphan the old chain. Hard forks are usually performed by people who wish to create a new token or chain that runs on different rules.</p>
<p>Ethereum&#8217;s hard fork after the DAO attack created a new blockchain. The original network was rebranded as Ethereum Classic, while the new chain retained the name &#8211; Ethereum.</p>
<p>It is worth noting that Ethereum would later undergo several hard forks. However, unlike the DAO event, none resulted in a controversial chain split except the 2022 Beacon Chain upgrade, which transitioned Ethereum to a PoS consensus mechanism. Other vital upgrades on the network include the Tangerine Whistle, Spurious Dragon, Byzantium, and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coming-up-constantinople-ethereum-is-getting-ready-to-todays-expected-2-hard-forks/" data-wpel-link="internal">Constantinople</a>.</p>
<h2>2020: The Ethereum Scalability Issues</h2>
<p>After surviving the DAO incident, Ethereum&#8217;s next major challenge was its scalability issue. Like Bitcoin, the Ethereum blockchain faces the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blockchains-and-the-scalability-problem/" data-wpel-link="internal">Blockchain Trilemma</a>, a concept first used by Buterin while describing the core functions of a decentralized blockchain network.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/blockchain_trilemma.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-228882" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/blockchain_trilemma.jpg" alt="blockchain_trilemma" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/blockchain_trilemma.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/blockchain_trilemma-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/blockchain_trilemma-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/blockchain_trilemma-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/blockchain_trilemma-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<p>The Ethereum co-founder stated that security, decentralization, and scalability are the three desirable elements of a blockchain network. However, it&#8217;s difficult for a blockchain to have efficient levels of all three features simultaneously. In other words, it must compromise one core feature to optimize for the other two.</p>
<p>By late 2017, Ethereum had become a favorite smart contract platform for dApp developers. The network also enjoyed euphoria from the bull market that year, with the blockchain game CryptoKitties pulling crowds into the Ethereum ecosystem. This resulted in network congestion, with transactions taking longer to confirm and gas fees shooting through the roof.</p>
<p>The scaling issues on Ethereum created a market for off-chain scaling products such as Polygon.</p>
<p><strong><em>You can find out more about Layer2 scaling solutions in this </em></strong><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-are-layer-2-scaling-solutions/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong><em>in-depth article</em></strong></a><strong><em>.</em></strong></p>
<p>The DeFi boom of 2020 and 2021 did not make things easy for Ethereum. While the blockchain continued to record a significant adoption rate, average users were plagued with high gas fees, thus creating the need for users to sort out cheaper alternatives such as BNB Chain and Tron.</p>
<p>To resolve its scalability issues, Ethereum implemented an upgrade in December 2020, marking the start of the network&#8217;s transition from PoW to PoS. The upgrade required 16,384 deposits of 32 staked ETH in the contract address before it was implemented.</p>
<p>Proof-of-stake is a blockchain consensus mechanism that verifies crypto transactions and creates new blocks through randomly selected validators, unlike PoW, which requires miners to solve mathematical puzzles. In PoS, validators must stake their coins before they are allowed to verify transactions on the network.</p>
<p>PoS is a more secure and energy-efficient consensus mechanism than proof-of-work architecture. According to the Ethereum Foundation, proof-of-stake is also better for implementing new scaling solutions, which Ethereum needs more than ever.</p>
<p>The upgrade created a separate PoS chain called the Beacon Chain, which ran parallel to the Ethereum PoW Mainnet. Both chains would then merge to form a single network called Ethereum 2.0 or ETH 2.0. However, the Foundation rebranded the new name to &#8220;Consensus Layer,&#8221; noting that ETH2 sounded like a new operating system, which was not the case. The rebrand was also part of the Foundation&#8217;s effort to prevent users from being victims of scams such as swapping ETH for ETH2.</p>
<h2>2022: The Ethereum Merge</h2>
<p>The Ethereum development team released several updates after the launch of the Beacon Chain in preparation for the Merge. Some of these upgrades were Altair and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-the-bellatrix-hard-fork-ethereums-last-upgrade-before-the-merge/" data-wpel-link="internal">Bellatrix</a>.</p>
<p>The precise explanation, as provided by the Ethereum Foundation, is:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The Merge represents the joining of the existing execution layer of Ethereum (the mainnet we use today) with its new proof-of-stake consensus layer – the Beacon Chain.”</p>
<figure id="attachment_228883" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-228883" style="width: 883px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/img1_merge.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-228883" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/img1_merge.jpg" alt="img1_merge" width="883" height="391" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/img1_merge.jpg 883w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/img1_merge-300x133.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/img1_merge-768x340.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/img1_merge-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 883px) 100vw, 883px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-228883" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Ethereum Foundation</figcaption></figure></blockquote>
<p>The <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-merge-a-turning-point-nft-wave-2-0-and-myetherwallets-approach-to-user-data-coo-brian-norton-interview/" data-wpel-link="internal">Ethereum Merge</a> was implemented with an upgrade called &#8220;Paris&#8221; at block 15537393 on September 15, 2022. At the time of the upgrade, over 13.4 million ETH coins were staked on the deposit contract. The fork saw Ethereum&#8217;s transition to a PoS consensus nearly two years after the Beacon genesis.</p>
<p>So what happened to Ethereum&#8217;s PoW miners after the Merge? The Ethereum network was forked to create a separate chain (similar to Ethereum Classic). The blockchain is called proof-of-work Ethereum (<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereumpow-ecosystem-continues-to-grow-as-support-for-mining-remains/" data-wpel-link="internal">ETHW</a>), and it allows miners to continue verifying blocks by solving complex mathematical puzzles for ETH rewards.</p>
<p><em><strong>You can take a look at our complete guide on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-the-merge-what-you-need-to-know-about-the-transition-to-ethereum-2-0/" data-wpel-link="internal">the Merge here</a>.</strong></em></p>
<h2>The Future: What&#8217;s Next After the Merge?</h2>
<p>With the Merge successfully implemented, the next major upgrade on Ethereum is Sharding, a multi-phase upgrade designed to improve the protocol&#8217;s scalability and overall capacity. This is known as an on-chain scaling solution.</p>
<p><a href="https://ethereum.org/en/upgrades/sharding/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Sharding</a> will work synergistically with layer2 rollups while splitting the entire Ethereum network into independent partitions called shards, thus improving the network&#8217;s throughput by up to 1000x. Aside from scalability, Sharding will introduce other benefits to Ethereum, such as more network participation and improved decentralization.</p>
<p>The upgrade is expected to be fully implemented around 2024 or beyond. This means that until then, Ethereum will likely continue to depend on off-chain scaling solutions such as <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-are-layer-2-scaling-solutions/" data-wpel-link="internal">layer 2</a> and sidechains.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereums-history-from-whitepaper-to-hardforks-and-the-eth-merge/" rel="nofollow">Ethereum&#8217;s History: From Whitepaper to Hardforks and the ETH Merge</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Following Long Consolidation, BTC Now Facing Huge Resistance: Bitcoin Price Analysis</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/following-long-consolidation-btc-now-facing-huge-resistance-bitcoin-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 16:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230264</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-dec25-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-dec25-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin continues to print minor daily fluctuations as the price consolidates inside a tight range with low volatility. Currently, the price is testing a significant resistance area, and in case a rejection takes place &#8211; BTC is likely to retest lower-price areas. On the other hand, a breakout could lead to a mini-rally. Technical Analysis [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin continues to print minor daily fluctuations as the price consolidates inside a tight range with low volatility. Currently, the price is testing a significant resistance area, and in case a rejection takes place &#8211; BTC is likely to retest lower-price areas. On the other hand, a breakout could lead to a mini-rally.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By <a href="http://twitter.com/greatest_trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>Bitcoin has failed to sustain above the 50-day and 100-day moving averages over the last few months. Most recently, the price got rejected from the 50-day moving average at $18K and has declined since then. However, it attempts to break above the 50-day moving average again.</p>
<p>Despite the ongoing struggle with the 50-day MA, the price momentum is not promising, as the overall activity and demand are at low levels. The market needs to recapture the players’ confidence before triggering a bullish rally.</p>
<p>In this regard, we can mention the MACD indicator: This indicator <strong>is about to turn green</strong>, signaling a first bullish sign in the short term, which might assist BTC in breaking above the 50-day moving average.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-1D-dec25-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-230278" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-1D-dec25-scaled.jpg" alt="BTC 1D dec25" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-1D-dec25-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-1D-dec25-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-1D-dec25-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-1D-dec25-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-1D-dec25-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-1D-dec25-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-1D-dec25-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a></p>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>The current lack of activity and low volatility is more evident on the following 4-hour timeframe chart. After going through a long-lasting downtrend, the price has rebounded from the $16K mark and is consolidating below the $17K threshold. However, the main struggle for Bitcoin is now surpassing this confluence zone.</p>
<p>Suppose the price returns above the mentioned level, a retracement to the 0.618 Fib level and the broken trendline will be the main barriers toward the $18K range.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-dec25-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-230277" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-dec25-scaled.jpg" alt="BTC 4H dec25" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-dec25-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-dec25-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-dec25-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-dec25-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-dec25-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-dec25-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-dec25-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a></p>
<h2>On-chain Analysis</h2>
<p>The following chart shows the 14-day moving average line of the Miner to Exchange Flow metric alongside Bitcoin’s price. This metric represents the total amount of coins transferred from the miners into exchanges.</p>
<p>A surge in the metric indicates possible selling pressure from the miners to cover their expenses during the bearish stage of the market. As is evident in the chart, the price declined significantly each time the metric experienced a spike.</p>
<p>However, the metric has recently plunged and marked a new multi-year low. This confirms that the miners’ selling pressure has been weakened, which might be considered a bullish sign for the price as they are a crucial cohort among the market participants.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin_Miner_to_Exchange_Flow_Total_All_Miners_All_Exchanges_SMA-1-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-230273" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin_Miner_to_Exchange_Flow_Total_All_Miners_All_Exchanges_SMA-1-scaled.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1612" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin_Miner_to_Exchange_Flow_Total_All_Miners_All_Exchanges_SMA-1-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin_Miner_to_Exchange_Flow_Total_All_Miners_All_Exchanges_SMA-1-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin_Miner_to_Exchange_Flow_Total_All_Miners_All_Exchanges_SMA-1-1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin_Miner_to_Exchange_Flow_Total_All_Miners_All_Exchanges_SMA-1-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin_Miner_to_Exchange_Flow_Total_All_Miners_All_Exchanges_SMA-1-1536x967.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin_Miner_to_Exchange_Flow_Total_All_Miners_All_Exchanges_SMA-1-2048x1290.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin_Miner_to_Exchange_Flow_Total_All_Miners_All_Exchanges_SMA-1-50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/following-long-consolidation-btc-now-facing-huge-resistance-bitcoin-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Following Long Consolidation, BTC Now Facing Huge Resistance: Bitcoin Price Analysis</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>State of Bitcoin in 2022: From HODler Confidence to Mining Transformation</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/state-of-bitcoin-in-2022-from-hodler-confidence-to-mining-transformation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 15:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bear Market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229904</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin_2022.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin_2022.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin long-term holders have shown resilience as speculators were eliminated.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>2022 has been a brutal year for the crypto investors market by the harsh crypto winter. It all started with the collapse of the TerraUSD algorithmic stablecoin, which prompted other major crypto players to fall like dominos: Three Arrows Capital. Voyager Digital, Celsius Network, FTX, BlockFi.</p>
<p>Not one project, protocol, or institution exists that hasn&#8217;t felt the sting of contagion this year. Bitcoin futures volumes are hovering near multi-year lows owing to the tightening liquidity, widespread deleveraging, and the impairment of several lending and trading desks in the sector. Open Interest, too, took a similar turn following the catastrophic fall of FTX. Bitcoin miners also bled heavily.</p>
<p>Despite spectacularly large losses, the accumulation trend stays strong in this bear market.</p>
<h2>HODlers Remain Unfazed</h2>
<p>Bitcoin is currently locked in the narrow range of $16,000 to $18,000 as the market continues to suffer from lingering macroeconomic uncertainty. That hasn&#8217;t stopped investors from piling up the tokens.</p>
<p>According to Glassnode&#8217;s last <a href="https://insights.glassnode.com/the-week-onchain-week-50-2022/?utm_campaign=woc_50_2022&amp;utm_medium=woc_newsletter&amp;utm_source=email" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">edition</a> of the year, the density of coin re-accumulation has increased after each market leg down. One that stood out, in particular, is the period between June to October when between $18k and $24k coins were acquired. The report stated,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;2022 was a brutal year, and it has driven volatility and volumes to multi-year lows, as liquidity and speculation dry up. With speculators gone, Bitcoin Long-term Holder supply has pushed to yet another ATH, and investors appear to be stepping in with increasing coin volume on each price leg down.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_229994" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-229994" style="width: 1600px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Pic1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-229994" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Pic1.png" alt="Bitcoin Accumulation Phases. Source: Glassnode" width="1600" height="794" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Pic1.png 1600w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Pic1-300x149.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Pic1-1024x508.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Pic1-768x381.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Pic1-1536x762.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Pic1-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1600px) 100vw, 1600px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-229994" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Accumulation Phases. Source: Glassnode</figcaption></figure>
<p>While institutions are being cautious, it&#8217;s the retail investors who are accumulating more and more Bitcoin. In fact, recent <a href="https://twitter.com/WClementeIII/status/1605223769555046400" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">data</a> suggest that nearly 17% of Bitcoin&#8217;s total circulating supply is now held by retail investors. According to Glassnode, such holders are those with less than 10 BTC in a wallet (currently worth $169K at today&#8217;s prices.) The percentage of Bitcoin supply held by retail investors has been on an upward trajectory since 2011.</p>
<h2>Mining Revenue Slump</h2>
<p>Bitcoin mining has undergone a dramatic transformation this year after being hit by significant income stress. A large portion of Bitcoin&#8217;s active hash rate was switched off, which triggered the difficulty adjustment to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-miners-in-peril-difficulty-sees-biggest-drop-since-july-2021/" data-wpel-link="internal">fall</a> by 7.32% most recently.</p>
<p>Over the past couple of months, many operators have taken their ASIC rigs offline while several other miners slid to bankruptcy or are on the verge of one. Compute North was the first in line to file for bankruptcy back in September.</p>
<p>Three months later, another prominent Bitcoin miner &#8211; Core Scientific &#8211; <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-miner-core-scientific-files-for-bankruptcy-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">filed</a> for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in Texas. Greenidge also approached the NYDIG to prepare for restructuring the financial debt of $74 million, though bankruptcy is still on the cards.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/state-of-bitcoin-in-2022-from-hodler-confidence-to-mining-transformation/" rel="nofollow">State of Bitcoin in 2022: From HODler Confidence to Mining Transformation</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is the Crypto Bear Market Coming to an End? 3 Key Indicators to Look</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/is-the-crypto-bear-market-coming-to-an-end-3-key-indicators-to-look/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 12:44:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230079</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Bitcoin_Winter.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Bitcoin_Winter.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Nansen analysts attempt to answer the tough question of whether crypto has bottomed out or if we have another leg down incoming.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Valuations in the cryptocurrency market have dropped significantly from their all-time highs, with the total market capitalization losing around $2.2 trillion &#8211; a decline of around 73%.</p>
<p>Many altcoins, including some from the large caps, have lost over 90% of their value since their all-time highs, and industry participants are scrambling to time the bottom.</p>
<p>In light of the above, crypto analytics resource Nansen released a <a href="https://research.nansen.ai/article/489/the-forest-for-the-trees-are-crypto-valuations-and-fundamentals-signaling-the-end-of-this-crypto-winter" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a> that identifies systematic patterns in crypto derivative markets and traditional spot markets, analyzing what they mean for the current market environment. In short, they are attempting to answer the question if the crypto bear market is coming to an end.</p>
<p>Nansen outlines three key takeaways.</p>
<h2>The US Dollar</h2>
<p>As of the time of writing these lines, the USD has started to lose strength against other major currencies such as the JPY and the CNY.</p>
<p>Nansen argues that one of the drivers for this could be the pricing of the peak Fed interest rates by future bond markets.</p>
<blockquote><p>Bond futures currently forecast that the Fed policy rate will peak at ~4.84% in May 2023 and will be cut by 40bps+ in H2 2023. Admittedly, US CPI releases have surprised to the downside for the second month in a row, which can account for part of the pricing out of rate hikes. &#8211; Reads the report.</p></blockquote>
<p>Nevertheless, rate cuts can take place if there&#8217;s a serious weakness on behalf of the US on a macro level, with their real growth slowing down considerably. The chairman of the Federal Reserve &#8211; Jerome Powell &#8211; has outlined on multiple occasions that the &#8220;risks of under-tightening outweighed the risk of over-tightening&#8221; and that the labor market was too high and needed rebalancing.</p>
<p>Using complex indicators to assess relative growth between the US and other considerations, Nansen came to the conclusion that:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;&#8230; it is probably too early to call for a transition to easier global financial conditions, and, therefore, that the fundamental case for bottoming of crypto assets is likely not there yet.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>With this, the analysts change their focus to the derivative markets.</p>
<h2>Calls vs. Puts for BTC and ETH</h2>
<p>The question that Nansen aims to answer here is if option investors in BTC and ETH have capitulated yet, and to address it, they take a look at the open-interest-weighted implied volatility of call vs. put options (CPIV).</p>
<p>The data they examine covers the period between January 2021 through November 2022, with the assumption that the derivative market is going to evolve in future cycles.</p>
<p>The conclusions that they came to can be summarized as follows:</p>
<ul>
<li>The CPIV indicator managed to generate more frequent risk-on and risk-off signals compared to the stablecoin indicator.</li>
<li>Both of them flagged the multi-month BTC decline that started in November of last year.</li>
<li>The stablecoin indicator came back to risk-on in May 2022, while the CPIV indicator was risk-off as of November 20, 2022.</li>
</ul>
<p>*Note: the stablecoin indicator mentioned above is the Nansen Smart Money Stablecoin risk appetite indicator.</p>
<h2>Crypto Risk Premium</h2>
<p>In the last section of the report, the analysts conceptualize and calculate a risk premium for crypto, called Crypto Risk Premium or CRP. It is linked to the fundamental value of the crypto assets held by investors.</p>
<p>The methodology the analysts adopt is developed by Ian Martin in a paper published in April 2015 called <em><a href="https://academic.oup.com/qje/article/132/1/367/2724543" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">What is the Expected Return on the Market?</a> </em>Nansen also uses historical options data of Deribit with consideration of the intra-day bid and ask prices of calls and puts on BTC, ETH, and SOL.</p>
<p>However, when pinning crypto and equity markets, the analysts make the caveat that crypto derivative markets are young and not as well-studied as equity options markets, meaning it&#8217;s necessary to keep an open mind when analyzing CRP estimates.</p>
<p>With that said, the conclusion (rather speculation) is that:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;&#8230;in the eventuality of a US recession and US equity sell-off (our main scenario for 2023 given the Fed’s determination to maintain tight financing conditions for longer), the ERP is likely to go much higher, and conversely, the CRP or crypto risk premium will probably also jump. It is therefore possible that crypto prices experience a further (and “last” ?) leg down in this cycle before financing conditions turn more favorable to both equity and crypto assets.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/is-the-crypto-bear-market-coming-to-an-end-3-key-indicators-to-look/" rel="nofollow">Is the Crypto Bear Market Coming to an End? 3 Key Indicators to Look</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Christmas Watch: Will 2023 Finally End Bitcoin Price&#8217;s Stagnancy Amid $17K?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/christmas-watch-will-2023-finally-end-bitcoin-prices-stagnancy-amid-17k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 09:36:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230239</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin_Christmas.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin_Christmas.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin's last several days were quite boring, will the end of the year change that?]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With the end of the year approaching fast, the primary cryptocurrency continues to remain stuck at familiar ground at just over $17,000, begging the question if that&#8217;s about to change anytime soon.</p>
<p>Most altcoins are also quite stagnant on a daily scale, aside from OKB, which has jumped by over 5% after the recent OKX proof-of-reserve statement.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Boring Below $17K</h2>
<p>The past week saw a substantial price decline from bitcoin when the asset fell to a three-week low at $16,300 on December 20. However, the bulls intercepted the move and pushed the asset back up by $500.</p>
<p>The US <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-stocks-fall-on-gdp-data-bitcoin-ethereum-hold-on-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> its GDP data on Thursday, and the PCE numbers came out on Friday, both of which were expected to bring some more volatility to the market. However, while the US stock market went down, BTC remained relatively flat, aside from a brief price drop.</p>
<p>The weekend started with bitcoin <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/weekend-watch-terra-classic-lunc-jumps-6-bitcoin-flat-amid-17k/" data-wpel-link="internal">standing close</a> to $17,000, and the asset has not moved an inch since then. It trades at $16,800 as of now as well on low trading volumes.</p>
<p>Somewhat expectedly, its dominance over the altcoins and its market cap have not moved either. The former stands at 40%, while the latter is at $325 billion.</p>
<figure id="attachment_230240" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-230240" style="width: 1791px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-8.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-230240" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-8.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1791" height="774" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-8.png 1791w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-8-300x130.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-8-1024x443.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-8-768x332.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-8-1536x664.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-8-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1791px) 100vw, 1791px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-230240" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>OKB Stands Out</h2>
<p>Most of the altcoins have failed to produce any significant movements in the past two days as well. Ethereum had a battle with $1,200 earlier this week, which it seems to be winning so far as it trades $20 above that line.</p>
<p>Binance Coin, Cardano, Ripple, Dogecoin, Shiba Inu, Polygon, Polkadot, and Tron are essentially at the same price spots they were yesterday, with swings of less than 1%.</p>
<p>OKX&#8217;s native cryptocurrency is the best performer from the larger-cap alts, just a few days after the exchange <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/okx-proof-of-reserves-report-bitcoin-ether-tether-reserve-ratios-over-100/" data-wpel-link="internal">published its latest proof-of-reserve report,</a> showing a 101% reserve ratio. OKB is up by over 5% on a daily scale and trades at $23.</p>
<p>With the lack of any big moves, the crypto market cap remains stuck at $810 billion.</p>
<figure id="attachment_230244" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-230244" style="width: 1852px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-6.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-230244" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-6.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1852" height="655" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-6.jpg 1852w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-6-300x106.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-6-1024x362.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-6-768x272.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-6-1536x543.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-6-50x18.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1852px) 100vw, 1852px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-230244" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/christmas-watch-will-2023-finally-end-bitcoin-prices-stagnancy-amid-17k/" rel="nofollow">Christmas Watch: Will 2023 Finally End Bitcoin Price&#8217;s Stagnancy Amid $17K?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>dApp Industry Thrives Despite Crypto Winter: DappRadar</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/dapp-industry-thrives-despite-crypto-winter-dappradar/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 00:33:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bear Market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230024</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/blockchain_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/blockchain_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The crypto winter has not harmed at least one industry niche. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">The cryptocurrency market is facing one of its most brutal crypto winters, marked by a sustained drop in digital asset prices and the failure of major crypto companies, as well as high-profile cases of hacks and heists.</p>
<p class="p2">Nonetheless, a recent report from blockchain data and analytics firm DappRadar suggests that the industry may not be in such a gloomy state, as it has shown remarkable resilience and maturity amid the crypto winter.</p>
<p class="p2">According to DappRadar&#8217;s <a href="https://dappradar.com/blog/dapp-industry-report-2022-dapp-industry-proves-resilient-in-crypto-winter" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">2022 Industry Report</a>, decentralized applications (dApps) usage has skyrocketed despite the bearish market conditions.</p>
<p class="p2">The dApp industry saw a 50% year-on-year increase in its daily unique active wallets (dUAW), rising from 1.58 million in 2021 to 2.37 million in 2022. This growth can be attributed to increased acceptance among consumers and businesses, as well as increased investor interest.</p>
<h2 class="p3">Blockchain Gaming and NFTs Lead Dapp Market Growth</h2>
<p class="p2">Blockchain gaming projects, specifically the GameFi sector, played a significant role in the dApp industry this year. GameFi accounted for 49% of all dApp activity, with an average of 1.15 million daily dUAW and 7.4 billion transactions.</p>
<p class="p2">The <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-nft/" data-wpel-link="internal">non-fungible token</a> (NFT) market also contributed to the dApp industry&#8217;s growth, with a 33% increase in daily dUAW and an 876% jump in unique NFT traders.</p>
<p class="p2">However, while the number of unique NFT traders rose significantly, the trading volume only increased by 0.41% compared to the previous year. NFT sales also boomed, rising 10.6% to $68.35 million, although another report <strong>suggested</strong> that nearly 60% of NFT trading volume this year was fake.</p>
<h2 class="p3">DeFi Shows Resilience Despite 73% Drop in TVL</h2>
<p class="p2">The decentralized finance (DeFi) sector faced challenges in 2022, losing more than 73% of its total value locked. Despite this, the market saw a 2% increase in daily dUAW, reaching 652,970.</p>
<p class="p2">This may not seem significant, but DappRadar notes that it is an impressive achievement for the DeFi sector after the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/do-kwon-sorry-for-cocky-tweets-takes-full-responsibility-for-terras-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">collapse of Terra Luna</a>, which was the second-largest DeFi ecosystem at the time.</p>
<p class="p2">The report concludes by acknowledging that the bear market has created an opportunity for the industry to learn from mistakes and focus on building sustainable projects while preparing for the next bull season. It also highlights the industry&#8217;s resilience and maturity as it continues to grow despite challenging market conditions.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dapp-industry-thrives-despite-crypto-winter-dappradar/" rel="nofollow">dApp Industry Thrives Despite Crypto Winter: DappRadar</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Impact of FTX&#8217;s Contagion to Continue into 2023: CryptoCompare</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/impact-of-ftxs-contagion-to-continue-into-2023-cryptocompare/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 21:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bear Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229792</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/FTX_Frozen.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/FTX_Frozen.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[CryptoCompare predicts that the impact of FTX's crash will continue into 2023, providing an opportunity for reflection ahead of the next bull run.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">This year has been tumultuous for the cryptocurrency industry, with major players like Terra, Three Arrows Capital (3AC), and FTX going underwater.</p>
<p class="p2">As the crypto space struggles to find footing amid the second wave of the crypto winter exacerbated by the latest FTX debacle, digital asset data provider CryptoCompare believes it will take a while for the industry to recover from the impact of the collapse.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>Crypto Projects to Focus on Survival</b></h2>
<p class="p2">In its 2022 Year in Review <a href="https://blog.cryptocompare.com/cryptocompare-year-in-review-2022-df6e3bb2cb5f" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a>, CryptoCompare noted that it would take some time for the market to fully recover from the impact of <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX&#8217;s collapse</a>, as the exchange&#8217;s ties to numerous crypto firms will continue to influence the industry&#8217;s recovery into the new year.</p>
<p class="p2">Nonetheless, the FTX debacle has also highlighted the need for developers to create sustainable projects.</p>
<p class="p2">As such, CryptoCompare predicts that in 2023, there will be a greater focus on &#8220;protocols and projects focusing on survival through cash preservation and on building applications with a market-product fit, rather than on marketing and copy-cat initiatives.&#8221;</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>Increased Regulatory Clarity Expected in 2023</b></h2>
<p class="p2">The crypto data provider also suggested that the FTX bankruptcy may encourage more global financial regulators to establish frameworks for regulating the crypto market.</p>
<p class="p2">Some regulators are already implementing stringent measures to protect investors. For instance, the Thai Securities and Exchange Commission recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/stringent-crypto-regulation-incoming-after-ftx-collapse-warns-thai-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> plans to incorporate stricter regulations on crypto assets.</p>
<p class="p2">CryptoCompare believes these regulations will be more effective if they distinguish between centralized and decentralized entities within the crypto space, as many failed companies were centralized. This distinction would also foster continued innovation in the decentralized finance sector.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>A Time for Reflection</b></h2>
<p class="p2">In conclusion, CryptoCompare believes the crypto winter offers a chance for market participants to reflect and focus on developing the industry while preparing for the next bull run.</p>
<blockquote>
<p class="p2">&#8220;In 2022, we saw the end of the bull market and the start of a bear cycle, which provides market participants with an opportunity to take a step back, reflect on the developments of the industry, and plan for the future,&#8221; the report said.</p>
</blockquote>
<p class="p2">While disheartening, bear markets are one of the proven ways to filter the broader market as they show that investors are in the market for the long term, not for speculation and short-term gain.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/impact-of-ftxs-contagion-to-continue-into-2023-cryptocompare/" rel="nofollow">Impact of FTX&#8217;s Contagion to Continue into 2023: CryptoCompare</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
