<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>Latest Crypto News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://kryptomoney.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<description>Latest Crypto News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 23:06:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.6</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/cropped-cropped-favicon_512x512_v2-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Latest Crypto News</title>
	<link>https://kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><itunes:subtitle>Latest Crypto News</itunes:subtitle><itunes:category text="News &amp; Politics"/><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Business News"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Investing"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Tech News"/></itunes:category><item>
		<title>CBDC Imposition Takes Center Stage at G7 Committee Meeting</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/cbdc-imposition-takes-center-stage-at-g7-committee-meeting/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 23:06:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65113</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The G7 committee recently gathered in Niigata, Japan, to discuss the potential of central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) in shaping a global financial system. The meeting brought together leading economies ahead of the annual G7 summit, with a focus on finding ways to enhance payment efficiency while safeguarding the stability and integrity of the monetary [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/cbdc-imposition-takes-center-stage-at-g7-committee-meeting/">CBDC Imposition Takes Center Stage at G7 Committee Meeting</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/cbdc-imposition-takes-center-stage-at-g7-committee-meeting/">CBDC Imposition Takes Center Stage at G7 Committee Meeting</a> was first posted on May 16, 2023 at 7:06 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/g7-considers-facebook-libra-as-risks-to-financial-stability-demand/">G7 committee</a> recently gathered in Niigata, Japan, to discuss the potential of central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) in shaping a global financial system. The meeting brought together leading economies ahead of the annual G7 summit, with a focus on finding ways to enhance payment efficiency while safeguarding the stability and integrity of the monetary systems.<br /><br />Transparency, reliability, and stability for global payments were key priorities for the committee, which sees <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/visa-chief-predicts-meaningful-role-for-stablecoins-and-cbdcs/">CBDCs</a> as a promising avenue to achieve these goals. While CBDCs differ from decentralized cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin, the committee emphasizes the importance of upholding fundamental principles such as compliance with legal requirements, economic governance practices, cybersecurity, and data protection.<br /><br />As the traditional banking system faces challenges and the fiat monetary system teeters on the edge, central banks have resorted to propping it up at the expense of citizens&#8217; purchasing power. The committee recognizes that imposing a CBDC can extend the life of the fiat system, but concerns arise regarding potential control over individuals&#8217; spending and financial freedom.<br /><br />Critics argue that the introduction of a CBDC could grant central banks unprecedented power to monitor and restrict transactions, limiting options like investing in cryptocurrencies. Preserving privacy and financial freedom becomes a significant concern, considering governments&#8217; past actions to freeze accounts and blacklist Bitcoin wallets. With CBDCs, the potential for enhanced financial surveillance raises questions about the balance between innovation and individual autonomy.<br /><br />While history reveals a pattern of increasing control during the decline of world empires, the hope remains that determined independent thinkers will continue to strive for freedom in the face of these challenges.</p>
<p>Image Credit – Pixabay.com</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/cbdc-imposition-takes-center-stage-at-g7-committee-meeting/">CBDC Imposition Takes Center Stage at G7 Committee Meeting</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/cbdc-imposition-takes-center-stage-at-g7-committee-meeting/">CBDC Imposition Takes Center Stage at G7 Committee Meeting</a> was first posted on May 16, 2023 at 7:06 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ledger Faces Backlash for Potential User Seed Phrase Breach</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/ledger-faces-backlash-for-potential-user-seed-phrase-breach/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 22:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ledger]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65109</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto hardware wallet provider Ledger is facing severe backlash from its online user base following the release of a controversial update that has raised concerns about significant security flaws. Despite Ledger&#8217;s claims that the new functionality is safe and optional, security experts and cryptocurrency holders are expressing their dissatisfaction and distancing themselves from the company. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/ledger-faces-backlash-for-potential-user-seed-phrase-breach/">Ledger Faces Backlash for Potential User Seed Phrase Breach</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ledger-faces-backlash-for-potential-user-seed-phrase-breach/">Ledger Faces Backlash for Potential User Seed Phrase Breach</a> was first posted on May 16, 2023 at 6:01 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Crypto hardware wallet provider <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/xrp-ledger-now-has-native-support-for-nfts/">Ledger</a> is facing severe backlash from its online user base following the release of a controversial update that has raised concerns about significant security flaws. Despite Ledger&#8217;s claims that the new functionality is safe and optional, security experts and cryptocurrency holders are expressing their dissatisfaction and distancing themselves from the company.<br /><br />The discontent began to escalate when a Reddit user named Joe_Smith_Reddit <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ledgerwallet/comments/13itm7u/comment/jkbyyfp/">posted</a> a question demanding a clear answer on whether Ledger has a built-in backdoor for accessing users&#8217; private keys.<br /><br />Private keys are crucial alphanumeric strings that allow users to access their cryptocurrencies on the blockchain. The specific inquiry revolved around Ledger&#8217;s recently introduced &#8220;Ledger Recover&#8221; service, designed for Nano X device owners to <a href="https://www.ledger.com/recover">recover</a> their crypto assets even if they lose both their wallet device and recovery phrase. The recovery phrase represents a user&#8217;s private key in mnemonic form.<br /><br />According to Ledger, the service enabled through firmware update 2.2.1, duplicates the recovery phrase on the device, encrypts the copy, fragments it into three parts, and secures it with Ledger, Coincover, and another unnamed provider. To utilize the service, users must verify their identity using an ID document and a selfie recording.<br /><br />Attempting to address the growing concerns, Ledger took to Twitter to emphasize that the service is completely optional and not automatically enabled through any firmware update. They added that users&#8217; secret recovery phrases are securely generated on their own devices, with no access granted to Ledger.<br /><br />Despite these assurances from Ledger, the community&#8217;s worries persist around one central issue: the update appears to expose that Ledger devices do not provide absolute protection of users&#8217; private keys against external access, contrary to the company&#8217;s claims. Reddit user StPinkie expressed disappointment, stating that trust in the proprietary secure element, which was a cornerstone of the company, has been shattered. <br /><br />They announced that they can no longer recommend Ledger to anyone concerned about maintaining their digital sovereignty.<br /><br />Notable crypto developer, writer, and auditor &#8220;foobar&#8221; echoed this sentiment on <a href="https://twitter.com/Ledger/status/1658458714771169282">Twitter</a>, urging followers to immediately transition away from Ledger wallets. They <a href="https://twitter.com/0xfoobar/status/1658478186408337408">highlighted</a> the update&#8217;s glaring problem of potentially exposing private keys to risk through malicious or accidental firmware updates.<br /><br />Users also pointed out a contradiction between Ledger&#8217;s website claims that users&#8217; keys &#8220;never leave the device&#8221; and the Ledger Recover service, which distributes users&#8217; private keys to three different providers in shards, as explained by CEO Pascal Gauthier.<br /><br />Within the community, many suggested that Ledger introduce a separate wallet dedicated to offering a seed-recovery service rather than rolling it out as a firmware update for existing customers who expected the highest level of security from their devices.<br /><br />It is worth noting tha<a href="https://www.ledger.com/message-ledgers-ceo-data-leak">t Ledger</a> has experienced previous security compromises, including when the personal information of over 270,000 customers was accidentally leaked in July 2020. However, this incident did not impact the security of users&#8217; private keys.<br /><br />Ledger saw a surge in sales following the collapse of FTX in November, as investors sought to secure their cryptocurrencies independently, avoiding reliance on centralized intermediaries.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/ledger-faces-backlash-for-potential-user-seed-phrase-breach/">Ledger Faces Backlash for Potential User Seed Phrase Breach</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ledger-faces-backlash-for-potential-user-seed-phrase-breach/">Ledger Faces Backlash for Potential User Seed Phrase Breach</a> was first posted on May 16, 2023 at 6:01 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MicroStrategy Rolls Out Wallet and Lightning Address for Account Holders</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/microstrategy-rolls-out-wallet-and-lightning-address-for-account-holders/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 23:11:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Wallet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroStrategy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65105</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a strong commitment to Bitcoin adoption, business intelligence firm MicroStrategy is intensifying its efforts to incorporate layer 2 scaling solutions, particularly the Lightning Network, this year. Executive chairman Michael Saylor recently provided an update, revealing that the company is developing a product to offer a Bitcoin wallet and Lightning address to every corporate account [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/microstrategy-rolls-out-wallet-and-lightning-address-for-account-holders/">MicroStrategy Rolls Out Wallet and Lightning Address for Account Holders</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/microstrategy-rolls-out-wallet-and-lightning-address-for-account-holders/">MicroStrategy Rolls Out Wallet and Lightning Address for Account Holders</a> was first posted on May 15, 2023 at 7:11 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In a strong commitment to Bitcoin adoption, business intelligence firm <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/microstrategy-turns-profitable-in-q1-after-betting-big-on-bitcoin/">MicroStrategy</a> is intensifying its efforts to incorporate layer 2 scaling solutions, particularly the Lightning Network, this year. Executive chairman Michael Saylor recently provided an <a href="https://twitter.com/saylor/status/1657807531664605185">update</a>, revealing that the company is developing a product to offer a Bitcoin wallet and Lightning address to every corporate account holder.<br /><br />The primary objective behind this initiative is to facilitate the swift and seamless development and deployment of Bitcoin rewards applications for employees, customers, prospects, and partners. The Lightning Network serves as a layer-2 payment protocol built on top of the Bitcoin blockchain, enabling off-chain transactions, increasing payment throughput, and reducing transaction fees.<br /><br /><a href="https://valkyrieinvest.com/daily-market-brief/the-valkyrie-market-brief-02-06-23/">Reports</a> indicate that the adoption of the Lightning Network is gaining momentum, particularly in emerging markets like South America and Africa. This can be attributed, in part, to the efforts of the Bitcoin payment company and wallet provider Strike.<br /><br />Back in December, Saylor shared MicroStrategy&#8217;s exploration of software and solutions that leverage the Lightning Network. These included solutions supporting enterprise marketing and a cybersecurity solution tailored for corporate websites. In April, the 58-year-old billionaire also announced the integration of Bitcoin&#8217;s Lightning Network into his corporate email address. This allows anyone to send BTC to Saylor using his company email address as an identifier.<br /><br />Aside from its focus on the Lightning Network, MicroStrategy has consistently expanded its Bitcoin holdings, making it the largest corporate holder of the flagship cryptocurrency. According to data compiled by Bitcoin Treasuries, MicroStrategy currently owns 140,000 BTC, accumulating more portions of the asset throughout all 11 previous quarters.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/microstrategy-rolls-out-wallet-and-lightning-address-for-account-holders/">MicroStrategy Rolls Out Wallet and Lightning Address for Account Holders</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/microstrategy-rolls-out-wallet-and-lightning-address-for-account-holders/">MicroStrategy Rolls Out Wallet and Lightning Address for Account Holders</a> was first posted on May 15, 2023 at 7:11 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>South Korean Authorities Launch Raids on UpBit and Bithumb</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/south-korean-authorities-launch-raids-on-upbit-and-bithumb/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 22:54:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bithumb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Upbit]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65097</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Reports have emerged stating that South Korean prosecutors have conducted raids on the offices of the country&#8217;s two leading cryptocurrency exchanges, Upbit and Bithumb. The raids are part of an ongoing investigation involving Kim Nam-kuk, a politician who faced public scrutiny over allegations of acquiring 800,000 Wemix tokens without adhering to the necessary regulations. The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/south-korean-authorities-launch-raids-on-upbit-and-bithumb/">South Korean Authorities Launch Raids on UpBit and Bithumb</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/south-korean-authorities-launch-raids-on-upbit-and-bithumb/">South Korean Authorities Launch Raids on UpBit and Bithumb</a> was first posted on May 15, 2023 at 6:54 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Reports have emerged stating that South Korean prosecutors have <a href="https://koreajoongangdaily.joins.com/2023/05/15/national/politics/korea-upbit-bithumb/20230515201129323.html">conducted raids</a> on the offices of the country&#8217;s two leading cryptocurrency exchanges, <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/upbit-crypto-exchange-announces-49-million-worth-of-ether-was-stolen/">Upbit</a> and Bithumb. The raids are part of an ongoing investigation involving Kim Nam-kuk, a politician who faced public scrutiny over allegations of acquiring 800,000 Wemix tokens without adhering to the necessary regulations. The authorities suspect that the platforms may have somehow been involved in the transfer of the coins from Bithumb to Upbit last year.<br /><br />To unravel the case involving Kim Nam-kuk, local media outlets reported that Korean authorities searched the headquarters of Upbit and Bithumb in Seoul. Recently, the Democratic Party (DP) urged Nam-kuk to sell his 800,000 Wemix coins amid accusations of potentially using insider information to accumulate them a few years ago. It is alleged that Nam-kuk withdrew the assets at the beginning of 2022, several months before the enforcement of legislation requiring cryptocurrency entities to report personal information for transfers exceeding $758. Notably, Nam-kuk was part of the team that proposed a delay in the income taxation on digital assets in South Korea. He has now stated his intention to sell the holdings, which are currently valued at approximately $660,000, in compliance with the DP&#8217;s recommendation.<br /><br /><a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1658069446802702336">Wu Blockchain</a> argued that Nam-kuk&#8217;s transfer of 800,000 Wemix coins from Bithumb to Upbit in 2022 may have sparked the investigation against the exchanges. Upbit deemed the transaction &#8220;improper&#8221; and reported it to the government at that time. In January, Korean prosecutors raided Bithumb&#8217;s offices following rumors of price manipulation of an undisclosed coin listed on the platform. The authorities clarified that the raid aimed to secure transaction details for a specific coin and had no direct connection to Bithumb itself.<br /><br />The recent inspection comes shortly after prosecutors sought an arrest warrant for Kang Jong-Hyun, the owner of<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/south-korean-financial-regulator-intends-to-close-11-crypto-exchange-companies/"> Bithumb</a>, on charges of embezzlement and market manipulation. Jong-Hyun&#8217;s sister also encountered legal issues, as the Seoul Southern District Prosecutor&#8217;s Office claimed she artificially inflated the share price of certain firms through the issuance of convertible bonds.<br /><br />Despite being one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges in South Korea, Bithumb has faced various controversies over the years. In December 2022, Park Mo, the largest shareholder of Bithumb Holdings Co., was found dead in front of his house in southern Seoul. Although initial investigations suggested suicide and found no signs of violence, the crypto community raised doubts. Mo was closely associated with Jong-Hyun and his sister and had supposedly discussed the potential purchase of his organization by the now-bankrupt FTX.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/south-korean-authorities-launch-raids-on-upbit-and-bithumb/">South Korean Authorities Launch Raids on UpBit and Bithumb</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/south-korean-authorities-launch-raids-on-upbit-and-bithumb/">South Korean Authorities Launch Raids on UpBit and Bithumb</a> was first posted on May 15, 2023 at 6:54 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>10 Ways to Earn Passive Income From Crypto in 2023</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/10-ways-to-earn-passive-income-from-crypto-in-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 06:53:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sponsored]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65100</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Do you want to boost your passive income from Bitcoin and crypto? Would you like to know the quickest way to activate the bitcoin income you are now receiving? There are more opportunities for passive income as a result of the surge in popularity of cryptocurrencies. The goal of producing residual income with bitcoin is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/10-ways-to-earn-passive-income-from-crypto-in-2023/">10 Ways to Earn Passive Income From Crypto in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/10-ways-to-earn-passive-income-from-crypto-in-2023/">10 Ways to Earn Passive Income From Crypto in 2023</a> was first posted on May 15, 2023 at 2:53 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you want to boost your passive income from Bitcoin and crypto? Would you like to know the quickest way to activate the bitcoin income you are now receiving? There are more opportunities for passive income as a result of the surge in popularity of cryptocurrencies. The goal of producing residual income with bitcoin is to make money continually without active engagement.</p>
<p>Instead of taking excessive trading risks, making the time-consuming effort, or letting your Bitcoin lie idle, you may now put it to work for as long as you like. Set up the situation gradually. Once set up, they will continue to generate income for you with no effort on your part. To get you started, here are a few suggestions for developing passive cryptocurrency income options. Many automatically recurring revenue streams can be produced by combining a few different approaches.</p>
<p><strong>1. Cloud Mining</strong><br />
<strong>2. Affiliate program: Get paid heavily for referring friends</strong><br />
<strong>3. Market NFTs</strong><br />
<strong>4. Yield Farming</strong><br />
<strong>5. Crypto Games</strong><br />
<strong>6. Forks and Airdrops</strong><br />
<strong>7. Airdrops</strong><br />
<strong>8. Sun Exchange</strong><br />
<strong>9. Create an account on YouTube</strong><br />
<strong>10. Learn to Earn</strong></p>
<h3>1. Cloud Mining</h3>
<p>With the emergence of cloud mining, it is now possible to mine cryptocurrencies using cloud computer resources that are rented rather than owned or directly operated. Creating an account, paying a modest fee, and mining bitcoins remotely are all activities that people can engage in. Due to cloud mining businesses, crypto mining is now more accessible and profitable for a wider range of users.</p>
<p>HappyMiner, a genuine cloud mining company, was founded in the US in 2018. Thanks to crypto mining software services like HappyMiner, anyone can mine Bitcoin from of the comfort of their own home. Clients can mine a variety of coins for a fair price using HappyMiner&#8217;s advanced mining technology. The mining sector thus offers them the biggest investment return.</p>
<h4>Advantage:</h4>
<ul>
<li>Join today and receive $10 right away.</li>
<li>There are about 2,800K users on the website, coming from 120 different nations.</li>
<li>You can generate more than 6 additional cryptocurrencies using the platform.</li>
<li>There are no service or deposit fees.</li>
<li>A wide range of investment choices, including hash rate contracts for different cryptocurrencies like the Litecoin stablecoin and Bitcoin and daily free packages for new cloud miners.</li>
<li>The company&#8217;s affiliate program allows you to introduce friends and receive up to a 4.5% referral reward.</li>
<li>The system is protected and secured using SSL and DDoS defense.</li>
<li>A range of high-return programs are offered, with daily interest rates ranging from 1.5 to 8%.</li>
</ul>
<p>Price: $10 for free trials, with additional fees for continued use With this platform, customers can register for personal accounts and right away start daily passive income generation.</p>
<p>For more details, Website: <a href="https://happyminer.us/?kryptomoney">https://happyminer.us/</a></p>
<h3>2. Affiliate program: Get paid heavily for referring friends</h3>
<p>You can earn money from a variety of cryptocurrency affiliate programs by referring people to their websites. It&#8217;s free to sign up for an affiliate program. After making an account, you will be given a special URL. You can start sharing the URL on websites, blogs, forums, and social media, among other places. Every time someone signs up or makes a purchase through your connection, you will get compensated. The potential to get going quickly and profit is the main advantage. Furthermore, money would keep coming in for days, weeks, months, and even years after you put in all that effort. Whether you run a blog, have a website, or have a significant following on social media, the affiliate program can be a great way to generate some respectable passive money.</p>
<p>We give you the option to make money by telling other people about our website. Even if you don&#8217;t make an investment, you can start making money. On each order, you can receive as much as 4.5% of what they spend. You can earn a significant referral bonus by copying and sharing your link with your friends.</p>
<p>For more details, Website: <a href="https://happyminer.us/affiliate?kryptomoney">https://happyminer.us/affiliate</a></p>
<h3>3. Market NFTs</h3>
<p>Non-fungible tokens, or NFTs, are unique assets stored on a digital ledger. NFTs have the excellent feature that the investment you store may be priceless. You may create NFTs for anything, including video, digital designs, photography, music, games, and GIFs.</p>
<p>Making an <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/wazirx-closes-nft-marketplace-due-to-low-engagements/">NFT</a> is easy. Websites like OpenSea let you to create an account and follow the step-by-step minting process (which involves additional gas fees).</p>
<p>Despite being a new business, NFT revenues have already shot above the $10 billion mark. You can still access the location. Just be aware that producing NFTs that will sell requires an upfront investment in time and minting costs.</p>
<h3>4. Yield Farming</h3>
<p>One of the more complicated possibilities here is yield farming, which will necessitate extensive more study for those who are interested. Yet it can also be one of the most profitable ways to use cryptocurrency for passive income.</p>
<p>Investors fund yield farms by putting their tokens into a liquidity pool, a unique kind of smart contract. A part of the fees made by traders using the pool goes to those who supply liquidity in this fashion.</p>
<h3>5. Crypto Games</h3>
<p>While playing bitcoin games online is becoming increasingly popular, passive income opportunities should grow. There are several crypto games available, and many of them offer rewards for using different kinds of crypto.</p>
<p>Axie Infinity, The Sandbox, Gods Unchained, Ethermon, and Pegaxy are just a few of the varied games.</p>
<h3>6. Forks and Airdrops</h3>
<p>An existing coin forks when it diverges into a new chain. New coins are manufactured and &#8220;dropped&#8221; onto users as a form of reward in an airdrop.</p>
<p>Users have no control over whether or when these occurrences might happen. But, your chances improve if you participate in the crypto economy.</p>
<h3>7. Airdrops</h3>
<p>Before an Initial Coin Offering, crypto projects would use airdrops as a marketing strategy to increase their circulation and popularity (ICO). This entails giving away free copies of the project&#8217;s native token to potential users. As a result, the pass receives more notice and circulates more widely before going on sale.</p>
<p>Airdrops come in a variety of forms. Some provide you tokens only for connecting your wallet, while others make you perform easy requirements like like the project&#8217;s social media page. Even though airdrops are unpredictable or rarely offer big profits, they can be a fun way to diversify your cryptocurrency holdings.</p>
<h3>9. Create an account on YouTube</h3>
<p>A YouTube channel can still be started. A startling 74% of people in the US use YouTube. A huge audience like that may be attracted for passive income. The issue? It requires a lot of work at first with little to no payoff.</p>
<p>Yet, if you have a long-term outlook and are content with front-loading your effort, a popular YouTube channel has huge potential for passive income. Ads, affiliate sales, sponsorships, branded integrations, and other passive income streams can all add up as you increase your audience, content, clicks, and views.</p>
<h3>10. Learn to Earn</h3>
<p>Some platforms reward users with cryptocurrency for using the learning center. It compensates users for their knowledge of the platform by encouraging them to watch videos and complete quizzes. Users receive these coins at the end of the course, and the content is often centered around a specific altcoin. Users can exchange these tokens for other tokens on the site, sell them for cash, or use the proceeds to buy tokens for another potential project, as some of them may not be suitable for long-term investment.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: This is a paid post. KryptoMoney does not endorse and is not responsible for or liable for any content, accuracy, quality, advertising, products, or other materials on this page. Readers should do their own research before taking any actions related to the company. KryptoMoney is not responsible, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with the use of or reliance on any content, goods, or services mentioned in the article.</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/10-ways-to-earn-passive-income-from-crypto-in-2023/">10 Ways to Earn Passive Income From Crypto in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/10-ways-to-earn-passive-income-from-crypto-in-2023/">10 Ways to Earn Passive Income From Crypto in 2023</a> was first posted on May 15, 2023 at 2:53 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tron’s Revenue Exceeded $90M in Q1, 2023</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/trons-revenue-exceeded-90m-in-q1-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 21:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON (TRX)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65090</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>According to a recent report from market intelligence firm Messari, the Tron blockchain experienced a notable surge in usage during the first quarter of 2023. Despite facing lawsuits from the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) against Tron ecosystem tokens, the network remained resilient, displaying robust activity. The market cap of Tron&#8217;s native token, TRX, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/trons-revenue-exceeded-90m-in-q1-2023/">Tron’s Revenue Exceeded $90M in Q1, 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/trons-revenue-exceeded-90m-in-q1-2023/">Tron’s Revenue Exceeded $90M in Q1, 2023</a> was first posted on May 14, 2023 at 5:02 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>According to a recent report from market intelligence firm Messari, the<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/tron-deals-with-major-blockchain-and-gaming-groups-in-south-korea/"> Tron blockchain</a> experienced a notable surge in usage during the first quarter of 2023. Despite facing lawsuits from the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) against Tron ecosystem tokens, the network remained resilient, displaying robust activity. The market cap of Tron&#8217;s native token, TRX, also saw a substantial increase of nearly 20% quarter-over-quarter (QoQ).<br /><br />In terms of revenue, Tron witnessed impressive growth, with total quarterly revenue reaching $90.04 million in Q1 2023. This marked an impressive 88% jump from Q4 2022 revenue of $47.96 million.<br /><br />The report highlighted a 7.7% increase in average daily transactions during the three-month review period, reaching approximately 7 million transactions. Messari attributed this growth partly to staking activity on the network. Although staking accounted for only about 3% of all transactions on the TRX network, the total transaction count originating from staking activities soared by 197% QoQ.<br /><br />The &#8220;State of Tron&#8221; <a href="https://messari.io/report/state-of-tron-q1-2023?">report,</a> commissioned by Tron itself, revealed that smart contracts triggered and TRX transfers dominated the transaction activity on the network, accounting for 88% of all transactions. <br /><br />Despite remaining relatively stable throughout Q1, these transaction types showcased the USDT smart contract as the primary driver of contract execution on TRON.<br /><br />Furthermore, transaction fees experienced a substantial surge during the first quarter. Statistics indicated a 59.2% increase in the average transaction fee denominated in TRX and an 80.2% increase when measured in USD. <br /><br />Committee proposal No. 79, approved in the previous quarter, played a crucial role in driving the hike in transaction fees. This proposal introduced changes to network parameters, increasing the energy required to execute smart contracts.<br /><br />Overall, the Tron blockchain demonstrated impressive growth in usage and market cap during Q1 2023, defying the challenges posed by SEC lawsuits. The network&#8217;s resilience, combined with the surge in revenue, transaction volume, and transaction fees, indicates a thriving ecosystem with increasing adoption and activity.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/trons-revenue-exceeded-90m-in-q1-2023/">Tron’s Revenue Exceeded $90M in Q1, 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/trons-revenue-exceeded-90m-in-q1-2023/">Tron’s Revenue Exceeded $90M in Q1, 2023</a> was first posted on May 14, 2023 at 5:02 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gbitcoins: Simplifying Passive Income with Cloud Mining – Easy, Safe, and Profitable</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/gbitcoins-simplifying-passive-income-with-cloud-mining/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 07:43:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sponsored]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cloud mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gbitcoins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65093</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With everything that is going around, having a stable source of passive income comes with many advantages. If you are wondering which is the best method to do so in the sense of being secured, the answer is cloud mining. And when it comes to finding the world&#8217;s best cloud mining services to help you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/gbitcoins-simplifying-passive-income-with-cloud-mining/">Gbitcoins: Simplifying Passive Income with Cloud Mining &#8211; Easy, Safe, and Profitable</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/gbitcoins-simplifying-passive-income-with-cloud-mining/">Gbitcoins: Simplifying Passive Income with Cloud Mining &#8211; Easy, Safe, and Profitable</a> was first posted on May 13, 2023 at 3:43 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With everything that is going around, having a stable source of passive income comes with many advantages. If you are wondering which is the best method to do so in the sense of being secured, the answer is cloud mining. And when it comes to finding the world&#8217;s best cloud mining services to help you out, look no further than the trusted and effective Gbitcoins!</p>
<p>Want to learn how to use <a href="https://gbitcoins.net/?kryptomoney">Gbitcoins</a> for effective cloud mining to acquire a desired passive income? Great!<br />
You are in the right place as everything you need to know about this is mentioned below in detail for your better understanding. So, do keep on reading!</p>
<h3>Why do so many new investors choose Gbitcoins?</h3>
<p>Currently, Gbitcoins (operating from America) is popular among investors from all over because the company is known for being an excellent cloud mining service provider. From renting extra resources to successfully broadening your hashing power, everything you need to optimize the entire process can be done easily with the help of Gbitcoins.</p>
<p>Learn how to open a Gbitcoins account in 3 easy-to-follow steps</p>
<h4>Step 1:</h4>
<p>Go to the company&#8217;s official website to open an account or register and click on the &#8220;Sign Up&#8221; tab visible on your screen.</p>
<h4>Step 2:</h4>
<p>You will receive a verification code on the official email address you provided when signing up. Input this code within the allotted time and proceed by clicking on the &#8220;Submit&#8221; tab.</p>
<h4>Step 3:</h4>
<p>Your account will be activated instantly. As soon as it gets activated, $15 will be added to your account by the company so that you can effectively kickstart your passive income-earning process via cloud mining.</p>
<p>Is cloud mining right for investors?</p>
<p>Anyone interested in effectively earning passive income knows about the benefits of <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/jpmorgan-maintains-bearish-stance-on-cryptocurrencies/">cryptocurrency</a> cloud mining.</p>
<p>With cloud mining (standard cryptocurrency mining using the shared computing power of a datacenter remotely), you can mine all profitable cryptocurrencies, such as Ethereum, Dogecoin, Bitcoin, and other similar cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>If you are interested in Bitcoin cloud mining, the service provider Gbitcoins will be the right fit as their miners focus mainly on Bitcoin mining for free. The company is known for investing in only cutting-edge technologies to provide all the required cloud mining services that can drastically increase your profit margin.</p>
<p>Besides the instant $15 deposit discussed above, Gbitcoins is also known for its lucrative affiliate program that offers an incentive of up to 5.5%. Earning passive income via cloud mining becomes an easy and effective process with the company&#8217;s many beneficial services.</p>
<h3>Is Gbitcoins legit?</h3>
<p>Do not confuse Gbitcoins as a scam website as the difference between such a site and Gbitcoins are far too many to count.</p>
<p>Unlike scam websites, the official website of Gbitcoins is licensed by the respected American government. The company can also provide legit cloud mining certification to prove its legitimacy. On the other hand, fake or scam websites are not certified cloud mining companies like Gbitcoins.</p>
<p>A tell-tale sign of a scam website is the fact you can open an account with a fake email address. When you deal with a scam website, you end up losing your valuable personal information and money. No such worries are associated with this well-loved cloud mining service provider. Customers feel safe cloud mining with Gbitcoins as they are known for offering the following benefits that are always absent in all scam websites:</p>
<ul>
<li>Account for cloud mining can be opened only with a legit or registered email id</li>
<li>Guaranteed payouts within 24 hours</li>
<li>SSL protection for all customers&#8217; vulnerable personal and banking information</li>
</ul>
<p>Hopefully, these major differences between Gbitcoins and standard scam websites have helped you to understand that this cloud mining service provider is legit and can effectively help out. Both you and your earnings will be safeguarded well if only Gbitcoins for cloud mining and passive income earning is considered.</p>
<h3>Gbitcoins Packages for Cloud Mining</h3>
<p>The company offers many different packages and every one of them offers a different set of advantages, contract length, and Return on Investment (ROI). However, no matter which package you go for, the profit will remain fixed and you will receive daily payouts. Once your contract term comes to an end, you can either continue with the same package or withdraw your collected fund.</p>
<p>Some fruitful Gbitcoins packages and their offers are the following:</p>
<ul>
<li>Package/Contract costing $6000</li>
</ul>
<p>The Contract Term or validity period of this package is 30 days. With this package, you will get a Daily Rate (DR) of 3% with a $6,000+$5,400 Fixed Return (FR).</p>
<ul>
<li>Package/Contract costing $3000</li>
</ul>
<p>The Contract Term of this package from Gbitcoins is 21 days with a $3,000+$1,638 Fixed Return at a Daily Rate of 2.6%.</p>
<ul>
<li>Package/Contract costing $1,500</li>
</ul>
<p>With a 2.25% Daily Rate and a 14 day Contract Term, customers can enjoy a $1,500+$472.5 Fixed Return from this package.</p>
<ul>
<li>Package/Contract costing $500</li>
</ul>
<p>The Contract Term of this package is 7 days with a $500+$70 Fixed Return at a Daily Rate of 2%.</p>
<ul>
<li>Package/Contract costing $100</li>
</ul>
<p>This package comes with a 3 day Contract Term and a Fixed Return of $100+$5.45 at a 1.82% Daily Rate.</p>
<ul>
<li>Package/Contract costing $15</li>
</ul>
<p>This one is valid for a day only and offers a $15+$0.9 Fixed Return</p>
<p>The process to withdraw your passive income from Gbitcoins</p>
<p>You can withdraw the fund that you earned via cloud mining with Gbitcoins into your account quickly and with minimum effort as the process is quite straightforward.</p>
<p>Here is what you need to do to withdraw your fund from the company&#8217;s <a href="https://gbitcoins.net/?kryptomoney">official website</a> (for first-timers):</p>
<ul>
<li>Browse your account to find the &#8220;Withdraw&#8221; tab and click on it</li>
<li>After getting access, you have to pick a wallet of your choice to continue</li>
<li>Enter the amount you want to withdraw from your account in the designated field (the minimum withdrawal limit is $100)</li>
<li>Shortly, your registered or chosen wallet will receive the requested amount of withdrawal (this process may take a couple of minutes to complete)</li>
</ul>
<h3>To Conclude</h3>
<p>Earning passive income becomes an easy process when cloud mining is selected. If you are interested in an effective cloud mining service performance, consider the trusted and helpful service provider Gbitcoins. They make the process profitable, secure, and faster.</p>
<p>To learn more about cloud mining and earning passive income securely, click on this link for the required official assistance &#8211; https://gbitcoins.net/?kryptomoney</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/gbitcoins-simplifying-passive-income-with-cloud-mining/">Gbitcoins: Simplifying Passive Income with Cloud Mining &#8211; Easy, Safe, and Profitable</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/gbitcoins-simplifying-passive-income-with-cloud-mining/">Gbitcoins: Simplifying Passive Income with Cloud Mining &#8211; Easy, Safe, and Profitable</a> was first posted on May 13, 2023 at 3:43 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Bids Farewell to Canada, Temporarily Halts Operations</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/binance-bids-farewell-to-canada-temporarily-halts-operations/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 22:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Canada]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65086</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a tweet on May 12, Binance announced its decision to halt operations in Canada, following the footsteps of other proactive crypto companies that have withdrawn from the Canadian marketplace. While acknowledging Canada&#8217;s sentimental value and expressing optimism for the country&#8217;s crypto sector, Binance cited recent regulatory guidance as the reason for its departure, deeming [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-bids-farewell-to-canada-temporarily-halts-operations/">Binance Bids Farewell to Canada, Temporarily Halts Operations</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-bids-farewell-to-canada-temporarily-halts-operations/">Binance Bids Farewell to Canada, Temporarily Halts Operations</a> was first posted on May 12, 2023 at 6:59 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In a tweet on <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1657099651210969088">May 12</a>, Binance announced its decision to halt operations in Canada, following the footsteps of other proactive crypto companies that have withdrawn from the Canadian marketplace.</p>
<p>While acknowledging Canada&#8217;s sentimental value and expressing optimism for the country&#8217;s crypto sector,<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-accused-of-deliberately-flouting-laws-by-cftc-chief/"> Binance</a> cited recent regulatory guidance as the reason for its departure, deeming it unfeasible to continue operating under the new conditions.</p>
<p>Despite disagreeing with the new guidelines, Binance expressed its intention to maintain engagement with Canadian regulators and return to the market when users regain the freedom to access a broader range of digital assets.</p>
<p>The regulatory landscape changed in February when Canadian securities regulators introduced new guidelines, mandating pre-registration filings and imposing specific rules on crypto companies.</p>
<p>Notably, companies operating in Canada are now required to segregate funds belonging to Canadian users and withhold margin or leverage trading from them.</p>
<p>Binance joins the ranks of Paxos, dYdX, Blockchain.com, and OKX, all of which have withdrawn their services from the Canadian market.</p>
<p>On the other hand, Kraken, Coinbase, Crypto.com, and Gemini have expressed their intent to continue operating in Canada.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-bids-farewell-to-canada-temporarily-halts-operations/">Binance Bids Farewell to Canada, Temporarily Halts Operations</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-bids-farewell-to-canada-temporarily-halts-operations/">Binance Bids Farewell to Canada, Temporarily Halts Operations</a> was first posted on May 12, 2023 at 6:59 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nexo to Exit UK Market as Part of Reorganization Strategy</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/nexo-to-exit-uk-market-as-part-of-reorganization-strategy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 22:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nexo]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65082</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nexo, a prominent cryptocurrency lending platform, has decided to dissolve two of its business units based in the United Kingdom as it grapples with regulatory challenges in various parts of Europe and North America. This move is part of a broader restructuring effort, although Nexo will continue its operations within the country. According to filings [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/nexo-to-exit-uk-market-as-part-of-reorganization-strategy/">Nexo to Exit UK Market as Part of Reorganization Strategy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/nexo-to-exit-uk-market-as-part-of-reorganization-strategy/">Nexo to Exit UK Market as Part of Reorganization Strategy</a> was first posted on May 11, 2023 at 6:56 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/nexo-settles-with-sec-for-45-million/">Nexo</a>, a prominent cryptocurrency lending platform, has decided to dissolve two of its business units based in the United Kingdom as it grapples with regulatory challenges in various parts of Europe and North America. This move is part of a broader restructuring effort, although Nexo will continue its operations within the country.<br /><br />According to filings reported by<a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/crypto-lender-nexo-takes-steps-to-dissolve-uk-units-1.1918939"> BNN Bloomberg</a>, Nexo has applied to remove Nexo Financial Services Ltd. and Nexo Clearing and Custody Ltd. from the UK company register. In a message to Bloomberg, Antoni Trenchev, co-founder of Nexo, explained that the company is undergoing restructuring and reevaluating its approach to client services.<br /><br />Aside from crypto trading and custody, Nexo offers a range of crypto-based financial products, including debit card services, borrowing, and savings accounts. The savings accounts, as advertised on their website, can yield &#8220;up to 15% APR on your crypto,&#8221; with Bitcoin reaching as high as 7% and USDC up to 12%.<br /><br />Regulators in the United States have expressed skepticism towards crypto-based interest-bearing accounts, highlighting their unusually high savings rates compared to traditional accounts. Unlike chartered banks, crypto financial platforms are not covered by federal deposit insurance. Scrutiny heightened in mid-2022 after several crypto lending platforms, including Celsius, Voyager, and later BlockFi, encountered financial difficulties.<br /><br />Nexo clarified that it is not facing the same dire financial situation as those firms. However, it continues to face ongoing scrutiny and charges from the Securities and Exchange Commission in the coming months. In December, Nexo announced its departure from the United States due to regulatory obstacles.<br /><br />Furthermore, Nexo&#8217;s Earn product is currently inaccessible in Canada due to the complete ban on crypto margin trading imposed by regulators in the country. The company&#8217;s troubles also extend to Bulgaria, where its offices were raided in January on allegations of money laundering, tax fraud, and computer fraud related to unlicensed banking services.</p>
<p>Trenchev dismissed these accusations as &#8220;ludicrous&#8221; and responded by filing a $1 million lawsuit against Bulgaria.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/nexo-to-exit-uk-market-as-part-of-reorganization-strategy/">Nexo to Exit UK Market as Part of Reorganization Strategy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/nexo-to-exit-uk-market-as-part-of-reorganization-strategy/">Nexo to Exit UK Market as Part of Reorganization Strategy</a> was first posted on May 11, 2023 at 6:56 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlockFi Clears Regulatory Hurdle To Repay $297M to Specific Customers</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/blockfi-clears-regulatory-hurdle-to-repay-297m-to-specific-customers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 22:24:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlockFI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65078</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a significant development within its ongoing bankruptcy proceedings, BlockFi has been granted authorization to refund $297 million to select customers, as reported by Reuters on May 11. This decision pertains specifically to customers who held funds in BlockFi&#8217;s Wallet rather than its interest-bearing accounts. The ruling was delivered by Judge Michael Kaplan, who determined [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/blockfi-clears-regulatory-hurdle-to-repay-297m-to-specific-customers/">BlockFi Clears Regulatory Hurdle To Repay $297M to Specific Customers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/blockfi-clears-regulatory-hurdle-to-repay-297m-to-specific-customers/">BlockFi Clears Regulatory Hurdle To Repay $297M to Specific Customers</a> was first posted on May 11, 2023 at 6:24 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In a significant development within its ongoing bankruptcy proceedings, <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/blockfi-set-to-pay-back-over-100000-to-california-users/">BlockFi</a> has been granted authorization to refund $297 million to select customers, as reported by <a href="https://www.reuters.com/legal/blockfi-gets-court-permission-return-297-million-wallet-customers-2023-05-11/">Reuters</a> on May 11. This decision pertains specifically to customers who held funds in BlockFi&#8217;s Wallet rather than its interest-bearing accounts.<br /><br />The ruling was delivered by Judge Michael Kaplan, who determined that while wallet users maintained ownership of their deposits, customers who stored funds in interest-bearing accounts relinquished ownership and granted control to BlockFi. Subsequently, the company utilized those assets for its lending activities.<br /><br />However, customers who transferred their funds to the wallet accounts as a last-minute measure when BlockFi filed for<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-lender-blockfi-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy-protection/"> bankruptcy</a> in November last year will not be eligible for the refund. Approximately 48,000 users attempted to move a total of $375 million from interest accounts to wallet accounts during that period.<br /><br />Although customer lawyers contended that this amount should also be returned, Judge Kaplan dismissed the claim, citing BlockFi&#8217;s failure to finalize those transactions and its prerogative to block such transfers during the service halt.<br /><br />BlockFi&#8217;s legal representatives previously argued that returning the $375 million sum would dilute the value of funds recoverable by wallet users. They further asserted that such a payout could impede BlockFi from refunding any funds altogether due to a lack of fund segregation.<br /><br />The tumultuous series of events began when BlockFi temporarily suspended user withdrawals and activity on November 10, 2022, in response to the collapse of the crypto exchange FTX. Subsequently, the company filed for bankruptcy on November 28.<br /><br />Earlier in March, BlockFi had already initiated refunds of $100,000 to users in California.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/blockfi-clears-regulatory-hurdle-to-repay-297m-to-specific-customers/">BlockFi Clears Regulatory Hurdle To Repay $297M to Specific Customers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/blockfi-clears-regulatory-hurdle-to-repay-297m-to-specific-customers/">BlockFi Clears Regulatory Hurdle To Repay $297M to Specific Customers</a> was first posted on May 11, 2023 at 6:24 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>