<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>Latest Crypto News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://kryptomoney.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<description>Latest Crypto News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 16:00:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.7</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/cropped-cropped-favicon_512x512_v2-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Latest Crypto News</title>
	<link>https://kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><itunes:subtitle>Latest Crypto News</itunes:subtitle><itunes:category text="News &amp; Politics"/><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Business News"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Investing"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Tech News"/></itunes:category><item>
		<title>Hong Kong To Give Retail Traders Green Light for Crypto Trading</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/hong-kong-to-give-retail-traders-green-light-for-crypto-trading/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 16:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hong Kong]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65146</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hong Kong is poised to announce the outcome of its consultation, signaling a push to permit retail crypto investors to engage in cryptocurrency trading. According to Bloomberg, the Securities and Financial Commission (SFC) will unveil a new regulatory framework that prioritizes investor protection. Hong Kong, once a prominent crypto hub where many platforms originated, faced [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/hong-kong-to-give-retail-traders-green-light-for-crypto-trading/">Hong Kong To Give Retail Traders Green Light for Crypto Trading</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/hong-kong-to-give-retail-traders-green-light-for-crypto-trading/">Hong Kong To Give Retail Traders Green Light for Crypto Trading</a> was first posted on May 23, 2023 at 12:00 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/hong-kong-sets-sights-on-may-for-crypto-exchange-licensing-rules/">Hong Kong</a> is poised to announce the outcome of its consultation, signaling a push to permit retail crypto investors to engage in cryptocurrency trading. <br /><br />According to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-05-23/hong-kong-to-step-up-push-for-crypto-hub-in-contrast-with-clampdowns-in-asia">Bloomberg</a>, the Securities and Financial Commission (SFC) will unveil a new regulatory framework that prioritizes investor protection. <br /><br />Hong Kong, once a prominent crypto hub where many platforms originated, faced challenges with stringent rules that restricted crypto trading to institutional investors with a minimum capital of $1 million. To revive its former prominence, the SFC is now allowing retail investors to trade major tokens like Bitcoin (BTC).<br /><br />The final approval appears imminent, with discussions on this matter ongoing for some time. To ensure necessary safeguards, the SFC plans to introduce a licensing regime for virtual asset service providers (VASPs) beginning June 1. <br /><br />Crypto industry leaders have long touted the potential of digital currencies to revolutionize finance, yet regulatory constraints in various jurisdictions have hindered progress. <br /><br />The move by the Hong Kong SFC sets a positive precedent, potentially inspiring other regulators to follow suit and nurture the nascent ecosystem. <br /><br />The convergence of these favorable regulatory changes is expected to fuel industry growth and exert significant influence on the prices of supported digital assets, which already show promising growth projections.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/hong-kong-to-give-retail-traders-green-light-for-crypto-trading/">Hong Kong To Give Retail Traders Green Light for Crypto Trading</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/hong-kong-to-give-retail-traders-green-light-for-crypto-trading/">Hong Kong To Give Retail Traders Green Light for Crypto Trading</a> was first posted on May 23, 2023 at 12:00 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tether’s USDT Now Supported by Strike for Payments</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/tethers-usdt-now-supported-by-strike-for-payments/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65142</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Strike, a digital payments platform, has integrated Tether&#8217;s USDT stablecoin into its platform, aiming to enhance the speed, safety, and efficiency of payments for its users. The integration not only facilitates seamless transactions but also promotes the broader adoption of USDT. By incorporating USDT into its Bitcoin lightning network-based platform, Strike allows users to transfer [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/tethers-usdt-now-supported-by-strike-for-payments/">Tether’s USDT Now Supported by Strike for Payments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/tethers-usdt-now-supported-by-strike-for-payments/">Tether’s USDT Now Supported by Strike for Payments</a> was first posted on May 23, 2023 at 10:29 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Strike, a digital payments platform, has integrated <a href="https://tether.to/en/tether-usdt-to-be-integrated-onto-strike-leading-global-money-app/">Tether&#8217;s USDT stablecoin</a> into its platform, aiming to enhance the speed, safety, and efficiency of payments for its users. The integration not only facilitates seamless transactions but also promotes the broader adoption of USDT. <br /><br />By incorporating USDT into its <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-lightning-capacity-hits-all-time-high-at-4200-btc/">Bitcoin lightning network</a>-based platform, Strike allows users to transfer their cryptocurrencies globally without being concerned about market volatility.<br /><br />The addition of Tether&#8217;s stablecoin enables users to swiftly convert their digital assets into fiat currency, resolving previous liquidity challenges that hindered widespread adoption. <br /><br />Paolo Ardoino, Tether&#8217;s CTO, expressed that this collaboration reflects the increasing acceptance and recognition of stablecoins as reliable and efficient digital payment solutions. He further emphasized that this partnership would drive innovation, foster the adoption of digital currencies, and contribute to building a more inclusive financial ecosystem.<br /><br />Meanwhile, Strike believes that this integration will reshape the crypto industry landscape and create new avenues for seamless digital transactions.<br /><br />According to CEO Jack Mallers, the<a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/05/21/whos-laughing-now-bitcoin-price-braced-for-3-billion-user-shock-as-strike-ceo-slams-coinbase-ethereum-bnb-xrp-cardano-dogecoin-polygon-and-solana/?sh=795e5be7e501"> decision</a> to choose USDT over Circle-backed USDC was based on the trust factor, as people outside the U.S. have concerns regarding Circle. Mallers revealed that Strike has expanded its services to over 65 countries, and the company plans to relocate its headquarters to the Bitcoin-friendly nation of El Salvador. <br /><br />This expansion will introduce Strike to new markets in Africa, Latin America, Eastern Europe, Asia, and the Caribbean, including countries such as Zambia and Antigua and Barbuda.<br /><br />The company&#8217;s ambitious move is expected to reach nearly 3 billion people, thereby driving global crypto adoption and usage to new heights.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/tethers-usdt-now-supported-by-strike-for-payments/">Tether’s USDT Now Supported by Strike for Payments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/tethers-usdt-now-supported-by-strike-for-payments/">Tether’s USDT Now Supported by Strike for Payments</a> was first posted on May 23, 2023 at 10:29 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tether’s Gamble on Bitcoin Might Cause Market Instability, Rivalry With MicroStrategy</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/tethers-gamble-on-bitcoin-might-cause-market-instability-rivalry-with-microstrategy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 23:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroStrategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65138</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the wake of Tether&#8216;s groundbreaking announcement regarding their plans to purchase Bitcoin, the cryptocurrency industry was buzzing with excitement and speculation. As the company behind the world&#8217;s largest stablecoin, Tether&#8217;s decision to allocate a significant portion of its monthly net realized operating profits for Bitcoin purchases sent shockwaves through the market. Previously, Tether had [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/tethers-gamble-on-bitcoin-might-cause-market-instability-rivalry-with-microstrategy/">Tether’s Gamble on Bitcoin Might Cause Market Instability, Rivalry With MicroStrategy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/tethers-gamble-on-bitcoin-might-cause-market-instability-rivalry-with-microstrategy/">Tether’s Gamble on Bitcoin Might Cause Market Instability, Rivalry With MicroStrategy</a> was first posted on May 21, 2023 at 7:49 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In the wake of <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/stablecoin-issuer-tethers-q1-profits-surge-to-1-5-billion/">Tether</a>&#8216;s groundbreaking announcement regarding their plans to purchase Bitcoin, the cryptocurrency industry was buzzing with excitement and speculation. As the company behind the world&#8217;s largest stablecoin, Tether&#8217;s decision to allocate a significant portion of its monthly net realized operating profits for Bitcoin purchases sent shockwaves through the market.<br /><br />Previously, Tether had acquired BTC but had kept it separate from its excess reserves. However, this marked the first time the company had unveiled a long-term strategy specifically aimed at Bitcoin. What made this announcement even more significant was that it was the first instance of a large crypto company openly sharing plans for recurring, monthly investments in BTC.<br /><br />The timing of Tether&#8217;s announcement was no coincidence. Just a few days earlier, on May 10, the company had released its attestation report for the first quarter of the year. This report, prepared by BDO Italia, an independent public accounting firm, provided a detailed breakdown of Tether Holdings&#8217; assets. It offered a level of transparency previously unseen, unveiling separate categories for Bitcoin, physical gold, corporate bonds, and overnight repo.<br /><br />The newfound transparency into Tether&#8217;s reserves sparked intense debate and speculation within the crypto industry. Traders and analysts eagerly dissected the implications of the company&#8217;s Bitcoin purchases and their exposure to U.S. Treasurys. Some experts praised Tether&#8217;s move as a bold step towards diversifying their holdings and embracing the potential of Bitcoin. They believed that Tether&#8217;s increased investment in BTC could further strengthen its stability and position in the market.<br /><br />On the other hand, skeptics voiced concerns about the risks associated with Tether&#8217;s Bitcoin investments. Questions arose regarding the potential impact on the stability of the stablecoin if the volatile nature of Bitcoin were to affect Tether&#8217;s balance sheet. Additionally, discussions ignited around the level of exposure Tether had to U.S. Treasurys and how this factor could influence its overall financial standing.<br /><br />Amidst the heated debates, the broader crypto community eagerly awaited the outcome of Tether&#8217;s bold strategy. As the dust settled, market participants were left wondering how this move would reshape the landscape of stablecoins, Bitcoin&#8217;s market dynamics, and the future of Tether itself.<br /><br />Regardless of the arguments and uncertainties, Tether&#8217;s decision to embrace<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/microstrategy-rolls-out-wallet-and-lightning-address-for-account-holders/"> Bitcoin</a> through regular monthly purchases marked a significant milestone in the evolution of the cryptocurrency industry. It served as a testament to the growing importance and acceptance of Bitcoin as a legitimate investment asset, even among major players like Tether. The effects of this strategy would undoubtedly reverberate throughout the market, influencing the behavior and strategies of other crypto companies in the months and years to come.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/tethers-gamble-on-bitcoin-might-cause-market-instability-rivalry-with-microstrategy/">Tether’s Gamble on Bitcoin Might Cause Market Instability, Rivalry With MicroStrategy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/tethers-gamble-on-bitcoin-might-cause-market-instability-rivalry-with-microstrategy/">Tether’s Gamble on Bitcoin Might Cause Market Instability, Rivalry With MicroStrategy</a> was first posted on May 21, 2023 at 7:49 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Ledger Records Impressive Growth in Q1</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/xrp-ledger-records-impressive-growth-in-q1/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 23:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Ledger (XRPL)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65134</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>According to a recent report by Messari, the XRP Ledger (XRPL) experienced significant growth during the first quarter of 2023. Key indicators highlighted a surge in activity, with a 13.9% increase in daily active addresses and a 10.7% rise in daily transactions. The most notable development was the impressive 55.5% price increase of XRP, surging [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/xrp-ledger-records-impressive-growth-in-q1/">XRP Ledger Records Impressive Growth in Q1</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/xrp-ledger-records-impressive-growth-in-q1/">XRP Ledger Records Impressive Growth in Q1</a> was first posted on May 19, 2023 at 7:14 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>According to a recent <a href="https://twitter.com/MessariCrypto/status/1659289748341653510">report</a> by Messari, the XRP Ledger (XRPL) experienced significant growth during the first quarter of 2023. Key indicators highlighted a surge in activity, with a 13.9% increase in daily active addresses and a 10.7% rise in daily transactions.<br /><br />The most notable development was the impressive 55.5% price increase of XRP, surging from $0.35 to $0.54. This boost was largely influenced by positive news from the ongoing legal case between Ripple and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).<br /><br />The Q1 report also emphasized the evolution of the<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/xrpl-nft-marketplace-reports-record-breaking-traffic-shortly-after-launch-of-xls-20-that-brings-native-nft-support/"> XRPL</a> ecosystem. The introduction of the XLS-20 standard facilitated NFT transactions, with five new transaction types established and five more proposed. Despite a slight decrease in NFT activity compared to the previous quarter, Q1 still saw 436,000 NFT mints and 277,000 accepted NFT offers. Additionally, the Coreum and Flare Network sidechains, focusing on interoperability and decentralized data, successfully reached their mainnet.<br /><br />XRP&#8217;s financial performance surpassed the overall increase in the total crypto market cap. XRP&#8217;s market cap rose by an impressive 59.9%, from $17.4 billion to $27.8 billion. A positive development in the SEC case against Ripple acted as a significant catalyst, leading to two substantial price surges in March. The transaction fees on the XRPL, which are burned, created deflationary pressure on the total supply of XRP, offsetting the inflation rate and contributing to the price increase.<br /><br />Looking ahead, XRPL developers are focused on NFTs, the metaverse, and smart contracts. The report outlined plans for Futureverse&#8217;s Root Network, Hooks, and an Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) sidechain. If successfully implemented, these advancements will add a layer of functionality to the XRPL ecosystem, which already offers features such as fast, energy-efficient cross-currency and cross-border payments.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/xrp-ledger-records-impressive-growth-in-q1/">XRP Ledger Records Impressive Growth in Q1</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/xrp-ledger-records-impressive-growth-in-q1/">XRP Ledger Records Impressive Growth in Q1</a> was first posted on May 19, 2023 at 7:14 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CFTC Has No Power To Regulate Cash Crypto Markets, Admits Chairman</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/cftc-has-no-power-to-regulate-cash-crypto-markets-admits-chairman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 23:55:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US CFTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65129</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) has no power to regulate cash crypto markets, admits chairman. According to Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) chairman Rostin Benham, his agency lacks the legal authority to regulate cash crypto markets. In a recent interview, Benham clarified that the CFTC&#8217;s jurisdiction is limited to addressing fraud and manipulation in cash [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/cftc-has-no-power-to-regulate-cash-crypto-markets-admits-chairman/">CFTC Has No Power To Regulate Cash Crypto Markets, Admits Chairman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/cftc-has-no-power-to-regulate-cash-crypto-markets-admits-chairman/">CFTC Has No Power To Regulate Cash Crypto Markets, Admits Chairman</a> was first posted on May 18, 2023 at 7:55 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Commodity Futures Trading Commission (<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/cftc-chairman-confirms-commodity-status-of-bitcoin-and-ether-says-xrp-is-uncertain/">CFTC</a>) has no power to regulate cash crypto markets, admits chairman. According to Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) chairman Rostin Benham, his agency lacks the legal authority to regulate cash crypto markets. <br /><br />In a recent <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-05-18/transcript-cftc-chair-rostin-behnam-on-the-fight-to-regulate-crypto">interview</a>, Benham clarified that the CFTC&#8217;s jurisdiction is limited to addressing fraud and manipulation in cash markets.<br /><br />However, he emphasized that the CFTC will still regulate the crypto sector through other means to protect investors. Benham considers many cryptocurrency tokens as commodity financial assets, allowing the application of regulations, notices, advisories, and enforcement actions. <br /><br />This aligns with his previous statements in March, where he classified assets like Ethereum and stablecoins as commodities. <br /><br />Despite the unique challenges presented by cryptocurrencies, Benham believes that existing policy approaches can be adapted to address them.<br /><br />It is noteworthy that the CFTC and the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) are the two main government agencies responsible for regulating the cryptocurrency space.<br /><br />While SEC chair Gary Gensler believes the CFTC should regulate certain assets without overriding the SEC&#8217;s authority, Benham contends that the CFTC should oversee assets that are not considered securities.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/cftc-has-no-power-to-regulate-cash-crypto-markets-admits-chairman/">CFTC Has No Power To Regulate Cash Crypto Markets, Admits Chairman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/cftc-has-no-power-to-regulate-cash-crypto-markets-admits-chairman/">CFTC Has No Power To Regulate Cash Crypto Markets, Admits Chairman</a> was first posted on May 18, 2023 at 7:55 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple CEO States the Company Is Mostly Recruiting Abroad</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/ripple-ceo-states-the-company-is-mostly-recruiting-abroad/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 23:43:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brad Garlinghouse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple CEO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65125</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse recently discussed the company&#8217;s hiring strategy in a CNBC International interview, revealing a shift towards focusing on international recruitment. Garlinghouse attributed this decision to the ongoing uncertainty surrounding cryptocurrency regulations in the United States. This ambiguity has prompted entrepreneurs and investors to explore more accommodating jurisdictions, with Europe emerging as a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/ripple-ceo-states-the-company-is-mostly-recruiting-abroad/">Ripple CEO States the Company Is Mostly Recruiting Abroad</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ripple-ceo-states-the-company-is-mostly-recruiting-abroad/">Ripple CEO States the Company Is Mostly Recruiting Abroad</a> was first posted on May 18, 2023 at 7:43 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse recently <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0W4fSOEFfkM&amp;ab_channel=CNBCInternationalTV">discussed</a> the company&#8217;s hiring strategy in a CNBC International interview, revealing a shift towards focusing on international recruitment. Garlinghouse attributed this decision to the ongoing uncertainty surrounding cryptocurrency regulations in the United States. <br /><br />This ambiguity has prompted entrepreneurs and investors to explore more accommodating jurisdictions, with Europe emerging as a significant beneficiary due to its well-defined and robust regulatory framework for digital assets.<br /><br />Garlinghouse emphasized the impact of regulatory confusion in the United States on <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ripple-teams-up-with-central-bank-of-montenegro-for-cbdc-stablecoin-initiatives/">Ripple</a>&#8216;s operations, explaining that the company has been compelled to allocate a significant portion of its resources outside of the country. He stated,<em> &#8220;95 percent of our customers are non-U.S., and this year most of our hiring will be non-U.S. for some of those exact same reasons.&#8221;</em> Ripple&#8217;s expansion in Europe is partially driven by the favorable regulatory environment offered by the continent.<br /><br />Looking ahead to the regulatory landscape for cryptocurrencies in light of the FTX case, Garlinghouse highlighted nations such as the United Arab Emirates, the United Kingdom, Singapore, and Europe for their clear rules and roadmaps. He believes that this clarity enables entrepreneurs and investors to engage more effectively with regulators. The recent acquisition of Swiss-based firm Medico by Ripple was partly influenced by the regulatory clarity found in Switzerland. Garlinghouse stressed the importance of differentiating between issues specific to cryptocurrencies and broader problems like fraud.<br /><br />To illustrate this point, he referred to the FTX case as a fraud issue rather than one specific to cryptocurrencies. He emphasized that fraud can occur in various asset classes and is not limited to the crypto industry. Garlinghouse suggested that the United States could learn from Europe and other countries that provide clear regulatory frameworks for digital assets.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/ripple-ceo-states-the-company-is-mostly-recruiting-abroad/">Ripple CEO States the Company Is Mostly Recruiting Abroad</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ripple-ceo-states-the-company-is-mostly-recruiting-abroad/">Ripple CEO States the Company Is Mostly Recruiting Abroad</a> was first posted on May 18, 2023 at 7:43 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>WazirX Reveals its WRX Token Under Binance’s Control</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/wazirx-reveals-its-wrx-token-under-binances-control/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 22:54:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WazirX (WRX)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65121</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WazirX, India&#8217;s leading cryptocurrency exchange, made a startling revelation that Binance, the global crypto giant, conducted the initial exchange offering (IEO) for its WRX token and currently maintains control over the token supply. In a statement released on May 16, the WazirX team clarified that Binance had kept all the proceeds, totaling around $2 million, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/wazirx-reveals-its-wrx-token-under-binances-control/">WazirX Reveals its WRX Token Under Binance&#8217;s Control</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/wazirx-reveals-its-wrx-token-under-binances-control/">WazirX Reveals its WRX Token Under Binance&#8217;s Control</a> was first posted on May 17, 2023 at 6:54 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://wazirx.com/blog/update-on-wrx-token-management/">WazirX</a>, India&#8217;s leading cryptocurrency exchange, made a startling revelation that Binance, the global crypto giant, conducted the initial exchange offering (IEO) for its WRX token and currently maintains control over the token supply.<br /><br />In a statement released on May 16, the WazirX team clarified that Binance had kept all the proceeds, totaling around $2 million, from the IEO for itself. Notably, the WazirX team emphasized that they had not received any token allocations.<br /><br />According to WazirX,<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-shifts-voyager-ftx-tokens-to-innovation-zone-amid-bankruptcy/"> Binance</a> holds control over all wallets containing locked and unlocked WRX tokens. It further revealed that Binance currently holds 580.7 million units of locked and unlocked WRX tokens, equivalent to approximately $74.5 million based on the token&#8217;s current price. Binance has conducted its quarterly burns for the WRX token and held the unlocked tokens in its account.<br /><br />In a series of transactions between April 2021 and March 2022, Binance moved 116.8 million unlocked WRX tokens to its treasury. However, WazirX pointed out that Binance has failed to conduct any of the scheduled quarterly burns for WRX since January 2022. WazirX emphasized that Binance bears the responsibility for executing the quarterly burn of WRX tokens.<br /><br />The relationship between Binance and WazirX has been marred by an ongoing dispute over the ownership structure of the Indian exchange. While WazirX claims to be owned by Binance, the CZ-led firm argues that it merely provides wallet services and technical support to the Indian exchange.<br /><br />This recent disclosure adds another layer of complexity to an already tense relationship. In February, the feud escalated to the point where Binance terminated its partnership with WazirX, instructing the Indian exchange to withdraw its assets from the platform.<br /><br />Amidst these developments, the WRX token has experienced a decline of over 7.1% in the past seven days, currently trading at $0.124. As the situation unfolds, questions regarding the control and management of the WRX token persist.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/wazirx-reveals-its-wrx-token-under-binances-control/">WazirX Reveals its WRX Token Under Binance&#8217;s Control</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/wazirx-reveals-its-wrx-token-under-binances-control/">WazirX Reveals its WRX Token Under Binance&#8217;s Control</a> was first posted on May 17, 2023 at 6:54 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Adoption in Turkey, Argentina, Philippines Rises Amidst Soaring Inflation</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-adoption-in-turkey-argentina-philippines-rises-amidst-soaring-inflation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 22:41:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Adoption]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65117</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>According to research conducted by GWI, Turkey experienced the highest growth in crypto ownership, with a significant surge of 27.1% from July-September 2021 to July–September 2022. Following closely, Argentina and the Philippines secured the second and third spots, respectively, with an impressive increase in their crypto ownership rates of 23.5% and 23.4%, as per GWI [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-adoption-in-turkey-argentina-philippines-rises-amidst-soaring-inflation/">Crypto Adoption in Turkey, Argentina, Philippines Rises Amidst Soaring Inflation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-adoption-in-turkey-argentina-philippines-rises-amidst-soaring-inflation/">Crypto Adoption in Turkey, Argentina, Philippines Rises Amidst Soaring Inflation</a> was first posted on May 17, 2023 at 6:41 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>According to research conducted by GWI, <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/turkeys-central-bank-to-continue-trials-for-digital-lira-in-2023/">Turkey</a> experienced the highest growth in crypto ownership, with a significant surge of 27.1% from July-September 2021 to July–September 2022. Following closely, Argentina and the Philippines secured the second and third spots, respectively, with an impressive increase in their crypto ownership rates of 23.5% and 23.4%, as per GWI research<a href="https://twitter.com/DocumentingBTC/status/1658874634702319616?s=20"> data.</a><br /><br />The study focuses on individuals aged 16 to 64 and examines their ownership of any form of cryptocurrency. A chart showcasing the top 15 countries with the highest surges in crypto ownership, along with the global average of an 11.9% increase, is provided below.<br /><br />While Turkey claims the top position in the chart, it&#8217;s worth noting that the United Arab Emirates, Vietnam, and Portugal also witnessed remarkable growth rates. Though the data doesn&#8217;t explicitly state the reasons behind the surge in crypto ownership, the top three countries share a common factor: rampant inflation.<br /><br />In late 2021, the Turkish lira experienced a rapid depreciation of 44% against the US dollar. Additionally, the country&#8217;s inflation rate exceeded 30% in early 2022 and closed the year at a staggering 72.31%. These economic circumstances prompted many Turks to turn to cryptocurrencies, leading to a significant surge in daily trading volume, which averaged around $1.8 billion.<br /><br />Similarly, Argentina faced an alarming inflation rate of 94.8% in 2022, the highest percentage observed since 1991. The devaluation of the Argentine peso likely contributed to citizens embracing cryptocurrencies, much like their counterparts in Turkey. Notably, the adoption of crypto in Argentina became evident when a <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-might-be-accepted-as-payment-option-for-government-services-in-liechtenstein-pm/">Bitcoin (BTC)</a> wallet became the number-one application in the country within a week of its launch.<br /><br />The situation in the Philippines mirrors the trends observed in Turkey and Argentina. The country witnessed a notable increase in inflation, with a rate of 8.1% recorded in December 2022, marking a significant 107% surge from the 3.9% registered in 2021. This rise in inflation is also reflected in the growing adoption of cryptocurrencies among the Filipino population.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-adoption-in-turkey-argentina-philippines-rises-amidst-soaring-inflation/">Crypto Adoption in Turkey, Argentina, Philippines Rises Amidst Soaring Inflation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-adoption-in-turkey-argentina-philippines-rises-amidst-soaring-inflation/">Crypto Adoption in Turkey, Argentina, Philippines Rises Amidst Soaring Inflation</a> was first posted on May 17, 2023 at 6:41 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CBDC Imposition Takes Center Stage at G7 Committee Meeting</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/cbdc-imposition-takes-center-stage-at-g7-committee-meeting/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 23:06:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65113</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The G7 committee recently gathered in Niigata, Japan, to discuss the potential of central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) in shaping a global financial system. The meeting brought together leading economies ahead of the annual G7 summit, with a focus on finding ways to enhance payment efficiency while safeguarding the stability and integrity of the monetary [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/cbdc-imposition-takes-center-stage-at-g7-committee-meeting/">CBDC Imposition Takes Center Stage at G7 Committee Meeting</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/cbdc-imposition-takes-center-stage-at-g7-committee-meeting/">CBDC Imposition Takes Center Stage at G7 Committee Meeting</a> was first posted on May 16, 2023 at 7:06 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/g7-considers-facebook-libra-as-risks-to-financial-stability-demand/">G7 committee</a> recently gathered in Niigata, Japan, to discuss the potential of central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) in shaping a global financial system. The meeting brought together leading economies ahead of the annual G7 summit, with a focus on finding ways to enhance payment efficiency while safeguarding the stability and integrity of the monetary systems.<br /><br />Transparency, reliability, and stability for global payments were key priorities for the committee, which sees <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/visa-chief-predicts-meaningful-role-for-stablecoins-and-cbdcs/">CBDCs</a> as a promising avenue to achieve these goals. While CBDCs differ from decentralized cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin, the committee emphasizes the importance of upholding fundamental principles such as compliance with legal requirements, economic governance practices, cybersecurity, and data protection.<br /><br />As the traditional banking system faces challenges and the fiat monetary system teeters on the edge, central banks have resorted to propping it up at the expense of citizens&#8217; purchasing power. The committee recognizes that imposing a CBDC can extend the life of the fiat system, but concerns arise regarding potential control over individuals&#8217; spending and financial freedom.<br /><br />Critics argue that the introduction of a CBDC could grant central banks unprecedented power to monitor and restrict transactions, limiting options like investing in cryptocurrencies. Preserving privacy and financial freedom becomes a significant concern, considering governments&#8217; past actions to freeze accounts and blacklist Bitcoin wallets. With CBDCs, the potential for enhanced financial surveillance raises questions about the balance between innovation and individual autonomy.<br /><br />While history reveals a pattern of increasing control during the decline of world empires, the hope remains that determined independent thinkers will continue to strive for freedom in the face of these challenges.</p>
<p>Image Credit – Pixabay.com</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/cbdc-imposition-takes-center-stage-at-g7-committee-meeting/">CBDC Imposition Takes Center Stage at G7 Committee Meeting</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/cbdc-imposition-takes-center-stage-at-g7-committee-meeting/">CBDC Imposition Takes Center Stage at G7 Committee Meeting</a> was first posted on May 16, 2023 at 7:06 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ledger Faces Backlash for Potential User Seed Phrase Breach</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/ledger-faces-backlash-for-potential-user-seed-phrase-breach/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 22:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ledger]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65109</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto hardware wallet provider Ledger is facing severe backlash from its online user base following the release of a controversial update that has raised concerns about significant security flaws. Despite Ledger&#8217;s claims that the new functionality is safe and optional, security experts and cryptocurrency holders are expressing their dissatisfaction and distancing themselves from the company. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/ledger-faces-backlash-for-potential-user-seed-phrase-breach/">Ledger Faces Backlash for Potential User Seed Phrase Breach</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ledger-faces-backlash-for-potential-user-seed-phrase-breach/">Ledger Faces Backlash for Potential User Seed Phrase Breach</a> was first posted on May 16, 2023 at 6:01 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Crypto hardware wallet provider <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/xrp-ledger-now-has-native-support-for-nfts/">Ledger</a> is facing severe backlash from its online user base following the release of a controversial update that has raised concerns about significant security flaws. Despite Ledger&#8217;s claims that the new functionality is safe and optional, security experts and cryptocurrency holders are expressing their dissatisfaction and distancing themselves from the company.<br /><br />The discontent began to escalate when a Reddit user named Joe_Smith_Reddit <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ledgerwallet/comments/13itm7u/comment/jkbyyfp/">posted</a> a question demanding a clear answer on whether Ledger has a built-in backdoor for accessing users&#8217; private keys.<br /><br />Private keys are crucial alphanumeric strings that allow users to access their cryptocurrencies on the blockchain. The specific inquiry revolved around Ledger&#8217;s recently introduced &#8220;Ledger Recover&#8221; service, designed for Nano X device owners to <a href="https://www.ledger.com/recover">recover</a> their crypto assets even if they lose both their wallet device and recovery phrase. The recovery phrase represents a user&#8217;s private key in mnemonic form.<br /><br />According to Ledger, the service enabled through firmware update 2.2.1, duplicates the recovery phrase on the device, encrypts the copy, fragments it into three parts, and secures it with Ledger, Coincover, and another unnamed provider. To utilize the service, users must verify their identity using an ID document and a selfie recording.<br /><br />Attempting to address the growing concerns, Ledger took to Twitter to emphasize that the service is completely optional and not automatically enabled through any firmware update. They added that users&#8217; secret recovery phrases are securely generated on their own devices, with no access granted to Ledger.<br /><br />Despite these assurances from Ledger, the community&#8217;s worries persist around one central issue: the update appears to expose that Ledger devices do not provide absolute protection of users&#8217; private keys against external access, contrary to the company&#8217;s claims. Reddit user StPinkie expressed disappointment, stating that trust in the proprietary secure element, which was a cornerstone of the company, has been shattered. <br /><br />They announced that they can no longer recommend Ledger to anyone concerned about maintaining their digital sovereignty.<br /><br />Notable crypto developer, writer, and auditor &#8220;foobar&#8221; echoed this sentiment on <a href="https://twitter.com/Ledger/status/1658458714771169282">Twitter</a>, urging followers to immediately transition away from Ledger wallets. They <a href="https://twitter.com/0xfoobar/status/1658478186408337408">highlighted</a> the update&#8217;s glaring problem of potentially exposing private keys to risk through malicious or accidental firmware updates.<br /><br />Users also pointed out a contradiction between Ledger&#8217;s website claims that users&#8217; keys &#8220;never leave the device&#8221; and the Ledger Recover service, which distributes users&#8217; private keys to three different providers in shards, as explained by CEO Pascal Gauthier.<br /><br />Within the community, many suggested that Ledger introduce a separate wallet dedicated to offering a seed-recovery service rather than rolling it out as a firmware update for existing customers who expected the highest level of security from their devices.<br /><br />It is worth noting tha<a href="https://www.ledger.com/message-ledgers-ceo-data-leak">t Ledger</a> has experienced previous security compromises, including when the personal information of over 270,000 customers was accidentally leaked in July 2020. However, this incident did not impact the security of users&#8217; private keys.<br /><br />Ledger saw a surge in sales following the collapse of FTX in November, as investors sought to secure their cryptocurrencies independently, avoiding reliance on centralized intermediaries.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/ledger-faces-backlash-for-potential-user-seed-phrase-breach/">Ledger Faces Backlash for Potential User Seed Phrase Breach</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ledger-faces-backlash-for-potential-user-seed-phrase-breach/">Ledger Faces Backlash for Potential User Seed Phrase Breach</a> was first posted on May 16, 2023 at 6:01 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>