<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>Latest Crypto News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://kryptomoney.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<description>Latest Crypto News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 23:30:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/cropped-cropped-favicon_512x512_v2-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Latest Crypto News</title>
	<link>https://kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><itunes:subtitle>Latest Crypto News</itunes:subtitle><itunes:category text="News &amp; Politics"/><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Business News"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Investing"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Tech News"/></itunes:category><item>
		<title>SEC To Investigate Audit Firms Hired by Cryptocurrency Companies</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/sec-to-investigate-audit-firms-hired-by-cryptocurrency-companies/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 23:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63634</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) of the United States said on Thursday that it is looking into audit firms that work for cryptocurrency companies. According to the Wall Street Journal (WSJ), the SEC will boost its scrutiny of audit firms that produce audit reports for crypto companies. The regulatory authority noted that it must [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/sec-to-investigate-audit-firms-hired-by-cryptocurrency-companies/">SEC To Investigate Audit Firms Hired by Cryptocurrency Companies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/sec-to-investigate-audit-firms-hired-by-cryptocurrency-companies/">SEC To Investigate Audit Firms Hired by Cryptocurrency Companies</a> was first posted on December 22, 2022 at 6:30 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) of the United States said on Thursday that it is looking into audit firms that work for cryptocurrency companies.<br /><br />According to the<a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/sec-heightening-scrutiny-of-auditors-crypto-work-11671681693"> Wall Street Journal (WSJ)</a>, the SEC will boost its scrutiny of audit firms that produce audit reports for crypto companies. The regulatory authority noted that it must take this measure due to worries that investors are receiving false reassurance from audit reports and risking exposure to cryptocurrencies. As the fallout from FTX&#8217;s bankruptcy spreads, more crypto businesses have been forced to produce reports on the health of their reserves.<br /><br />Several <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-exchanges-prepares-ahead-of-expected-bitcoin-cash-fork-on-the-15th-of-november/">crypto exchanges</a> advocated releasing proof-of-reserves to reassure clients that their assets were safe and to demonstrate that the company is financially healthy and steady.<br /><br />Acting SEC Chief Accountant Paul Munter told the WSJ:<br /><br /><em>We’re warning investors to be very wary of some of the claims that are being made by crypto companies.</em><br /><br />The SEC maintains its anti-crypto stance and has steadily intensified its monitoring of enterprises dealing in digital assets as the market grows. As bitcoin firms are now required to disclose the health of their finances, the SEC has decided to scrutinize how cryptocurrency firms present audit firm reports. Banks and auditing firms have been hesitant to cooperate with cryptocurrency firms because regulatory pressure surrounding cryptocurrencies remains ambiguous.<br /><br /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bybit-introduces-merkle-tree-verified-proof-of-reserves/">Mazars</a>, a French corporation, just temporarily suspended its auditing services to Binance, Crypto.com, and KuCoin. Mazars even removed the link to Binance&#8217;s proof-of-reserve assessment from its website after discovering that the exchange&#8217;s Bitcoin reserves were overcollateralized.<br /><br />Bloomberg was the first to disclose that Mazars had terminated its services to the aforementioned crypto businesses, and that other auditing firms, including FTX&#8217;s auditor Armanino, had also stopped working with crypto exchanges like OKX and Gate.io.<br /><br />As a result, the SEC is issuing warnings to audit firms working on crypto audits, believing that crypto exchanges are utilizing audit firms&#8217; proof-of-reserve reports to their advantage. The SEC sees a risk in this because it contains insufficient financial information to determine whether a corporation has enough assets to cover its liabilities.<br /><br />The SEC&#8217;s chair, Gary Gensler, cautioned that investors are still exposed to the dangers associated with the crypto market unless these firms comply with time-tested securities regulations. Gensler was responding to the SEC&#8217;s fraud accusations against former Alameda Research CEO Caroline Ellison and FTX co-founder Gary Wang. Gensler also stated that the government will continue to employ all available measures to bring the bitcoin business into compliance.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/sec-to-investigate-audit-firms-hired-by-cryptocurrency-companies/">SEC To Investigate Audit Firms Hired by Cryptocurrency Companies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/sec-to-investigate-audit-firms-hired-by-cryptocurrency-companies/">SEC To Investigate Audit Firms Hired by Cryptocurrency Companies</a> was first posted on December 22, 2022 at 6:30 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Twitter Incorporates Crypto and Stock Charts</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/twitter-incorporates-crypto-and-stock-charts/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 22:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63627</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Twitter announced a new feature called &#8220;Cashtags&#8221; on Thursday, which includes price charts for major cryptocurrencies and stock assets. Elon Musk, the new owner of Twitter and a tech millionaire, offered a feature built exclusively for the financial industry, with a particular advantage for traders, financial specialists, investors, and organizations. $Cashtags allows users to view [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/twitter-incorporates-crypto-and-stock-charts/">Twitter Incorporates Crypto and Stock Charts</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/twitter-incorporates-crypto-and-stock-charts/">Twitter Incorporates Crypto and Stock Charts</a> was first posted on December 22, 2022 at 5:35 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/elon-musk-pays-visit-to-twitters-headquarters-ahead-of-takeover/">Twitter</a> announced a new feature called &#8220;Cashtags&#8221; on Thursday, which includes price charts for major cryptocurrencies and stock assets. Elon Musk, the new owner of Twitter and a tech millionaire, offered a feature built exclusively for the financial industry, with a particular advantage for traders, financial specialists, investors, and organizations. <br /><br />$Cashtags allows users to view graphs, charts, and other data from stocks, cryptocurrencies, and exchange-traded funds (ETFs) within a tweet.<br /><br />According to the official Twitter Business account:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>When you Tweet the symbol of a major stock, ETF, or cryptocurrency with a $ in front of it (like $BTC), people on Twitter see a clickable link that takes them to search results. Starting today, these search results will include the pricing graphs for major symbols.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>It went on to say:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>You can also search for symbols directly, without clicking on a link within a Tweet. Most symbols with and without the $ sign will work in search (QQQ or $QQQ).</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Users can enable the new option by clicking on<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-and-altcoins-tumble-more-declines-to-expect-what-analysts-and-on-chain-data-say-on-the-health-of-the-crypto-markets/"> $BTC and $ETH</a>, or by searching for any crypto asset. Users can access the wallet provider by clicking on the &#8216;View on Robinhood&#8217; link. The addition of a link to Robinhood may indicate a potential relationship between the two companies, although no official announcement has been made.<br /><br />Elon Musk congratulated the Twitter team and stated that this is<em> &#8220;only one of many product improvements coming to financial Twitter!&#8221;</em></p>
<p>Musk has previously stated that his crypto holdings consist of only Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Dogecoin (DOGE), and Doge holders have been eagerly expecting the announcement of a payments connection since his takeover of Twitter. However, the digital tycoon announced his resignation as Twitter&#8217;s CEO, and Dogecoin has inevitably responded unfavorably in the market after outperforming the market in November, not long after Tesla CEO Elon Musk acquired Twitter for $44 billion in October.<br /><br />In September, a complaint was also filed alleging Musk of running a pyramid scheme to fund DOGE.</p>
<p><strong>Image Credit:</strong> Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/twitter-incorporates-crypto-and-stock-charts/">Twitter Incorporates Crypto and Stock Charts</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/twitter-incorporates-crypto-and-stock-charts/">Twitter Incorporates Crypto and Stock Charts</a> was first posted on December 22, 2022 at 5:35 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ADA Price Analysis: Cardano Touts Massive On-Chain Growth in 2022, What’s Next for ADA Price?</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/ada-price-analysis-cardano-touts-massive-on-chain-growth-in-2022-whats-next-for-ada-price/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 15:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA/USD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA/USD Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63614</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cardano’s ADA is currently down 3% at $0.25 The Cardano foundation has taken to Twitter to share the highlights of the year 2022 The number of Plutus scripts is 4445 which marks a 394% increase since the year 2021 Cardano’s ADA is currently down 3% in the last 24 hours at $0.25 as the crypto [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/ada-price-analysis-cardano-touts-massive-on-chain-growth-in-2022-whats-next-for-ada-price/">ADA Price Analysis: Cardano Touts Massive On-Chain Growth in 2022, What’s Next for ADA Price?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ada-price-analysis-cardano-touts-massive-on-chain-growth-in-2022-whats-next-for-ada-price/">ADA Price Analysis: Cardano Touts Massive On-Chain Growth in 2022, What’s Next for ADA Price?</a> was first posted on December 22, 2022 at 10:03 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li>Cardano’s ADA is currently down 3% at $0.25</li>
<li>The Cardano foundation has taken to Twitter to share the highlights of the year 2022</li>
<li>The number of Plutus scripts is 4445 which marks a 394% increase since the year 2021</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ada-price-analysis-key-levels-to-watch-amid-present-volatility-cardanos-sundaeswap-announces-new-milestone/">Cardano’s ADA</a> is currently down 3% in the last 24 hours at $0.25 as the crypto market seeks a positive catalyst for its recovery. The Cardano Foundation has taken to Twitter to share the highlights of the about-to-be-concluded year 2022. According to the graphic posted, the number of transactions reached 56.9 million, up 139% from 2021. At the same time, the overall number of wallets grew by 47% to 3.80 million, while the number of delegated wallets increased by 27% to 1.24 million. According to GitHub data, Cardano ranks among the top three chains in terms of daily development activity. According to the latest statistics provided by IOG, 1,151 projects are in various stages of development on the Cardano blockchain. So far, 111 projects have been launched. The number of Plutus scripts is 4445, which marks a 394% increase since the year 2021, while native tokens are now over 7.3 million, marking a 192% increase since 2021. Minting policies are up 69% year on year to 66,950.<br /><br /><strong>Key Levels</strong><br />Resistance Levels: $0.650, $0.500, $0.300<br />Support Levels: $0.250, $0.150, $0.100</p>
<h4>ADA/USD Daily Chart: Bearish</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1436" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-63630 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD-Daily-Dec-22.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD-Daily-Dec-22.png 1436w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD-Daily-Dec-22-300x144.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD-Daily-Dec-22-1024x491.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD-Daily-Dec-22-768x368.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD-Daily-Dec-22-750x359.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD-Daily-Dec-22-1140x546.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1436px) 100vw, 1436px" /><em><span style="color: #999999">ADA/USD Daily Chart</span></em></h6>
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ada-price-analysis-cardano-price-dips-network-adds-70000-new-holders-within-a-month/">ADA/USD</a> is trading in a weak downtrend beneath the technical daily moving averages of 50 and 200 as the pair remains under pressure near its yearly low. The price is trading a little below the 2021 lows.<br /><br />Prolonged recovery from $0.250 (low) towards the $0.300 level could pave the way for a retest of further lows around the $0.200 level. At the moment, the ADA trend is bearish, with the resistance level of $0.300 holding in the event of a strong rebound.</p>
<h4>ADA/USD 4-Hour Chart: Bearish</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1436" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-63631 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD-4-Hour-Dec-22.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD-4-Hour-Dec-22.png 1436w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD-4-Hour-Dec-22-300x144.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD-4-Hour-Dec-22-1024x491.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD-4-Hour-Dec-22-768x368.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD-4-Hour-Dec-22-750x359.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSD-4-Hour-Dec-22-1140x546.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1436px) 100vw, 1436px" /><em><span style="color: #999999">ADA/USD 4-Hour Chart</span></em></h6>
<p>On the 4-hour chart, ADA/USD risk is weighted to the downside as the pair develops below the firmly bearish 50 and 200 moving averages. With negative levels, technical indications have swung to the downside. The RSI, on the other hand, has not yet entered the oversold area, allowing for more selling.<br /><br />A break below the $0.250 horizontal support level might result in a larger loss, with investors looking for a move toward the $0.200 level. The price should hold at this position because this is a strong area of support. If the consolidation breaks down, the bears will be seeking a move toward the $0.150 area.</p>
<p><strong>Note:</strong><em> Kryptomoney.com is not a financial advisor. Do your research before investing your funds in any financial asset or presented product or event. We are not responsible for your investing results</em></p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/ada-price-analysis-cardano-touts-massive-on-chain-growth-in-2022-whats-next-for-ada-price/">ADA Price Analysis: Cardano Touts Massive On-Chain Growth in 2022, What’s Next for ADA Price?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ada-price-analysis-cardano-touts-massive-on-chain-growth-in-2022-whats-next-for-ada-price/">ADA Price Analysis: Cardano Touts Massive On-Chain Growth in 2022, What’s Next for ADA Price?</a> was first posted on December 22, 2022 at 10:03 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple and MoneyGram Collaborate To Build New Remittance Platform</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/ripple-and-moneygram-collaborate-to-build-new-remittance-platform/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 21:32:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MoneyGram]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63619</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>MoneyGram, a former Ripple partner, and Frente Corretora, a current partner, have collaborated to launch a new remittance service in Brazil with no fees for consumers. MoneyGram Online (MGO), a new service, allows customers to send money from Brazil to any country in the world in near real-time. Account deposit, mobile wallet, and cash pick-up [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/ripple-and-moneygram-collaborate-to-build-new-remittance-platform/">Ripple and MoneyGram Collaborate To Build New Remittance Platform</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ripple-and-moneygram-collaborate-to-build-new-remittance-platform/">Ripple and MoneyGram Collaborate To Build New Remittance Platform</a> was first posted on December 21, 2022 at 4:32 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/moneygram-app-now-includes-crypto-trading-tools-for-bitcoin-ether-and-litecoin/">MoneyGram</a>, a former Ripple partner, and Frente Corretora, a current partner, have collaborated to launch a new <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/moneygram-launches-moneygram-online-mgo-website-in-brazil-301707173.html">remittance service</a> in Brazil with no fees for consumers. MoneyGram Online (MGO), a new service, allows customers to send money from Brazil to any country in the world in near real-time. Account deposit, mobile wallet, and cash pick-up from retail locations are among the services offered by the organization.<br /><br />MoneyGram Chairman and CEO Alex Holmes remarked:</p>
<p><em>“We’re confident that this launch will enable us to capture growth from new customer segments, deepen relationships with established customers, and create tremendous value for years to come.”</em></p>
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/brazilian-congress-makes-move-to-regulate-cryptocurrency-payments/">Brazil</a> is becoming a more active user of cryptocurrencies and digital assets. Latin American remittances abroad have increased significantly in recent years, according to the World Bank.<br /><br />Furthermore, according to Accenture&#8217;s 2022 Global Consumer Payments Research, Latin America is only second to Asia Pacific in terms of the adoption of next-generation payment platforms.<br /><br />Meanwhile, Brazil ranks ninth in terms of cryptocurrency users. According to Bloomberg, 32.3 million Brazilians, or 19% of the population, use cryptocurrency.<br /><br />Furthermore, in the SEC v. Ripple action, a recent motion accepted MoneyGram and &#8220;third party A&#8217;s&#8221; request to redact documents filed in conjunction with Daubert filings. This was done to protect Ripple&#8217;s confidential business ventures as well as the lawful privacy interests of third parties.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/ripple-and-moneygram-collaborate-to-build-new-remittance-platform/">Ripple and MoneyGram Collaborate To Build New Remittance Platform</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ripple-and-moneygram-collaborate-to-build-new-remittance-platform/">Ripple and MoneyGram Collaborate To Build New Remittance Platform</a> was first posted on December 21, 2022 at 4:32 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Granted Virtual Asset Service Provider License in Ireland</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-granted-virtual-asset-service-provider-license-in-ireland/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 20:59:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63610</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase is one of the oldest cryptocurrency exchanges in the world. It debuted in 2012 and has a dedicated fan base. The exchange was also among the first to welcome a large number of cryptocurrency enthusiasts. The exchange just announced on one of its blogs that it has obtained a license to operate in Ireland. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-granted-virtual-asset-service-provider-license-in-ireland/">Coinbase Granted Virtual Asset Service Provider License in Ireland</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-granted-virtual-asset-service-provider-license-in-ireland/">Coinbase Granted Virtual Asset Service Provider License in Ireland</a> was first posted on December 21, 2022 at 3:59 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-reveals-over-33000000000-worth-of-bitcoin-in-its-reserves/">Coinbase</a> is one of the oldest cryptocurrency exchanges in the world. It debuted in 2012 and has a dedicated fan base. The exchange was also among the first to welcome a large number of cryptocurrency enthusiasts.</p>
<p>The exchange just announced on one of its <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/coinbase-secures-regulatory-approval-and-welcomes-new-country-director-in">blogs</a> that it has obtained a license to operate in Ireland.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>“Coinbase is delighted to announce that we have successfully registered with the Central Bank of Ireland as a Virtual Asset Service Provider, and to introduce Cormac Dinan as our new Country Director for Ireland.“</p>
</blockquote>
<p>According to the information, Coinbase has now secured an Irish virtual asset service provider license. The exchange will now be able to offer its services and goods to individuals in Ireland as a result of the license.<br /><br />Cormac Dinan was also named as the company&#8217;s new country director, according to the release. Dinan, who has more than 20 years of experience, will oversee the exchange&#8217;s activities in the country.<br /><br />According to the VASP, the exchange will be subject to the Criminal Justice Money Laundering and Terrorist Financing Act of 2010.</p>
<p>I’m looking forward to strengthening Ireland’s operations and helping the sector’s continued growth. <em>&#8220;Creating an environment which champions innovation while strengthening trust in crypto is something I am really eager to progress,&#8221;</em> said Cormac Dinan.<br /><br />Coinbase Europe Limited and Coinbase Custody International Limited are covered by the VASP. Since 2018, the exchange has also been operational in Ireland. The exchange can now offer its services across the country thanks to its recent registration with the Central Bank of Ireland.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-granted-virtual-asset-service-provider-license-in-ireland/">Coinbase Granted Virtual Asset Service Provider License in Ireland</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-granted-virtual-asset-service-provider-license-in-ireland/">Coinbase Granted Virtual Asset Service Provider License in Ireland</a> was first posted on December 21, 2022 at 3:59 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MATIC Price Analysis: Polygon Shares Upcoming Expectations for 2023, How Will MATIC Price React Going Forward?</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/matic-price-analysis-polygon-shares-upcoming-expectations-for-2023-how-will-matic-price-react-going-forward/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATIC/USD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATIC/USD Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon (MATIC)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63601</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Polygon forged partnerships with some of the world&#8217;s biggest companies to build on its platform in 2022 778,000 smart contracts deployed on the Polygon network Polygon anticipates a massive year for DeFi in 2023 2022 was Polygon’s breakout year. Polygon forged partnerships with some of the world&#8217;s biggest companies to build on its platform. 778,000 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/matic-price-analysis-polygon-shares-upcoming-expectations-for-2023-how-will-matic-price-react-going-forward/">MATIC Price Analysis: Polygon Shares Upcoming Expectations for 2023, How Will MATIC Price React Going Forward?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/matic-price-analysis-polygon-shares-upcoming-expectations-for-2023-how-will-matic-price-react-going-forward/">MATIC Price Analysis: Polygon Shares Upcoming Expectations for 2023, How Will MATIC Price React Going Forward?</a> was first posted on December 20, 2022 at 7:55 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li>Polygon forged partnerships with some of the world&#8217;s biggest companies to build on its platform in 2022</li>
<li>778,000 smart contracts deployed on the Polygon network</li>
<li>Polygon anticipates a massive year for DeFi in 2023</li>
</ul>
<p>2022 was Polygon’s breakout year. <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/matic-price-analysis-matic-up-8-amid-positive-news-polygon-sees-major-integration-with-the-graph-network/">Polygon</a> forged partnerships with some of the world&#8217;s biggest companies to build on its platform. 778,000 smart contracts deployed on the Polygon network. Polygon shares upcoming expectations for 2023 as it says it looks forward to delivering future-proof innovation with ZK solutions. It also anticipates a massive year for DeFi in 2023 while it hopes to support its builders and more in 2023 and beyond. Acentrik, a strategic initiative by Mercedes-Benz, is also building a decentralized data marketplace that will make it easy for enterprises to share and monetize data across domains. In the past week, Bermuda-based Jewel Bank announced it was issuing a fully backed stablecoin Jewel USD (JUSD) which would be accessed through the Polygon network. The blockchain will be used for JUSD transactions, and the bank will leverage the Polygon ecosystem for future commercial and retail stablecoin-based payment solutions. At the time of publication, MATIC was changing hands at $0.800, up 1.80% in the last 24 hours.<br /><br /><strong>Key Levels</strong><br />Resistance Levels: $1.300, $1.150, $1.000<br />Support Levels: $0.750, $0.500, $0.350</p>
<h4>MATIC/USD Daily Chart: Ranging</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1436" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-63615 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD-4-Daily-Dec-21.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD-4-Daily-Dec-21.png 1436w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD-4-Daily-Dec-21-300x144.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD-4-Daily-Dec-21-1024x491.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD-4-Daily-Dec-21-768x368.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD-4-Daily-Dec-21-750x359.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD-4-Daily-Dec-21-1140x546.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1436px) 100vw, 1436px" /><em><span style="color: #999999">MATIC/USD Daily Chart</span></em></h6>
<p>The<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/matic-price-analysis-matic-prepares-for-next-move-polygon-based-projects-unlock-web3-onboarding-for-india/"> MATIC/USD</a> daily chart shows a recovery from the previous day&#8217;s low of $0.757 to an intraday high of $0.803. The first significant resistance level around the daily moving average MA 50 at $0.900 would probably cap any advance, barring a sustained cryptocurrency rally. Above here is the second important resistance level at $1.00<br /><br />The bulls will attempt to push the price over $0.900 if the price moves upward from present levels and crosses the $0.800 threshold. On the other hand, the bears are currently trying to keep the price below its $0.800 level. If they are successful, a previously-used buyer congestion zone between $0.700 and $0.800 is seen. Also, the MATIC/USD pair could test the MA 50 close in a subsequent rebound.</p>
<h4>MATIC/USD 4-Hour Chart: Bearish</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1436" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-63616 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD-4-Hour-Dec-21.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD-4-Hour-Dec-21.png 1436w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD-4-Hour-Dec-21-300x144.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD-4-Hour-Dec-21-1024x491.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD-4-Hour-Dec-21-768x368.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD-4-Hour-Dec-21-750x359.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD-4-Hour-Dec-21-1140x546.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1436px) 100vw, 1436px" /><span style="color: #999999">MATIC/USD 4-Hour Chart</span></h6>
<p>After losing both moving averages MA 50 and MA 200, MATIC is relying on the horizontal support level at $0.757 to hold. MATIC may decline as far as $0.700 if the support at $0.757 fails. The RSI is attempting to move past its middle means that the bulls will defeat the bears. On the other hand, the MA 50 resistance ceiling may restrict further price movement, delaying the bulls.<br /><br />Polygon (MATIC) might be propelled over significant obstacles at $0.850 and $0.900 with a breakout above the MA 50 closing at $0.950. Only when it trades above $0.870 around the MA 200 is the MATIC/USD pair bullish; significant resistance is located at the $0.850 and $0.900 levels.</p>
<p><strong>Note:</strong><em> Kryptomoney.com is not a financial advisor. Do your research before investing your funds in any financial asset or presented product or event. We are not responsible for your investing results</em></p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/matic-price-analysis-polygon-shares-upcoming-expectations-for-2023-how-will-matic-price-react-going-forward/">MATIC Price Analysis: Polygon Shares Upcoming Expectations for 2023, How Will MATIC Price React Going Forward?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/matic-price-analysis-polygon-shares-upcoming-expectations-for-2023-how-will-matic-price-react-going-forward/">MATIC Price Analysis: Polygon Shares Upcoming Expectations for 2023, How Will MATIC Price React Going Forward?</a> was first posted on December 20, 2022 at 7:55 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum and Visa to Work Together to Advance Crypto Development</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/ethereum-and-visa-to-work-together-to-advance-crypto-development/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 22:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto payments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[visa]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63606</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The world&#8217;s largest payment company, Visa, released a document on Monday outlining potential future automatic payment collaborations with the Ethereum network. Account abstraction, a method developed by Visa to enable automated programmable payments on the Ethereum network, makes use of smart contracts. According to reports from CoinDesk, Visa&#8217;s proposal would entail developing a smart contract [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/ethereum-and-visa-to-work-together-to-advance-crypto-development/">Ethereum and Visa to Work Together to Advance Crypto Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ethereum-and-visa-to-work-together-to-advance-crypto-development/">Ethereum and Visa to Work Together to Advance Crypto Development</a> was first posted on December 20, 2022 at 5:00 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The world&#8217;s largest payment company, <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/visa-plans-to-release-its-cryptocurrency-wallet/">Visa</a>, released a document on Monday outlining potential future automatic payment collaborations with the Ethereum network.<br /><br />Account abstraction, a <a href="https://usa.visa.com/solutions/crypto/auto-payments-for-self-custodial-wallets.html">method developed</a> by Visa to enable automated programmable payments on the Ethereum network, makes use of smart contracts. According to reports from CoinDesk, Visa&#8217;s proposal would entail developing a smart contract that would serve as an intermediary between user accounts and a contract account and would enable the creation of a self-custodial wallet capable of making automatic and recurring payments without requiring user involvement. Visa advised that the feature be implemented on the Ethereum layer 2 network StarkNet and further stated that such a solution would enable recurring payments to be performed exclusively using blockchain networks. The Ethereum mainnet does not currently support these capabilities.<br /><br />Although cryptocurrency auto-payments won&#8217;t necessarily have the biggest influence on banking and payments, they do show that major payment companies like Visa are committed to taking an active role in the crypto field. In a conversation in the news, Visa&#8217;s Head of CBDC and Protocols stated:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>&#8220;We want to have an opportunity to actively contribute to technical developments happening in the crypto ecosystem. The best way to do that is learning by doing—actually getting deeper into Web3 infrastructures and blockchain protocols, areas I think are going to be really important for payments&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Visa has some experience in the cryptocurrency world. Recently, Blockchain.com announced the introduction of a <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-visa-cards-in-canada-what-you-need-to-know/">pre-paid Visa card</a> focused on cryptocurrencies, each of which is connected to a verified Blockchain.com Wallet account. Customers utilizing these cards will be able to make online purchases of tangible products and services from U.S. retailers that accept Visa using their crypto or fiat balances.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/ethereum-and-visa-to-work-together-to-advance-crypto-development/">Ethereum and Visa to Work Together to Advance Crypto Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ethereum-and-visa-to-work-together-to-advance-crypto-development/">Ethereum and Visa to Work Together to Advance Crypto Development</a> was first posted on December 20, 2022 at 5:00 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Indonesian Exchange Tokyocrypto Now Acquired by Binance</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/indonesian-exchange-tokyocrypto-now-acquired-by-binance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 21:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tokyocrypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63597</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance is utilizing the current market conditions to enter the Asian market. On December 19, Binance announced that it had taken a majority stake in the Indonesian cryptocurrency exchange Tokocrypto. Pang Xue Kai, the company&#8217;s founder, and outgoing CEO had resigned, and Binance had since appointed a new CEO. To conduct business lawfully in Indonesia, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/indonesian-exchange-tokyocrypto-now-acquired-by-binance/">Indonesian Exchange Tokyocrypto Now Acquired by Binance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/indonesian-exchange-tokyocrypto-now-acquired-by-binance/">Indonesian Exchange Tokyocrypto Now Acquired by Binance</a> was first posted on December 20, 2022 at 4:19 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-us-to-acquire-voyager-digital-assets/">Binance</a> is utilizing the current market conditions to enter the Asian market. On December 19, Binance announced that it had taken a majority stake in the Indonesian cryptocurrency exchange Tokocrypto. Pang Xue Kai, the company&#8217;s founder, and outgoing CEO had resigned, and Binance had since appointed a new CEO.<br /><br />To conduct business lawfully in Indonesia, according to <a href="https://www.cnbcindonesia.com/tech/20221219165022-37-398232/binance-caplok-tokocrypto-tunjuk-ceo-baru">CNBC Indonesia</a>, Binance intends to gradually purchase all of Tokocrypto&#8217;s shares. The exchange has all necessary licenses from the Commodity Futures Trading Regulatory Agency (BAPPEBTI).<br /><br />It is important to note that Binance has a long and strong partnership with the Indonesian exchange and has been investing in Tokocrypto since 2020.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>“Tokocrypto came from our idea more than four years ago, and I am very proud to see every growth, achievement, and contribution that the company has made to advance Indonesia’s digital economy.”</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Pang Xue Kai continued by saying that this choice was &#8220;carefully&#8221; made with the exchange&#8217;s future in mind to take advantage of all the potential possibilities Binance has to offer and create a second physical trading platform for crypto assets.<br /><br />The crew at Tokocrypto had to be reduced, but interim CEO Yudhono Rawis emphasized that it was the best move to do to combat the difficult macroeconomic circumstances that were affecting the worldwide market.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>“It is regrettable that we have had to reduce the size of the company to ensure we remain in a good position to cope with the uncertain macroeconomic conditions and we extend our sincerest apologies to the affected employees.”</p>
</blockquote>
<p>By acquiring additional cryptocurrency exchanges, Binance is expanding into the Asian market and avoiding the time-consuming licensing procedures that have recently become more stringent as a result of the failure of numerous cryptocurrency exchanges and investment funds, including Three Arrows Capital, Voyager Digital, FTX, and Alameda Research, among many others.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/indonesian-exchange-tokyocrypto-now-acquired-by-binance/">Indonesian Exchange Tokyocrypto Now Acquired by Binance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/indonesian-exchange-tokyocrypto-now-acquired-by-binance/">Indonesian Exchange Tokyocrypto Now Acquired by Binance</a> was first posted on December 20, 2022 at 4:19 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DOGE Price Analysis: Dogecoin Down 8% as Unusual Pattern Shows Up on Chart</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/doge-price-analysis-dogecoin-down-8-as-unusual-pattern-shows-up-on-chart/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 11:29:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE/USD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE/USD Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63583</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The price of Dogecoin declined over 9% on Monday DOGE is down 8.22% in the past 24 hours at $0.074 Dogecoin is establishing the &#8220;Here We Go Round the Mulberry Bush&#8221; chart pattern, according to veteran trader Peter Brandt The price of Dogecoin declined over 8% on Monday after Tesla CEO Elon Musk asked Twitter [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/doge-price-analysis-dogecoin-down-8-as-unusual-pattern-shows-up-on-chart/">DOGE Price Analysis: Dogecoin Down 8% as Unusual Pattern Shows Up on Chart</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/doge-price-analysis-dogecoin-down-8-as-unusual-pattern-shows-up-on-chart/">DOGE Price Analysis: Dogecoin Down 8% as Unusual Pattern Shows Up on Chart</a> was first posted on December 20, 2022 at 6:29 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li>The price of Dogecoin declined over 9% on Monday</li>
<li>DOGE is down 8.22% in the past 24 hours at $0.074</li>
<li>Dogecoin is establishing the <em>&#8220;Here We Go Round the Mulberry Bush&#8221;</em> chart pattern, according to veteran trader Peter Brandt</li>
</ul>
<p>The price of <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/doge-price-analysis-dogecoin-dips-10-onchain-data-shows-dogecoin-pumps-often-reliable-reflection-of-crowd-euphoria/">Dogecoin</a> declined over 8% on Monday after Tesla CEO Elon Musk asked Twitter users whether he should continue to run the social media platform. At the time of publication, DOGE was down 8.22% in the past 24 hours and 18.22% since the past week at $0.074. Dogecoin is establishing the<em> &#8220;Here We Go Round the Mulberry Bush&#8221;</em> chart pattern, according to veteran trader Peter Brandt. The pattern&#8217;s unusual name is a reference to a popular English nursery rhyme for youngsters. It is designed to be sung while youngsters dance around in a circle. The lyrics depict a bunch of youngsters moving around a mulberry bush doing various tasks, such as collecting water and washing clothes. Brandt appears to be implying that Dogecoin is currently undergoing a <em>&#8220;round trip,&#8221;</em> which means that price gains are being followed by losses. The metaphor here is bringing up the fact that DOGE is incapable of advancing as it keeps spinning in circles.<br /><br /><strong>Key Levels</strong><br />Resistance Levels: $0.1100, $0.0922, $0.0750<br />Support Levels: $0.0654, $0.0550, $0.0500</p>
<h4>DOGE/USD Daily Chart: Ranging</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1436" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-63602 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD-Daily-Dec-20.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD-Daily-Dec-20.png 1436w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD-Daily-Dec-20-300x144.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD-Daily-Dec-20-1024x491.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD-Daily-Dec-20-768x368.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD-Daily-Dec-20-750x359.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD-Daily-Dec-20-1140x546.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1436px) 100vw, 1436px" /><em><span style="color: #999999">DOGE/USD Daily Chart</span></em></h6>
<p>After hitting a low earlier this week, the <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/dogecoin-is-witnessing-a-selloff-after-an-impressive-rise-in-late-october/">DOGE/USD</a> pair is currently down but slightly higher. The price of the pair increased to an intraday high of $0.0754 after falling to a low of $0.0700 in the previous session. The rally is being driven by a desire to hold onto recent gains. After the RSI retreated towards the oversold zone, buyers saw the retracement as a chance to purchase the dip.<br /><br />Even the most bullish analyst expectations haven&#8217;t been met due to the massive loss, which started the month around the $0.1068 mark. The daily chart&#8217;s slight rebound suggests that the surge might be gaining momentum. Once momentum returns, the next target would be above $0.1000 and the recent high of $0.1589.</p>
<h4>DOGE/USD 4-Hour Chart: Bearish</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1436" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-63603 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD-Daily-Dec-20-1.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD-Daily-Dec-20-1.png 1436w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD-Daily-Dec-20-1-300x144.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD-Daily-Dec-20-1-1024x491.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD-Daily-Dec-20-1-768x368.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD-Daily-Dec-20-1-750x359.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD-Daily-Dec-20-1-1140x546.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1436px) 100vw, 1436px" /><span style="color: #999999">DOGE/USD 4-Hour Chart</span></h6>
<p>The 4-hour DOGE rise has slowed below the short-term moving average (MA 50). Although the recent climb to an intraday high of $0.0746 has placed the bears on the defensive. After the relative strength index revealed overextension, intraday traders profited. The present consolidation could provide the bulls with an opportunity to reorganize and catch their breath.<br /><br />The demand zone at $0.0700 is a critical support level for the rebound. On the upside, the nearest resistance is $0.0750, followed by the moving average (MA 50). And its breach might spark a further rise toward the all-time high of $0.1000. A close above the near-term resistance level of $0.0800 might indicate that sentiment favors higher prices in the immediate run.</p>
<p><strong>Note:</strong><em> Kryptomoney.com is not a financial advisor. Do your research before investing your funds in any financial asset or presented product or event. We are not responsible for your investing results</em></p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/doge-price-analysis-dogecoin-down-8-as-unusual-pattern-shows-up-on-chart/">DOGE Price Analysis: Dogecoin Down 8% as Unusual Pattern Shows Up on Chart</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/doge-price-analysis-dogecoin-down-8-as-unusual-pattern-shows-up-on-chart/">DOGE Price Analysis: Dogecoin Down 8% as Unusual Pattern Shows Up on Chart</a> was first posted on December 20, 2022 at 6:29 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Edward Snowden To Accept Bitcoin as CEO of Twitter</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/edward-snowden-to-accept-bitcoin-as-ceo-of-twitter/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 22:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63593</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new drama is developing around Twitter as Elon Musk prepares to consider some new candidates for that crucial position and is seriously considering stepping down as the platform&#8217;s CEO. Many people, including Edward Snowden, have expressed their readiness to assume responsibility and their willingness to accept payment in Bitcoin. I take payment in Bitcoin. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/edward-snowden-to-accept-bitcoin-as-ceo-of-twitter/">Edward Snowden To Accept Bitcoin as CEO of Twitter</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/edward-snowden-to-accept-bitcoin-as-ceo-of-twitter/">Edward Snowden To Accept Bitcoin as CEO of Twitter</a> was first posted on December 19, 2022 at 5:07 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A new drama is developing around Twitter as <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/dogecoin-jumps-8-as-elon-musk-renews-bid-to-buy-twitter-bitcoin-and-altcoins-rebound-on-this-potential-catalyst/">Elon Musk</a> prepares to consider some new candidates for that crucial position and is seriously considering stepping down as the platform&#8217;s CEO. Many people, including <a href="https://twitter.com/Snowden/status/1604628658852970496">Edward Snowden</a>, have expressed their readiness to assume responsibility and their willingness to accept payment in Bitcoin.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">I take payment in Bitcoin. <a href="https://t.co/wW0Qa9NxWi">https://t.co/wW0Qa9NxWi</a></p>
— Edward Snowden (@Snowden) <a href="https://twitter.com/Snowden/status/1604628658852970496?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 19, 2022</a></blockquote>
<p>Elon Musk expressed a desire to hand over the reins of one of the biggest social media platforms in the world to someone else who is committed enough to do so, but the well-known security expert and Bitcoin and cryptocurrency enthusiast responded. Snowden is not only prepared to take over as CEO but is also open to receiving bitcoin in exchange for his services.<br /><br />In the past, Snowden has said a lot of things about Bitcoin and the cryptocurrency market as a whole. He has never acknowledged accepting Bitcoin in exchange for his services, though. In the comments section below Snowden&#8217;s statement, some users made fun of the fact that Elon Musk does not particularly enjoy remote work, even though for Snowden, given his complicated relationship with the U.S. government, that is his only option.<br /><br />Snowden predicted the cryptocurrency market and the market as a whole back in November, urging his subscribers to start using safe DEX. Decentralized trading platforms saw a sharp increase in user traffic after the<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-begins-its-proof-of-reserves-after-ftx-collapse/"> collapse of FTX</a> because, in theory, they are nothing more than sophisticated networks of interconnected wallets and addresses. Sadly, Musk is unlikely to give Snowden the CEO position and will probably select a different heir. Regarding the suggestion he made a few hours ago, Snowden has not yet made any further remarks.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/edward-snowden-to-accept-bitcoin-as-ceo-of-twitter/">Edward Snowden To Accept Bitcoin as CEO of Twitter</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/edward-snowden-to-accept-bitcoin-as-ceo-of-twitter/">Edward Snowden To Accept Bitcoin as CEO of Twitter</a> was first posted on December 19, 2022 at 5:07 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>