<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title/>
	<atom:link href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 07:21:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3</generator>
	<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><itunes:subtitle/><itunes:category text="News &amp; Politics"/><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Business News"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Investing"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Tech News"/></itunes:category><item>
		<title>Benefits of Online Casino Betting</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/benefits-of-online-casino-betting/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/benefits-of-online-casino-betting/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 07:21:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sponsored]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online betting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Casino]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online casino free credit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online gambling Singapore]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65555</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Online casino betting is a popular way to place bets on your favorite games. It involves betting on a specific outcome in a game and, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/benefits-of-online-casino-betting/">Benefits of Online Casino Betting</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/benefits-of-online-casino-betting/">Benefits of Online Casino Betting</a> was first posted on August 16, 2023 at 7:21 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Online casino betting is a popular way to place bets on your favorite games. It involves betting on a specific outcome in a game and, with luck and strategy, can lead to big wins. Most online casinos offer free play options, so you can try out different </span><a href="https://www.ace969.com/sg/en-us/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">online gambling Singapore</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> games before committing any real money. This gives you an idea of how much you can win and how fun the games are to play. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The best online casinos are those that allow players to play in their own currency, accept major credit cards and e-wallets like PayPal, and offer secure encryption for player data. Some also have live chat and phone support. The best sites also have high payout percentages and are licensed and regulated. They should also have an extensive library of games and a good reputation among players. </span></p>
<h2>Benefits of Online Casino Betting That Every Player Should Know</h2>
<ol>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>Convenience</strong>: One of the biggest advantages of online betting sites is the convenience that they offer. Users can place bets from anywhere at any time using an internet-connected device, such as a computer or mobile phone. This eliminates the need to travel to a physical location, such as a casino or sportsbook, saving users time and money.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">
<p></span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>Better Odds</strong>: Another advantage of online betting sites is that they often offer better odds than traditional brick-and-mortar establishments. This is because online sites have lower overhead costs, which allows them to offer more favorable odds to users. Additionally, users can shop around and compare odds from different sites to find the best value for their bets.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">
<p></span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>Wide Selection of Games and Sports</strong>: Online betting sites typically offer a much wider selection of games and sports to bet on than traditional establishments. Users can choose from a variety of sports, such as football, basketball, and tennis, as well as a wide range of casino games, such as slots, blackjack, and roulette. This allows users to find the games and sports that they are most interested in and to try out new games without having to travel to a physical location.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">
<p></span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>Bonuses and Promotions</strong>: Many online betting sites offer bonuses and promotions to users, such as free bets, </span><a href="https://www.atebits.com/what-is-casino-credit/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">online casino free credit</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, deposit bonuses, and cashback offers. These promotions can help users to get more value for their bets and to try out new games without having to risk their own money.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">
<p></span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>Live Betting and Streaming</strong>: Online betting sites often offer live betting and streaming options, which allow users to place bets in real-time and to watch the action unfold live. This adds an extra layer of excitement to the betting experience and allows users to stay up-to-date with the latest scores and results.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">
<p></span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>Safety and Security</strong>: Online betting sites use advanced encryption and security measures to protect users&#8217; personal and financial information. This ensures that users can gamble online with peace of mind, knowing that their information is safe and secure.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">
<p></span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>Flexibility and Control</strong>: Online betting sites allow users to have more flexibility and control over their bets. Users can place bets of any size, from small wagers to large bets, and can choose from a variety of different betting options, such as point spreads, moneylines, and over/under bets.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">
<p></span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>Access to Information and Statistics</strong>: <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/is-crypto-betting-safe/">Online betting</a> sites often provide users with access to a wealth of information and statistics about different sports and games. This can help users to make more informed betting decisions and to increase their chances of winning.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">
<p></span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>Social Interaction</strong>: Online betting sites often have social features, such as chat rooms and forums, which allow users to interact with each other and share tips and advice. This can help users to feel more connected to the betting community and to learn from other users&#8217; experiences and strategies.</span></li>
</ol>
<h2>Verdict</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Online gambling is a growing industry with a huge variety of games and betting options. These include online poker, bingo, and lottery games as well as a range of casino and sports bets. There are even a number of mobile apps available to make the process of gambling on the go easier and more convenient. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Unlike traditional brick-and-mortar casinos, online casinos are able to offer more games and bonuses. Some are even completely virtual, allowing you to play your favorite games from the comfort of your own home. While they may not be as exciting as the real thing, these websites can still provide a great gambling experience. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you want to try your hand at a new casino game, it is recommended that you start off small and gradually increase your stakes as your confidence grows. This will help you avoid over-betting and losing too much money. Another tip is to stick with games that you enjoy. For example, if you enjoy spinning reels, try playing slot games. If you prefer betting on numbers, try out a game of roulette. And if you love playing cards, then try out an online baccarat game. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In Michigan, there are a number of reputable online casinos and sportsbooks available to residents. The largest Michigan casino operator, Rivers Casino, runs a sportsbook and an online casino under the BetRivers brand. This company is a subsidiary of Chicago-based Rush Street Interactive, which also operates the PlaySugarHouse online casino in New Jersey and Pennsylvania.</span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/benefits-of-online-casino-betting/">Benefits of Online Casino Betting</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/benefits-of-online-casino-betting/">Benefits of Online Casino Betting</a> was first posted on August 16, 2023 at 7:21 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/benefits-of-online-casino-betting/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>First Spot Bitcoin ETF Goes Live in Europe</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/first-spot-bitcoin-etf-goes-live-in-europe/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/first-spot-bitcoin-etf-goes-live-in-europe/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 21:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BItcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Europe]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65552</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a landscape dominated by US SEC rejections and delays for spot Bitcoin ETF applications, a breakthrough has emerged on the European front. The Jacobi [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/first-spot-bitcoin-etf-goes-live-in-europe/">First Spot Bitcoin ETF Goes Live in Europe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/first-spot-bitcoin-etf-goes-live-in-europe/">First Spot Bitcoin ETF Goes Live in Europe</a> was first posted on August 15, 2023 at 9:10 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a landscape dominated by US SEC rejections and delays for <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-spot-etfs-would-be-extremely-lucrative-according-to-bloomberg-expert/">spot Bitcoin ETF</a> applications, a breakthrough has emerged on the European front. The Jacobi FT Wilshire Bitcoin ETF, a pioneering product compliant with SFDR Article 8 via its innovative decarbonization strategy, has made its debut.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230815404630/en/Jacobi-Asset-Management-lists-Europe">announcement</a>, dated August 15, reveals that Jacobi Asset Management and Wilshire Indexes have joined forces to create this groundbreaking spot Bitcoin ETF. Trading under the ticker BCOIN, the ETF has already secured a listing on Euronext Amsterdam.</p>
<p>Notably, Jacobi has introduced a verifiable built-in Renewable Energy Certificate (REC) solution, a strategic move that enables institutional investors to access Bitcoin&#8217;s benefits while aligning with environmental, social, and governance (ESG) objectives.</p>
<p>Regulated by the Guernsey Financial Services Commission (GFSC), the ETF boasts a robust ecosystem of key players. Fidelity Digital Assets is the custodian, Flow Traders undertakes the role of market maker, and Authorized Participants include Jane Street and DRW.</p>
<p>Mark Makepeace, CEO of Wilshire Indexes, expressed the significance of the Jacobi FT Wilshire Bitcoin ETF&#8217;s launch, characterizing it as a pivotal moment for the digital asset industry and a transformative step for the global financial sector. Wilshire Indexes, renowned for developing institutional-grade digital asset benchmarks, looks forward to driving the progress of the broader digital asset ecosystem through this partnership.</p>
<p>Although spot Bitcoin ETFs have been introduced in various countries, such as Brazil and Canada, the <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/us-sec-chairman-demands-strict-regulations-for-crypto-operations-across-the-country/">US SEC</a> remains steadfast in rejecting all similar applications. However, the dynamics may shift soon, following the mid-June filing by BlackRock, the world&#8217;s largest asset manager, for a spot Bitcoin ETF.</p>
<p>In a realm where regulatory dynamics are both fluid and pivotal, the emergence of the Jacobi FT Wilshire Bitcoin ETF underscores the growing global interest in facilitating cryptocurrency access through regulated and environmentally conscious financial products.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/first-spot-bitcoin-etf-goes-live-in-europe/">First Spot Bitcoin ETF Goes Live in Europe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/first-spot-bitcoin-etf-goes-live-in-europe/">First Spot Bitcoin ETF Goes Live in Europe</a> was first posted on August 15, 2023 at 9:10 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/first-spot-bitcoin-etf-goes-live-in-europe/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Shines on Gemini After Massive Price Jump</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/xrp-shines-on-gemini-after-massive-price-jump/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/xrp-shines-on-gemini-after-massive-price-jump/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 20:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP (XRP)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65547</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Promising news emerges for traders invested in XRP as cryptocurrency market data provider Kaiko reveals positive developments regarding the cryptocurrency&#8217;s market dynamics on the Gemini [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/xrp-shines-on-gemini-after-massive-price-jump/">XRP Shines on Gemini After Massive Price Jump</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/xrp-shines-on-gemini-after-massive-price-jump/">XRP Shines on Gemini After Massive Price Jump</a> was first posted on August 15, 2023 at 8:16 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Promising news emerges for traders invested in <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/xrp-price-analysis-xrp-outperforms-top-ten-in-gains-xrp-investment-products-see-inflows-amid-positive-lawsuit-clarity/">XRP</a> as cryptocurrency market data provider <a href="https://twitter.com/KaikoData/status/1691442869586829312">Kaiko</a> reveals positive developments regarding the cryptocurrency&#8217;s market dynamics on the <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/gemini-launches-global-platform-amidst-us-regulatory-challenges/">Gemini exchange</a>. The crucial aspect of market depth, defined as a market&#8217;s ability to absorb substantial orders without significantly impacting the asset&#8217;s price, has been restored for XRP on the Gemini platform.<br /><br />The recent announcement by Gemini of its XRP listing has added to the growing list of exchanges that have reintroduced XRP to their trading offerings. This development was followed by a notable surge in XRP&#8217;s valuation on the Gemini exchange, briefly propelling the token&#8217;s price to an impressive $50. However, this surge was short-lived, as prices swiftly normalized, aligning with spot market prices across other exchanges.<br /><br />The initial spike in XRP&#8217;s value on Gemini was potentially attributed to low liquidity during the hours following the token&#8217;s relisting. The sudden price increase could have been triggered by a sizeable market order, which found limited available offers at that time, causing the order to be executed at an unusually high price point.<br /><br />Crypto analyst <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1689929018143903744">Ali</a> suggests that the market depth drop could have played a role in this scenario. Notably, the market depth for XRP on Gemini was observed to be so shallow that a relatively small order of $37,000 could prompt a 2% price movement.<br /><br />Kaiko, shedding further light on the situation, tweeted that XRP&#8217;s 1% market depth experienced a temporary decline on Gemini due to market makers pulling back in response to the rapid price spike to $50. However, this setback has since been rectified, bringing reassurance to traders. The cryptocurrency data provider&#8217;s update assures traders that XRP&#8217;s market depth has rebounded and achieved a more stable state.<br /><br />In a parallel positive development, Gemini has introduced the &#8220;XRP faucet,&#8221; an initiative involving the daily distribution of 4,000 XRP starting at 3 p.m. EST and continuing until August 18, 11:59 p.m. ET. This endeavor is expected to further engage the XRP community and expand its participation on the Gemini platform.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/xrp-shines-on-gemini-after-massive-price-jump/">XRP Shines on Gemini After Massive Price Jump</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/xrp-shines-on-gemini-after-massive-price-jump/">XRP Shines on Gemini After Massive Price Jump</a> was first posted on August 15, 2023 at 8:16 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/xrp-shines-on-gemini-after-massive-price-jump/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trump’s Crypto Stash Worth Up to Half a Million ETH</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/trumps-crypto-stash-worth-up-to-half-a-million-eth/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/trumps-crypto-stash-worth-up-to-half-a-million-eth/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 22:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[donald trump]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65543</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Donald Trump&#8217;s most recent public financial disclosure has revealed his ownership of Ethereum (ETH), valued between $250,000 and $500,000. The 2023 Office of Government Ethics [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/trumps-crypto-stash-worth-up-to-half-a-million-eth/">Trump’s Crypto Stash Worth Up to Half a Million ETH</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/trumps-crypto-stash-worth-up-to-half-a-million-eth/">Trump’s Crypto Stash Worth Up to Half a Million ETH</a> was first posted on August 13, 2023 at 10:45 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Donald Trump&#8217;s most recent public <a href="https://www.documentcloud.org/documents/23876912-donald-trump-oge-public-financial-disclosure-report-2023-part-1">financial disclosure</a> has revealed his ownership of Ethereum (ETH), valued between $250,000 and $500,000.<br /><br />The 2023 Office of Government Ethics (OGE) financial disclosure documents, recently made public, contain an entry labeled &#8220;Cryptocurrency Wallet (Ethereum),&#8221; with the former President estimating its value to be within the $250,000 to $500,000 range.<br /><br />This cryptocurrency wallet likely corresponds to the <a href="https://twitter.com/BotRalgo/status/1690350249100070914?s=20">proceeds</a> from the sale of non-fungible tokens (NFTs) that Trump launched in December 2022 after leaving the White House. The NFT collection, consisting of 44,000 limited edition digital trading cards depicting the former President in various costumes and poses, was sold out within a day.<br /><br />Reports suggest that Trump&#8217;s venture into <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/nfts-diminish-as-sales-decline-to-lowest-levels-in-a-year/">NFTs</a> generated over $8.9 million in sales, with approximately $298,000 earned in licensing fees. These earnings were collected through the same crypto wallet under the Trump entity, CIC Digital, which also received the licensing fees.<br /><br />Former first lady Melania Trump also briefly engaged with NFTs, converting several iconic images from NASA&#8217;s Apollo moon landings into digital artworks that sold for $75 each. However, the endeavor faced criticism from NASA, which contended that the project violated the space agency&#8217;s merchandise regulations.<br /><br />Interestingly, Trump&#8217;s ownership of cryptocurrency marks a shift from his prior skepticism. In 2019, he expressed his disapproval of <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-btc-sets-new-record-highs-of-35868-fundamental-indicators-reveal-something-quite-significant/">Bitcoin (BTC)</a>, stating that he was &#8220;not a fan&#8221; of it, deeming it &#8220;not money&#8221; and asserting that its value was based on &#8220;thin air.&#8221; During his re-election campaign in 2021, Trump reiterated his stance, referring to cryptocurrencies as &#8220;fake.&#8221;<br /><br />This new disclosure of Ethereum ownership suggests a more nuanced relationship with the crypto space for the former President.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/trumps-crypto-stash-worth-up-to-half-a-million-eth/">Trump’s Crypto Stash Worth Up to Half a Million ETH</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/trumps-crypto-stash-worth-up-to-half-a-million-eth/">Trump’s Crypto Stash Worth Up to Half a Million ETH</a> was first posted on August 13, 2023 at 10:45 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/trumps-crypto-stash-worth-up-to-half-a-million-eth/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Singapore Red Cross Opens Up to Donations in Cryptos</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/singapore-red-cross-opens-up-to-donations-in-cryptos/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/singapore-red-cross-opens-up-to-donations-in-cryptos/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 22:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Singapore]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65538</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Singapore Red Cross, a charitable organization dedicated to humanitarian aid and community services, has opened up the option for people to donate using digital currencies, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/singapore-red-cross-opens-up-to-donations-in-cryptos/">Singapore Red Cross Opens Up to Donations in Cryptos</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/singapore-red-cross-opens-up-to-donations-in-cryptos/">Singapore Red Cross Opens Up to Donations in Cryptos</a> was first posted on August 13, 2023 at 10:31 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Singapore Red Cross, a charitable organization dedicated to humanitarian aid and community services, has opened up the option for people to donate using digital currencies, forging a partnership with the crypto payment gateway Triple-A.<br /><br />Through this collaboration, individuals can now contribute to the<a href="https://redcross.sg/news-stories/stories/1292-coin-a-new-way-to-give.html"> charity</a>&#8216;s cause through donations in digital currencies. Donors can specify an amount in fiat currency, which will then be automatically converted into the chosen cryptocurrency. The organization has enabled the acceptance of major digital assets by market capitalization, including Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), USDT and USDC.<br /><br />Singapore Red Cross clarified that it does not favor any specific cryptocurrency and is open to receiving any of the aforementioned digital currencies.<br /><br />However, it&#8217;s important to note that contributions made in this manner are not currently eligible for tax deductions. Those seeking tax benefits should consider making their donations through credit card payments.<br /><br />The organization emphasized that each cryptocurrency donation will be directed towards its humanitarian efforts, focusing on enhancing the well-being of various marginalized groups, including children, isolated seniors, individuals with disabilities, and disadvantaged families.<br /><br />The initiative was summed up with the phrase, &#8220;Coin a new way to give today, your support will go a long way.&#8221;<br /><br />This move by Singapore Red Cross follows in the footsteps of other charitable organizations that have embraced cryptocurrency donations. <br /><br />For instance, in October 2021, the Nicklaus Children’s Hospital Foundation, a non-profit based in Florida, began accepting donations in various cryptocurrencies such as BTC, ETH, BCH, LTC, and DOGE.<br /><br />Similarly, renowned organizations like Susan G. Komen and the National Children’s Advocacy Center have also ventured into accepting cryptocurrency donations. The <a href="https://www.nationalcac.org/crypto-give/">former partnered</a> with The Giving Rock to facilitate contributions in over 50 cryptocurrencies, while the latter, located in Huntsville, Alabama, became the first non-profit in the area to embrace such donations in November 2022. Donors to these organizations who opt for cryptocurrency donations can also avail of tax benefits.<br /><br />Hannah Alderson, the Crypto-project Coordinator, highlighted the positive impact of these contributions, explaining that they translate into tangible benefits such as therapy hours for children, parenting classes, medical examinations, hope, healing, and justice for children who have suffered from neglect or abuse.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/singapore-red-cross-opens-up-to-donations-in-cryptos/">Singapore Red Cross Opens Up to Donations in Cryptos</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/singapore-red-cross-opens-up-to-donations-in-cryptos/">Singapore Red Cross Opens Up to Donations in Cryptos</a> was first posted on August 13, 2023 at 10:31 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/singapore-red-cross-opens-up-to-donations-in-cryptos/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PayPal’s Stablecoin Launch Face Hurdles, Bank of America</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/paypals-stablecoin-launch-face-hurdles-bank-of-america/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/paypals-stablecoin-launch-face-hurdles-bank-of-america/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 22:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65534</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>According to insights from Bank of America Corp, PayPal Holdings Inc.&#8217;s introduction of a stablecoin is expected to enhance payment efficiencies and the customer experience, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/paypals-stablecoin-launch-face-hurdles-bank-of-america/">PayPal&#8217;s Stablecoin Launch Face Hurdles, Bank of America</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/paypals-stablecoin-launch-face-hurdles-bank-of-america/">PayPal&#8217;s Stablecoin Launch Face Hurdles, Bank of America</a> was first posted on August 12, 2023 at 10:50 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>According to insights from Bank of America Corp, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-08-11/paypal-s-pypl-stablecoin-entree-faces-headwinds-bank-of-america-says?utm_medium=social&amp;utm_source=twitter&amp;utm_content=crypto&amp;utm_campaign=socialflow-organic">PayPal</a> Holdings Inc.&#8217;s introduction of a stablecoin is expected to enhance payment efficiencies and the customer experience, even though initial adoption may not be substantial. The bank points to factors such as the absence of compatibility with crypto wallets, trading pairs on exchanges, and new features as hindrances to quick adoption.<br /><br />Bank of America&#8217;s strategists Alkesh Shah and Andrew Moss mentioned in a recent note that in the longer term, PayPal&#8217;s PYUSD stablecoin might face challenges in gaining traction due to increasing competition from central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) and yield-bearing stablecoins.<br /><br />The strategists observed that while investors may have been content with non-yield-bearing stablecoins when interest rates were low, the attractiveness of yield-bearing stablecoins is likely to grow with short-term rates above 5%. They referred to stablecoins like USDT and USDC issued by Tether and Circle Internet Financial.<br /><br />PayPal <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/paypal-sees-record-high-crypto-deposits-reaching-943m/">recently</a> made headlines by announcing the launch of its stablecoin, PayPal USD, which is backed by Paxos Trust Co. and is fully collateralized by dollar deposits, short-term Treasuries, and similar assets. The token is pegged to the US dollar and will be gradually rolled out to PayPal customers in the US.<br /><br />Bank of America acknowledged that the payments giant&#8217;s entry into the stablecoin arena could potentially boost the adoption of digital tokens for payments, especially after the setbacks faced by the crypto industry in 2022. The bank emphasized that investors are generally concerned with the safety and accessibility of stablecoins on major trading platforms.<br /><br />The strategists, however, expressed that they do not anticipate the launch of PYUSD to lead to swift regulatory clarity, as the issuance of this stablecoin doesn&#8217;t significantly impact systemic risk in traditional markets. They noted that while the launch may not alter systemic risk, it might encounter regulatory challenges if non-banks are prohibited from issuing stablecoins.<br /><br />Despite <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/stablecoin-face-supply-crunch-amid-rising-adoption/">stablecoins</a> having existed for nearly a decade, their use has largely been confined to traders moving digital assets between exchanges. The total value of stablecoins in circulation is estimated at around $126 billion, with Tether&#8217;s USDT being the largest by far.<br /><br />While PayPal is not the first company to venture into stablecoin creation, its launch comes after a high-profile attempt by Meta Platforms Inc., which faced regulatory hurdles and eventually faltered. Even PayPal temporarily halted its PYUSD project in response to heightened regulatory scrutiny.<br />Maxine Waters, a prominent Democrat and vocal critic of Meta&#8217;s project criticized PayPal&#8217;s launch for not having sufficient regulatory oversight.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/paypals-stablecoin-launch-face-hurdles-bank-of-america/">PayPal&#8217;s Stablecoin Launch Face Hurdles, Bank of America</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/paypals-stablecoin-launch-face-hurdles-bank-of-america/">PayPal&#8217;s Stablecoin Launch Face Hurdles, Bank of America</a> was first posted on August 12, 2023 at 10:50 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/paypals-stablecoin-launch-face-hurdles-bank-of-america/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hong Kong SEC Makes Crypto-Friendly Move</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/hong-kong-sec-makes-crypto-friendly-move/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/hong-kong-sec-makes-crypto-friendly-move/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 21:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hong Kong]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65530</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Hong Kong Virtual Asset Exchange (HKVAX), a platform with a focus on providing services like securities token offerings and various cryptocurrency-related solutions, has attained [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/hong-kong-sec-makes-crypto-friendly-move/">Hong Kong SEC Makes Crypto-Friendly Move</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/hong-kong-sec-makes-crypto-friendly-move/">Hong Kong SEC Makes Crypto-Friendly Move</a> was first posted on August 12, 2023 at 9:50 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The Hong Kong Virtual Asset Exchange (<a href="https://www.hkvax.com/news/detail?diffId=1673250247927656448">HKVAX</a>), a platform with a focus on providing services like securities token offerings and various cryptocurrency-related solutions, has attained preliminary approval from the Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) to operate under the country&#8217;s securities regulations.<br /><br />The SFC has granted HKVAX preliminary approval for conducting Type 1 and Type 7 regulated activities. These designations enable the platform to engage in activities related to securities trading and the provision of automated trading services, catering to both retail and institutional investors.<br /><br />In a recent announcement, HKVAX highlighted the significance of this accomplishment. The platform expressed its intent to offer a diverse range of products, encompassing services such as over-the-counter (OTC) brokerage, a high-caliber exchange platform, and a <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/hong-kong-updates-new-guidelines-for-crypto-exchange-platforms/">custody</a> solution backed by insurance coverage.<br /><br />Anthony Ng, the CEO and co-founder of HKVAX, underlined the importance of this regulatory approval as a crucial step for the platform. Ng articulated the platform&#8217;s strategy to not only expand its product offerings within the Hong Kong market but also collaborate with strategic investors for upcoming funding rounds.<br /><br />It is worth noting that HKVAX is not alone in receiving approval from the SFC. On August 3rd, HashKey and OSL achieved a significant milestone by becoming the first exchanges in Hong Kong to secure the necessary licenses for providing cryptocurrency trading services.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/hong-kong-sec-makes-crypto-friendly-move/">Hong Kong SEC Makes Crypto-Friendly Move</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/hong-kong-sec-makes-crypto-friendly-move/">Hong Kong SEC Makes Crypto-Friendly Move</a> was first posted on August 12, 2023 at 9:50 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/hong-kong-sec-makes-crypto-friendly-move/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kraken Surpasses Coinbase As Top US Exchange for Altcoins in July, Data Reveals</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/kraken-surpasses-coinbase-as-top-us-exchange-for-altcoins-in-july-data-reveals/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/kraken-surpasses-coinbase-as-top-us-exchange-for-altcoins-in-july-data-reveals/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:38:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kraken]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65514</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Kraken, a cryptocurrency trading platform, has overtaken its competitor Coinbase to claim the top spot as the most liquid exchange for altcoins in the United [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/kraken-surpasses-coinbase-as-top-us-exchange-for-altcoins-in-july-data-reveals/">Kraken Surpasses Coinbase As Top US Exchange for Altcoins in July, Data Reveals</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/kraken-surpasses-coinbase-as-top-us-exchange-for-altcoins-in-july-data-reveals/">Kraken Surpasses Coinbase As Top US Exchange for Altcoins in July, Data Reveals</a> was first posted on August 12, 2023 at 6:38 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/kraken-pushes-back-on-irs-treasure-hunt-for-crypto-user-information/">Kraken</a>, a cryptocurrency trading platform, has overtaken its competitor Coinbase to claim the<a href="https://twitter.com/DessislavaIane2/status/1689301335760363521?s=20"> top spot</a> as the most liquid exchange for altcoins in the United States for July.<br /><br />Dessislava Laneva, a research analyst at crypto data platform Kaiko, shared in a <a href="https://twitter.com/DessislavaIane2/status/1689301335760363521?s=20">tweet</a> that Kraken had secured a substantial 47% market depth for the top 10 altcoins by the close of July. This is a significant shift from January 2023, when Kraken held just 39% of the market depth for altcoins, and Coinbase led with 45%. Meanwhile, Binance.US, the U.S. branch of the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange Binance, held a 7% market share, with a combined 9% among six other platforms.<br /><br />However, a comprehensive analysis conducted by researchers at Kaiko unveiled that Kraken&#8217;s market share has surged to 47%, positioning <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/coinbase-posts-impressive-22-revenue-jump-in-q1-but-reports-79m-loss/">Coinbase</a> at 41%, Binance.US at 1%, and the remaining exchanges at 10%. This transition signifies that Kraken now possesses a greater capacity to absorb substantial market orders without causing significant fluctuations in the altcoin&#8217;s price.<br /><br />In addition to its expanding market depth, Kraken&#8217;s prominence among platforms facilitating USD deposits has also observed notable growth. The exchange&#8217;s share in the EUR spot market has risen from 35% to an impressive 53%. Furthermore, Kraken&#8217;s AUD spot market has witnessed an astounding sixfold increase over the past months.<br /><br />While Kraken enjoys considerable advancement in its digital asset market share, Coinbase has grappled with regulatory obstacles in recent times, potentially leading to a decrease in its trading volumes. The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission took legal action against Coinbase in early June, levying multiple allegations, including unregistered broker operations, securities exchange activities, and clearing agency functions.<br /><br />Brian Armstrong, CEO of Coinbase, recently disclosed that the Commission had mandated the suspension of trading in all altcoins due to their classification as securities, thus violating federal regulations.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/kraken-surpasses-coinbase-as-top-us-exchange-for-altcoins-in-july-data-reveals/">Kraken Surpasses Coinbase As Top US Exchange for Altcoins in July, Data Reveals</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/kraken-surpasses-coinbase-as-top-us-exchange-for-altcoins-in-july-data-reveals/">Kraken Surpasses Coinbase As Top US Exchange for Altcoins in July, Data Reveals</a> was first posted on August 12, 2023 at 6:38 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/kraken-surpasses-coinbase-as-top-us-exchange-for-altcoins-in-july-data-reveals/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why VC Spectra is Winning Over Arbitrum and Monero Investors: The Prospects of 900% ROI</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/why-vc-spectra-is-winning-over-arbitrum-and-monero-investors-the-prospects-of-900-roi/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/why-vc-spectra-is-winning-over-arbitrum-and-monero-investors-the-prospects-of-900-roi/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 09:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VC Spectra (SPCT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65526</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking for a robust network that democratizes access to blockchain and technology projects? Enter VC Spectra (SPCT), a new decentralized asset management protocol offering early [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/why-vc-spectra-is-winning-over-arbitrum-and-monero-investors-the-prospects-of-900-roi/">Why VC Spectra is Winning Over Arbitrum and Monero Investors: The Prospects of 900% ROI</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/why-vc-spectra-is-winning-over-arbitrum-and-monero-investors-the-prospects-of-900-roi/">Why VC Spectra is Winning Over Arbitrum and Monero Investors: The Prospects of 900% ROI</a> was first posted on August 11, 2023 at 9:16 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p align="left">Looking for a robust network that democratizes access to blockchain and technology projects? Enter VC Spectra (SPCT), a new decentralized asset management protocol offering early investors a 900% ROI once it launches on exchanges. Although Arbitrum (ARB) and Monero (XMR) have initiated various system upgrades, VC Spectra (SPCT) blows them off the water, utilizing machine-learning algorithms for profitable trade execution. Discover why SPCT is winning over ARB and XMR.<u><b></b></u></p>
<h2 class="western">VC Spectra (SPCT): The New Sheriff In Town Redefining Blockchain</h2>
<p align="left"><a href="https://vcspectra.io/"><span style="color: #1155cc;"><u>VC Spectra (SPCT)</u></span></a> is the go-to decentralized hedge fund utilizing state-of-the-art technology to execute profitable trading decisions. The platform grants users voting rights, exclusive access to pre-ICOs and early-stage blockchain ventures.</p>
<p align="left">Moreover, VC Spectra&#8217;s native token (SPCT) is a BRC-20 standard token built on the Bitcoin blockchain. The token enables asset management, seamless exchange, and decentralized trading on the Spectra platform. SPCT implements a deflationary model with a burn mechanism that progressively reduces token supply, increasing VC Spectra (SPCT) value.</p>
<p align="left">Through strict risk management principles, VC Spectra (SPCT) strategically allocates 40% of its funds to a carefully curated portfolio and another 40% to specific ICOs.As a user-centric platform, VC Spectra (SPCT) goes beyond buybacks and quarterly dividends linked to investment earnings.</p>
<p align="left">With Stage 2 of the public presale underway, SPCT is valued at $0.011, marking a 37.5% spike from its initial $0.008 price. SPCT is projected to skyrocket by 127.27% to $0.025 once the platform advances to Stage 3.</p>
<p align="left">Market forecasts paint a positive picture, with <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/spct-vs-doge-vs-bnb-future-of-high-returns/">VC Spectra (SPCT)</a> positioned to surge by 900% from its initial $0.008 price to $0.08 once it hits the exchanges. Grab your SPCT tokens today and enjoy a 25% bonus on any deposit.<u><b></b></u></p>
<h2 class="western">Arbitrum’s Evolution Continues: Spotlight on ARB’s the Cutting-Edge Improvements</h2>
<p align="left">Arbitrum Foundation has introduced its long-awaited inaugural grant initiative. Dubbed “Foundation Grants,” this program is dedicated to fostering the expansion of the Arbitrum (ARB) ecosystem by bestowing grants upon partner projects and extending support for educational initiatives.</p>
<p align="left">Each grant furnished via this initiative will follow a structure anchored in milestones and key performance indicators (KPIs), ensuring productive collaboration with chosen recipients to meet predefined objectives. The implementation of the Foundation Grant Program will occur in a series of distinct phases, each catering to applications from specific segments within the Arbitrum ecosystem. Moreover, the inaugural phase will prioritize the development of decentralized applications and infrastructure for both Arbitrum Nova and Arbitrum One.</p>
<p align="left">So, it’s no surprise Arbitrum (ARB) spiked by 4.4% over the past week, from $1.13 to $1.18. Driven by its focus on efficiency and sustainability, Arbitrum’s (ARB) price is expected to increase by 13.6%, from $1.18 to $1.34 in the coming weeks.</p>
<h2 class="western">Momentum Shift: Monero (XMR) Exhibits Promising Bullish Trend</h2>
<p align="left">Monero’s (XMR) price jumped by 2.03% over the past week, from $158.14 to $161.36. Experts point out that the rising demand for spot Bitcoin ETFs positively influenced Monero’s (XMR) price dynamics.</p>
<p align="left">Additionally, Monero&#8217;s (XMR) dynamic fee structure prevents fees from becoming excessively high, regardless of increasing usage. The blockchain operates without any set limits, ensuring flexibility and affordability.</p>
<p align="left">Furthermore, the global competition surrounding the development of CBDCs has further contributed to Monero’s (XMR) growing popularity. Monero’s (XMR) enhanced ring signatures also enable quick and secure validation of private transactions.</p>
<p align="left">As Monero (XMR) bolsters its network capabilities, experts say Monero’s (XMR) price can spike by 5.52%, from $161.36 to $170.27.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/why-vc-spectra-is-winning-over-arbitrum-and-monero-investors-the-prospects-of-900-roi/">Why VC Spectra is Winning Over Arbitrum and Monero Investors: The Prospects of 900% ROI</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/why-vc-spectra-is-winning-over-arbitrum-and-monero-investors-the-prospects-of-900-roi/">Why VC Spectra is Winning Over Arbitrum and Monero Investors: The Prospects of 900% ROI</a> was first posted on August 11, 2023 at 9:16 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/why-vc-spectra-is-winning-over-arbitrum-and-monero-investors-the-prospects-of-900-roi/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bittrex Agrees to $24 Million Settlement with SEC</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/bittrex-agrees-to-24-million-settlement-with-sec/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/bittrex-agrees-to-24-million-settlement-with-sec/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 22:19:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bittrex]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65524</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bankrupt cryptocurrency exchange Bittrex and its CEO have reached a settlement with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for a sum of $24 million. This [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bittrex-agrees-to-24-million-settlement-with-sec/">Bittrex Agrees to $24 Million Settlement with SEC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bittrex-agrees-to-24-million-settlement-with-sec/">Bittrex Agrees to $24 Million Settlement with SEC</a> was first posted on August 10, 2023 at 10:19 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bankrupt cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bittrex-announces-partnership-to-launch-new-crypto-platform-for-middle-east-and-north-africa/">Bittrex</a> and its CEO have reached a settlement with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for a sum of $24 million. This agreement comes after the SEC filed charges against the exchange in April for functioning as an unregistered trading platform.</p>
<p>In the court filing submitted on Thursday, neither the exchange nor its foreign affiliate, along with former CEO William Shihara, admitted or denied the allegations. Bittrex Global GmbH, the foreign affiliate, has also agreed to resolve the accusations, about its failure to register as a national securities exchange, according to an<a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2023-150"> official statement by the SEC</a>.</p>
<p>Gurbir S. Grewal, who heads the SEC&#8217;s enforcement division, emphasized that Bittrex had attempted to eliminate any indications that the token issuers&#8217; online statements were linked to investment contracts, to evade federal securities regulations. This attempt was ultimately unsuccessful, leading to the charges. Grewal noted that the settlement highlights the significance of the economic realities behind such offerings, rather than merely altering labels or descriptions.</p>
<p>William Shihara expressed contentment with the settlement outcome in an emailed statement, regarding it as a positive resolution. He stressed the importance of achieving a balance between fostering innovation, supporting entrepreneurs, and safeguarding consumers. Shihara hoped that this settlement could contribute to advancing these goals.</p>
<p>Bittrex had applied for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in May, disclosing estimated assets and liabilities ranging between $500 million and $1 billion. The company had already revealed plans to withdraw from the U.S. market in March. At its peak, Bittrex accounted for nearly 23% of USD support in the cryptocurrency exchange market during the initial months of 2018.</p>
<p>The SEC has taken a strong stance against unregistered crypto exchanges, as demonstrated by their legal actions against Bittrex and, more recently, Coinbase in June. SEC Chair Gary Gensler has consistently underscored the necessity for compliance within the cryptocurrency sector.</p>
<p>He has highlighted that while trading platforms deal with various crypto tokens, they often lack the established safeguards against fraud and manipulation that are present in traditional financial markets. Gensler reiterated this concern during an interview with Bloomberg last month.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bittrex-agrees-to-24-million-settlement-with-sec/">Bittrex Agrees to $24 Million Settlement with SEC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bittrex-agrees-to-24-million-settlement-with-sec/">Bittrex Agrees to $24 Million Settlement with SEC</a> was first posted on August 10, 2023 at 10:19 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/bittrex-agrees-to-24-million-settlement-with-sec/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bakkt Revenue Surges to $348 Million Despite Falling Trading Volume</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/bakkt-revenue-surges-to-348-million-despite-falling-trading-volume/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/bakkt-revenue-surges-to-348-million-despite-falling-trading-volume/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 21:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BAKKT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65522</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The digital asset platform Bakkt has revealed a remarkable surge in its total revenue for the second quarter of this year, reaching $348 million. This [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bakkt-revenue-surges-to-348-million-despite-falling-trading-volume/">Bakkt Revenue Surges to $348 Million Despite Falling Trading Volume</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bakkt-revenue-surges-to-348-million-despite-falling-trading-volume/">Bakkt Revenue Surges to $348 Million Despite Falling Trading Volume</a> was first posted on August 10, 2023 at 9:54 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The digital asset platform<a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bakkt-to-buy-apex-crypto-for-200-million/"> Bakkt</a> has revealed a remarkable surge in its total revenue for the second quarter of this year, reaching $348 million. This represents a significant leap from the $14 million recorded in the same quarter of the previous year, 2022.</p>
<p>A spokesperson for the company clarified that the current quarter&#8217;s revenue of $348 million is inclusive of gross revenue, adhering to Generally Accepted Accounting Principles (GAAP), while the $14 million reported last year was based on total revenue on a net basis.</p>
<p>Based in New York City, Bakkt attributed its impressive earnings to the acquisition of Apex Crypto in April. The substantial increase in gross crypto services revenue was primarily fueled by the trading activities of Apex Crypto. The company communicated this in an <a href="https://investors.bakkt.com/news/news-details/2023/Bakkt-Reports-Second-Quarter-2023-Results/default.aspx">official earnings statement</a>.</p>
<p>Gavin Michael, the CEO of Bakkt, underlined the significance of acquiring Apex Crypto at the start of the quarter. He stated, &#8220;The completion of our acquisition of Apex Crypto marked a pivotal moment for our company. We&#8217;ve been able to significantly expand our presence within the crypto ecosystem, achieving strong traction by engaging new clients.&#8221;</p>
<p>Apex Crypto has since been rebranded as Bakkt Crypto Solutions. Bakkt further<a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bakkt-set-to-launch-crypto-transaction-app-by-2020/"> bolstered</a> its client portfolio by bringing invstr, Swan Bitcoin, and Blockchain.com into the fold.</p>
<p>While Bakkt&#8217;s traded volume experienced a decline of 51%, amounting to $531 million, the number of transacting accounts also witnessed a 20% drop compared to the previous year. The company attributed these declines in trading to the prevailing &#8220;slowdown&#8221; within the crypto market.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, Bakkt noted a 3% increase in its assets under custody, which reached $660 million. This growth can be attributed to the elevated values of certain cryptocurrencies, as stated by Bakkt.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bakkt-revenue-surges-to-348-million-despite-falling-trading-volume/">Bakkt Revenue Surges to $348 Million Despite Falling Trading Volume</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bakkt-revenue-surges-to-348-million-despite-falling-trading-volume/">Bakkt Revenue Surges to $348 Million Despite Falling Trading Volume</a> was first posted on August 10, 2023 at 9:54 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/bakkt-revenue-surges-to-348-million-despite-falling-trading-volume/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stablecoins Face Supply Crunch Amid Rising Adoption</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/stablecoin-face-supply-crunch-amid-rising-adoption/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/stablecoin-face-supply-crunch-amid-rising-adoption/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 22:48:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stablecoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65518</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Amid the widely applauded launch of a stablecoin by PayPal this week, signaling the entrance of a prominent American payment giant into the blockchain arena, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/stablecoin-face-supply-crunch-amid-rising-adoption/">Stablecoins Face Supply Crunch Amid Rising Adoption</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/stablecoin-face-supply-crunch-amid-rising-adoption/">Stablecoins Face Supply Crunch Amid Rising Adoption</a> was first posted on August 9, 2023 at 10:48 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Amid the widely applauded launch of a stablecoin by <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/paypal-sees-record-high-crypto-deposits-reaching-943m/">PayPal</a> this week, signaling the entrance of a prominent American payment giant into the blockchain arena, the overall supply of this asset category has experienced a prolonged decline spanning more than a year.</p>
<p>Recent <a href="https://www.federalreserve.gov/supervisionreg/srletters/SR2308.htm#:~:text=To%20obtain%20a%20written%20notification,of%20its%20activities%2C%20and%20the">data</a> underscores a steady reduction in the aggregate supply of stablecoins since the midpoint of 2022. The trajectory continued into 2023, witnessing a decline of approximately 12%. The total supply dwindled from $139 billion at the outset of the year to $122 billion by August.</p>
<p>Market analysts are now anticipating a potential reversal of this downturn, particularly given PayPal&#8217;s newfound involvement in the sector. The belief is that PayPal&#8217;s active engagement could validate the utility of stablecoins, not only elucidating their functional value but also compelling traditional financial institutions to embrace these digital assets due to competitive pressures. Mark Lurie, CEO of Shipyard Software, expressed this sentiment, emphasizing that if PayPal effectively demonstrates the practical application of stablecoins, it could trigger a significant wave of adoption.</p>
<p>Concurrently, regulatory frameworks seem to be positioning themselves to accommodate an expansion in<a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/stablecoin-issuer-tethers-q1-profits-surge-to-1-5-billion/"> stablecoin</a> utilization. In a communiqué directed at state member banks with interest in &#8220;issuing, holding, or transacting in dollar tokens to facilitate payments,&#8221; the U.S. Federal Reserve stipulated the necessity for banks to establish robust protocols to manage liquidity and mitigate the risks of illicit financial activities.</p>
<p>The central bank has taken a proactive stance, unveiling the &#8220;Novel Activities Supervision Program&#8221; to bolster oversight over banks engaged in stablecoin activities. This program encompasses a comprehensive supervision enhancement across all financial institutions under its purview. The focus is extended to include cryptocurrency, distributed ledger technology, and novel partnerships between nonbank entities and financial service providers, aimed at delivering technologically-driven financial solutions to consumers.</p>
<p>Simultaneously, the UK Treasury has joined this regulatory trend. They have <a href="https://assets.publishing.service.gov.uk/government/uploads/system/uploads/attachment_data/file/1176540/Payments_Regulation_and_the_Systemic_Perimeter_-_Consultation_Response.pdf">released</a> a consultation response detailing updated propositions for a regulatory framework overseeing systemic stablecoins. The framework delineates the collaborative supervisory approach between the Bank of England and the Financial Conduct Authority, orchestrating stablecoin issuance and usage oversight in tandem.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/stablecoin-face-supply-crunch-amid-rising-adoption/">Stablecoins Face Supply Crunch Amid Rising Adoption</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/stablecoin-face-supply-crunch-amid-rising-adoption/">Stablecoins Face Supply Crunch Amid Rising Adoption</a> was first posted on August 9, 2023 at 10:48 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/stablecoin-face-supply-crunch-amid-rising-adoption/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			<enclosure length="502962" type="application/pdf" url="https://assets.publishing.service.gov.uk/government/uploads/system/uploads/attachment_data/file/1176540/Payments_Regulation_and_the_Systemic_Perimeter_-_Consultation_Response.pdf"/><itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><itunes:subtitle>Amid the widely applauded launch of a stablecoin by PayPal this week, signaling the entrance of a prominent American payment giant into the blockchain arena, [&amp;#8230;] The post Stablecoins Face Supply Crunch Amid Rising Adoption appeared first on . Stablecoins Face Supply Crunch Amid Rising Adoption was first posted on August 9, 2023 at 10:48 pm. &amp;copy;2023 &amp;quot;Kryptomoney&amp;quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at susanta@brishti.in</itunes:subtitle><itunes:summary>Amid the widely applauded launch of a stablecoin by PayPal this week, signaling the entrance of a prominent American payment giant into the blockchain arena, [&amp;#8230;] The post Stablecoins Face Supply Crunch Amid Rising Adoption appeared first on . Stablecoins Face Supply Crunch Amid Rising Adoption was first posted on August 9, 2023 at 10:48 pm. &amp;copy;2023 &amp;quot;Kryptomoney&amp;quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at susanta@brishti.in</itunes:summary><itunes:keywords>News, BUSD, stablecoins, Tether, USDC</itunes:keywords></item>
		<item>
		<title>Aptos Strikes Partnership With Microsoft, Price Soar 10%</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/aptos-strikes-partnership-with-microsoft-price-soar-10/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/aptos-strikes-partnership-with-microsoft-price-soar-10/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 21:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aptos (APT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MICROSOFT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65496</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Aptos (APT) is experiencing a significant surge in bullish momentum today, prompted by the exciting news of its recent collaboration with the esteemed American multinational [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/aptos-strikes-partnership-with-microsoft-price-soar-10/">Aptos Strikes Partnership With Microsoft, Price Soar 10%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/aptos-strikes-partnership-with-microsoft-price-soar-10/">Aptos Strikes Partnership With Microsoft, Price Soar 10%</a> was first posted on August 9, 2023 at 9:31 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/aptos-apt-400-gains-in-january-traced-to-crazy-buying-in-korean-communities-aave-v3-deploys-on-ethereum/">Aptos (APT)</a> is experiencing a significant surge in bullish momentum today, prompted by the exciting news of its recent collaboration with the esteemed American multinational technology behemoth, Microsoft Incorporated. The protocol&#8217;s announcement of this partnership has generated enthusiasm within the broader digital currency landscape. This strategic alliance will encompass ventures into asset tokenization solutions, an intensified focus on digital payments and the exploration of Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs).<br /><br />The Microsoft<a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/08/09/microsoft-aptos-blockchain-ai-web3/?guccounter=1&amp;guce_referrer=aHR0cHM6Ly91LnRvZGF5Lw&amp;guce_referrer_sig=AQAAAByZ9n9jNE4Pxt2_1vNbUTNhI9wiRN-PstU8a2YClet5gPYN1fsN5lSnN8duuS2EWMfLFLct5jXKDxly_sTHi9pCISgUWDTYKiKBLLMgowlEjtCbQojHpKtFPkkyANbWhR9mOOhjzogJnTmW_f3p31hDn5wOSGsbCjekqfldcjcS"> partnership</a> illuminates a constellation of promising growth indicators for Aptos. The project has consistently achieved remarkable milestones since its inception in the past year. With Microsoft&#8217;s involvement, Aptos is set to solidify its status as a Layer 1 blockchain, extending its influence beyond the boundaries of the Web 3.0 ecosystem into the expansive realm of technology at large.<br /><br />By the terms of the Aptos-Microsoft collaboration, Aptos will leverage the capabilities of Microsoft Azure OpenAI services to enhance its offerings comprehensively. In a joint statement issued by both entities, it was emphasized that the diverse array of services from both organizations will be advantageous for Aptos&#8217; &#8220;developers in their endeavors to construct intelligent contracts and decentralized applications.&#8221;<br /><br />This announcement catalyzed a 10% increase in the<a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/aptos/"> price of Aptos (APT)</a>, reaching $7.52 per coin. Despite the prevailing volatility within the cryptocurrency sphere, the recent surge has repositioned APT as a standout contender among high-potential tokens.<br /><br />The strategic agreement between <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/aptos-apt-400-gains-in-january-traced-to-crazy-buying-in-korean-communities-aave-v3-deploys-on-ethereum/">Aptos</a> and Microsoft has been met with applause from stakeholders within the digital currency ecosystem. However, it also underscores a broader trend evident among emerging Web 3.0 protocols. Much like Aptos, Ankr Protocol has solidified a parallel partnership with Microsoft over the past year.<br /><br />Notably, other prominent tech giants, such as Google and Amazon, are similarly intensifying their engagement with the blockchain domain through collaborations with burgeoning Web 3.0 protocols. These partnerships collectively reinforce the notion that blockchain and traditional technology frameworks can harmoniously coexist.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/aptos-strikes-partnership-with-microsoft-price-soar-10/">Aptos Strikes Partnership With Microsoft, Price Soar 10%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/aptos-strikes-partnership-with-microsoft-price-soar-10/">Aptos Strikes Partnership With Microsoft, Price Soar 10%</a> was first posted on August 9, 2023 at 9:31 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/aptos-strikes-partnership-with-microsoft-price-soar-10/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Google Bard’s Golden Trio: VC Spectra (SPCT), Ethereum (ETH), and Optimism (OP) Tipped as 2023’s Investment Powerhouses</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/google-bards-golden-trio-vc-spectra-spct-ethereum-eth-and-optimism-op-tipped-as-2023s-investment-powerhouses/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/google-bards-golden-trio-vc-spectra-spct-ethereum-eth-and-optimism-op-tipped-as-2023s-investment-powerhouses/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 05:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VC Spectra (SPCT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65508</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>While Ethereum (ETH) records a pessimistic outlook, Optimism (OP) and VC Spectra (SPCT) have been building traction over the past weeks. Their performance has prompted [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/google-bards-golden-trio-vc-spectra-spct-ethereum-eth-and-optimism-op-tipped-as-2023s-investment-powerhouses/">Google Bard&#8217;s Golden Trio: VC Spectra (SPCT), Ethereum (ETH), and Optimism (OP) Tipped as 2023&#8217;s Investment Powerhouses</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/google-bards-golden-trio-vc-spectra-spct-ethereum-eth-and-optimism-op-tipped-as-2023s-investment-powerhouses/">Google Bard&#8217;s Golden Trio: VC Spectra (SPCT), Ethereum (ETH), and Optimism (OP) Tipped as 2023&#8217;s Investment Powerhouses</a> was first posted on August 9, 2023 at 5:42 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p align="left">While Ethereum (ETH) records a pessimistic outlook, Optimism (OP) and <span style="color: #1155cc;"><u>VC Spectra (SPCT)</u></span> have been building traction over the past weeks. Their performance has prompted the attention of market analysts and investors alike.</p>
<p align="left">However, though Ethereum (ETH) is currently having a significant price decline, experts suggest this is a perfect &#8220;bag the token&#8221; period as Ethereum (ETH) will yield maximum profits alongside well-performing tokens like VC Spectra (SPCT) and Optimism (OP).</p>
<h2 class="western">VC Spectra (SPCT) Inspires Investors&#8217; Interest With its Unique Feature</h2>
<p align="left"><a href="https://vcspectra.io/"><span style="color: #1155cc;"><u>VC Spectra (SPCT)</u></span></a> has attracted the interest of investors all over the world with its decentralized investment management platform. The VC Spectra (SPCT) platform offers a secure and all-inclusive investment solution with the potential for sustainable returns on investment (ROI) for its customers. The platform enables investments with high-profit potential and minimal risk in the blockchain and technology industries.</p>
<p align="left">VC Spectra (SPCT) is in Stage 2 of its public presale, selling at $0.011 per token. Despite still being in its presale, <span style="color: #1155cc;"><u>VC Spectra (SPCT)</u></span> is proving its profiting potential. During Stage 1 of its presale, VC Spectra (SPCT) was selling each token at $0.008. When it rose to its current price of $0.011, early investors made a 37.5% ROI! The existing thing is that this is not the final increase VC Spectra (SPCT) will make.</p>
<p align="left">The token has been predicted to hit $0.08 at the final stage of its presale. This guarantees investors who partake now a 627% ROI when the presale ends. Furthermore, <span style="color: #1155cc;"><u>VC Spectra&#8217;s (SPCT)</u></span> price increase during its presale is an insight into the price increases it will make when it is launched. The platform&#8217;s unique world utility guarantees it will be a formidable player in the crypto market.</p>
<h2 align="left">Ethereum&#8217;s (ETH) Current Decline Could Be a Perfect Buying Period</h2>
<p align="left">Over the past few weeks, Ethereum&#8217;s (ETH) price has been bouncing in an extremely sluggish spectrum, leaving investors unsure about the next move. The value of <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/ethereum-eth-braces-for-new-wave-of-volatility-data-shows/">Ethereum</a> (ETH) has dropped by 1.89% in the last seven days, falling from $1,870.21 on July 31, 2023, to $1,834.81 at the time of writing. Experts suggest this is a perfect buying period, as Ethereum (ETH) will experience a significant price rally in the coming months.</p>
<p align="left">Ethereum (ETH) is presently preparing for the impending Cancun-Deneb upgrade. Though no date has been selected, the event is expected to take place before the end of 2023. The update is intended to increase the scalability, security, and data storage of the Ethereum (ETH) network while cutting transaction costs.</p>
<p align="left">Furthermore, the highly anticipated EIP-4844 will occur alongside Ethereum&#8217;s (ETH) Dencun upgrade. Ethereum Improvement Proposal 4844 (EIP-4844) aims to significantly reduce transaction costs, which could unlock many new applications in Ethereum&#8217;s (ETH) ecosystem. An increase in network activity might send a spark to Ethereum (ETH), sending it into a price uproar. With this, Ethereum (ETH) could hit significant price levels before the end of 2023.</p>
<h2 class="western">Optimism (OP) Maintains Positive Outlook</h2>
<p align="left">The price of Optimism (OP) has increased by over 20% in recent weeks due to a combination of underlying solid reasons. One of these factors is Zora, a popular Web3 NFT minting platform, which is now connected to the Optimism (OP) network. Optimism&#8217;s (OP) affiliation with Zora has helped its stand out among layer-2 competitors, experiencing a <b>47% increase in daily transactions</b> since July 20, 2023.</p>
<p align="left">Furthermore, Optimism (OP) has issued its first Fault Proof, which is essential for allowing protocol decentralization. This has further expanded Optimism&#8217;s (OP) reach, enabling more activities in its ecosystem. These events have helped Optimism (OP) build and maintain a bullish momentum over the past weeks.</p>
<p align="left">Optimism (OP) has seen a <b>7% </b>increase since the month began, rising from $1.58 on August 1, 2023, to $1.70 at the time of writing. Based on Optimism&#8217;s (OP) previous price movements and Bitcoin&#8217;s halving cycles, market analysts predict that Optimism (OP) will continue on its uptrend, reaching the $2 price level by September 2023.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/google-bards-golden-trio-vc-spectra-spct-ethereum-eth-and-optimism-op-tipped-as-2023s-investment-powerhouses/">Google Bard&#8217;s Golden Trio: VC Spectra (SPCT), Ethereum (ETH), and Optimism (OP) Tipped as 2023&#8217;s Investment Powerhouses</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/google-bards-golden-trio-vc-spectra-spct-ethereum-eth-and-optimism-op-tipped-as-2023s-investment-powerhouses/">Google Bard&#8217;s Golden Trio: VC Spectra (SPCT), Ethereum (ETH), and Optimism (OP) Tipped as 2023&#8217;s Investment Powerhouses</a> was first posted on August 9, 2023 at 5:42 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/google-bards-golden-trio-vc-spectra-spct-ethereum-eth-and-optimism-op-tipped-as-2023s-investment-powerhouses/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Transforms Carbon Market with New Alliance</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/ripple-transforms-carbon-market-with-new-alliance/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/ripple-transforms-carbon-market-with-new-alliance/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 09:44:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65506</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple, a pioneer in blockchain technology, has initiated a far-reaching endeavor to infuse carbon markets with transparency, trustworthiness, and ethical standards. Historically, carbon markets, which [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/ripple-transforms-carbon-market-with-new-alliance/">Ripple Transforms Carbon Market with New Alliance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/ripple-transforms-carbon-market-with-new-alliance/">Ripple Transforms Carbon Market with New Alliance</a> was first posted on August 8, 2023 at 9:44 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/ripple-ceo-states-the-company-is-mostly-recruiting-abroad/">Ripple</a>, a pioneer in blockchain technology, has<a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230807853646/en/Centigrade-Announces-New-Open-Data-Platform-to-Restore-Trust-in-Carbon-Markets"> initiated</a> a far-reaching endeavor to infuse carbon markets with transparency, trustworthiness, and ethical standards.</p>
<p>Historically, carbon markets, which facilitate the trading of carbon credits to counterbalance CO2 emissions, have grappled with issues of opacity and doubt. Demonstrating its unwavering commitment to addressing climate change, Ripple committed a substantial $100 million investment towards this cause last year.</p>
<p>In a strategic collaboration with Centigrade, a technology provider focused on climate solutions, Ripple now seeks to elevate its efforts even further. Centigrade has launched an open data platform designed to cultivate faith in the global voluntary<a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/eco-friendly-bitcoin-mining/"> carbon markets</a>.</p>
<p>The platform&#8217;s primary objective is to offer top-notch data, streamlined accessibility, and heightened transparency, all working together to nurture an equitable, dynamic, and efficient carbon market. However, it&#8217;s important to note that this platform doesn&#8217;t serve as a trading or rating system; rather, its purpose lies in providing indispensable data to all stakeholders within the carbon credit ecosystem, encompassing sellers, buyers, and service providers.</p>
<p>This bold initiative by Ripple and Centigrade positions them as pivotal players in delivering a vital service to the carbon market. By making informed decisions possible for investors, the open data platform could potentially stimulate the availability of high-quality credits, thus ensuring the smooth operation of both carbon and nature markets.</p>
<p>This undertaking stands as a core component of Ripple&#8217;s comprehensive strategy to combat climate change. Having previously invested in the tokenization of carbon credits, Ripple persists in advocating for environmentally conscious practices within the realm of cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/ripple-transforms-carbon-market-with-new-alliance/">Ripple Transforms Carbon Market with New Alliance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/ripple-transforms-carbon-market-with-new-alliance/">Ripple Transforms Carbon Market with New Alliance</a> was first posted on August 8, 2023 at 9:44 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/ripple-transforms-carbon-market-with-new-alliance/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shocking Predictions: Top 3 Coins That Could Outperform Bitcoin This Year</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/shocking-predictions-top-3-coins-that-could-outperform-bitcoin-this-year/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/shocking-predictions-top-3-coins-that-could-outperform-bitcoin-this-year/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 04:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon (MATIC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UniSwap (UNI)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VC Spectra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VC Spectra (SPCT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65503</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In an epic turn of events, experts have named VC Spectra (SPCT), Uniswap (UNI), and Polygon (MATIC) the best investments to make in 2023. With [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/shocking-predictions-top-3-coins-that-could-outperform-bitcoin-this-year/">Shocking Predictions: Top 3 Coins That Could Outperform Bitcoin This Year</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/shocking-predictions-top-3-coins-that-could-outperform-bitcoin-this-year/">Shocking Predictions: Top 3 Coins That Could Outperform Bitcoin This Year</a> was first posted on August 8, 2023 at 4:08 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In an epic turn of events, experts have named VC Spectra (SPCT), Uniswap (UNI), and Polygon (MATIC) the best investments to make in 2023. With VC Spectra (SPCT) scoring high gains in its ongoing presale, investors remain hopeful that VC Spectra (SPCT) will outperform Bitcoin (BTC) this year.</p>
<p>What about Uniswap (UNI) and Polygon (MATIC)? Well, let’s find out!</p>
<h2>Unleashing the Future of Asset Management: VC Spectra (SPCT)</h2>
<p>Prepare to embark on an extraordinary journey into the realm of innovative asset management. <a href="https://vcspectra.io/">VC Spectra (SPCT)</a> is no ordinary platform; it&#8217;s a revolutionary force, <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/matic-price-analysis-matic-jumps-8-as-investment-manager-hamilton-lane-tokenizes-on-ploygon/">reshaping the investment landscape for investors</a> from all walks of life.</p>
<p>At the core of VC Spectra (SPCT) lies the power of Artificial Intelligence, a force that ensures the utmost security and transparency for your valuable assets.</p>
<p>But that&#8217;s not all – VC Spectra takes decentralization to a whole new level. Experience the thrill of exclusive voting rights, where your voice truly matters. The traditional approach to investment management is a thing of the past; VC Spectra (SPCT) empowers you to actively participate in shaping your financial future.</p>
<p>VC Spectra has garnered tremendous interest<strong>.</strong> The ongoing public presale has been a beacon of hope for investors, attracting significant attention at every stage. Stage 2 gave a profit of 37.5% to Stage 1 investors and introduced a new price of $0.011.</p>
<p>Stage 3 plans to take things a bit further by introducing a 127.27% growth and <a href="https://vcspectra.io/">VC Spectra (SPCT)</a> price of $0.025.</p>
<p>VC Spectra&#8217;s enterprising goal is to reach a target price of $0.08 for its tokens, projecting an awe-inspiring 627% growth from the initial Stage 2 price.</p>
<h2>Uniswap (UNI) Just Rose Above Its Support Region: What’s Next?</h2>
<p>Uniswap (UNI) has been in the spotlight lately due to its recent price movements. After reaching an all-time high of $44.97 on May 3, 2021, the cryptocurrency experienced fluctuations but has since gained popularity among crypto investors.</p>
<p>Since June 20, 2023, the price of Uniswap (UNI) has been on a steady upward trend, showing no signs of decline. As of July 31, it stood at $6.50, a modest increase of 1.2% from its 24-hour high of $6.42. Notably, the trading volume spiked to $144.8 million, marking a significant 21.75% increase within 24 hours.</p>
<p>Analysts forecast that Uniswap&#8217;s (UNI) price will fluctuate between $6.15 and $6.98, with an average annual value of $6.41. Uniswap (UNI) is trading at $6.18 on August 4, reflecting a 6.61% decrease in the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>However, despite the rise in Uniswap&#8217;s (UNI) price, Uniswap v3&#8217;s performance declined. The trading volume for Ethereum (ETH) and Optimism (OP) networks decreased after reaching a peak in mid-July.</p>
<h2>Polygon’s (MATIC) Volley Of Losses: Time To Switch?</h2>
<p>Polygon (MATIC) has experienced a rollercoaster ride in its price over the past few weeks. On July 8, Polygon (MATIC) was trading at $0.67, but it quickly jumped to $0.84 on July 14, representing a 25.3% increase. However, the excitement was short-lived, falling by 11.9% to $0.74 on July 20 and dropping to $0.70 on July 26. As of August 2, Polygon (MATIC) is trading at $0.69.</p>
<p>This continuous drop surprised investors, especially considering the decrease in Ethereum&#8217;s network activity. Many had anticipated that Polygon (MATIC) would benefit from this situation and rally, but unfortunately, it disappointed by declining further.</p>
<p>As a result, bearish predictions suggest Polygon (MATIC) could fall by 34% to $0.45. On the other hand, some bullish analysts foresee a rebound in the altcoin sector by the end of the year, leading to an 18% rise in Polygon&#8217;s (MATIC) price to $0.82.</p>
<p>During these fluctuations, Polygon (MATIC) remains a topic of interest for investors, and its future performance will be closely monitored in the coming months.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/shocking-predictions-top-3-coins-that-could-outperform-bitcoin-this-year/">Shocking Predictions: Top 3 Coins That Could Outperform Bitcoin This Year</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/shocking-predictions-top-3-coins-that-could-outperform-bitcoin-this-year/">Shocking Predictions: Top 3 Coins That Could Outperform Bitcoin This Year</a> was first posted on August 8, 2023 at 4:08 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/shocking-predictions-top-3-coins-that-could-outperform-bitcoin-this-year/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>China Breaks Silence on Crypto Matters</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/china-breaks-silence-on-crypto-matters/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/china-breaks-silence-on-crypto-matters/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 22:28:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[China]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65492</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Chinese Communist Party has issued a strong warning to overseas telecommunications and network fraud groups, vowing to take decisive action against their illegal and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/china-breaks-silence-on-crypto-matters/">China Breaks Silence on Crypto Matters</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/china-breaks-silence-on-crypto-matters/">China Breaks Silence on Crypto Matters</a> was first posted on August 6, 2023 at 10:28 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The Chinese Communist Party has issued a strong warning to <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/indian-cryptocurrency-exchange-move-overseas-post-rbi-clampdown/">overseas</a> telecommunications and network fraud groups, vowing to take decisive action against their illegal and criminal activities. <br /><br />The party expressed concern that fraud groups are exploiting new technologies and formats, including Blockchain, metaverse, virtual currencies, and artificial intelligence, to deceive and harm people. In response, the party pledged to collaborate with relevant countries to dismantle electronic fraud centers and rescue victims trapped in these schemes.<br /><br />At a recent plenary meeting of the China Central Political and Legal Committee, the need for systematic management, rule of law, and management at the source was emphasized to prevent overseas telecommunications and network fraud, along with other illegal and criminal activities. <br /><br />The committee highlighted that fraud groups are using deceptive tactics, such as posing as<em> &#8220;high-paying recruiters,&#8221;</em> to lure and coerce innocent individuals into fraudulent activities, leading to a range of nefarious practices like violent detention and human trafficking that jeopardize people&#8217;s safety and property.<br /><br />To combat these threats effectively, the committee will examine the current law enforcement model and explore the establishment of a normalized cooperation mechanism to target overseas telecommunications and network fraud. The goal is to establish a strong, long-term deterrent against criminals while maintaining a friendly cooperative relationship between China and related countries.<br /><br />Additionally, the committee emphasized its commitment to strengthen oversight of new technologies and formats exploited by fraud groups to modernize their criminal tools. Notably, <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/indians-engage-in-international-purchases-using-bitcoins-amidst-tightening-regulations/">Blockchain</a> was specifically highlighted in the statement as a technology requiring increased vigilance.<br /><br />With these measures in place, the Chinese Communist Party aims to tackle the rising challenge of overseas telecom and network fraud effectively and safeguard its citizens from falling victim to these illegal activities.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/china-breaks-silence-on-crypto-matters/">China Breaks Silence on Crypto Matters</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/china-breaks-silence-on-crypto-matters/">China Breaks Silence on Crypto Matters</a> was first posted on August 6, 2023 at 10:28 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/china-breaks-silence-on-crypto-matters/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Block Sees Over 30% Increase in BTC Revenue in Q2</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/block-sees-over-30-increase-in-btc-revenue-in-q2/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/block-sees-over-30-increase-in-btc-revenue-in-q2/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 21:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Block]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Square]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65488</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Block, formerly known as Square and led by former Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey, has revealed impressive growth in its Bitcoin revenue for the second quarter [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/block-sees-over-30-increase-in-btc-revenue-in-q2/">Block Sees Over 30% Increase in BTC Revenue in Q2</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/block-sees-over-30-increase-in-btc-revenue-in-q2/">Block Sees Over 30% Increase in BTC Revenue in Q2</a> was first posted on August 6, 2023 at 9:54 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://block.xyz/">Block</a>, formerly known as Square and led by former Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey, has revealed impressive growth in its Bitcoin revenue for the second quarter of 2023. The payment technology firm reported that its Bitcoin revenue for this period reached approximately $2.39 billion, marking a substantial 34% increase compared to the figure reported in Q2 2022, which was nearly $1.8 billion.<br /><br />The surge in Bitcoin <a href="https://s29.q4cdn.com/628966176/files/doc_financials/2023/q2/2Q23_Block_Shareholder-Letter.pdf">revenue</a> can be attributed to the company&#8217;s mobile application, Cash App, which enables monetary transfers and has become a significant player on the crypto scene. Cash App&#8217;s BTC gross profit also showed promising growth, reaching $44 million, a 7% increase year-over-year.<br /><br />Block <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/SQ/?guccounter=1&amp;guce_referrer=aHR0cHM6Ly9jcnlwdG9wb3RhdG8uY29tLw&amp;guce_referrer_sig=AQAAANllAnch98Hs14joIJt0WW5y10L6DtcREFFOW98cufxp6Q3XAPV8OkOPQbH4XiQNNrqIHyJ_L7lrFw9RVS8tVrXAYa-XzbIw_sjtkBfEnv9YwZQO5nqrn9MXPmvb82YdZzfYg5gMXUqy-ndHaekiQ1a2w1yNHt2AolZdOlLLG2Mh">attributed</a> the year-over-year increase in Bitcoin revenue and gross profit to the higher quantity of Bitcoin sold to customers. However, this growth was partially offset by a decrease in the average market price of Bitcoin compared to the previous year.<br /><br />Despite the surge in <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-off-to-strong-q2-as-it-ends-q1-down-only-10/">Bitcoin</a> revenue, Block did not incur any Bitcoin impairment losses during the period. As of the end of June 2023, the company&#8217;s BTC investment was valued at $245 million. However, due to a slight price decrease in the following weeks, Block&#8217;s stash of 8,027 BTC is currently worth approximately $234 million.<br /><br />With this substantial BTC investment, Block has cemented its position as one of the top 10 largest corporate holders of Bitcoin, according to CoinGecko&#8217;s data. MicroStrategy holds the top job, having recently purchased an additional 420 BTC, bringing its total Bitcoin holdings to 152,800 BTC.<br /><br />In addition to the positive bitcoin revenue, Block&#8217;s overall financial results (excluding bitcoin revenue) were also encouraging. However, the company&#8217;s shares did not experience an immediate uptick, as SQ&#8217;s stock price closed at over $73 on August 3, but subsequently dipped by approximately 6% in after-hours trading.<br /><br />Block had previously reported a decline in bitcoin revenue, with $1.83 billion generated from Cash App in Q4 2022, an 8.5% decrease compared to the figures from Q4 2021. The company explained that this disappointing number was a result of the market crash that occurred last year, which dampened investor interest in the primary cryptocurrency.<br /><br />Despite the decrease in revenue at the time, Block&#8217;s overall financial results were favorable, leading to a 7% spike in its shares. The company&#8217;s strong performance in the crypto and financial sectors continues to attract investors&#8217; attention and interest.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/block-sees-over-30-increase-in-btc-revenue-in-q2/">Block Sees Over 30% Increase in BTC Revenue in Q2</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/block-sees-over-30-increase-in-btc-revenue-in-q2/">Block Sees Over 30% Increase in BTC Revenue in Q2</a> was first posted on August 6, 2023 at 9:54 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/block-sees-over-30-increase-in-btc-revenue-in-q2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			<enclosure length="6832652" type="application/pdf" url="https://s29.q4cdn.com/628966176/files/doc_financials/2023/q2/2Q23_Block_Shareholder-Letter.pdf"/><itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><itunes:subtitle>Block, formerly known as Square and led by former Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey, has revealed impressive growth in its Bitcoin revenue for the second quarter [&amp;#8230;] The post Block Sees Over 30% Increase in BTC Revenue in Q2 appeared first on . Block Sees Over 30% Increase in BTC Revenue in Q2 was first posted on August 6, 2023 at 9:54 pm. &amp;copy;2023 &amp;quot;Kryptomoney&amp;quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at susanta@brishti.in</itunes:subtitle><itunes:summary>Block, formerly known as Square and led by former Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey, has revealed impressive growth in its Bitcoin revenue for the second quarter [&amp;#8230;] The post Block Sees Over 30% Increase in BTC Revenue in Q2 appeared first on . Block Sees Over 30% Increase in BTC Revenue in Q2 was first posted on August 6, 2023 at 9:54 pm. &amp;copy;2023 &amp;quot;Kryptomoney&amp;quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at susanta@brishti.in</itunes:summary><itunes:keywords>News, Bitcoin (BTC), Block, Square</itunes:keywords></item>
		<item>
		<title>Tether Triumphs as US Court Dismisses Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/tether-triumphs-as-us-court-dismisses-lawsuit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/tether-triumphs-as-us-court-dismisses-lawsuit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 16:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65485</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tether and its sister company, Bitfinex, which are both owned by iFinex, have achieved a significant legal victory as a U.S. court has thrown out [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/tether-triumphs-as-us-court-dismisses-lawsuit/">Tether Triumphs as US Court Dismisses Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/tether-triumphs-as-us-court-dismisses-lawsuit/">Tether Triumphs as US Court Dismisses Lawsuit</a> was first posted on August 6, 2023 at 4:54 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/Tether_to/status/1687568481745510400">Tether</a> and its sister company, Bitfinex, which are both owned by iFinex, have achieved a significant legal victory as a U.S. court has thrown out a class-action lawsuit against them. Chief Judge Laura Taylor Swain of the U.S. District Court for the Southern District of New York ordered the complete dismissal of the lawsuit brought by Matthew Anderson and Shawn Dolifka against Tether and Bitfinex.<br /><br />The court ruled that the plaintiffs&#8217; complaint lacked plausible allegations of injury and failed to provide any evidence of diminished actual value for the USDT stablecoin.<br /><br />The lawsuit, initiated in December 2021, centered around allegations concerning Tether&#8217;s <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/tether-supply-increase-amidst-bitcoin-price-hike/">stablecoin</a> backing. However, the court&#8217;s recent decision to dismiss the case at an early stage suggests that the plaintiffs&#8217; claims lacked legal merit.<br /><br />In a similar vein, U.S. crypto exchange Coinbase also sought a dismissal of an SEC complaint against it, citing the recent Ripple ruling that determined XRP was not a security when traded on exchanges.<br /><br />Furthermore, Tether <a href="https://tether.to/en/tether-excess-reserves-increase-by-850m-to-reach-3-3b-as-leading-stablecoin-reveals-72-5b-overall-exposure-in-us-t-bills-and-unveils-energy-related-investments/">reported</a> in a BDO assurance opinion for the second quarter of 2023 that its excess reserves increased by $850 million. <br /><br />Excess reserves represent the company&#8217;s profits not distributed to shareholders, which Tether chose to maintain in addition to the 100% reserves backing all outstanding tokens.<br /><br />Tether noted in the report that its reserves are exceptionally liquid, with 85% of its investments held in cash and cash equivalents. During the period from April to June 2023, the company&#8217;s operational profits exceeded $1 billion, demonstrating a strong 30% quarter-over-quarter growth.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/tether-triumphs-as-us-court-dismisses-lawsuit/">Tether Triumphs as US Court Dismisses Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/tether-triumphs-as-us-court-dismisses-lawsuit/">Tether Triumphs as US Court Dismisses Lawsuit</a> was first posted on August 6, 2023 at 4:54 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/tether-triumphs-as-us-court-dismisses-lawsuit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlockFi Clears Major Hurdle in US Bankruptcy Court</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/blockfi-clears-major-hurdle-in-us-bankruptcy-court/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/blockfi-clears-major-hurdle-in-us-bankruptcy-court/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 16:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlockFI]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65475</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BlockFi, the bankrupt crypto lender, recently announced that the US Bankruptcy Court for the District of New Jersey has conditionally approved its disclosure statement. This [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/blockfi-clears-major-hurdle-in-us-bankruptcy-court/">BlockFi Clears Major Hurdle in US Bankruptcy Court</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/blockfi-clears-major-hurdle-in-us-bankruptcy-court/">BlockFi Clears Major Hurdle in US Bankruptcy Court</a> was first posted on August 6, 2023 at 4:26 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/blockfi-clears-regulatory-hurdle-to-repay-297m-to-specific-customers/">BlockFi</a>, the bankrupt crypto lender, recently announced that the US Bankruptcy Court for the District of New Jersey has conditionally approved its disclosure statement. This marks a significant step in BlockFi&#8217;s reorganization process, which has been underway for eight months since the company filed for relief under Chapter 11 of the United States Bankruptcy Code.<br /><br />In an <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230802310688/en/BlockFi%E2%80%99s-Disclosure-Statement-Conditionally-Approved-by-Court">official statement</a> on August 2nd, Mark Renzi, BlockFi&#8217;s Chief Restructuring Officer, emphasized the lender&#8217;s commitment to maximizing recoveries for its creditors. He expressed his satisfaction with the conditional approval of the Disclosure Statement, stating that it brings BlockFi <em>&#8220;one step closer to accomplishing that goal.&#8221;</em><br /><br />Renzi urged BlockFi&#8217;s <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/blockfi-minces-25-million-in-2-weeks-as-the-bitcoin-and-ether-investors-seek-interest/">clients</a> to support the plan, believing it offers the best route to efficiently return crypto assets to the clients. The company&#8217;s focus, if the bankruptcy plan is approved, will be on recovering funds from other defunct firms, such as Alameda, FTX, 3AC, Emergent, Marex, and Core Scientific. This effort is aimed at maximizing recoveries for clients and defending against claims by third parties that could significantly dilute clients&#8217; assets.<br /><br />However, not everyone is on board with the proposed bankruptcy plans. The disgraced crypto exchange FTX, the fallen hedge fund Three Arrows Capital (3AC), and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) have expressed strong opposition to the plan.<br /><br />The proposed bankruptcy plan provides clients with the option for releases, allowing them to avoid withdrawing from a voluntary third-party release, which would absolve them from any claims and causes of action that BlockFi may have against them. This release is applicable for most clients, except those who withdrew $250,000 or more from BlockFi Interest Accounts (BIA) or BlockFi Private Client (BPC) Accounts on or after November 2, 2022.<br /><br />The scheduled date for voting on the proposed reorganization plan is September 11, when the fate of BlockFi&#8217;s restructuring efforts will be determined.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/blockfi-clears-major-hurdle-in-us-bankruptcy-court/">BlockFi Clears Major Hurdle in US Bankruptcy Court</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/blockfi-clears-major-hurdle-in-us-bankruptcy-court/">BlockFi Clears Major Hurdle in US Bankruptcy Court</a> was first posted on August 6, 2023 at 4:26 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/blockfi-clears-major-hurdle-in-us-bankruptcy-court/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>VC Spectra (SPCT) vs. Dogecoin (DOGE) vs. BNB: A Glimpse into the Future of High Returns!</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/spct-vs-doge-vs-bnb-future-of-high-returns/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/spct-vs-doge-vs-bnb-future-of-high-returns/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 05:38:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VC Spectra (SPCT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65478</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Among the top contenders offering unique opportunities for exponential growth are VC Spectra (SPCT), Dogecoin (DOGE), and BNB. VC Spectra has rapidly gained traction in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/spct-vs-doge-vs-bnb-future-of-high-returns/">VC Spectra (SPCT) vs. Dogecoin (DOGE) vs. BNB: A Glimpse into the Future of High Returns!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/spct-vs-doge-vs-bnb-future-of-high-returns/">VC Spectra (SPCT) vs. Dogecoin (DOGE) vs. BNB: A Glimpse into the Future of High Returns!</a> was first posted on August 6, 2023 at 5:38 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Among the top contenders offering unique opportunities for exponential growth are VC Spectra (SPCT), Dogecoin (DOGE), and BNB. VC Spectra has rapidly gained traction in the market, securing an impressive $2.4 million within a mere two-week period through its private seed sale, thereby setting ambitious growth objectives for the future.</p>
<p>With their diverse potential, these cryptocurrencies present captivating prospects for investors seeking significant returns in the dynamic world of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>BUY SPCT TOKENS NOW</strong></p>
<h2>Discover the Revolutionary Potential of VC Spectra (SPCT)</h2>
<p><a href="https://vcspectra.io/">VC Spectra (SPCT)</a> stands out as a pioneering force, providing investors with a <strong>unique opportunity</strong> to engage in early-stage projects.</p>
<p>What sets <a href="https://vcspectra.io/">VC Spectra (SPCT)</a> apart is its rigorous due diligence process that evaluates the viability and potential of each project meticulously. VC Spectra’s (SPCT) team of experts scrutinizes critical aspects, ensuring that only the most promising ventures make it to the presale stage.</p>
<p>Operating on the BRC-20 standard, the VC Spectra (SPCT) token serves a myriad of functions, including decentralized trading, asset management, and covering transaction fees.</p>
<p>The current public presale in Stage 2 presents a compelling opportunity for investors, with the VC Spectra (SPCT) token available at an attractive price of $0.011.</p>
<p>The allure intensifies as we look ahead to Stage 3, where projections suggest the VC Spectra (SPCT) token could reach <strong>$0.025</strong>. <a href="https://vcspectra.io/"> </a>VC Spectra (SPCT) will deliver its holders a staggering 127.27% increase from the current price and a remarkable 212.5% gain from the initial offering of $0.008.</p>
<h2>Elon Musk&#8217;s Endorsement: Dogecoin (DOGE) in the Spotlight Again</h2>
<p>Dogecoin (DOGE) once again captured the spotlight due to a subtle but meaningful alteration in Elon Musk&#8217;s Twitter bio. Musk has been hinting at the possibility of integrating Dogecoin (DOGE) into his ventures.</p>
<p>The Twitter rebrand on July 25 displayed both an &#8220;X&#8221; and a &#8220;D&#8221; in Musk&#8217;s profile. While the &#8220;X&#8221; represents the platform&#8217;s new branding, the &#8220;D&#8221; was widely interpreted as Dogecoin (DOGE), sparking speculation. This reignited rumors of potential usage of payments with Dogecoin (DOGE) on Musk&#8217;s &#8220;everything app.&#8221;</p>
<p>This seemingly minor development managed to score a small price gain for Dogecoin (DOGE), as it surged by 6% on July 25, rising from $0.77 to $0.82. However, the excitement was short-tempered and Dogecoin’s (DOGE) price quickly started falling. As of August 2, Dogecoin (DOGE) is trading at $0.74, reflecting a decrease of 3.9% compared to its price of $0.77 on July 25.</p>
<p>The revived interest triggered by Musk&#8217;s social media activity holds the potential for a significant positive impact on Dogecoin (DOGE) in the near future.</p>
<h2>BNB Chain Partners with PLANET</h2>
<p>BNB Chain has recently joined forces with PLANET, an innovative blockchain platform dedicated to driving positive change for a sustainable future.</p>
<p>The partnership between BNB Chain and PLANET was officially announced on July 27 through <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bnb-chain-reopens-operations-following-2-million-token-exploit/">BNB Chain</a>&#8216;s official Twitter/X account. PLANET now becomes an ecosystem partner to BNB Chain, establishing a powerful collaboration in the realm of blockchain for environmental good.</p>
<p>The partnership with BNB Chain is a major boost to PLANET&#8217;s mission of using the power of celebrities, fandom, and cutting-edge technology to promote sustainability.</p>
<p>The partnership&#8217;s positive influence is reflected in BNB&#8217;s price performance. Between July 27 and August 2, BNB witnessed a 0.54% price increase, climbing from $238.3 to $240.6.</p>
<p>Analysts are optimistic about market sentiment for BNB, projecting a continued upward trend toward $250.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/spct-vs-doge-vs-bnb-future-of-high-returns/">VC Spectra (SPCT) vs. Dogecoin (DOGE) vs. BNB: A Glimpse into the Future of High Returns!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/spct-vs-doge-vs-bnb-future-of-high-returns/">VC Spectra (SPCT) vs. Dogecoin (DOGE) vs. BNB: A Glimpse into the Future of High Returns!</a> was first posted on August 6, 2023 at 5:38 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/spct-vs-doge-vs-bnb-future-of-high-returns/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>