<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>Latest Crypto News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://kryptomoney.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<description>Latest Crypto News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 21:36:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/cropped-cropped-favicon_512x512_v2-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Latest Crypto News</title>
	<link>https://kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><itunes:subtitle>Latest Crypto News</itunes:subtitle><itunes:category text="News &amp; Politics"/><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Business News"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Investing"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Tech News"/></itunes:category><item>
		<title>What’s in Store for Cryptocurrencies in 2023? Here Are Five Market Predictions</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/whats-in-store-for-cryptocurrencies-in-2023-here-are-five-market-predictions/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 21:34:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto market prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrencies 2023]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63752</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The crypto market has had a particularly turbulent year, with several decentralized and centralized firms failing or trying to stay afloat. It appears that we are nearing the end of the bear market, with bad individuals and practices being cleansed in a dramatic and necessary process for the overall system&#8217;s maturation. Regardless, the Web3 innovations [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/whats-in-store-for-cryptocurrencies-in-2023-here-are-five-market-predictions/">What’s in Store for Cryptocurrencies in 2023? Here Are Five Market Predictions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/whats-in-store-for-cryptocurrencies-in-2023-here-are-five-market-predictions/">What’s in Store for Cryptocurrencies in 2023? Here Are Five Market Predictions</a> was first posted on December 30, 2022 at 4:34 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The crypto market has had a particularly turbulent year, with several decentralized and centralized firms failing or trying to stay afloat. <br /><br />It appears that we are nearing the end of the bear market, with bad individuals and practices being cleansed in a dramatic and necessary process for the overall system&#8217;s maturation. <br /><br />Regardless, the Web3 innovations that emerge from this crypto winter will revolutionize the world. Following the events of 2022, the year 2023 is offered with a mixed perspective. Rather, the forecasts are mixed.</p>
<h2>Here Are Five Predictions</h2>
<p>1. Mark Connors, head of research for Canadian crypto asset manager, said he expects a price rebound in 2023 and TradFi businesses, among others, to take a more active role not just in finding applications for blockchain technology, but also in regulatory development.&#8221;Leadership will come from the corporate side, not the regulatory side,&#8221; Alex Connors predicts.<br /><br />2. Second, 2023 will be a watershed moment for digital assets. It will be the fundamental Layer 1s, Bitcoin, Ethereum, and TradFi firms using NFTs. In 2022, the ecosystem consisted of alt-level coins such as Solana, Algorand, and others supplying the majority of the non-Bitcoin, Ethereum, and stablecoin market cap.<br /><br />3. According to Connors, the Fed might stop quantitative tightening before the third quarter. They will halt because the Treasury market might fail as it did in September 2019. Money markets will crash, the Fed will print, and cryptocurrency will fall as precipitously as it did in March 2020. As a market, we&#8217;re still in our infancy. We do not control our own fate based on pricing and adoption.<br /><br />4. Fourth, stablecoins will find additional uses outside of crypto capital markets, resulting in greater mainstream adoption — particularly among enterprises — and innovation inside Web3. Governments and private blockchain developers will continue to do research and development, with some announcing centralized public infrastructure such as central bank digital currencies or marketplace infrastructure.<br /><br />5. While cryptocurrency venture capital funding will continue to fall through the first half of 2023, this is not necessarily a bad thing; rather, it is normalizing to a rational level. Investors don&#8217;t want to catch a falling knife, so they&#8217;re waiting for a bottom while also considering broader macroeconomic issues and the potential of a worldwide recession.<br /><br />At the same time, new settlements (layer 1s/2s), interoperability (layer 0/bridge), lending, and trading protocols will be funded to fill the void left by previous hacks, treasury shortfalls, regulatory changes, and exchange collapses.<br /><br /><strong>Overall, Web 3 will continue to grow</strong><br />&#8220;Larger macroeconomic downturn market conditions should hopefully drive crypto initiatives away from speculation and more towards utility &#8211; one big utility category just being meaningful, entertaining, social interactions,&#8221; Alex Zhang, the de facto leader of Friends with Benefits DAO, predicts. <br /><br />He anticipates growth in &#8220;interoperable identity, on-chain social graphs, and crypto-abstracted social experiences,&#8221; as well as &#8220;more meaningful Web3 social platforms and protocols.&#8221;</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/whats-in-store-for-cryptocurrencies-in-2023-here-are-five-market-predictions/">What’s in Store for Cryptocurrencies in 2023? Here Are Five Market Predictions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/whats-in-store-for-cryptocurrencies-in-2023-here-are-five-market-predictions/">What’s in Store for Cryptocurrencies in 2023? Here Are Five Market Predictions</a> was first posted on December 30, 2022 at 4:34 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Happened in Crypto Market in 2022? 83 Billion SHIB Burned While 572,000 BTC Left Exchanges</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/here-is-what-happened-in-crypto-market-in-2022-83-billion-shib-burned-while-572000-btc-left-exchanges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 21:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2022 crypto market review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency predictions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBA INU (SHIB)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63749</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In 2022, cryptocurrencies experienced a tough year defined by industry failures and plummeting prices. The price decline began in late 2021. That&#8217;s when inflation rates began to rise, raising fears that the Federal Reserve might raise borrowing costs when the calendar flipped. Bitcoin fell 19% in December as investors shifted into assets deemed safer in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/here-is-what-happened-in-crypto-market-in-2022-83-billion-shib-burned-while-572000-btc-left-exchanges/">What Happened in Crypto Market in 2022? 83 Billion SHIB Burned While 572,000 BTC Left Exchanges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/here-is-what-happened-in-crypto-market-in-2022-83-billion-shib-burned-while-572000-btc-left-exchanges/">What Happened in Crypto Market in 2022? 83 Billion SHIB Burned While 572,000 BTC Left Exchanges</a> was first posted on December 30, 2022 at 4:01 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In 2022, cryptocurrencies experienced a tough year defined by industry failures and plummeting prices. The price decline began in late 2021. <br /><br />That&#8217;s when inflation rates began to rise, raising fears that the Federal Reserve might raise borrowing costs when the calendar flipped. Bitcoin fell 19% in December as investors shifted into assets deemed safer in an uncertain economy.<br /><br />The sell-off continued in January, with Bitcoin down 17% and Ethereum down 26%. The crypto winter did not arrive for several months. Markets even temporarily stabilized. Then, in May, stablecoins were formally declared unstable. A stablecoin is a sort of digital currency that is pegged to the US dollar one-to-one.<br /><br />When TerraUSD or UST fell below $1 and its sister token, LUNA tumbled, a different kind of fear ensued. The peg had gone. Confidence vanished. The fall of LUNA took the loss of more than $40 billion in wealth. Suddenly, it appeared that nothing in crypto was safe.<br /><br />The major cryptocurrencies plummeted, with bitcoin falling 16% in a single week, down by more than half from its peak six months earlier. On the macroeconomic front, inflation showed no signs of abating, and the central bank remained committed to raising rates to the extent necessary to halt the rise in consumer prices. The bottom fell out in June.<br /><br />Because of &#8220;extreme market conditions,&#8221; lending platform Celsius halted withdrawals. BlockFi, a crypto lender, also cut 20% of its personnel after more than quintupling since the end of 2020.<br /><br />Three Arrows Capital, or 3AC, a prominent crypto hedge fund, defaulted on a debt worth more than $670 million, and FTX negotiated an agreement allowing it to buy BlockFi at a fraction of the company&#8217;s latest private valuation.<br /><br />In June, Bitcoin experienced its worst month on record, shedding about 38% of its value. Ethereum fell by more than 40%. Then there were the bankruptcies.<br /><br />3AC, based in Singapore, declared bankruptcy in July, just months after revealing that the company had $10 billion in assets.<br /><br />The firm&#8217;s risky strategy entailed borrowing money from throughout the industry and then investing it in other, typically fledgling, crypto businesses.<br /><br />Following the demise of 3AC, crypto brokerage Voyager Digital was not far behind. This is due to 3AC&#8217;s significant default on a Voyager loan.<br /><br />Celsius was the next to seek Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in mid-July. Customers were being paid up to 17% interest to hold their cryptocurrency on the platform. It would lend those assets to counterparties prepared to pay exorbitant interest rates. <br /><br />As liquidity ran out, the framework crumbled. Meanwhile, Bankman-Fried was portraying himself as an industry savior. Then came the most calamitous tumble: FTX&#8217;s precipitous fall in November, following Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao&#8217;s statement that his company was selling its FTT tokens, the native currency of FTX.</p>
<h2>83 Billion SHIB Burned While 572,000 BTC Left Exchanges</h2>
<p>83 billion Shiba Inu tokens were burned in 2022, according to SHIB Burn Tracker. This amount is comparable to $1.74 million at an annual arithmetic average SHIB price of $0.000021. Furthermore, at the start of the year, 83 billion SHIB represented 0.014% of the total token supply.<br /><br />According to a crypto analyst, Lark Davis, 572,000 bitcoin left exchanges in 2022. Only 11% of the total supply is left on exchanges, about 2.1 million coins.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/here-is-what-happened-in-crypto-market-in-2022-83-billion-shib-burned-while-572000-btc-left-exchanges/">What Happened in Crypto Market in 2022? 83 Billion SHIB Burned While 572,000 BTC Left Exchanges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/here-is-what-happened-in-crypto-market-in-2022-83-billion-shib-burned-while-572000-btc-left-exchanges/">What Happened in Crypto Market in 2022? 83 Billion SHIB Burned While 572,000 BTC Left Exchanges</a> was first posted on December 30, 2022 at 4:01 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here Is What Crypto Traders Are Monitoring As Year Ends; 2023 Predictions for Bitcoin, Ethereum, MANA, Enjin Coin, Augur</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/here-is-what-crypto-traders-are-monitoring-as-year-ends-2023-predictions-for-bitcoin-ethereum-mana-enjin-coin-augur/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 20:34:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Augur (REP)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Decentraland MANA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Enjin Coin (ENJ)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX collapse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quant (QNT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63741</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>According to blockchain analytics firm Santiment, 2022 was arguably the most visible year in terms of crypto markets being influenced by news events. Santiment observes that as the year ends, traders are monitoring four major news events: the pandemic, second is the FTX collapse, and the arraignment of its cofounder, Sam Bankman-Fried. The third issue [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/here-is-what-crypto-traders-are-monitoring-as-year-ends-2023-predictions-for-bitcoin-ethereum-mana-enjin-coin-augur/">Here Is What Crypto Traders Are Monitoring As Year Ends; 2023 Predictions for Bitcoin, Ethereum, MANA, Enjin Coin, Augur</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/here-is-what-crypto-traders-are-monitoring-as-year-ends-2023-predictions-for-bitcoin-ethereum-mana-enjin-coin-augur/">Here Is What Crypto Traders Are Monitoring As Year Ends; 2023 Predictions for Bitcoin, Ethereum, MANA, Enjin Coin, Augur</a> was first posted on December 30, 2022 at 3:34 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>According to blockchain analytics firm Santiment, 2022 was arguably the most visible year in terms of crypto markets being influenced by news events.<br /><br />Santiment observes that as the year ends, traders are monitoring four major news events: the pandemic, second is the FTX collapse, and the arraignment of its cofounder, Sam Bankman-Fried. The third issue at hand has to do with getting clues on the Fed’s interest rate hikes to come in 2023. Then last is the Russia-Ukraine War news.<br /><br />Santiment predicts that as FUD (Fear, Uncertainty, and doubt) eases on these four issues, prices might likely rise.</p>
<h2>2023 Predictions for Bitcoin, Ethereum, MANA, Enjin Coin, Augur</h2>
<p>Alex Gladstein, chief strategy officer of the Human Rights Foundation, comments on a Bitcoin conference held in Ghana. “I was blown away,” says Gladstein. “They’re all just building on bitcoin. <br /><br />It’s legitimately amazing,” he says, which is why he believes that “global adoption might probably be the number one story for 2023.”<br /><br />Analyst Michael van de Poppe predicts a target of $38,500 for Bitcoin. Coin bureau analyst ‘’Guy’’ rather doesn&#8217;t make a price prediction for Ethereum and believes that a flippening could happen and ETH might reach five digits. On the other hand, He believes that the cryptocurrency might trade sideways next year.<br /><br />According to Santiment, Quant, Decentraland, and Enjin are among the largest market cap assets that saw significant amounts of coins leaving exchanges in 2022. Though their respective prices are down big, as is the rest of crypto, it highlights that these are good signs for a better 2023.<br /><br />There is also a stable growth of daily active addresses for Augur (REP). Santiment analysts predict that a downward trend in the value of the token might be reversed and the reversal to growth will begin.<br /><br /><strong>Is the contagion over?</strong><br />&#8220;The contagion is far from done,&#8221; says Cas Piancey, co-host of the &#8220;Crypto Critics&#8217; Corner&#8221; podcast. Piancey believes that &#8220;businesses, banks, and funds are urgently hoping the market gets past the FTX and Alameda collapse or simply concentrates on their misconduct,&#8221; but whether individuals like it or not, &#8220;you can&#8217;t wish away a credit crunch and exposure to problematic counterparties.<br /><br />We will see the closure of funds and the failure of companies that we did not predict, largely because the contagion is too vast and too difficult for us all to estimate.&#8221;<br /><br />&#8220;Harsh crypto regulation will be presented, and the community will wage an epic battle to combat the aspects of it that endanger decentralization,&#8221; says Laura Shin, host of the “Unchained” podcast.<br /><br />On the other hand, Santiment believes Bitcoin&#8217;s ranging prices have a lot to do with declining whale interest. If prices continue sliding and a spike in Whale interest occurs, this might be a historically bullish signal.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/here-is-what-crypto-traders-are-monitoring-as-year-ends-2023-predictions-for-bitcoin-ethereum-mana-enjin-coin-augur/">Here Is What Crypto Traders Are Monitoring As Year Ends; 2023 Predictions for Bitcoin, Ethereum, MANA, Enjin Coin, Augur</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/here-is-what-crypto-traders-are-monitoring-as-year-ends-2023-predictions-for-bitcoin-ethereum-mana-enjin-coin-augur/">Here Is What Crypto Traders Are Monitoring As Year Ends; 2023 Predictions for Bitcoin, Ethereum, MANA, Enjin Coin, Augur</a> was first posted on December 30, 2022 at 3:34 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Enables Apple Pay, Google Pay Payment Services</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/binance-enables-apple-pay-google-pay-payment-services/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 16:37:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63727</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The crypto exchange revealed in its latest Binance Build update that the platform had integrated the two payment systems. The Binance team confirmed on Twitter, “Apple Pay and Google Pay payment options are now available on Binance! Purchase crypto, with ease.” Customers can now purchase Bitcoins using either Apple Pay or Google Pay. The upgrade [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-enables-apple-pay-google-pay-payment-services/">Binance Enables Apple Pay, Google Pay Payment Services</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-enables-apple-pay-google-pay-payment-services/">Binance Enables Apple Pay, Google Pay Payment Services</a> was first posted on December 30, 2022 at 11:37 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The crypto exchange revealed in its latest <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/feed/post/141143">Binance Build update</a> that the platform had integrated the two payment systems.<br /><br />The Binance team confirmed on <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1608523244323147778">Twitter</a>,</p>
<blockquote>
<p>“Apple Pay and Google Pay payment options are now available on Binance! Purchase crypto, with ease.”</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Customers can now purchase<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/50925-2/"> Bitcoins</a> using either Apple Pay or Google Pay. The upgrade has already been implemented, and preliminary feedback indicates that the new capability is functional.<br /><br />This strategy would be beneficial in attracting more clients to Binance, especially given Apple Pay&#8217;s 44 million and Google Pay&#8217;s 25 million user bases. Both of these payment platforms are the most popular in the world, with the first and second-most users, respectively. <br /><br />The move to embrace these two payment systems will make Binance and cryptocurrencies in general more accessible to a large number of potential customers. This update has the potential to bring in the newest crypto customers for Binance and the rest of the crypto sector. However, the truth remains that these two payment options are not available in every country. It remains to be seen how Binance will do.<br /><br /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-receives-clean-bill-of-health-from-cryptoquant/">Binance</a> is hardly the first cryptocurrency company to accept more mainstream payment methods. Apple Pay has been embraced by various cryptocurrency platforms, such as MetaMask. In March 2022, this crypto wallet, which is the main method of interacting with the Ethereum blockchain (DeFi, Web3 dApps, NFTs), integrated Apple Pay into its platform. Klever, another cryptocurrency wallet, implemented Apple Pay support in April 2021 to provide consumers with a more convenient payment alternative.<br /><br />The cryptocurrency exchange has recently made headlines after it was revealed that Binance.US intended to acquire Voyager Digital assets. The cryptocurrency exchange made a $1 billion bid and was successful in acquiring the Voyager assets just a few weeks ago.<br /><br />Binance had also temporarily halted USDC stablecoin withdrawals, causing some market-wide concern in mid-December. The stated reason for the pause was a lack of USDC reserves, which required a BUSD to USDC swap before the service could restart as usual.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-enables-apple-pay-google-pay-payment-services/">Binance Enables Apple Pay, Google Pay Payment Services</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-enables-apple-pay-google-pay-payment-services/">Binance Enables Apple Pay, Google Pay Payment Services</a> was first posted on December 30, 2022 at 11:37 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Users Fund in Crypto Worth $3.5B Withheld by Bahamian Regulator</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/ftx-users-fund-in-crypto-worth-3-5b-withheld-by-bahamian-regulator/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 15:43:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63742</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Users of FTX who were caught up in the shocking collapse of the cryptocurrency exchange might finally hear some good news from the Bahamas. The Bahamas&#8217; Securities Commission (SCB) announced on Thursday that it has successfully preserved $3.5 billion in cryptocurrency linked to its local affiliate, FTX Digital Markets (FTXDM), the organization behind Sam Bankman-Fried&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/ftx-users-fund-in-crypto-worth-3-5b-withheld-by-bahamian-regulator/">FTX Users Fund in Crypto Worth $3.5B Withheld by Bahamian Regulator</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ftx-users-fund-in-crypto-worth-3-5b-withheld-by-bahamian-regulator/">FTX Users Fund in Crypto Worth $3.5B Withheld by Bahamian Regulator</a> was first posted on December 30, 2022 at 10:43 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Users of <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ftxs-sam-bankman-fried-to-be-arraigned-jan-3-2023-solanas-founders-battle-to-suppress-ftxs-stain-on-sol-token/">FTX</a> who were caught up in the shocking collapse of the cryptocurrency exchange might finally hear some good news from the Bahamas.</p>
<p>The Bahamas&#8217; Securities Commission (SCB)<a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/12/30/bahamas-regulator-seized-3point5-billion-of-ftx-crypto-assets.html?utm_term=Autofeed&amp;utm_medium=Social&amp;utm_content=Main&amp;utm_source=Twitter#Echobox=1672404801"> announced</a> on Thursday that it has successfully preserved $3.5 billion in cryptocurrency linked to its local affiliate, FTX Digital Markets (FTXDM), the organization behind Sam Bankman-Fried&#8217;s international platform.</p>
<p>The Commission <a href="https://www.scb.gov.bs/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SCB-seeks-court-direction-Press-Release-29Dec22-Final.pdf">stated</a> that it perceived dangers to the platform&#8217;s surviving digital assets after FTX was subject to cyberattacks before declaring bankruptcy in November. With the aid of infrastructure start-up Fireblocks, it was able to get a court order to protect the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>At the time of the transfer on November 12, market prices were used to determine the worth of the remaining assets. Since then, the cryptocurrency markets have remained largely stable.</p>
<p>The assets will be kept by the Commission until the Supreme Court instructs it to distribute them to creditors. Although its legal authority to do so is still in question, it has now asked for permission to disclose information about the assets in FTX&#8217;s US-based bankruptcy proceedings.</p>
<p>The Bahamas&#8217; Securities Commission (SCB) said it will:</p>
<blockquote><p>“continue to conduct a comprehensive and diligent investigation into the causes of FTX’s failure, act in accordance with directions issued by the Supreme Court of The Bahamas, collaborate with other supervisory authorities, and take such further actions as needed to preserve the assets of FTXDM and to safeguard the interests of customers and creditors of FTXDM.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Per reports, the Department of Justice is investigating the hacking event that resulted in the unauthorized withdrawal of approximately $500 million in cryptocurrency from FTX&#8217;s functioning hot wallets.</p>
<p>According to lawyers, the top 50 FTX companies owe between 100,000 and one million debtors&#8217; money, totaling $3.1 billion. FTX claims that <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ftx-sam-bankman-fried-charged-with-eight-criminal-offenses/">Bankman-Fried</a> stole billions of dollars worth of cryptocurrency and transferred it to the trading unit Alameda Research, which ultimately lost the money by employing dangerous market tactics.</p>
<p>Last week, Bankman-Fried was extradited from The Bahamas to the US, where he will now be prosecuted on an enormous eight-count indictment that includes fraud and conspiracy allegations. Gary Wang, the chief technical officer of Alameda Research, and Caroline Ellison, the company&#8217;s CEO, have already entered guilty pleas to related crimes.</p>
<p>While he waits for his trial, Bankman-Fried is currently under house arrest at his parent&#8217;s house in California. A $250 million bond backed by the mansion was signed, and a US Magistrate Court granted him bail.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/ftx-users-fund-in-crypto-worth-3-5b-withheld-by-bahamian-regulator/">FTX Users Fund in Crypto Worth $3.5B Withheld by Bahamian Regulator</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ftx-users-fund-in-crypto-worth-3-5b-withheld-by-bahamian-regulator/">FTX Users Fund in Crypto Worth $3.5B Withheld by Bahamian Regulator</a> was first posted on December 30, 2022 at 10:43 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			<enclosure length="590684" type="application/pdf" url="https://www.scb.gov.bs/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SCB-seeks-court-direction-Press-Release-29Dec22-Final.pdf"/><itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><itunes:subtitle>Users of FTX who were caught up in the shocking collapse of the cryptocurrency exchange might finally hear some good news from the Bahamas. The Bahamas&amp;#8217; Securities Commission (SCB) announced on Thursday that it has successfully preserved $3.5 billion in cryptocurrency linked to its local affiliate, FTX Digital Markets (FTXDM), the organization behind Sam Bankman-Fried&amp;#8217;s [&amp;#8230;] The post FTX Users Fund in Crypto Worth $3.5B Withheld by Bahamian Regulator appeared first on Latest Crypto News. FTX Users Fund in Crypto Worth $3.5B Withheld by Bahamian Regulator was first posted on December 30, 2022 at 10:43 am. &amp;copy;2021 &amp;quot;Latest Crypto News&amp;quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at info@kryptomoney.com</itunes:subtitle><itunes:summary>Users of FTX who were caught up in the shocking collapse of the cryptocurrency exchange might finally hear some good news from the Bahamas. The Bahamas&amp;#8217; Securities Commission (SCB) announced on Thursday that it has successfully preserved $3.5 billion in cryptocurrency linked to its local affiliate, FTX Digital Markets (FTXDM), the organization behind Sam Bankman-Fried&amp;#8217;s [&amp;#8230;] The post FTX Users Fund in Crypto Worth $3.5B Withheld by Bahamian Regulator appeared first on Latest Crypto News. FTX Users Fund in Crypto Worth $3.5B Withheld by Bahamian Regulator was first posted on December 30, 2022 at 10:43 am. &amp;copy;2021 &amp;quot;Latest Crypto News&amp;quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at info@kryptomoney.com</itunes:summary><itunes:keywords>News, FTX, Sam Bankman-Fried</itunes:keywords></item>
		<item>
		<title>SHIB Price Analysis: SHIB Rebounds as Crypto Market Stays Down; SHIB Lead Developer Prepares for “Huge” Shibarium Launch</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/shib-price-analysis-shib-rebounds-as-crypto-market-stays-down-shib-lead-developer-prepares-for-huge-shibarium-launch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 14:45:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB/USD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB/USD Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63731</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The price of Shiba Inu (SHIB) slightly rose over the past 24 hours At the time of writing, SHIB was up 1.83% at $0.0000081 Shytoshi Kusama, lead Shiba Inu developer, is preparing for a huge Shibarium launch The price of Shiba Inu (SHIB) slightly rose over the past 24 hours, outperforming several cryptocurrencies. At the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/shib-price-analysis-shib-rebounds-as-crypto-market-stays-down-shib-lead-developer-prepares-for-huge-shibarium-launch/">SHIB Price Analysis: SHIB Rebounds as Crypto Market Stays Down; SHIB Lead Developer Prepares for “Huge” Shibarium Launch</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/shib-price-analysis-shib-rebounds-as-crypto-market-stays-down-shib-lead-developer-prepares-for-huge-shibarium-launch/">SHIB Price Analysis: SHIB Rebounds as Crypto Market Stays Down; SHIB Lead Developer Prepares for “Huge” Shibarium Launch</a> was first posted on December 30, 2022 at 9:45 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li>The price of Shiba Inu (SHIB) slightly rose over the past 24 hours</li>
<li>At the time of writing, SHIB was up 1.83% at $0.0000081</li>
<li>Shytoshi Kusama, lead Shiba Inu developer, is preparing for a huge Shibarium launch</li>
</ul>
<p>The price of <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/here-is-how-shiba-inu-shib-could-reach-0-01-where-and-when-will-bitcoin-bottom-out/">Shiba Inu (SHIB)</a> slightly rose over the past 24 hours, outperforming several cryptocurrencies. At the time of writing, SHIB was up 1.83% at $0.0000081 as the general crypto market posted losses. Shytoshi Kusama, the lead Shiba Inu developer, is preparing for a huge Shibarium launch. Kusama recently tweeted that he was meeting with Unification Foundation developers to complete and launch Shibarium, a layer-2 solution, <em>&#8220;very soon.&#8221;</em> The announcement has already sparked interest in the Shiba Inu community. For the time being, investors are waiting for additional information on Shibarium&#8217;s development progress, and Kusama&#8217;s team is now <em>&#8220;aligning, onboarding, and finalizing&#8221;</em> the much-anticipated layer-2 solution before its release. Shibarium is one of the most ambitious projects in the Shiba Inu ecosystem, and Kusama&#8217;s team is hard at work on it. The layer-2 solution will allow users to benefit from faster transactions at lower costs. The layer-2 solution will provide users with faster transactions cheaply, allowing them to benefit from an improved user experience.<br /><br /><strong>Key Levels</strong><br />Resistance Levels: $0.00001518, $0.00001300, $0.00001000<br />Support Levels: $0.00000800, $0.00000700, $0.00000600</p>
<h4>SHIB/USD Daily Chart: Ranging</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1488" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-63736 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-Daily-Dec-30.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-Daily-Dec-30.png 1488w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-Daily-Dec-30-300x139.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-Daily-Dec-30-1024x473.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-Daily-Dec-30-768x355.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-Daily-Dec-30-750x347.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-Daily-Dec-30-1140x527.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1488px) 100vw, 1488px" /><em><span style="color: #999999">SHIB/USD Daily Chart</span></em></h6>
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/shib-price-analysis-how-will-shib-price-fare-as-2022-ends-19-4-million-shib-burned-at-once-with-burn-rate-up-107/">SHIB/USD</a> initially traded higher the prior day but retreated around $0.00000828. While pulling down, bears emerged as traders focused on levels around $0.00000800. To begin investigating the bearish scenario, a substantial decline below $0.00000790 is required. The pair may continue to fall, with pessimistic traders looking for a goal around $0.00000700.<br /><br />Subsequent growth from $0.00000800 might be viewed as the next phase of growth inside a long-term consolidation trend. Further increases are expected as long as the $0.00000800 support is maintained. Meanwhile, a strong breakout of $0.00000885 would demonstrate that the bounce from $0.00000712 is still on, bringing the bounce back into focus.</p>
<h4>SHIB/USD 4-Hour Chart: Ranging</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1488" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-63737 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-4-Hour-Dec-30.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-4-Hour-Dec-30.png 1488w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-4-Hour-Dec-30-300x139.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-4-Hour-Dec-30-1024x473.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-4-Hour-Dec-30-768x355.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-4-Hour-Dec-30-750x347.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-4-Hour-Dec-30-1140x527.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1488px) 100vw, 1488px" /><em><span style="color: #999999">SHIB/USD 4-Hour Chart</span></em></h6>
<p>The SHIB/USD intraday bias is turning positive as consolidation from $0.00000779 continues. Continuous progress is expected until a minor support level of $0.00000800 is sustained. However, only a rise over the relative strength index (RSI) midline of 50 would reverse the neutral to bearish picture.<br /><br />A break of the minor resistance zone at the 4-hour moving average (MA 50) at $0.00000820 should result in a retest of the upper level of $0.00000950. A sustained breach of the minor support level at $0.00000800, on the other hand, would extend the correction with another drop to $0.00000700.</p>
<p><strong>Note:</strong><em> Kryptomoney.com is not a financial advisor. Do research before investing your funds in any financial asset, presented product, or event. We are not responsible for your investing results</em></p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/shib-price-analysis-shib-rebounds-as-crypto-market-stays-down-shib-lead-developer-prepares-for-huge-shibarium-launch/">SHIB Price Analysis: SHIB Rebounds as Crypto Market Stays Down; SHIB Lead Developer Prepares for “Huge” Shibarium Launch</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/shib-price-analysis-shib-rebounds-as-crypto-market-stays-down-shib-lead-developer-prepares-for-huge-shibarium-launch/">SHIB Price Analysis: SHIB Rebounds as Crypto Market Stays Down; SHIB Lead Developer Prepares for “Huge” Shibarium Launch</a> was first posted on December 30, 2022 at 9:45 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX’s Sam Bankman-Fried To Be Arraigned January 3; Solana’s Founders Battle To Suppress FTX’s Stain on SOL Token</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/ftxs-sam-bankman-fried-to-be-arraigned-jan-3-2023-solanas-founders-battle-to-suppress-ftxs-stain-on-sol-token/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 20:43:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alameda Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX collapse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana (SOL)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63719</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>According to Reuters, FTX Cofounder Sam Bankman-Fried is scheduled to enter a plea next week in response to criminal charges that he misled investors and stole billions of dollars in client funds at his bankrupt FTX bitcoin exchange. According to court records, the 30-year-old is scheduled to be arraigned before U.S. District Judge Lewis Kaplan [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/ftxs-sam-bankman-fried-to-be-arraigned-jan-3-2023-solanas-founders-battle-to-suppress-ftxs-stain-on-sol-token/">FTX’s Sam Bankman-Fried To Be Arraigned January 3; Solana’s Founders Battle To Suppress FTX’s Stain on SOL Token</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ftxs-sam-bankman-fried-to-be-arraigned-jan-3-2023-solanas-founders-battle-to-suppress-ftxs-stain-on-sol-token/">FTX’s Sam Bankman-Fried To Be Arraigned January 3; Solana’s Founders Battle To Suppress FTX’s Stain on SOL Token</a> was first posted on December 29, 2022 at 3:43 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>According to Reuters, FTX Cofounder Sam Bankman-Fried is scheduled to enter a plea next week in response to criminal charges that he misled investors and stole billions of dollars in client funds at his bankrupt FTX bitcoin exchange.<br /><br />According to court records, the 30-year-old is scheduled to be arraigned before U.S. District Judge Lewis Kaplan in Manhattan federal court on the afternoon of January 3, 2023.<br /><br />On Tuesday, Kaplan was assigned to the case after the original judge recused herself because her husband&#8217;s law firm counseled FTX prior to its collapse.<br /><br />Bankman-Fried was released on a $250 million bond on December 22 and ordered to live with his parents in Palo Alto, California, where they both teach at Stanford Law School. He is being monitored electronically.<br /><br />On November 11, FTX filed for bankruptcy. On December 13, its new CEO, John Ray, told Congress that the exchange had lost $8 billion in customer funds while being operated by &#8220;grossly incompetent, unsophisticated employees.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Solana’s Founders Fight To Remove FTX’s Stain on SOL Token</h2>
<p>SOL, Solana&#8217;s crypto token, has dropped 96% from its all-time high of $260 in November 2021 to about $10, harmed first by a year-long crypto rout that swept the whole market and then by FTX&#8217;s decline. <br /><br />SOL fell as much as 12% on Wednesday alone, owing to fears that significant holders are selling the token, which serves as the basic cryptocurrency for financial transactions on the blockchain.<br /><br />The token&#8217;s decline can be interpreted as a sign of losing faith in the entire platform, which once had a market value of about $80 billion and is now worth a fraction of that.<br /><br />Solana, the blockchain network originally championed by Sam Bankman-Fried, is attracting a lot of attention as industry watchers question if its former ties to the disgraced crypto billionaire and his now-defunct FTX business will harm its future.Its founders are trying everything possible to break that link.</p>
<p>Prior to FTX&#8217;s bankruptcy and Bankman-Fried&#8217;s arrest in December on several fraud charges, the former crypto kingmaker was a vocal proponent of Solana, a blockchain marketed as a speedier and more efficient alternative to the market-leading Ethereum network.<br /><br />Bankman-Fried has even spoken at conferences and virtual fireside talks alongside Solana founder Anatoly Yakovenko.<br /><br />The Solana Foundation stated in its November blog post that it had less than $1 million in cash or cash equivalents on FTX.com as of Nov. 6, when the crypto exchange suspended withdrawals, and that it did not know how FTX and Alameda&#8217;s assets would be settled during bankruptcy proceedings. <br /><br />Still, following FTX’s collapse, some crypto projects are leaving the Solana network, which has also experienced multiple outages in the last year. DeGods and y00ts, two well-known NFT projects on Solana, are switching to Ethereum and Polygon, respectively.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/ftxs-sam-bankman-fried-to-be-arraigned-jan-3-2023-solanas-founders-battle-to-suppress-ftxs-stain-on-sol-token/">FTX’s Sam Bankman-Fried To Be Arraigned January 3; Solana’s Founders Battle To Suppress FTX’s Stain on SOL Token</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ftxs-sam-bankman-fried-to-be-arraigned-jan-3-2023-solanas-founders-battle-to-suppress-ftxs-stain-on-sol-token/">FTX’s Sam Bankman-Fried To Be Arraigned January 3; Solana’s Founders Battle To Suppress FTX’s Stain on SOL Token</a> was first posted on December 29, 2022 at 3:43 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Turkey’s Central Bank To Continue Trials for Digital Lira in 2023</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/turkeys-central-bank-to-continue-trials-for-digital-lira-in-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 20:04:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Bank of Turkey]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Turkey]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63724</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Turkey&#8217;s central bank announced Thursday that the first payment transactions on the Digital Turkish Lira Network had been completed successfully as part of preliminary research. The Fed will continue to conduct &#8220;limited, closed-circuit pilot tests&#8221; in the first quarter of 2023. As the advanced phases of the pilot project are revealed, it wants to expand [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/turkeys-central-bank-to-continue-trials-for-digital-lira-in-2023/">Turkey’s Central Bank To Continue Trials for Digital Lira in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/turkeys-central-bank-to-continue-trials-for-digital-lira-in-2023/">Turkey’s Central Bank To Continue Trials for Digital Lira in 2023</a> was first posted on December 29, 2022 at 3:04 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/turkeys-new-economic-roadmap-includes-central-bank-digital-currency/">Turkey&#8217;s central bank</a> announced Thursday that the first payment transactions on the Digital Turkish Lira Network had been completed successfully as part of preliminary research.<br /><br />The Fed will continue to conduct <em>&#8220;limited, closed-circuit pilot tests&#8221;</em> in the first quarter of 2023. As the advanced phases of the pilot project are revealed, it wants to expand the Digital Turkish Lira Collaboration Platform to select banks and financial technology firms.<br /><br />The bank said in a<a href="https://www.tcmb.gov.tr/wps/wcm/connect/EN/TCMB+EN/Main+Menu/Announcements/Press+Releases/2022/ANO2022-55"> statement</a>:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>&#8220;Will continue to run tests for authentic architectural setups designed in areas such as the use of distributed ledger technologies in payment systems and the integration of these technologies with instant payment systems,&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The bank also stated that during 2023, studies on the Digital Turkish Lira&#8217;s economic and legal foundation as well as its technological requirements will be given top priority.<br /><br />India, Kazakhstan, and other nations are also aiming toward central bank digital currencies.<br /><br />Earlier this year, the <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/us-federal-reserve-board-member-hints-at-dlt-research-with-focus-on-cbdc/">U.S. Federal Reserve</a> released a report outlining the advantages and disadvantages of CBDCs, and the European Central Bank is considering ways to incorporate decentralized ledger technology into current payment settlement systems.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/turkeys-central-bank-to-continue-trials-for-digital-lira-in-2023/">Turkey’s Central Bank To Continue Trials for Digital Lira in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/turkeys-central-bank-to-continue-trials-for-digital-lira-in-2023/">Turkey’s Central Bank To Continue Trials for Digital Lira in 2023</a> was first posted on December 29, 2022 at 3:04 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Clients Refuse To Give Evidence in Ongoing Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-clients-refuse-to-give-evidence-in-ongoing-lawsuit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 15:12:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63714</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>According to a new emergency motion filed in federal court, Coinbase clients are refusing to release their account information, stalling progress toward moving their claim to arbitration. A recent application in federal court indicated that the plaintiffs would provide the required information in exchange for a protective order. A recent application in federal court indicated [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-clients-refuse-to-give-evidence-in-ongoing-lawsuit/">Coinbase Clients Refuse To Give Evidence in Ongoing Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-clients-refuse-to-give-evidence-in-ongoing-lawsuit/">Coinbase Clients Refuse To Give Evidence in Ongoing Lawsuit</a> was first posted on December 29, 2022 at 10:12 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>According to a new emergency motion filed in federal court, Coinbase <a href="https://twitter.com/skye_witley/status/1608235756597936128?s=46&amp;t=SohrjdvHf-psfQMCvj9pow">clients</a> are refusing to release their account information, stalling progress toward moving their claim to arbitration. A recent application in federal court indicated that the plaintiffs would provide the required information in exchange for a protective order.<br /><br />A recent application in federal court indicated that the plaintiffs would provide the required information in exchange for a protective order.<br /><br /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-reveals-over-33000000000-worth-of-bitcoin-in-its-reserves/">Coinbase</a> objected to the agreement and sought a provision in the protective order that would allow the firm to seek arbitration for the dispute.<br /><br />Coinbase was unable to reconcile consumers to their separate arbitration agreements while this issue was still being resolved. Coinbase requested a hearing in response to the latest emergency motion.<br /><br />The lawsuit claims that Coinbase failed to secure its users&#8217; accounts, leaving them vulnerable to theft and unlawful transfers. It also accused Coinbase of causing financial harm to users by locking them out of their accounts, either permanently or temporarily, as well as failing to comply with federal requirements by listing securities on its trading platform.<br /><br />The dispute has laid bare previously unknown vulnerabilities with cryptocurrency firms&#8217; inadequate cybersecurity practices. The crypto exchange has previously filed various arbitration cases with the United States Supreme Court.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-clients-refuse-to-give-evidence-in-ongoing-lawsuit/">Coinbase Clients Refuse To Give Evidence in Ongoing Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-clients-refuse-to-give-evidence-in-ongoing-lawsuit/">Coinbase Clients Refuse To Give Evidence in Ongoing Lawsuit</a> was first posted on December 29, 2022 at 10:12 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XTZ Price Analysis: Will Tezos Make a Comeback in 2023? Binance US Announces Support for XTZ Staking</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/xtz-price-analysis-will-tezos-make-a-comeback-in-2023-binance-us-announces-support-for-xtz-staking/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 14:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tezos (XTZ)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XTZ/USD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XTZ/USD Price Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63705</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Expectations abound for a possible crypto recovery in 2023 At the time of writing, Tezos (XTZ) is down 2.00% in 24 hours at $0.740 Binance US has announced that its customers will now be able to stake Tezos (XTZ) and earn up to 7% APY at inception The year 2022 is drawing to a close. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/xtz-price-analysis-will-tezos-make-a-comeback-in-2023-binance-us-announces-support-for-xtz-staking/">XTZ Price Analysis: Will Tezos Make a Comeback in 2023? Binance US Announces Support for XTZ Staking</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/xtz-price-analysis-will-tezos-make-a-comeback-in-2023-binance-us-announces-support-for-xtz-staking/">XTZ Price Analysis: Will Tezos Make a Comeback in 2023? Binance US Announces Support for XTZ Staking</a> was first posted on December 29, 2022 at 9:48 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li>Expectations abound for a possible crypto recovery in 2023</li>
<li>At the time of writing, Tezos (XTZ) is down 2.00% in 24 hours at $0.740</li>
<li>Binance US has announced that its customers will now be able to stake Tezos (XTZ) and earn up to 7% APY at inception</li>
</ul>
<p>The <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/three-catalysts-that-might-propel-shib-in-2023-helium-migrating-to-solana-in-q1-next-year/">year 2022</a> is drawing to a close. Following a bearish year all around, expectations abound for a possible crypto recovery in 2023. At the time of writing, <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/xtz-price-analysis-striking-rally-holds-back-beneath-4-43-on-xtz-usd-tezos-q2-growth-remains-positive-on-etoro/">Tezos (XTZ)</a> is down 2.00% in 24 hours at $0.740. Binance US, a subsidiary of the Binance crypto exchange, has announced that its customers will now be able to stake Tezos (XTZ) and earn up to 7% APY at inception. Customers would now be able to buy, sell, convert, or stake XTZ in minutes on Binance US, a major staking provider. Also, advanced trading is available on the XTZ/USD, XTZ/BUSD, and XTZ/BTC pairs. XTZ is the native asset of the Tezos network. The token is required to participate in the blockchain’s proof of stake consensus mechanism, pay transaction fees, or participate in governance, and is also used as a unit of exchange across the network. While Tezos has a similar target audience as Ethereum, the network sets itself apart via its consensus mechanism and its self-amendment capabilities, which allow the network to implement major upgrades without the need for a hard fork. Like Ethereum, the Tezos network can be used to create a token, dApps, games, and NFT projects.<br /><br /><strong>Key Levels</strong><br />Resistance Levels: $2.00, $1.50, $1.00<br />Support Levels: $0.725, $0.45, $0.30</p>
<h4>XTZ/USD Daily Chart: Bearish</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1436" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-63720 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XTZUSD-Daily-Dec-29.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XTZUSD-Daily-Dec-29.png 1436w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XTZUSD-Daily-Dec-29-300x144.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XTZUSD-Daily-Dec-29-1024x491.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XTZUSD-Daily-Dec-29-768x368.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XTZUSD-Daily-Dec-29-750x359.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XTZUSD-Daily-Dec-29-1140x546.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1436px) 100vw, 1436px" /><em><span style="color: #999999">XTZ/USD Daily Chart</span></em></h6>
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/xtz-price-analysis-amid-crypto-market-slump-xtz-usd-upswings-to-3-07-on-tezos-kalamint-mainnet-launch/">XTZ/USD</a> declined as low as $0.726, suggesting that some selling occurred beneath the consolidative floor of $0.80. The RSI has yet to show any signs of improvement as it approaches 25. In the upcoming sessions, it&#8217;s important to pay special attention to how the moving averages are converging. It will be encouraging for the XTZ/USD pair if the MA 50 bearish stance wanes.<br /><br />However, if the price gains momentum and breaks through the convergent barrier of the MAs at approximately $1.0, early upside restrictions could develop from the $1.15 level before the $1.50 level, which marks the consolidation&#8217;s ceiling. XTZ&#8217;s price could move in the direction of the resistance band of $1.50-$2.00 if this barrier is broken. Otherwise, bears could test sellers’ efforts to steer XTZ&#8217;s price back lower.</p>
<h4>XTZ/USD 4-Hour Chart: Bearish</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1436" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-63721 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XTZUSD-Daily-Dec-29-1.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XTZUSD-Daily-Dec-29-1.png 1436w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XTZUSD-Daily-Dec-29-1-300x144.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XTZUSD-Daily-Dec-29-1-1024x491.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XTZUSD-Daily-Dec-29-1-768x368.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XTZUSD-Daily-Dec-29-1-750x359.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XTZUSD-Daily-Dec-29-1-1140x546.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1436px) 100vw, 1436px" /><em><span style="color: #999999">XTZ/USD 4-Hour Chart</span></em></h6>
<p>XTZ/USD 4-Hour chart might return to the upside on oversold RSI, where the price can try to reach the MA 50 at the $0.785 resistance zone, which if broken would pave the way for the $0.800 level. If investors choose to keep dumping off the asset below the current price at $0.739, support might then move in the direction of the $0.720 range before reaching the $0.700 level.<br /><br />However, near the MA 50, at the $0.785 level, a bullish reversal may find instant support. The $0.800-$0.850 range, marked by the most recent consolidation, could represent the next objective if these bears fail to swing lower. Overall, if positive price activity is unable to sustain an ascent past the moving averages, XTZ&#8217;s consolidation pattern might continue.</p>
<p><strong>Note:</strong><em> Kryptomoney.com is not a financial advisor. Do research before investing your funds in any financial asset, presented product, or event. We are not responsible for your investing results</em></p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/xtz-price-analysis-will-tezos-make-a-comeback-in-2023-binance-us-announces-support-for-xtz-staking/">XTZ Price Analysis: Will Tezos Make a Comeback in 2023? Binance US Announces Support for XTZ Staking</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/xtz-price-analysis-will-tezos-make-a-comeback-in-2023-binance-us-announces-support-for-xtz-staking/">XTZ Price Analysis: Will Tezos Make a Comeback in 2023? Binance US Announces Support for XTZ Staking</a> was first posted on December 29, 2022 at 9:48 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>