<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title/>
	<atom:link href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 04:03:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><itunes:subtitle/><itunes:category text="News &amp; Politics"/><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Business News"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Investing"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Tech News"/></itunes:category><item>
		<title>Compound and Pepe Fade Away As VC Spectra Takes Center Stage</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/compound-and-pepe-fade-away-as-vc-spectra-takes-center-stage/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/compound-and-pepe-fade-away-as-vc-spectra-takes-center-stage/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 04:03:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VC Spectra]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65449</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a shifting cryptocurrency landscape, Compound (COMP) and Pepe (PEPE) are losing their spotlight as VC Spectra (SPCT) emerges as the new star. With its [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/compound-and-pepe-fade-away-as-vc-spectra-takes-center-stage/">Compound and Pepe Fade Away As VC Spectra Takes Center Stage</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/compound-and-pepe-fade-away-as-vc-spectra-takes-center-stage/">Compound and Pepe Fade Away As VC Spectra Takes Center Stage</a> was first posted on August 1, 2023 at 4:03 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a shifting cryptocurrency landscape, Compound (COMP) and Pepe (PEPE) are losing their spotlight as VC Spectra (SPCT) emerges as the new star. With its remarkable performance capturing market attention, VC Spectra (SPCT) is taking center stage, leaving other tokens in the shadows. VC Spectra (SPCT) recently raised over $2.4 million in a private presale.</p>
<p>Will VC Spectra (SPCT) be able to keep Compound (COMP) and Pepe (PEPE) at bay? Let’s find out.</p>
<h2>Compound (COMP): Why Are Investors Leaving?</h2>
<p>Compound (COMP) has displayed an intriguing price pattern, setting up two higher highs on July 2 and July 15 at $71 and $76, respectively. A closer examination reveals potential signals for an impending trend reversal.</p>
<p>On July 7, the Wave Trend indicator flashed a bearish crossover in the overbought region, suggesting it was time to sell. Despite this signal, Compound’s (COMP) price continued its ascent, establishing a higher high on July 15, which resulted in a bearish divergence, marking the second sell signal.</p>
<p>Notably, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) and Awesome Oscillator (AO) have registered lower highs, contrasting Compound’s (COMP) higher highs. This pattern, known as bearish divergence, frequently foreshadows a downtrend.</p>
<p>While the outlook for Compound’s (COMP) price correction is based on multiple sell signals, the crypto market recently experienced an unexpected bullish shift due to SEC vs. Ripple lawsuit developments.</p>
<p>Under these circumstances, the potential bearish thesis for Compound’s (COMP) price can be invalidated if it produces a daily candlestick close above the $76 hurdle and successfully transforms it into a support level. Should this occur, Compound (COMP) bulls could potentially propel the altcoin toward the $80 mark, <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/3-critical-btc-predictions-from-market-experts-for-2021/">according to market experts</a>.</p>
<h2>PEPE Fighting For Breather: Will It Go Down?</h2>
<p>A newcomer in meme coins, PEPE, has experienced a sharp decline of 17% within just 72 hours. Despite this downtrend, the frog-themed crypto has entered an accumulation zone, presenting a potential opportunity for long-term investors.</p>
<p>This dip caused PEPE to break below the crucial 50-day Moving Average (MA) at $0.0000014923, prompting a selling spree among PEPE holders following its drop below the 50-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA).</p>
<p>While the RSI and EMA indicators currently show a neutral outlook, market analysts view this lower low as the perfect buying spot for PEPE, anticipating a substantial influx of buy action if the market cap increases.</p>
<h2>VC Spectra (SPCT): Moving Towards High Gains In Stage 3 of Public Presale</h2>
<p>VC Spectra (SPCT) is gaining significant traction as a revolutionary asset management platform in cryptocurrencies. <a href="https://vcspectra.io/">VC Spectra (SPCT)</a> provides a transformative opportunity for individuals from diverse financial backgrounds.</p>
<p>With the power of blockchain technology, the platform ensures the safety of investors&#8217; assets, fostering a system of open verification for all transactions. Furthermore, VC Spectra (SPCT) allow exclusive voting rights to its investors using a decentralized investment management system.</p>
<p>The ongoing public presale of <a href="https://vcspectra.io/">VC Spectra (SPCT)</a> tokens has already achieved remarkable milestones, attracting investors, with each stage offering attractive investment prospects. The private presale raised over $2.4 million, reflecting strong investor confidence.</p>
<p>Stage 2 saw an impressive surge in the VC Spectra (SPCT) token price, reaching $0.011 from $0.008 in Stage 1 and delivering a substantial 37.5% ROI to investors participating during this phase.</p>
<p>Moving into Stage 3, the token price rises to $0.025, presenting another opportunity for investors to witness a significant 127.27% price surge compared to Stage 2.</p>
<p>The platform&#8217;s ultimate goal is to reach a target price of $0.08 for VC Spectra&#8217;s (SPCT) tokens, representing a 627% surge from the initial Stage 2 price.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/compound-and-pepe-fade-away-as-vc-spectra-takes-center-stage/">Compound and Pepe Fade Away As VC Spectra Takes Center Stage</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/compound-and-pepe-fade-away-as-vc-spectra-takes-center-stage/">Compound and Pepe Fade Away As VC Spectra Takes Center Stage</a> was first posted on August 1, 2023 at 4:03 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/compound-and-pepe-fade-away-as-vc-spectra-takes-center-stage/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX and Genesis: In Principle Agreement Reached</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/ftx-and-genesis-in-principle-agreement-reached/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/ftx-and-genesis-in-principle-agreement-reached/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 22:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genesis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65446</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FTX and Genesis have reached a preliminary agreement to settle their legal dispute, according to their legal representatives. The settlement will address the claims made [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/ftx-and-genesis-in-principle-agreement-reached/">FTX and Genesis: In Principle Agreement Reached</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/ftx-and-genesis-in-principle-agreement-reached/">FTX and Genesis: In Principle Agreement Reached</a> was first posted on July 30, 2023 at 10:29 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-28/bankrupt-crypto-platforms-ftx-genesis-set-to-resolve-dispute">FTX and Genesis</a> have reached a preliminary agreement to settle their legal dispute, according to their legal representatives. The settlement will address the claims made by both bankrupt firms against each other while under court supervision. The specific details of the settlement have not been disclosed yet.</p>
<p>The agreement comes after both FTX and Genesis had previously accused each other of owing money. FTX filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy last November, followed by Genesis three months later.</p>
<p>FTX sought to recover funds from the lending firm and non-debtor affiliates to repay its creditors, with Genesis being its largest unsecured creditor and owing over $226 million.</p>
<p>On the other hand, <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/ftx-concludes-series-b-1-fundraise-generates-420m-from-round/">FTX</a> claimed that DCG&#8217;s lending arm owed approximately $4 billion, which was later revised to $2 billion. Genesis rejected this claim and even filed its motion stating that FTX was entitled to nothing.</p>
<p>The settlement agreement is subject to documentation, and the exact terms will be revealed once finalized. The resolution is expected to put an end to the legal battle between the two parties and provide clarity on their financial obligations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/ftx-and-genesis-in-principle-agreement-reached/">FTX and Genesis: In Principle Agreement Reached</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/ftx-and-genesis-in-principle-agreement-reached/">FTX and Genesis: In Principle Agreement Reached</a> was first posted on July 30, 2023 at 10:29 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/ftx-and-genesis-in-principle-agreement-reached/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Remittance Now Available on Bahamas Payment Platform</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/crypto-remittance-now-available-on-bahamas-payment-platform/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/crypto-remittance-now-available-on-bahamas-payment-platform/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 21:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[The Bahamas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDCoin (USDC)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65437</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Migrants are sending money home at unprecedented rates, despite the high costs of traditional remittances. Island Pay, a Bahamas-based fintech company, is advancing financial inclusion [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/crypto-remittance-now-available-on-bahamas-payment-platform/">Crypto Remittance Now Available on Bahamas Payment Platform</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/crypto-remittance-now-available-on-bahamas-payment-platform/">Crypto Remittance Now Available on Bahamas Payment Platform</a> was first posted on July 30, 2023 at 9:30 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Migrants are sending money home at unprecedented rates, despite the high costs of traditional remittances. Island Pay, a<a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-25/bahamas-payment-platform-island-pay-is-latest-to-offer-crypto-remittance?utm_medium=social&amp;utm_source=twitter&amp;utm_content=crypto&amp;utm_campaign=socialflow-organic"> Bahamas</a>-based fintech company, is advancing financial inclusion with its digital wallet, CiNKO, in Latin America and the Caribbean. The wallet uses Circle&#8217;s <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/circle-reveals-usdc-stablecoin-redemptions-close-to-6-billion/">USDC stablecoin</a>, enabling prepaid card funding and peer-to-peer payments, even without a bank account.<br /><br />The pursuit of crypto-powered remittances is growing, with various crypto wallets and payment systems emerging. Circle collaborates with MoneyGram and Stellar, while Mexico-based Bitso partners with Stellar for USDC transactions. Western Union also launches digital payment platforms to counter crypto competition.<br /><br />CiNKO is part of Circle&#8217;s initiative to introduce stablecoins and decentralized finance in Latin America, potentially reducing remittance costs by 80%. Despite the challenges, remittances in the region have surged, reaching $145 billion in 2021. Island Pay&#8217;s Douglas highlights USDC&#8217;s stability, pegged to the US dollar, and its growing merchant ecosystem, enhancing its usability.<br /><br />The CiNKO wallet aims to onboard 100,000 users in Central and South America, fostering financial inclusion and convenience. Island Pay&#8217;s flexibility allows for expansion beyond Latin America, as crypto-powered remittances promise transformative impacts on financial accessibility for millions globally.</p>
<p><em>Image Credit: Shutterstock</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/crypto-remittance-now-available-on-bahamas-payment-platform/">Crypto Remittance Now Available on Bahamas Payment Platform</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/crypto-remittance-now-available-on-bahamas-payment-platform/">Crypto Remittance Now Available on Bahamas Payment Platform</a> was first posted on July 30, 2023 at 9:30 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/crypto-remittance-now-available-on-bahamas-payment-platform/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shibarium Beta Bridge Launches Public Testing, Moves Closer to Layer-2 Release</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/shibarium-beta-bridge-launches-public-testing-moves-closer-to-layer-2-release/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/shibarium-beta-bridge-launches-public-testing-moves-closer-to-layer-2-release/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 23:48:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBA INU (SHIB)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shibarium]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65439</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The team behind SHIB has made an exciting announcement, revealing the beta version release of the Shibarium Bridge for public testing. This bridge will enable [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/shibarium-beta-bridge-launches-public-testing-moves-closer-to-layer-2-release/">Shibarium Beta Bridge Launches Public Testing, Moves Closer to Layer-2 Release</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/shibarium-beta-bridge-launches-public-testing-moves-closer-to-layer-2-release/">Shibarium Beta Bridge Launches Public Testing, Moves Closer to Layer-2 Release</a> was first posted on July 29, 2023 at 11:48 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The team behind <a href="https://twitter.com/LucieSHIB/status/1684252125704880131">SHIB</a> has made an exciting announcement, revealing the beta version release of the Shibarium Bridge for public testing. This bridge will enable users to transfer tokens between two networks, marking a significant step forward for the project.</p>
<p>In its initial phase, the <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/shib-price-analysis-shiba-inu-tumbles-in-market-selloff-upcoming-shibarium-release-to-be-a-gamechanger/">Shibarium</a> Bridge will facilitate the transfer of testnet ether tokens to the layer-2 network. The team aims to make each transfer quick and efficient, with a maximum time frame of up to 30 minutes.</p>
<p>What sets the Shibarium Bridge apart is its compatibility with the ERC-20 token standard, focusing on enhancing scalability. This development comes on the heels of Shytoshi Kusama, a prominent developer, announcing that Shibarium is scheduled to go live after an upcoming conference in Toronto, set to take place in August this year.</p>
<p>While updates regarding the highly anticipated layer-2 have spurred minor rallies, concerns about Shibarium&#8217;s code previously impacted the value of SHIB considerably in March. However, the addition of Shibarium, especially the layer-2 component, is seen as critical for positioning the meme coin among more serious contenders in the Web3 space. By increasing throughput, the project can effectively handle significant growth and attract a larger user base. Faster transaction speeds will undoubtedly make the platform more appealing to potential users.</p>
<p>Shibarium will be built upon four tokens—<a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/shiba-inus-bone-explodes-50-cardano-xrp-ethereum-and-binance-receive-inflows-as-investors-pull-funds-out-of-bitcoin/">BONE</a>, TREAT, SHIB and LEASH—which will play a crucial role in the applications developed on top of the blockchain. The integration of these tokens will add further utility and value to the ecosystem, offering diverse opportunities for users and developers alike.</p>
<p>As the Shibarium Bridge enters its beta phase, the community eagerly awaits the full release and the subsequent impact it will have on the SHIB project and the wider cryptocurrency space. With the potential to bolster scalability and transaction speed, Shibarium could pave the way for SHIB&#8217;s continued growth and recognition as a formidable player in the evolving Web3 landscape.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/shibarium-beta-bridge-launches-public-testing-moves-closer-to-layer-2-release/">Shibarium Beta Bridge Launches Public Testing, Moves Closer to Layer-2 Release</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/shibarium-beta-bridge-launches-public-testing-moves-closer-to-layer-2-release/">Shibarium Beta Bridge Launches Public Testing, Moves Closer to Layer-2 Release</a> was first posted on July 29, 2023 at 11:48 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/shibarium-beta-bridge-launches-public-testing-moves-closer-to-layer-2-release/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Sandbox (SAND) Announces Historic Partnership With British Museum</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/the-sandbox-sand-announces-historic-partnership-with-british-museum/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/the-sandbox-sand-announces-historic-partnership-with-british-museum/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 22:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[The SandBox (SAND)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65405</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Sandbox (SAND), a blockchain-based virtual gaming platform, has made headlines with its recent historic partnership announcement with the prestigious British Museum. This groundbreaking collaboration [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/the-sandbox-sand-announces-historic-partnership-with-british-museum/">The Sandbox (SAND) Announces Historic Partnership With British Museum</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/the-sandbox-sand-announces-historic-partnership-with-british-museum/">The Sandbox (SAND) Announces Historic Partnership With British Museum</a> was first posted on July 29, 2023 at 10:55 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The<a href="https://sandboxgame.medium.com/the-british-museum-is-bringing-history-to-the-sandbox-54003eae9fc7"> Sandbox (SAND)</a>, a blockchain-based virtual gaming platform, has made headlines with its recent historic partnership announcement with the prestigious British Museum. This groundbreaking collaboration marks a significant milestone in the world of blockchain gaming and signals a new era for the integration of blockchain technology into the cultural and gaming sectors.<br /><br />The prestigious British Museum is embarking on a groundbreaking venture into the metaverse through a strategic partnership with <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/the-sandbox-sand-raises-red-flag-on-security-threats-heres-what-to-know/">The Sandbox</a>. This collaboration opens up exciting possibilities for users to immerse themselves in world history like never before, all from the comfort of their digital environments.<br /><br />As the first public national museum globally, the British Museum has long been committed to being a &#8220;museum of the world, for the world,&#8221; and this vision remains at the core of its mission and values. By teaming up with The Sandbox, the museum is embracing cutting-edge technology to further its mission and expand its reach to a diverse and global audience.<br /><br />Together with the collection, the British Museum&#8217;s licensing partner, The Sandbox will create a range of digital collectibles inspired by some of the museum&#8217;s most treasured artifacts dating back to its founding in 1753. These digital collectibles and immersive experiences will enable people from around the world to discover and engage with the fascinating objects in the British Museum&#8217;s collections.<br /><br />Sebastien Borget, COO, and Co-Founder of The Sandbox, expressed great excitement about the collaboration, emphasizing how it offers a unique opportunity for players to delve into the rich history, art, and culture curated within the British Museum. Regardless of their geographic location, users can now access and enjoy the remarkable collections of human history that the museum has to offer.<br /><br />This partnership represents an exceptional chance for enthusiasts, collectors, and knowledge seekers to expand their understanding of world culture without leaving their homes. The British Museum&#8217;s entrance into the metaverse with The Sandbox promises to be an enriching and immersive journey.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/the-sandbox-sand-announces-historic-partnership-with-british-museum/">The Sandbox (SAND) Announces Historic Partnership With British Museum</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/the-sandbox-sand-announces-historic-partnership-with-british-museum/">The Sandbox (SAND) Announces Historic Partnership With British Museum</a> was first posted on July 29, 2023 at 10:55 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/the-sandbox-sand-announces-historic-partnership-with-british-museum/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>VC Spectra Attracts Investors as Arbitrum and Polygon Price Drops</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/vc-spectra-attracts-investors-as-arbitrum-and-polygon-price-drops/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/vc-spectra-attracts-investors-as-arbitrum-and-polygon-price-drops/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 04:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon (MATIC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SPCT tokens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VC Spectra (SPCT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65422</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the crypto world, Arbitrum (ARB) and Polygon (MATIC) are well-established but face a lot of price fluctuations. Therefore, you need a more reliable investment [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/vc-spectra-attracts-investors-as-arbitrum-and-polygon-price-drops/">VC Spectra Attracts Investors as Arbitrum and Polygon Price Drops</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/vc-spectra-attracts-investors-as-arbitrum-and-polygon-price-drops/">VC Spectra Attracts Investors as Arbitrum and Polygon Price Drops</a> was first posted on July 29, 2023 at 4:15 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the crypto world, Arbitrum (ARB) and Polygon (MATIC) are well-established but face a lot of price fluctuations.</p>
<p>Therefore, you need a more reliable investment solution, such as VC Spectra (SPCT). After <strong>raising $2.4 million</strong> in a seed sale event, VC Spectra continues to surprise everyone with its presale!</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>BUY SPECTRA TOKENS NOW</strong></p>
<h2>Solana-Based Gaming Platform Aurory Goes Cross-Chain with Arbitrum (ARB)</h2>
<p>Over the previous week, Arbitrum (ARB) had a negative price movement resulting from <strong>hostile market conditions.</strong></p>
<p>Luckily, in the last 24 hours, Arbitrum (ARB) has recorded a 0.60% price boost because the <strong>Aurory gaming ecosystem has expanded</strong> and plans to include Arbitrum (ARB) in its blockchain. Because of this, the current price of Arbitrum (ARB) is $1.17.</p>
<p>Besides this, experts also have optimistic predictions about Arbitrum (ARB). Since the trading volume of Arbitrum (ARB) is still <strong>under control</strong>, the Arbitrum (ARB) coin shouldn’t overwhelm and fall on a bearish run.</p>
<h2>Polygon (MATIC) Will Receive Gen 4 Collectible Avatars</h2>
<p>After spending some time on a bearish run because of the <strong>lousy market state</strong>, <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/cardano-ada-solana-sol-and-polygon-matic-are-securities-sec-asserts/">Polygon</a> (MATIC) is now having a brighter future.</p>
<p>Polygon (MATIC) will <strong>receive Gen 4 collectible avatars</strong> that Reddit plans to drop today, July 26, 2023. As a result, Polygon (MATIC) faces a 1.05% increase, contributing to a Polygon (MATIC) price of $0.7229. Also, the trading volume of Polygon (MATIC) exploded by 27.61%.</p>
<p>According to analysts, Polygon (MATIC) will stay on a bullish run only if the pressure that Polygon (MATIC) faces <strong>don’t affect it negatively</strong>.</p>
<h2>VC Spectra (SPCT) Showcases Impressive Presale Stats</h2>
<p><a href="https://vcspectra.io/">VC Spectra</a> (SPCT) is a revolutionary decentralized hedge fund that offers a lot of benefits for investors. This fantastic passive income option works on trustless and transparent blockchain infrastructure. In addition, it also provides <strong>regular dividends and buybacks</strong> from investment profits.</p>
<p>Furthermore, VC Spectra (SPCT) gives you access to ICOs during private seed sale events, and you’ll even get total voting rights.</p>
<p>More precisely, VC Spectra (SPCT) has <strong>algorithmic and systematic</strong> trading strategies that help it make informed decisions.</p>
<p>What’s even better, <a href="https://vcspectra.io/">VC Spectra</a> (SPCT) comes with unique SPCT tokens. Before they got into presale, they were part of a private seed sale. Within two weeks, VS Spectra sold 125 million SPCT tokens and <strong>raised $2.4 million</strong>. These tokens are standard BRC-20 ones and enable you to exchange, trade decentralized, manage assets, and pay transaction fees.</p>
<p>SPCT tokens are currently in Stage 2 of the public presale and <strong>increased by 37.5%.</strong> In other words, you can now get SPCT tokens for <strong>$0.011</strong>. Moreover, VC Spectra (SPCT) is in front of a 627% surge once its tokens launch on popular exchanges.</p>
<p>Furthermore, VC Spectra (SPCT) tokens will enter Stage 3 and <strong>jump by 127.27%</strong> from the current price. Therefore, they’ll cost <strong>$0.025.</strong> As soon as the presale of VC Spectra finishes, SPCT tokens will get a price of <strong>$0.08.</strong></p>
<p>That’s why we recommend purchasing SPCT tokens now, so you can benefit from all price increases while they are still affordable!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/vc-spectra-attracts-investors-as-arbitrum-and-polygon-price-drops/">VC Spectra Attracts Investors as Arbitrum and Polygon Price Drops</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/vc-spectra-attracts-investors-as-arbitrum-and-polygon-price-drops/">VC Spectra Attracts Investors as Arbitrum and Polygon Price Drops</a> was first posted on July 29, 2023 at 4:15 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/vc-spectra-attracts-investors-as-arbitrum-and-polygon-price-drops/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>When To Sell Filecoin (FIL)? Maker (MKR) and VC Spectra (SPCT) Hint at Further Price Upside</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/when-to-sell-filecoin-fil-maker-mkr-and-vc-spectra-spct-hint-at-further-price-upside/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/when-to-sell-filecoin-fil-maker-mkr-and-vc-spectra-spct-hint-at-further-price-upside/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 05:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VC Spectra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VC Spectra (SPCT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VC Spectra update]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65407</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Recent weeks have seen notable price gains for Filecoin (FIL), Maker (MKR), and VC Spectra (SPCT). Although all three have established a reputation as significant [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/when-to-sell-filecoin-fil-maker-mkr-and-vc-spectra-spct-hint-at-further-price-upside/">When To Sell Filecoin (FIL)? Maker (MKR) and VC Spectra (SPCT) Hint at Further Price Upside</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/when-to-sell-filecoin-fil-maker-mkr-and-vc-spectra-spct-hint-at-further-price-upside/">When To Sell Filecoin (FIL)? Maker (MKR) and VC Spectra (SPCT) Hint at Further Price Upside</a> was first posted on July 28, 2023 at 5:04 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Recent weeks have seen notable price gains for Filecoin (FIL), Maker (MKR), and VC Spectra (SPCT). Although all three have established a reputation as significant <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/whats-in-store-for-cryptocurrencies-in-2023-here-are-five-market-predictions/">cryptocurrencies</a>, VC Spectra (SPCT) is the most promising alternative.</p>
<p>VC Spectra (SPCT) raised $2.4 million during its private seed sale, and investors are currently making a beeline to purchase SPCT tokens. Do crypto traders think <a href="https://vcspectra.io/">VC Spectra</a> (SPCT) is a more promising investment than Filecoin (FIL) and Maker (MKR)? Let&#8217;s find out!</p>
<p>BUY SPCT TOKENS NOW</p>
<h2>Will The Filecoin (FIL) $5 Resistance Present An Opportunity For Short Selling?</h2>
<p>Filecoin&#8217;s (FIL) price in the first week of July 2023 was $4.73. As of July 25, 2023, the price has decreased to $4.50, indicating a decline of 4.9%.</p>
<p>In contrast, Filecoin&#8217;s (FIL) storage utilization experienced a 7% increase during the second quarter of 2023. The revenue generated in the same quarter was over $11 million, representing a 40% decrease compared to the previous year. Surprisingly, Filecoin&#8217;s (FIL) market performance has yet to reflect this growth.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, a recurring resistance at the $5 price level has hindered progress. Filecoin (FIL) has encountered two instances of price rejections at the hurdle, rendering it a potential entry point for short selling.</p>
<p>Bullish analysts believe that Filecoin (FIL) might end the year trading at $5, given that network use is increasing. However, bearish analysts predict that Filecoin&#8217;s (FIL) recent surge will be brief and that the token will decline to $3.25.</p>
<h2>Maker (MKR) Remains One of the Top Gainers in July 2023</h2>
<p>Maker (MKR) experienced a significant price increase from July 15 to July 22, reaching its highest in almost a year. As of July 25, 2023, Maker&#8217;s (MKR) price is $1,140, indicating a remarkable 9% surge within 24 hours.</p>
<p>Three additional reasons suggest Maker (MKR) has the potential for further price appreciation.</p>
<ul>
<li>In mid-May, MakerDAO, the decentralized autonomous organization (DAO) introduced a five-phase roadmap.</li>
<li>Major players in the cryptocurrency market have recently made significant deposits, swaps, and accumulations of Maker (MKR) tokens.</li>
<li>The recent implementation of a token buyback program by MakerDAO resulted in a 28% increase in the value of Maker (MKR).</li>
</ul>
<p>The buyback scheme boosted confidence in Maker (MKR), attracting short-term traders and long-term investors to capitalize on the token&#8217;s positive market trend.</p>
<p>The sentiment among Maker&#8217;s (MKR) is bullish, with analysts forecasting a potential price increase to $1,208 within the next 10 days.</p>
<h2>VC Spectra (SPCT) Provides Expansion Potential in Innovative Investment</h2>
<p>VC Spectra (SPCT) is a groundbreaking decentralized fund and trading platform for asset management. The investment team at VC Spectra (SPCT) uses a rigorous selection method to find promising blockchain and tech ventures.</p>
<p>Furthermore, <a href="https://vcspectra.io/">VC Spectra (SPCT)</a> utilizes artificial intelligence to maximize returns while minimizing losses. In addition, the platform leverages cutting-edge algorithmic and systematic trading tactics, which result in very profitable trade execution.</p>
<p>VC Spectra token SPCT is a BRC-20 token used for exchange, decentralized trading, asset management, and transaction fees.</p>
<p>VC Spectra (SPCT) demonstrated its strong potential to early investors by raising over $2.4 million in just two weeks during the private presale. On July 19, 2023, VC Spectra (SPCT) advanced from Stage 1 to Stage 2 of its public presale, resulting in a 37.5% ROI.</p>
<p>VC Spectra&#8217;s (SPCT) Stage 2 public presale tokens are selling at $0.011. Investors in the presale will receive a 25% bonus and a 627% ROI on their deposits.</p>
<p>Additionally, early adopters can expect a $0.025 price increase during the Stage 3 presale, with additional advantages.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/when-to-sell-filecoin-fil-maker-mkr-and-vc-spectra-spct-hint-at-further-price-upside/">When To Sell Filecoin (FIL)? Maker (MKR) and VC Spectra (SPCT) Hint at Further Price Upside</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/when-to-sell-filecoin-fil-maker-mkr-and-vc-spectra-spct-hint-at-further-price-upside/">When To Sell Filecoin (FIL)? Maker (MKR) and VC Spectra (SPCT) Hint at Further Price Upside</a> was first posted on July 28, 2023 at 5:04 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/when-to-sell-filecoin-fil-maker-mkr-and-vc-spectra-spct-hint-at-further-price-upside/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MakerDAO Community Votes For DAI Interest Rate Hike To 8%</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/makerdao-community-votes-for-dai-interest-rate-hike-to-8/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/makerdao-community-votes-for-dai-interest-rate-hike-to-8/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:10:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Decentralized finance (DeFi)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MakerDAO (MKR)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65397</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>MakerDAO&#8216;s community has shown strong support for the implementation of the Enhanced DAI Savings Rate (EDSR) proposal, with an overwhelming majority of over 99.9% voting [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/makerdao-community-votes-for-dai-interest-rate-hike-to-8/">MakerDAO Community Votes For DAI Interest Rate Hike To 8%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/makerdao-community-votes-for-dai-interest-rate-hike-to-8/">MakerDAO Community Votes For DAI Interest Rate Hike To 8%</a> was first posted on July 28, 2023 at 12:10 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://vote.makerdao.com/polling/QmcTRPLx#vote-breakdown">MakerDAO</a>&#8216;s community has shown strong support for the implementation of the Enhanced DAI Savings Rate (EDSR) proposal, with an overwhelming majority of over 99.9% voting in favor. The voting process began on July 24 and recently concluded, with less than 0.5% of the community voting against it.<br /><br />The EDSR, as outlined in the proposal presented by MakerDAO&#8217;s founder, Rune Christensen, will temporarily increase the DAI savings rate (DSR) for users when DSR utilization is low. Once utilization reaches a certain threshold, the one-time EDSR mechanism will be phased out.<br /><br />Currently, MakerDAO <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/makerdao-votes-over-decreasing-stablecoin-fees-for-first-time-in-5-months/">offers</a> a DAI savings rate of 3.19%, which is among the highest in the decentralized finance (DeFi) sector. However, this high rate has not generated the desired growth in demand and capital inflow for the DeFi lending protocol. With the implementation of the EDSR, the savings rate could potentially reach as high as 8%, more than double what competitors like Aave and Compound offer.<br /><br />The intention behind the elevated interest rate is to encourage stablecoin users to consider DAI over other popular rivals like USDT and <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/makerdaos-creator-thinks-selling-usdc-might-be-a-risky-move/">USDC</a>. By doing so, DAI holders would receive a larger share of the protocol&#8217;s earnings, incentivizing greater adoption of the token.<br /><br />Founder Rune Christensen emphasized the importance of focusing on growing the demand for DAI and DSR as a key short-term mission for the MakerDAO community.<br /><br />The governance vote came at a time of concern over <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/dai-records-new-milestone-with-1-billion-market-cap-for-the-first-time/">DAI</a>&#8216;s circulation, which has seen a decline of about one-third over the past year. Despite boasting a substantial market capitalization of $4.5 billion, the daily trading volume of DAI has also experienced a significant drop of over 80% since last year.<br /><br />The strong community support for the Enhanced DAI Savings Rate proposal reflects the MakerDAO community&#8217;s determination to boost demand for DAI and further solidify its position in the competitive DeFi landscape. The hope is that the increased interest rate will attract more users and ultimately address the decline in circulation experienced recently.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/makerdao-community-votes-for-dai-interest-rate-hike-to-8/">MakerDAO Community Votes For DAI Interest Rate Hike To 8%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/makerdao-community-votes-for-dai-interest-rate-hike-to-8/">MakerDAO Community Votes For DAI Interest Rate Hike To 8%</a> was first posted on July 28, 2023 at 12:10 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/makerdao-community-votes-for-dai-interest-rate-hike-to-8/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH) Volatility at Multiyear Lows</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-btc-ethereum-eth-volatility-at-multiyear-lows/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-btc-ethereum-eth-volatility-at-multiyear-lows/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 23:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65360</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) have experienced a significant decline in volatility, reaching multiyear lows. This newfound stability has raised several questions among investors and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-btc-ethereum-eth-volatility-at-multiyear-lows/">Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH) Volatility at Multiyear Lows</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-btc-ethereum-eth-volatility-at-multiyear-lows/">Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH) Volatility at Multiyear Lows</a> was first posted on July 27, 2023 at 11:29 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/something-is-brewing-on-bitcoin-btc-and-ethereum-eth-this-is-what-key-and-on-chain-indicators-are-insinuating/">Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH)</a> have experienced a significant decline in volatility, reaching multiyear lows. This newfound stability has raised several questions among investors and analysts about the implications for these leading cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-65398 " src="https://www.kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Kaiko-data-300x277.png" alt="" width="212" height="196" srcset="https://www.kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Kaiko-data-300x277.png 300w, https://www.kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Kaiko-data-768x709.png 768w, https://www.kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Kaiko-data.png 880w" sizes="(max-width: 212px) 100vw, 212px" /></p>
<h6 style="text-align: center"><span style="color: #999999"><em>BTC and ETH 90day Historical Volatility, Courtesy: <a style="color: #999999" href="https://twitter.com/KaikoData/status/1684562442838487040">KaikoData</a></em></span></h6>
<p>Bitcoin and Ethereum have <a href="https://twitter.com/KaikoData/status/1684562442838487040">shown</a> a remarkable decline in price volatility in recent months, reaching levels not seen in several years. This phenomenon has surprised many market participants, given the traditionally erratic nature of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<h2>Possible Reasons for Decreased Volatility</h2>
<p><strong>Market Maturation:</strong> As the crypto market matures, it tends to attract a broader range of investors, including institutional players with longer investment horizons. This influx of more traditional investors could stabilize the market, reducing short-term speculative activity and consequent price swings.<br /><br /><strong>Increased Adoption and Liquidity:</strong> As cryptocurrencies gain wider acceptance and are adopted by more businesses and individuals, liquidity in the market improves. Greater liquidity tends to absorb sudden price movements, resulting in reduced volatility.<br /><br /><strong>Regulatory Clarity:</strong> Clearer regulatory frameworks and government acceptance of cryptocurrencies in various jurisdictions can instill confidence among investors. Regulatory clarity may deter manipulative practices and reduce market uncertainty, leading to more stable price behavior.<br /><br /><strong>Market Sentiment:</strong> Positive news and developments within the crypto space, such as technological advancements or notable endorsements from influential figures, can contribute to positive market sentiment. A more optimistic outlook could lead to a reduction in panic selling and excessive speculation.<br /><br />The recent decline in volatility for <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-volatility-reduced-after-third-halving-as-hash-rate-falls/">Bitcoin</a> and Ethereum marks a notable shift in the cryptocurrency market. While it is challenging to predict the future trajectory with certainty, the reduced volatility could signify a maturing market attracting a broader range of investors.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-btc-ethereum-eth-volatility-at-multiyear-lows/">Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH) Volatility at Multiyear Lows</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-btc-ethereum-eth-volatility-at-multiyear-lows/">Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH) Volatility at Multiyear Lows</a> was first posted on July 27, 2023 at 11:29 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-btc-ethereum-eth-volatility-at-multiyear-lows/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>$60 Million Worth of Bitcoin Transferred by Whales in Less Than a Week</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/60-million-worth-of-bitcoin-transferred-by-whales-in-less-than-a-week/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/60-million-worth-of-bitcoin-transferred-by-whales-in-less-than-a-week/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 01:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65355</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Last week, several prominent investors holding substantial amounts of BTC, which had been dormant for years, made notable movements with their holdings. On July 20, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/60-million-worth-of-bitcoin-transferred-by-whales-in-less-than-a-week/">$60 Million Worth of Bitcoin Transferred by Whales in Less Than a Week</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/60-million-worth-of-bitcoin-transferred-by-whales-in-less-than-a-week/">$60 Million Worth of Bitcoin Transferred by Whales in Less Than a Week</a> was first posted on July 26, 2023 at 1:04 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Last week, several prominent investors holding substantial amounts of <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-btc-to-break-equilibrium-and-trigger-volatility-glassnode/">BTC</a>, which had been dormant for years, made notable movements with their holdings. On July 20, two wallets originating from 2011, each containing 10 BTC (worth $292,767 at the current valuation), transferred their assets to new addresses. The following day, a wallet that had remained inactive for 12 years and held 5 BTC ($146,383) also saw some activity.</p>
<p>Another significant event occurred when approximately $30.3 million worth of &#8220;digital gold,&#8221; equivalent to 1,037 BTC, moved after lying <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1682577125520601089">dormant</a> since 2012, a period when the price per coin was just $4.92.<br /><br />Adding to these movements, on July 24, a wallet from 2010 transferred a substantial 50 BTC, valued at $1.4 million. These instances highlight the activity of Bitcoin Whales, a term used for investors who accumulate large amounts of BTC (typically at least 1,000 BTC) and hold onto them for extended periods, reaping significant gains as a result of Bitcoin&#8217;s remarkable price surge over the past decade.<br /><br />Bitcoin&#8217;s value has experienced extraordinary growth, rising from under $95 per coin a decade ago to $29,203 today, reflecting an astounding 30,700% increase. Such long-term investors have outperformed traders engaged in short-term buying and selling, acknowledging the cryptocurrency&#8217;s inherent volatility in the short run.<br /><br />Throughout this year, Bitcoin whales have been notably active. According to a report by the blockchain data firm <a href="https://insights.glassnode.com/the-week-onchain-week-30-2023/">Glassnode</a> on Monday, there has been a substantial increase in whale activity in recent months. Many of these whales have been seen moving their holdings to exchanges, a typical strategy for cashing out or reallocating assets to other digital currencies.<br /><br />The identity of these whales, whether they are individuals or entities, remains unclear. Dr. Kirill Kretov, a developer of automated trading tools and a blockchain analyst, suggests that these transactions might represent commercial entities acquiring Bitcoin from individual holders. <br /><br />Regardless of the entities involved, these movements indicate significant shifts in the Bitcoin market and continue to draw attention to the actions of major BTC holders.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/60-million-worth-of-bitcoin-transferred-by-whales-in-less-than-a-week/">$60 Million Worth of Bitcoin Transferred by Whales in Less Than a Week</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/60-million-worth-of-bitcoin-transferred-by-whales-in-less-than-a-week/">$60 Million Worth of Bitcoin Transferred by Whales in Less Than a Week</a> was first posted on July 26, 2023 at 1:04 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/60-million-worth-of-bitcoin-transferred-by-whales-in-less-than-a-week/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance to Boost Japan Services With New Platform Launching in August</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/binance-to-boost-japan-services-with-new-platform-launching-in-august/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/binance-to-boost-japan-services-with-new-platform-launching-in-august/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:41:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65357</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance, the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange, is set to launch its full range of services on its new platform in Japan this August. The announcement [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/binance-to-boost-japan-services-with-new-platform-launching-in-august/">Binance to Boost Japan Services With New Platform Launching in August</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/binance-to-boost-japan-services-with-new-platform-launching-in-august/">Binance to Boost Japan Services With New Platform Launching in August</a> was first posted on July 26, 2023 at 12:41 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/binance-publishes-list-containing-10-fundamental-rights-for-crypto-users/">Binance</a>, the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange, is set to launch its full range of services on its new platform in Japan this August. The announcement was made by the founder of Binance, Changpeng Zhao, during a video presentation at a conference in Tokyo on Tuesday.</p>
<p>The move comes after Binance acquired Sakura Exchange BitCoin in November last year. In May of this year, the firm revealed its plans to create a platform that fully complies with local regulations in Japan, signaling its commitment to operating within the country&#8217;s legal framework.</p>
<p>While expanding its presence in other Asian markets like South Korea and Thailand, Binance has also faced significant <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-25/binance-to-start-full-services-on-new-japan-platform-in-august?utm_source=twitter&amp;utm_medium=social&amp;utm_content=crypto&amp;utm_campaign=socialflow-organic">regulatory scrutiny</a> in various jurisdictions worldwide. This increased attention from regulators has prompted the exchange to take steps to ensure compliance and address regulatory concerns.</p>
<p>During the conference in Japan, Binance&#8217;s local General Manager, Takeshi Chino, hinted at the possibility of introducing stablecoins in the country. Japan&#8217;s stablecoin law, which came into effect on June 1, permits licensed banks, registered money transfer agents, and trust companies to issue such tokens.</p>
<p>Richard Teng, the head of regional markets at Binance and seen by some as a potential successor to Changpeng Zhao, expressed optimism about the future of cryptocurrencies. He highlighted the growing interest in crypto from traditional financial players, suggesting that this trend could accelerate mass adoption at a much faster pace.</p>
<p>Overall, Binance&#8217;s forthcoming full-scale platform in Japan and its potential entry into the stablecoin market demonstrate the exchange&#8217;s dedication to navigating the regulatory landscape while continuing to drive innovation and crypto adoption in the region and beyond.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/binance-to-boost-japan-services-with-new-platform-launching-in-august/">Binance to Boost Japan Services With New Platform Launching in August</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/binance-to-boost-japan-services-with-new-platform-launching-in-august/">Binance to Boost Japan Services With New Platform Launching in August</a> was first posted on July 26, 2023 at 12:41 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/binance-to-boost-japan-services-with-new-platform-launching-in-august/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple’s Victory Over SEC in Lawsuit: What’s Next?</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/ripples-victory-over-sec-in-lawsuit-whats-next/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/ripples-victory-over-sec-in-lawsuit-whats-next/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 01:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP (XRP)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65346</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a landmark ruling, Ripple, the blockchain-based payment network, emerged victorious in its legal battle against the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The court&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/ripples-victory-over-sec-in-lawsuit-whats-next/">Ripple&#8217;s Victory Over SEC in Lawsuit: What&#8217;s Next?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/ripples-victory-over-sec-in-lawsuit-whats-next/">Ripple&#8217;s Victory Over SEC in Lawsuit: What&#8217;s Next?</a> was first posted on July 25, 2023 at 1:07 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In a landmark ruling, <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/xrp-price-analysis-positive-advance-amid-new-win-in-sec-lawsuit-ripplenet-bags-soc-2-certification/">Ripple</a>, the blockchain-based payment network, emerged victorious in its legal battle against the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The court&#8217;s <a href="https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-judge-says-sec-lawsuit-vs-ripple-labs-can-proceed-trial-some-claims-2023-07-13/">decision</a> has far-reaching implications not only for Ripple but also for the broader cryptocurrency industry. With the lawsuit behind it, Ripple now faces a pivotal moment as it sets its sights on the future.<br /><br />The SEC filed a lawsuit against Ripple in late 2020, alleging that the company&#8217;s native cryptocurrency, XRP, was an unregistered security. The lawsuit sent shockwaves through the crypto community, as the outcome could have serious ramifications for other digital assets with uncertain regulatory status.<br /><br />Ripple staunchly defended its case, arguing that XRP is not a security but rather a digital currency utilized for cross-border transactions. Throughout the legal battle, Ripple received<a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/xrp-price-analysis-xrp-jumps-13-ripple-sees-backing-from-another-major-player-in-lawsuit/"> support</a> from numerous industry players and its community, which believed that the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit could stifle innovation and disrupt the cryptocurrency market.<br /><br />In a surprising turn of events, the court ruled in favor of Ripple, stating that XRP did not meet the criteria of a security under U.S. securities laws. The judge&#8217;s decision was a significant victory for the company, vindicating its position and providing a precedent for other cryptocurrencies facing similar regulatory challenges.</p>
<h2>What&#8217;s Next for Ripple?</h2>
<p>With the lawsuit in the rearview mirror, Ripple now faces several critical decisions and opportunities. The court&#8217;s ruling bolsters market confidence in XRP and Ripple&#8217;s operations. This newfound certainty may encourage a surge of interest from investors and businesses, potentially leading to increased adoption of the Ripple network for cross-border payments and remittances.<br /><br />Ripple&#8217;s victory may pave the way for other blockchain projects and cryptocurrencies to reassess their regulatory strategies. <br /><br />As regulatory uncertainty lifts, Ripple can focus on forging stronger partnerships with financial institutions and other blockchain projects.<br /><br />Despite the court&#8217;s favorable ruling, Ripple will likely continue to work closely with regulators to ensure compliance with relevant laws and regulations.<br /><br />Ripple&#8217;s triumph over the SEC represents a significant turning point for the cryptocurrency industry. The verdict not only vindicates Ripple&#8217;s position on XRP&#8217;s <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/07/24/implications-of-ripple-sec-court-ruling-for-wider-crypto-industry-are-unclear-bank-of-america/#:~:text=%E2%80%9CThe%20judge%20ruled%20that%20Ripple's,market%2C%E2%80%9D%20analysts%20Alkesh%20Shah%20and">regulatory status</a> but also provides much-needed clarity for the broader blockchain community.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/ripples-victory-over-sec-in-lawsuit-whats-next/">Ripple&#8217;s Victory Over SEC in Lawsuit: What&#8217;s Next?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/ripples-victory-over-sec-in-lawsuit-whats-next/">Ripple&#8217;s Victory Over SEC in Lawsuit: What&#8217;s Next?</a> was first posted on July 25, 2023 at 1:07 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/ripples-victory-over-sec-in-lawsuit-whats-next/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Exchange and Sam Bankman-Fried: A Cautionary Tale of Excess</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/ftx-exchange-and-sam-bankman-fried-a-cautionary-tale-of-excess/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65344</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the fast-paced world of cryptocurrency exchanges, few names have captured the spotlight as brightly as FTX and its enigmatic CEO, Sam Bankman-Fried. Founded in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/ftx-exchange-and-sam-bankman-fried-a-cautionary-tale-of-excess/">FTX Exchange and Sam Bankman-Fried: A Cautionary Tale of Excess</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/ftx-exchange-and-sam-bankman-fried-a-cautionary-tale-of-excess/">FTX Exchange and Sam Bankman-Fried: A Cautionary Tale of Excess</a> was first posted on July 25, 2023 at 12:32 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In the fast-paced world of cryptocurrency exchanges, few names have captured the spotlight as brightly as FTX and its enigmatic CEO, <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bitcoins-next-strong-support-is-25000-says-ftx-ceo-and-founder/">Sam Bankman-Fried</a>. Founded in 2017, FTX quickly rose to prominence, known for its innovative products and aggressive marketing strategies. However, like many tales of meteoric success, the story of FTX and its charismatic leader eventually took a dramatic turn, leading to its eventual downfall.<br /><br />FTX&#8217;s journey to the top of the crypto exchange world was swift. Under Bankman-Fried&#8217;s leadership, the platform gained a reputation for offering an extensive range of trading products, including leveraged tokens and derivatives linked to various digital assets. Investors and traders flocked to the exchange, drawn by the allure of high leverage and the potential for extraordinary profits.<br /><br />Moreover, Bankman-Fried&#8217;s captivating persona and visionary statements earned him a considerable following among the crypto community. He was hailed as a young genius and an emblem of the new financial era.<br /><br />Amid the growing popularity, concerns started to emerge about the risk associated with FTX&#8217;s highly leveraged products. Regulators from different countries warned about the dangers of such instruments, fearing that retail investors might face significant losses without fully understanding the risks involved.<br /><br />As FTX expanded its offerings, it also ventured into uncharted territory by launching exotic derivatives tied to unpredictable and volatile cryptocurrencies. This move exposed the exchange to heightened risks and potential market manipulation, which did not go unnoticed by regulators and industry experts.<br /><br />Furthermore, allegations of improper business practices and unethical behavior started surfacing. Rumors of insider trading, market manipulation, and lax security measures spread like wildfire across social media platforms, damaging FTX&#8217;s reputation and credibility.<br /><br />The tipping point for FTX came when regulators launched a full-scale<a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/ftx-sam-bankman-fried-transferred-assets-to-bahamas-government-after-bankruptcy/"> investigation</a> into the exchange and its CEO. With mounting evidence of wrongdoing and an increasingly negative public perception, the exchange&#8217;s user base started to erode rapidly. Investors and traders, once excited by the promise of astronomical gains, now seek refuge in more reputable and compliant platforms.<br /><br />As FTX&#8217;s trading volumes plummeted, liquidity dried up, and the exchange faced an increasing number of withdrawal requests. With the exchange&#8217;s financial stability called into question, FTX struggled to survive the relentless storm of scrutiny.<br /><br />The downfall of FTX serves as a stark reminder of the perils that await those who prioritize short-term gains over long-term sustainability and regulatory compliance. The story of Sam Bankman-Fried and FTX stands as a cautionary tale for entrepreneurs and industry leaders alike, emphasizing the importance of transparency, responsibility, and ethical practices in the world of cryptocurrencies.<br /><br />As the dust settles on the FTX saga, the world watches with a discerning eye, awaiting the next chapter in the ever-changing landscape of cryptocurrencies, hoping that lessons learned from past mistakes will pave the way for a more sustainable and trustworthy future.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/ftx-exchange-and-sam-bankman-fried-a-cautionary-tale-of-excess/">FTX Exchange and Sam Bankman-Fried: A Cautionary Tale of Excess</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/ftx-exchange-and-sam-bankman-fried-a-cautionary-tale-of-excess/">FTX Exchange and Sam Bankman-Fried: A Cautionary Tale of Excess</a> was first posted on July 25, 2023 at 12:32 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Comprehensive Guide on Selling USDT in Dubai</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/a-comprehensive-guide-on-selling-usdt-in-dubai/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 14:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65294</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As cryptocurrencies continue to rise in popularity, USDT (Tether) has emerged as one of the most widely used stablecoins in the digital currency market. Designed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/a-comprehensive-guide-on-selling-usdt-in-dubai/">A Comprehensive Guide on Selling USDT in Dubai</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/a-comprehensive-guide-on-selling-usdt-in-dubai/">A Comprehensive Guide on Selling USDT in Dubai</a> was first posted on July 13, 2023 at 2:28 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>As cryptocurrencies continue to rise in popularity, USDT (Tether) has emerged as one of the most widely used stablecoins in the digital currency market. Designed to maintain a stable value by pegging it to a fiat currency, USDT offers a reliable and convenient means of transacting in the crypto market. This comprehensive guide will provide you with all the insights into the history of USDT, its key features, and a step-by-step process on how to sell USDT in Dubai.</p> 

<h2>Selling USDT in Dubai</h2>

<p>One of the most sought after questions in the UAE crypto market is <a href="https://finchain.tech/sell-usdt-in-dubai/">how to sell USDT in Dubai</a>? Perhaps, the answer to this question is simple and straightforward. Hence, we have provided you a detailed step-by-step guide on the selling process of USDT:</p>
<ul>
    <li>Step 1: Choose a trusted and reputed cryptocurrency exchange</li>
    <li>Step 2: Complete account creation and verification</li>
    <li>Step 3: Deposit USDT</li>
    <li>Step 4: Place a sale order on the crypto exchange</li>
    <li>Step 5: Execute the sell order</li>
    <li>Step 6: Withdraw the funds</li>
</ul>
<h3>Step 1: Choose a trusted and reputed cryptocurrency exchange</h3>

<p>Select a reputable cryptocurrency exchange that supports USDT trading and operates in Dubai. Ensure that the exchange offers USDT trading pairs with major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin (BTC) or Ethereum (ETH).</p>

<h3>Step 2: Complete account creation and verification</h3>

<p>Once you have identified the platform you wish to trade on, the next step will be for you to create an account and verify yourself. During this step, you will need to provide all the relevant fields of information and ensure it to be accurate.</p>

<p>Additionally, the verification process is as per the exchange&#8217;s requirements. Therefore, it will include identity verification and KYC (Know Your Customer) procedures.

<h3>Step 3: Deposit USDT</h3>

<p>Generate a USDT wallet address on the exchange platform. Transfer your USDT tokens from your personal wallet to the provided exchange wallet address. Ensure that you initiate the transfer on the correct blockchain network as per the specifications provided by the exchange.</p>

<h3>Step 4: Place a sale order on the crypto exchange platform</h3>

<p>Access the trading interface on the exchange and navigate to the USDT trading pair (e.g., BTC/USDT or ETH/USDT). Specify the amount of USDT you wish to sell and set the desired selling price or choose a market order for an immediate sale. Review the details and confirm the sell order.</p>

<h3>Step 5: Execute the sell order</h3> 

<p>After your sell order is being placed, the platform’s order matching system will find a buyer willing to purchase your USDT at the specified price. Once the order is executed, the USDT will be exchanged for the chosen cryptocurrency or fiat currency (e.g., AED) as per the trading pair.</p>

<h3>Step 6: Withdraw the funds</h3>

<p>If you wish to convert the received funds into fiat currency, you must navigate to the withdrawal section of the exchange platform. Here you will be provided with a set of instructions that you must follow to withdraw your funds to your bank account. You can also select an alternative withdrawal method offered by the exchange.</p>

<h2>History of USDT: When and how it started?</h2>

<p>USDT was launched in 2014 by Tether Limited. It was initially built on the Bitcoin blockchain as an Omni Layer protocol token. However, in 2018, USDT expanded to other major blockchain networks, including Ethereum (ERC-20) and Tron (TRC-20).</p>

<p>Tether Limited aims to maintain a 1:1 ratio between USDT and the U.S. dollar, providing stability to investors worldwide.</p>

<h2>Features of USDT that you must know about</h2>

<p>There are several features associated with USDT. However, we have mentioned some of the most important features that describe the nature of this stable coin.</p>
<ul>
    <li>Stable value</li>
    <li>Widespread acceptance</li>
    <li>Liquidity</li>
    <li>Transparency</li>
    <li>Global availability</li>
</ul>
<h3>Stable value</h3>

<p>USDT coins have been designed to retain a stable value equivalent to the underlying fiat currency (usually the U.S. dollar).</p>

<h3>Widespread acceptance</h3>

<p>USDT has also garnered widespread acceptance on various cryptocurrency <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/tag/exchanges-news/" target="_blank">exchanges</a>, making it easily tradable.</p>

<h3>Liquidity</h3>

<p>Due to its popularity, USDT coins generally enjoy <a href="https://www.wallstreetmojo.com/liquidity-in-cryptocurrency/#:~:text=Moreover%2C%20an%20asset%20with%20high,investors%20and%20high%20trading%20volume" target="_blank">high liquidity</a>, allowing investors for easy buying and selling experience.</p>

<h3>Transparency</h3>

<p>Tether Limited claims to provide regular audits to ensure that the USDT tokens in circulation are fully backed by reserves.</p>

<h3>Global availability</h3>

<p>Lastly, USDT is accessible to users worldwide and can be utilized for cross-border transactions.</p>

<h2>Sell USDT in Dubai: Easy and quick</h2>

<p>USDT (Tether) has become an essential stablecoin in the cryptocurrency market, providing users with stability and liquidity. Selling USDT in Dubai follows a straightforward process, involving choosing a reputable exchange, creating an account, depositing USDT, placing a sell order, executing the trade, and withdrawing the funds. Remember to conduct thorough research on exchange platforms, adhere to security measures, and consider transaction fees before engaging in any selling or trading activities.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/a-comprehensive-guide-on-selling-usdt-in-dubai/">A Comprehensive Guide on Selling USDT in Dubai</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/a-comprehensive-guide-on-selling-usdt-in-dubai/">A Comprehensive Guide on Selling USDT in Dubai</a> was first posted on July 13, 2023 at 2:28 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>WhiteBIT Announced the Retrodrop for WB Network Testing</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/whiteBIT-announced-the-retrodrop-for-WB-network-testing/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 14:50:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65292</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In preparation for the release of the WB Network mainnet, representatives of the WhiteBIT crypto exchange shared the details of a retrodrop, a reward for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/whiteBIT-announced-the-retrodrop-for-WB-network-testing/">WhiteBIT Announced the Retrodrop for WB Network Testing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/whiteBIT-announced-the-retrodrop-for-WB-network-testing/">WhiteBIT Announced the Retrodrop for WB Network Testing</a> was first posted on July 3, 2023 at 2:20 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><i>In preparation for the release of the WB Network mainnet, representatives of the WhiteBIT crypto exchange shared the details of a retrodrop, a reward for testing the WB Network blockchain.</i></p>
<p>WhiteBIT, one of Europe&#8217;s largest crypto exchanges, has announced a retrodrop for testing WB Network blockchain. The launch of the testnet took place in March of this year, and with the approach of the mainnet release, the exchange began to talk about a possible retrodrop. On June 9, WhiteBIT published a post with the code word &#8220;retrodrop&#8221; causing a stir among the exchange community and the cryptocurrency community in general.</p>
<p>The &#8220;retrodrop&#8221; signifies the exchange&#8217;s endorsement for the crypto community to actively engage in the WB Network testing, enabling them to personally assess the potential of the blockchain. For this purpose, the WhiteBIT team allocated an as-yet undisclosed amount of WBT from the ecosystem fund. This occasion holds significance not only for the blockchain project&#8217;s journey but also for the broader crypto community. It empowers anyone with the desire to explore the network&#8217;s capabilities to participate and receive rewards in the process.</p>
<h3>Completion of three types of activities provides participation in retrodrop.</h3>
<p>Exchange-related tasks, namely the creation of WB Soul and the holding of WhiteBIT Token (WBT). You can read the details in the <a href="https://blog.whitebit.com/en/wb-soul-ecosystem/">article</a>. WB Soul serves as a digital representation of a user within the WB Network blockchain, acting as a bridge between the WhiteBIT exchange and the blockchain. It is essential to note that creating a WB Soul is a mandatory requirement for participating in the retrodrop. While other activities remain optional, completing them can enhance the overall experience.</p>
<p><a href="https://whitebit.com/boost">Holding WBT</a> involves storing the exchange&#8217;s native token on a special holding balance on the exchange, which provides holders with a number of advantages and bonuses. There are 11 levels of holding. The higher the level, the greater the reward. In an unconventional move for retrodrops, the exchange representatives have expressed their intention to honor the devoted supporters and enthusiasts of the WhiteBIT ecosystem by introducing this specific requirement.</p>
<p>Testnet-related tasks: WhiteBIT team has decided not to publicize the list of these activities to ensure transparency of the process. Users are encouraged to explore the blockchain and define their own approach to testing.</p>
<p>Finally, community and social media tasks on the <a href="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://zealy.io/c/wbnetwork/questboard&#038;sa=D&#038;source=docs&#038;ust=1688033761922694&#038;usg=AOvVaw0PaXvEu1U5FvaEGop1xw3w">Zealy</a> platform.</p>
<p>WBT rewards will be distributed shortly after the mainnet release. The team promises to inform the users about the details in separate publications.</p>
<h3>What are the main features of WB Network?</h3>
<p>To ensure EVM compatibility and the ability to integrate DeFi solutions, WB Network was developed on the basis of Geth (Go-Ethereum). Proof-of-Authority (PoA) was chosen as the consensus algorithm. According to the working principle of PoA, the only validators and block generators are trusted authorized nodes. Proof-of-Authority provides a high TPS (the number of transactions that the network can process per second), low fees, a predictable block generation interval, and protection against single hacks. One of the unique features of the WB Network blockchain is its own WB Soul Ecosystem. It makes it possible to create a WB Soul — a kind of identification card of a user in the WB Network, which will bridge the blockchain and the WhiteBIT exchange. WB Soul will serve as a digital ID for users of the exchange and the WB Network, which will combine CEX with the Web3 ecosystem solutions. In addition, during a conversation with WhiteBIT representatives, it became clear that the presence of WB Soul will play an important role in the long-awaited WBT Earn program.</p>
<p>Volodymyr Nosov, the CEO of WhiteBIT, commented on the excitement surrounding the news of testing and retrodrop. He stated, &#8220;Our goal is for the WB Network blockchain to be the product of collective community interaction, blending the expertise of industry leaders with the insights of users, developers, and enthusiasts. Users are best equipped to optimize the convenience and efficiency of a project as vast as blockchain. Hence, we invite everyone to explore the potential of this future blockchain and witness the realization of our shared vision.&#8221;</p>
<p>WhiteBIT is one of the largest European centralized crypto exchanges, originally from Ukraine, founded in 2018. Today, the company has more than 1,000 specialists. The exchange offers 350+ trading pairs, 270+ assets, and 10+ state currencies. The highest average daily trading volume is more than $2.5 billion. WhiteBIT is the official crypto partner of FC Barcelona, FC Trabzonspor, and the national football team of Ukraine.</p>
<p>Contact of WhiteBIT Press Service<br />
<a href="mailto:">pr@whitebit.com</a><br />
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/whiteBIT-announced-the-retrodrop-for-WB-network-testing/">WhiteBIT Announced the Retrodrop for WB Network Testing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/whiteBIT-announced-the-retrodrop-for-WB-network-testing/">WhiteBIT Announced the Retrodrop for WB Network Testing</a> was first posted on July 3, 2023 at 2:20 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chibi Finance $1M “Rug Pull” on Arbitrum Network: ARB Rises Thanks to a Whale, Smart Investors Move to A New Token with A 900% Potential</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/chibi-finance-rug-pull-on-arbitrum-network/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 14:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65290</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>DeFi project Chibi Finance deleted its online presence after redistributing nearly $1 million worth of tokens staked on Arbitrum&#8217;s (ARB) network. Although Arbitrum (ARB) is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/chibi-finance-rug-pull-on-arbitrum-network/">Chibi Finance $1M “Rug Pull” on Arbitrum Network: ARB Rises Thanks to a Whale, Smart Investors Move to A New Token with A 900% Potential</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/chibi-finance-rug-pull-on-arbitrum-network/">Chibi Finance $1M “Rug Pull” on Arbitrum Network: ARB Rises Thanks to a Whale, Smart Investors Move to A New Token with A 900% Potential</a> was first posted on June 30, 2023 at 2:32 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DeFi project Chibi Finance deleted its online presence after redistributing nearly $1 million worth of tokens staked on Arbitrum&#8217;s (ARB) network. Although Arbitrum (ARB) is currently surging because of a recent massive withdrawal by an Arbitrum (ARB) whale, smart crypto investors are choosing VC Spectra (SPCT) as a permanent solution because of its <strong>amazing 900% potential</strong> and <strong>incredible real-life utility.</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://vcspectra.io/">BUY SPECTRA TOKENS NOW</a></p>
<p>Chibi Finance Vanishes After Stealing Over 90,000 Arbitrum (ARB) Tokens</p>
<p>The team behind <strong>Arbitrum (ARB) based DeFi project Chibi Finance</strong> disappeared after stealing user deposits worth approximately $1 million. The rug pull involved <strong>90,563.95</strong> Arbitrum (ARB) tokens staked by Chibi Finance&#8217;s users.</p>
<p>The perpetrators allegedly bridged the funds from Arbitrum&#8217;s (ARB) to Ethereum&#8217;s (ETH) network and used <strong>Tornado Cash</strong> to cover their tracks. Hence, analysts have advised crypto traders to always do their due diligence and conduct proper research before investing in DeFi projects.</p>
<p>Arbitrum (ARB) is currently priced at <strong>$1.1440</strong>, surging by <strong>17.71%</strong> in the last two weeks. This increase in Arbitrum&#8217;s (ARB) price reflects the June 25 massive Binance <strong>withdrawal of 450,881 Arbitrum (ARB) tokens</strong> (worth approximately $507,000) by previously dormant Arbitrum (ARB) whale ‘0x1b67’.</p>
<p>Arbitrum (ARB) enthusiasts believe that the token will manage to uphold its uptrend in the following term. However, bears advise traders to <strong>invest elsewhere</strong> since Chibi Finance is the 12th Arbitrum (ARB) based project to perform a rug pull in 2023.</p>
<h3>VC Spectra (SPCT) Outshines Competitors as a Hidden Crypto Gem</h3>
<p>VC Spectra&#8217;s (SPCT) <strong>outstanding stability</strong> and <strong>growth potential</strong> have inspired many investors to move away from unreliable tokens like Arbitrum (ARB). Due to its <strong>advanced real-world utility</strong>, this new crypto gem has attracted a large following in the crypto community while still in the public presale phase.</p>
<p>VC Spectra (SPCT) is a <strong>decentralized hedge fund</strong> that provides optimal gains at a minimal risk via the best investment possibilities in the current market space. VC Spectra (SPCT) explores the most lucrative options in current blockchain projects and technology startups and additionally brings users numerous unique benefits.</p>
<p>VC Spectra (SPCT) token holders can delve into a wide array of tokens and niche markets. The platform&#8217;s highly precise <strong>AI systems</strong> detect which projects have the highest chances to succeed through a <strong>rigorous risk analysis</strong> process. Thus, VC Spectra (SPCT) holders can diversify their portfolio with the most viable investments and receive <strong>quarterly dividends and buybacks</strong> from the profits.</p>
<p>Furthermore, VC Spectra (SPCT) convenient interface and visual tools empower users to detect recurring market trends and track their portfolio&#8217;s performance. The VC Spectra (SPCT) deflationary token grants exclusive access to pre-ICO discounts and voting rights for future investments.</p>
<p>In other words, VC Spectra (SPCT) token holders can benefit from the platform&#8217;s successful core funds while having an active say in its <strong>democratic community</strong>.</p>
<p>Currently priced at <strong>$0.008</strong>, the VC Spectra (SPCT) token will bring investors 37.5% returns once it enters the 2nd presale stage and surges to <strong>$0.011</strong>. However, early adopters will obtain as much as <strong>10x gains</strong> during the next presale stages and unbelievably more after <a href="https://vcspectra.io/">VC Spectra (SPCT)</a> official launch!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/chibi-finance-rug-pull-on-arbitrum-network/">Chibi Finance $1M “Rug Pull” on Arbitrum Network: ARB Rises Thanks to a Whale, Smart Investors Move to A New Token with A 900% Potential</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/chibi-finance-rug-pull-on-arbitrum-network/">Chibi Finance $1M “Rug Pull” on Arbitrum Network: ARB Rises Thanks to a Whale, Smart Investors Move to A New Token with A 900% Potential</a> was first posted on June 30, 2023 at 2:32 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chainlink Bulls Break The $6 Barrier – Can LINK Copy SPCT and Continue Its Upward Trajectory?</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/chainlink-bulls-break-barrier-continue/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 11:45:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65288</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chainlink (LINK) has seen quite some action in the past few weeks. Finally, it has garnered enough bulls to break out. Yet, there are multiple [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/chainlink-bulls-break-barrier-continue/">Chainlink Bulls Break The $6 Barrier – Can LINK Copy SPCT and Continue Its Upward Trajectory?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/chainlink-bulls-break-barrier-continue/">Chainlink Bulls Break The $6 Barrier – Can LINK Copy SPCT and Continue Its Upward Trajectory?</a> was first posted on June 29, 2023 at 11:38 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Chainlink (LINK) has seen quite some action in the past few weeks. Finally, it has garnered enough bulls to break out. Yet, there are multiple strong resistance points (places where many people are selling the token), and <strong>LINK needs serious bulls to copy SPCT’s 900% surge potential</strong>. So, the question remains: can LINK copy VC Spectra (SPCT) as it has previously copied BTC? Let’s delve into the details!</p>

<h2><strong><a href="https://vcspectra.io/">BUY SPECTRA TOKENS NOW</a></h2></strong>

<h3>Chainlink Bulls Break The $6 Barrier, Yet Things Don’t Seem Too Bullish</h3>

<p>After seeing a long haul from the sub $6 range in the previous weeks, <strong>Chainlink (LINK) has finally broken through the $6 barrier</strong>. LINK followed in as BTC plummeted 16% and hit its monthly high of $31,233. However, LINK immediately faced its first resistance point of $6.36, which it couldn’t break.</p>

<p>Consequently, <strong>a slightly bearish trend closed the Chainlink token trade at $5.91</strong>. Regardless of the settling bear trend, the bulls finally rose, and the Chainlink token gained 5.49% and <strong>rose above the resistance line of $6.36 momentarily before dropping to $6.1-ish levels on 25th June</strong>.</p>

<p>Getting to the overall trend, the 4H and weekly Chainlink charts clearly show <strong>a growing bear market for LINK</strong>. The token is being oversold, which might result in a further drop in its value. This situation resembles April’s bear market for the Chainlink (LINK) token.</p>

<p>With the recent up trend, we finally see some action from the Chainlink bulls resulting in a slightly bullish trend. However, the $6.36 resistance line might be too much for the bulls after two failed attempts to break through.</p>

<p>Whether Chainlink’s LINK token can break the resistance and turn strongly bullish as the SPCT token entirely depends on its market cap and overall volume, which, as of the time of this writing, is not looking bullish.</p>

<h3>VC Spectra (SPCT) Overtakes the Market with An Upward Trajectory</h3>

<p>VC Spectra (SPCT), the parent chain of the SPCT token, has already raised more than $2.3 million in presales. This ultimately promises its investors a <strong>900% surge</strong> and <strong>10x</strong> their investment as the VC Spectra token price draws nearer to the launch target of <strong>$0.08</strong> from the current price of <strong>$0.008</strong>.</p>

<p>Additionally, VC Spectra (SPCT) is well on its way to maintaining its upward trajectory. With multiple investment portfolios and the strong backing of a hedge fund, VC Spectra (SPCT) is looking to top the charts in green. Especially since there are <strong>no intermediaries involved</strong>, users have <strong>full authority over their funds</strong> and can move them around at will.</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/chainlink-bulls-break-barrier-continue/">Chainlink Bulls Break The $6 Barrier – Can LINK Copy SPCT and Continue Its Upward Trajectory?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/chainlink-bulls-break-barrier-continue/">Chainlink Bulls Break The $6 Barrier – Can LINK Copy SPCT and Continue Its Upward Trajectory?</a> was first posted on June 29, 2023 at 11:38 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is the Minimum RSP Amount in Singapore?</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/what-is-the-minimum-rsp-amount-in-singapore/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 23:41:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65286</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Retirement Sum Scheme (RSS) is designed to help Singaporeans save for retirement. It is crucial in providing financial security and stability, especially during old [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/what-is-the-minimum-rsp-amount-in-singapore/">What is the Minimum RSP Amount in Singapore?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/what-is-the-minimum-rsp-amount-in-singapore/">What is the Minimum RSP Amount in Singapore?</a> was first posted on June 23, 2023 at 7:41 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The Retirement Sum Scheme (RSS) is designed to help Singaporeans save for retirement. It is crucial in providing financial security and stability, especially during old age. However, the RSS also has its limitations. One of them is the minimum Retirement Sum (RSP) amount that Singaporeans need to commit to enjoying the benefits provided by this scheme.</p>
<p>Under the current Central Provident Fund (CPF) Board rules, Singaporean citizens below 55 must set aside a minimum sum of S$85,500 in their CPF accounts as part of their RSP commitment. This amount is known as the Basic Retirement Sum (BRS). Those aged 55 and above must meet a higher RSP amount, the Full Retirement Sum (FRS). This amount is set at S$171,000.</p>
<p>The CPF Board periodically reviews and adjusts the FRS and BRS amounts to reflect changes in life expectancy and inflation levels. The last review for both sets of figures occurred two years ago when they were reviewed upwards by 4%.</p>
<p>In its review report, the CPF Board further stated that &#8220;the Basic Retirement Sum and Full Retirement Sum will be reviewed every five years so that members can enjoy retirement adequacy&#8221;. Singaporeans below 55 can expect their RSP amounts to grow over time.</p>
<p>Additionally, those needing more retirement funds can commit additional amounts beyond the minimum RSP requirement. It can be done in two ways. The first is through the Flexible Retirement Sum (FRS), which allows members to set aside additional funds for a higher monthly payout upon reaching 55.</p>
<p>The second way of topping up one&#8217;s RSP amount is through the Special Retirement Sum (SRS). This scheme incentivises Singaporeans to top up their CPF accounts with extra funds, and it offers them a higher monthly payout after they reach the age of 65.</p>
<h2>Other ways Singaporeans are saving for their retirement</h2>
<p>Many Singaporeans are finding other innovative ways of saving for their retirement. One popular option is the Voluntary Retirement Scheme (VRS). This scheme encourages Singaporeans to top up their CPF accounts with extra funds while still working, and it offers them a higher monthly payout once they reach the age of 65.</p>
<p>Another option is to take out an annuity plan from an insurance company. Annuities provide a steady income stream throughout one&#8217;s retirement, which helps ensure financial security in old age. However, this can be expensive and may only be ideal for some.</p>
<p>Some Singaporeans also invest in property as part of their retirement savings strategy. Property prices in Singapore have been rising steadily over the years, which means that investing in property now can result in huge returns when one reaches retirement age. But it&#8217;s crucial to remember that real estate investments can come with risks, so you should research before deciding.</p>
<p>A more recent development in Singapore is using robo-advisors for retirement planning. Robo-advisors use advanced algorithms and data analytics to offer low-cost personalised investment advice. These services allow users to track their progress towards reaching their goals and make adjustments accordingly.</p>
<p>Many Singaporeans are turning to social media to save for retirement. Using platforms such as Facebook and Instagram, users can connect with people with similar financial and social interests and goals, which can help them find new investment opportunities or ideas for saving money over the long term.</p>
<p>For those looking for more traditional options, endowment plans are available through banks or insurance companies that offer guaranteed returns over a certain period, offering peace of mind and financial security during one&#8217;s golden years.</p>
<p>A <a href="https://www.home.saxo/en-sg/products/regular-savings-plan" target="_blank">regular savings plan</a> is also essential for retirement planning. It involves setting aside a small amount of money monthly and investing it in long-term instruments such as stocks and mutual funds. Regular saving helps to accumulate a substantial sum over time, which can be used during retirement.</p>
<h3>Conclusion</h3>
<p>Singaporeans must assess their financial well-being and understand how much they need to save to fully enjoy a comfortable retirement. It includes familiarising themselves with the minimum RSP amounts to make informed decisions when setting up their respective CPF accounts. In addition, those who need more funds can also consider topping up their accounts through the FRS and SRS schemes for extra financial security in their later years.</p>timed sell orders for BNB tokens, capitalizing on the situation. Data from TradingView reveals that around 125,000 BNB, equivalent to $37 million, were sold in a surge of aggregated sell orders on the BNB/USDT order book on Binance.</p>
<p>These sell orders occurred at 11:45 p.m. UTC on June 4 and 1:45 a.m. UTC on June 5, just before the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) announced its lawsuit against Binance.</p>
<p>Furthermore, <a href="https://coinalyze.net/binance-coin/open-interest/">Coinalyze</a> data indicates that BNB&#8217;s open interest, which represents the total number of outstanding derivative contracts held by investors, increased by approximately $30 million in the first nine hours of June 5.</p>
<p>This rise in open interest occurred before the news of the SEC&#8217;s allegations, revealed at 11:15 a.m., which accused Binance of commingling customer funds and operating an unregistered securities exchange. An increase in open interest suggests that new traders are entering the market and initiating new positions rather than closing existing ones.</p>
<p>Following the SEC&#8217;s crackdown, the price of BNB, which the SEC considers a security, experienced a drop of over 9%, falling from $300 to $272 within an hour.</p>
<p>Traders who speculated that the price of BNB would decrease before 11:15 a.m. on June 5 profited significantly from the subsequent price action following the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Binance, the largest cryptocurrency exchange by trading volume.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/what-is-the-minimum-rsp-amount-in-singapore/">What is the Minimum RSP Amount in Singapore?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/what-is-the-minimum-rsp-amount-in-singapore/">What is the Minimum RSP Amount in Singapore?</a> was first posted on June 23, 2023 at 7:41 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Users Sold BNB Token in Millions Ahead of SEC Lawsuits</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/binance-users-sold-bnb-token-in-millions-ahead-of-sec-lawsuits/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 23:41:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance (BNB)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65275</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ahead of the significant SEC crackdown on Binance, it appears that some traders executed well-timed sell orders for BNB tokens, capitalizing on the situation. Data [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/binance-users-sold-bnb-token-in-millions-ahead-of-sec-lawsuits/">Binance Users Sold BNB Token in Millions Ahead of SEC Lawsuits</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/binance-users-sold-bnb-token-in-millions-ahead-of-sec-lawsuits/">Binance Users Sold BNB Token in Millions Ahead of SEC Lawsuits</a> was first posted on June 11, 2023 at 7:41 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Ahead of the significant <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/sec-hits-coinbase-with-lawsuit-a-day-after-binance/">SEC crackdown</a> on Binance, it appears that some traders executed well-timed sell orders for BNB tokens, capitalizing on the situation. Data from TradingView reveals that around 125,000 BNB, equivalent to $37 million, were sold in a surge of aggregated sell orders on the BNB/USDT order book on Binance.</p>
<p>These sell orders occurred at 11:45 p.m. UTC on June 4 and 1:45 a.m. UTC on June 5, just before the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) announced its lawsuit against Binance.</p>
<p>Furthermore, <a href="https://coinalyze.net/binance-coin/open-interest/">Coinalyze</a> data indicates that BNB&#8217;s open interest, which represents the total number of outstanding derivative contracts held by investors, increased by approximately $30 million in the first nine hours of June 5.</p>
<p>This rise in open interest occurred before the news of the SEC&#8217;s allegations, revealed at 11:15 a.m., which accused Binance of commingling customer funds and operating an unregistered securities exchange. An increase in open interest suggests that new traders are entering the market and initiating new positions rather than closing existing ones.</p>
<p>Following the SEC&#8217;s crackdown, the price of BNB, which the SEC considers a security, experienced a drop of over 9%, falling from $300 to $272 within an hour.</p>
<p>Traders who speculated that the price of BNB would decrease before 11:15 a.m. on June 5 profited significantly from the subsequent price action following the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Binance, the largest cryptocurrency exchange by trading volume.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/binance-users-sold-bnb-token-in-millions-ahead-of-sec-lawsuits/">Binance Users Sold BNB Token in Millions Ahead of SEC Lawsuits</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/binance-users-sold-bnb-token-in-millions-ahead-of-sec-lawsuits/">Binance Users Sold BNB Token in Millions Ahead of SEC Lawsuits</a> was first posted on June 11, 2023 at 7:41 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Circle Continues Public Listing Plans, Unfazed by SEC’s Recent Actions</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/circle-continues-public-listing-plans-unfazed-by-secs-recent-actions/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 23:27:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[circle]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65271</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Despite the recent SEC action against Coinbase, crypto payments technology company Circle, along with others in the industry, remains determined to pursue its goal of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/circle-continues-public-listing-plans-unfazed-by-secs-recent-actions/">Circle Continues Public Listing Plans, Unfazed by SEC’s Recent Actions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/circle-continues-public-listing-plans-unfazed-by-secs-recent-actions/">Circle Continues Public Listing Plans, Unfazed by SEC’s Recent Actions</a> was first posted on June 9, 2023 at 7:27 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Despite the recent <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/sec-hits-coinbase-with-lawsuit-a-day-after-binance/">SEC action against Coinbase,</a> crypto payments technology company Circle, along with others in the industry, remains determined to pursue its goal of going public. However, industry executives acknowledge that the current environment poses challenges for most companies considering a public listing.</p>
<p>In 2021, <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/circle-breaks-boundaries-with-new-cross-chain-usdc-protocol/">Circle</a> announced its intention to become a public company through a merger with a special purpose acquisition company (SPAC).</p>
<p>However, CEO Jeremy Allaire mentioned in a December 2022 tweet that his company had not completed SEC qualification in time.</p>
<p>Earlier this year, Circle reiterated that going public is still a fundamental part of its strategy, which was confirmed by a company spokesperson and a recent job posting. While no specific deadline has been set, Circle is actively taking steps to progress toward becoming a public company as soon as feasible.</p>
<p>A recent job listing for corporate counsel at Circle also indicated the company&#8217;s intentions. The role would involve assisting with the potential SEC process related to going public and supporting the development of policies, practices, and processes for the public company.</p>
<p>Circle&#8217;s determination to go public remains intact, despite the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Coinbase. Coinbase has been a public company for over two years, having completed its initial public offering in April 2021 after the SEC approved its registration on Form S-1. However, the SEC has accused Coinbase of operating as an unregistered exchange, allegations that Coinbase has denied.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/circle-continues-public-listing-plans-unfazed-by-secs-recent-actions/">Circle Continues Public Listing Plans, Unfazed by SEC’s Recent Actions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/circle-continues-public-listing-plans-unfazed-by-secs-recent-actions/">Circle Continues Public Listing Plans, Unfazed by SEC’s Recent Actions</a> was first posted on June 9, 2023 at 7:27 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Google Provides $1M Protection Against Crypto Mining Attacks</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/google-provides-1m-protection-against-crypto-mining-attacks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 23:05:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin hacks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google cloud]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65267</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Google Cloud has introduced a new initiative to safeguard certain customers against the costs incurred during undetected crypto mining attacks, offering them up to $1 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/google-provides-1m-protection-against-crypto-mining-attacks/">Google Provides $1M Protection Against Crypto Mining Attacks</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/google-provides-1m-protection-against-crypto-mining-attacks/">Google Provides $1M Protection Against Crypto Mining Attacks</a> was first posted on June 8, 2023 at 7:05 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/google-cloud-users-can-now-pay-via-coinbase-with-bitcoin-ethereum-and-dogecoin/">Google Cloud</a> has introduced a new initiative to safeguard certain customers against the costs incurred during undetected crypto mining attacks, offering them up to $1 million in protection. This program is specifically available to subscribers of Google&#8217;s Security Command Center Premium, a cyber threat detection service.<br /><br />Philip Bues, a cloud security expert at market research firm IDC, praised Google Cloud&#8217;s proactive step in addressing the issue. Bues emphasized that crypto mining attacks pose significant security and financial risks for organizations lacking adequate preventative controls and threat detection capabilities in their cloud environments.<br /><br />The decision to provide coverage for these types of breaches stems from a<a href="https://services.google.com/fh/files/blogs/gcat_threathorizons_full_sept2022.pdf"> report</a> published by Google&#8217;s Cybersecurity Action Team in September 2022. The report revealed that 65% of cases involving compromised cloud accounts were linked to hackers engaging in cryptocurrency mining.<br /><br />The report also highlighted that these attacks are often carried out through partially or fully automated means, making them swift and easily executed.<br /><br />If a hacker successfully evades Google&#8217;s detection mechanisms and proceeds to run crypto mining software on a user&#8217;s cloud account, Google Cloud will assume responsibility for the associated expenses. They will provide coverage of up to $1 million towards the customer&#8217;s bill.<br /><br />It is worth noting that this protection program is not related to Bitcoin mining. Instead, it exclusively applies to individuals using mining software, with one of the popular cryptocurrencies mined in this manner being Monero (XMR).</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/google-provides-1m-protection-against-crypto-mining-attacks/">Google Provides $1M Protection Against Crypto Mining Attacks</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/google-provides-1m-protection-against-crypto-mining-attacks/">Google Provides $1M Protection Against Crypto Mining Attacks</a> was first posted on June 8, 2023 at 7:05 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>