<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>Latest Crypto News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://kryptomoney.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<description>Latest Crypto News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 22:07:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/cropped-cropped-favicon_512x512_v2-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Latest Crypto News</title>
	<link>https://kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><itunes:subtitle>Latest Crypto News</itunes:subtitle><itunes:category text="News &amp; Politics"/><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Business News"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Investing"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Tech News"/></itunes:category><item>
		<title>Edward Snowden To Accept Bitcoin as CEO of Twitter</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/edward-snowden-to-accept-bitcoin-as-ceo-of-twitter/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 22:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63593</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new drama is developing around Twitter as Elon Musk prepares to consider some new candidates for that crucial position and is seriously considering stepping down as the platform&#8217;s CEO. Many people, including Edward Snowden, have expressed their readiness to assume responsibility and their willingness to accept payment in Bitcoin. I take payment in Bitcoin. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/edward-snowden-to-accept-bitcoin-as-ceo-of-twitter/">Edward Snowden To Accept Bitcoin as CEO of Twitter</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/edward-snowden-to-accept-bitcoin-as-ceo-of-twitter/">Edward Snowden To Accept Bitcoin as CEO of Twitter</a> was first posted on December 19, 2022 at 5:07 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A new drama is developing around Twitter as <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/dogecoin-jumps-8-as-elon-musk-renews-bid-to-buy-twitter-bitcoin-and-altcoins-rebound-on-this-potential-catalyst/">Elon Musk</a> prepares to consider some new candidates for that crucial position and is seriously considering stepping down as the platform&#8217;s CEO. Many people, including <a href="https://twitter.com/Snowden/status/1604628658852970496">Edward Snowden</a>, have expressed their readiness to assume responsibility and their willingness to accept payment in Bitcoin.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">I take payment in Bitcoin. <a href="https://t.co/wW0Qa9NxWi">https://t.co/wW0Qa9NxWi</a></p>
— Edward Snowden (@Snowden) <a href="https://twitter.com/Snowden/status/1604628658852970496?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 19, 2022</a></blockquote>
<p>Elon Musk expressed a desire to hand over the reins of one of the biggest social media platforms in the world to someone else who is committed enough to do so, but the well-known security expert and Bitcoin and cryptocurrency enthusiast responded. Snowden is not only prepared to take over as CEO but is also open to receiving bitcoin in exchange for his services.<br /><br />In the past, Snowden has said a lot of things about Bitcoin and the cryptocurrency market as a whole. He has never acknowledged accepting Bitcoin in exchange for his services, though. In the comments section below Snowden&#8217;s statement, some users made fun of the fact that Elon Musk does not particularly enjoy remote work, even though for Snowden, given his complicated relationship with the U.S. government, that is his only option.<br /><br />Snowden predicted the cryptocurrency market and the market as a whole back in November, urging his subscribers to start using safe DEX. Decentralized trading platforms saw a sharp increase in user traffic after the<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-begins-its-proof-of-reserves-after-ftx-collapse/"> collapse of FTX</a> because, in theory, they are nothing more than sophisticated networks of interconnected wallets and addresses. Sadly, Musk is unlikely to give Snowden the CEO position and will probably select a different heir. Regarding the suggestion he made a few hours ago, Snowden has not yet made any further remarks.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/edward-snowden-to-accept-bitcoin-as-ceo-of-twitter/">Edward Snowden To Accept Bitcoin as CEO of Twitter</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/edward-snowden-to-accept-bitcoin-as-ceo-of-twitter/">Edward Snowden To Accept Bitcoin as CEO of Twitter</a> was first posted on December 19, 2022 at 5:07 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance US To Acquire Voyager Digital Assets</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/binance-us-to-acquire-voyager-digital-assets/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 21:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Voyager Digital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63557</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance.US has reached a deal to acquire Voyager Digital&#8217;s assets. The bid from the cryptocurrency exchange also means that there&#8217;s a path for Voyager customer funds to be unlocked &#8220;as soon as possible.&#8221; It was previously reported in November that CZ had confirmed that Binance US would be bidding for Voyager&#8217;s assets. Voyager confirmed today [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-us-to-acquire-voyager-digital-assets/">Binance US To Acquire Voyager Digital Assets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-us-to-acquire-voyager-digital-assets/">Binance US To Acquire Voyager Digital Assets</a> was first posted on December 19, 2022 at 4:34 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Binance.US has reached a deal to acquire Voyager Digital&#8217;s assets. The bid from the cryptocurrency exchange also means that there&#8217;s a path for Voyager customer funds to be unlocked <em>&#8220;as soon as possible.&#8221;</em><br /><br />It was previously reported in November that CZ had confirmed that Binance US would be bidding for Voyager&#8217;s assets. Voyager confirmed today in an official announcement that the exchange will purchase the following assets:<br /><br />It was previously reported in November that CZ had confirmed that Binance US would be bidding for Voyager&#8217;s assets.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>&#8220;Our bid is a reflection of our guiding principle that customers should come first. Our goal is simple: return users their cryptocurrencies on the fastest timeline possible. […] We hope our selection brings to an end a painful bankruptcy process which saw customers unfairly dragged into it at no fault of their own. Upon close of the deal, users will be able to seamlessly access their digital assets on the Binance.US platform, where they will continue to receive future disbursements from the Voyager estate,&#8221; said Brian Shroder, CEO and President at Binance US.</p>
</blockquote>
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/voyager-digital-survey-reveals-investors-are-more-bullish-on-crypto-despite-recent-market-crash/">Voyager</a> will now seek bankruptcy court approval to enter into an asset purchase agreement with Binance.US at a hearing scheduled for January 5, 2023.<br /><br />According to Schroder, once the deal is completed, Voyager customers will be able to access future disbursements of their crypto holdings through the Binance.US platform from the Voyager bankruptcy estate.<br />Voyager previously approved a bid for FTX to acquire its customer deposit accounts in a deal valued at $1.42 billion struck in late September. The Texas Securities Board was reviewing the offer before it fell through in November after FTX declared bankruptcy.<br /><br />Binance has come under increased scrutiny since FTX, the partner company of the American exchange, filed for bankruptcy. The major cryptocurrency exchange Binance has a licensing agreement with Binance.US, which is a separate legal entity. Changpeng Zhao, CEO of Binance, owns a majority interest in it.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-us-to-acquire-voyager-digital-assets/">Binance US To Acquire Voyager Digital Assets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-us-to-acquire-voyager-digital-assets/">Binance US To Acquire Voyager Digital Assets</a> was first posted on December 19, 2022 at 4:34 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Start NFT Project for Your Business – Vital Steps</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/how-to-start-nft-project-for-your-business/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 06:21:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sponsored]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT collection]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT project]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63588</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The ways and methods by which businesses operate these days are being revolutionized by web 3.0. There is increased data searchability, personalized web, and fading out the usage of third parties. This indicates that businesses will now save resources and at the same time create solid relationships with clients. These are made possible by the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/how-to-start-nft-project-for-your-business/">How to Start NFT Project for Your Business &#8211; Vital Steps</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/how-to-start-nft-project-for-your-business/">How to Start NFT Project for Your Business &#8211; Vital Steps</a> was first posted on December 19, 2022 at 1:21 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The ways and methods by which businesses operate these days are being revolutionized by web 3.0. There is increased data searchability, personalized web, and fading out the usage of third parties. This indicates that businesses will now save resources and at the same time create solid relationships with clients. These are made possible by the implementation of web 3.0. In the web 3.0 space, NFTs are booming in brand development. NFTs projects are creating lots of buzz as virtual assets are making opportunities for brands to engage their target audience. All is possible through virtual platforms. You may wonder how to start your own <a href="https://www.business2community.com/nft/new-nft-projects">NFT project</a>; however, it should be known that the buzz around NFT is meaningful.</p>
<h2>Reasons to Start NFT Project for Your Business &#8211; NFT Statistics for 2022</h2>
<p>Here are some verified statistics that show the potential and growth of NFTs in 2022. 950,000 wallets were acquired and sold in the first quarter of 2022. In 2021, the <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/krakens-nft-marketplace-launches-in-beta/">NFT market</a> was valued at $41 billion. £30 billion is already spent on NFTs this year 2022, making this year&#8217;s investment valued higher than the 2021 total. The Merge was sold for $91.8 million, making it the most expensive NFT ever sold. Monthly, on OpenSea, approximately 250,000 people trade NFTs. Every week in the Blockchain, $10 to $20m worth of NFTs are sold.</p>
<h3>Application of NFTs to Your Business</h3>
<p>Seeing the achievement so far, it sounds interesting to know how to start your own NFT project. However, you need to learn how to <a href="https://www.socialplug.io/blog/how-to-promote-nft-s-on-twitter-5-best-strategies">grow your NFT project on Twitter</a> for a massive gain. Here is how to apply NFTs to your business.</p>
<p><strong>1. Trade Real-world Assets as NFTs</strong></p>
<p>The versatility of NFT construction makes it easy to present it as a real-world asset such as real estate or art. There are already real estate deals that were sealed through the sale of NFTs. NFTs are still new and growing. However, with this kind of transaction completed, the trend has already changed the status quo and eliminated the use of middlemen from the setting. Now resources can be conserved from transactions for other purposes.</p>
<p><strong>2. Use NFTs as a Community Enabler</strong></p>
<p>Several communities having the same interest and like-minded people are starting to use NFTs as validation tokens or means for accessing the community. For instance, ownership of a part of a collection of NFTs. On platforms like Discord, certain NFT holders can only have access to a channel to communicate with other members of the same interest after confirming their NFT ownership. <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/terms/d/digital-wallet.asp">Digital wallets</a> integrated into the Discord platform, for instance, are used to validate ownership for connectivity and interoperability between different platforms. There are communities with open areas for all and sundry. However, users can only participate and engage with other members. But they cannot access member-only areas without validated NFT ownership. Validation gives access to premium content, opinions, and insights.</p>
<p><strong>3. NFT Brand Activations</strong></p>
<p>As soon as an NFT collection has been created, the next stage would be the marketing opportunities. On <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/meta-reports-9-4-billion-in-metaverse-losses-for-the-year/">Metaverse</a> and Discord, users have learned more about NFTs and NFT brands in a virtual space. Brands have discovered the advantages of this space and are beginning to move their marketing efforts into virtual brand activations that are more like life experiences and exclusive.</p>
<p><strong>4. Use as Secondary Market</strong></p>
<p>The initial sale of an NFT collection is known as the primary sale. While the secondary market is the reselling of the collection. Right to secondary sale royalties is automated with NFTs. This is done without any need for extended legal work due to its simple lines of code. With this, artists can get their share of all the sales of their collections.</p>
<p>NFTs also have the potential to do the following:</p>
<ul>
<li>Promote brand loyalty with limited-edition merchandise</li>
<li>Generate funds for social causes</li>
<li>Enhance supply chain management</li>
</ul>
<p>Discovering how to make use of NFTs for businesses can help to boost brand loyalty and reputation. It prevents piracy, creates a good customer experience, and enhances supply chain tracking. Smart companies would do great when NFTs are incorporated into their businesses. The next question is how to start your own NFT project.</p>
<h3>Developing NFTs for Businesses</h3>
<p>If you have the desire to create an NFT project for your business, here is a professional and easy strategy that will guide you from the scratch to success stage in your NFT journey. This procedure consists of 5 steps. These steps are well explained to help you start your NFT project in your business today.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Ideation</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>This is the stage of the conception of your NFT project. At this level, you do more brainstorming to discover a valuable NFT project for your business via brand immersion. Here you need to discover your niche and track where it fits best in the NFT industry. It may be from gaming and media to marketing, data tools, etc.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Experience</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>After you must have borne the idea, it&#8217;s time to take a step further by looking at the worth of the NFT project, and discerning what the project will bring to your business. At this level, you develop a track path for NFT success, figuring out which community you will join as you begin your journey into the NFT industry.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Design</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>This is the level where you create your brand art. Ensure you work with experienced designers. Possibly, you can choose to partner with local artists to design attractive collaborations. As soon as your designs are set, get a plan for minting processes. Your NFT artwork must be minted professionally so your community can get your NFTs.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Activation</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>Getting close to success level, setting up a marketing team, or working with an experienced agency. Develop a strategy that aligns with your project. Open an NFT collection in OpenSea or any other platform. Create a Discord channel, Twitter, and other social media that accept NFTs. The agency you work with will help you set up multiple streams of marketing strategies to create awareness and attention to your NFT project. To reach your target audience, they make use of creative messages, and organic and paid mediums to catch interested individuals to your brand. When your audience starts gathering, your agency should be able to maintain and keep them by sensitizing them about the project. They should understand your mission, project utility, and why they should be involved. Every channel should be well managed. After validation of membership, NFT holders can access a collection dedicated channel and interact with other community members.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Execution</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>An experienced digital agency or the team you set up should be able to update the process and keep up marketing your brand using digital campaigns to promote your NFTs to the target audience. Do not allow your project to stop there. After the primary market, which is known as the first sale of an NFT artwork, the secondary market should move on. The secondary market holds all subsequent resale of your NFT artworks.</p>
<p>A brand&#8217;s right to secondary sale royalties is guaranteed with NFTs. This is made possible because of the simple lines of code, with no extra legal work needed. Brands or artists can always get a cut or percentage of every future sale of their work. Experts can help you to discover the secondary market opportunities and revenue opportunities that await you in the NFT industry.</p>
<h3>Conclusion</h3>
<p>In all, you can see that <a href="https://medium.com/unpluggd-digital/how-to-develop-an-nft-project-1305f82f331">how to start your own NFT project</a> is not as difficult as it seems. You need to understand your idea and then get experts who have been through the process before to guide you. Organize a team that is interested in the NFT project. Then get to work your NFT project into a success.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/how-to-start-nft-project-for-your-business/">How to Start NFT Project for Your Business &#8211; Vital Steps</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/how-to-start-nft-project-for-your-business/">How to Start NFT Project for Your Business &#8211; Vital Steps</a> was first posted on December 19, 2022 at 1:21 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ETH Price Analysis: How Will Ethereum Price End in 2022? ETH Holders’ Conviction at Its Highest per This Metric</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/eth-price-analysis-how-will-ethereum-price-end-in-2022-eth-holders-conviction-at-its-highest-per-this-metric/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 21:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH/USD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH/USD Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63576</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum (ETH) is slightly up in the last 24 hours at $1,186 Long-term investors presently hold 80% of the ETH supply The bullishness stems from the fact that ETH supply has been deflationary Ethereum (ETH) is slightly up in the last 24 hours at $1,186, but down 76% from its all-time high of $4,890. On-chain [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/eth-price-analysis-how-will-ethereum-price-end-in-2022-eth-holders-conviction-at-its-highest-per-this-metric/">ETH Price Analysis: How Will Ethereum Price End in 2022? ETH Holders’ Conviction at Its Highest per This Metric</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/eth-price-analysis-how-will-ethereum-price-end-in-2022-eth-holders-conviction-at-its-highest-per-this-metric/">ETH Price Analysis: How Will Ethereum Price End in 2022? ETH Holders’ Conviction at Its Highest per This Metric</a> was first posted on December 18, 2022 at 4:00 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li>Ethereum (ETH) is slightly up in the last 24 hours at $1,186</li>
<li>Long-term investors presently hold 80% of the ETH supply</li>
<li>The bullishness stems from the fact that ETH supply has been deflationary</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ethereum-eth-trading-at-this-juncture-implies-one-thing-this-is-what-on-chain-data-says/">Ethereum (ETH)</a> is slightly up in the last 24 hours at $1,186, but down 76% from its all-time high of $4,890. On-chain data suggests that Ethereum holders’ convictions might be at their highest despite the 2022 selloff. Long-term investors, referring to those who have held the token for more than six months, presently hold 80% of the ETH supply, according to Glassnode HODL waves data, which is quite comparable to the 2018 bear market level. The HODL wave is a metric that measures the number of investors who hold a specific digital asset. The fact that many long-term holders have yet to sell their holdings indicates their belief in the long-term worth of ETH. This suggests that most investors remain bullish on the asset and believe it will recover greatly in value over time. The bullishness stems from the fact that ETH supply has been deflationary on several occasions since the Merge event. According to analysts, greater network activity will result in a continuous deflationary supply.<br /><br /><strong>Key Levels</strong><br />Resistance Levels: $1,700, $1,500, $1,300<br />Support Levels: $1,100, $1,000, $879</p>
<h4>ETH/USD Daily Chart: Bearish</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1436" height="773" class="alignnone wp-image-63584 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD-Daily-Dec-18.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD-Daily-Dec-18.png 1436w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD-Daily-Dec-18-300x161.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD-Daily-Dec-18-1024x551.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD-Daily-Dec-18-768x413.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD-Daily-Dec-18-750x404.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD-Daily-Dec-18-1140x614.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1436px) 100vw, 1436px" /><em><span style="color: #999999">ETH/USD Daily Chart</span></em></h6>
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/eth-price-analysis-ethereum-briefly-loses-1200-whales-quietly-add-to-holdings-amid-price-drop/">ETH/USD</a> plunged to lows of $1,155 on Friday, continuing the selling interest from the price level of $1,351. The MA 50 ($1,300), which recently made a bearish turn, stays above the price. The ETH/USD pair may touch the ascending trendline at the $1,100 level if it makes another downward move below the intraday low of $1,172.<br /><br />Additional declines could lead to the $879 bottom, which was registered on June 18. If upward pressure builds, ETH may encounter resistance before moving on to the $1,500 level. The $879 yearly low might also be the target for a retest following such a successful decline in this price region.</p>
<h4>ETH/USD 4-Hour Chart: Ranging</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1436" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-63585 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD-4-Hour-Dec-18.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD-4-Hour-Dec-18.png 1436w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD-4-Hour-Dec-18-300x144.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD-4-Hour-Dec-18-1024x491.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD-4-Hour-Dec-18-768x368.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD-4-Hour-Dec-18-750x359.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD-4-Hour-Dec-18-1140x546.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1436px) 100vw, 1436px" /><em><span style="color: #999999">ETH/USD 4-Hour Chart</span></em></h6>
<p>Following the pullback from recently recorded highs of $1,351, ETH is currently edging sideways, constrained beneath the MAs 50 and 200. On the 4-hour chart, the RSI has marginally crossed back above the 30 levels but is still within the oversold region. This might imply that a relief rally is possible for the upcoming sessions. The MA 200 at $1,230 might act as an immediate barrier.<br /><br />Overcoming this, the ETH/USD pair might reach a high of $1,300 before posing a threat to the $1,500–$1,700 range. Alternately, if the price drops below the $1,100 low, initial support could come from the $1,000 level before the $879 trough. Overall, Ethereum must hold the $1,100 support level, though it might be necessary to breach the $1,000 level.</p>
<p><strong>Note:</strong><em> Kryptomoney.com is not a financial advisor. Do your research before investing your funds in any financial asset or presented product or event. We are not responsible for your investing results</em></p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/eth-price-analysis-how-will-ethereum-price-end-in-2022-eth-holders-conviction-at-its-highest-per-this-metric/">ETH Price Analysis: How Will Ethereum Price End in 2022? ETH Holders’ Conviction at Its Highest per This Metric</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/eth-price-analysis-how-will-ethereum-price-end-in-2022-eth-holders-conviction-at-its-highest-per-this-metric/">ETH Price Analysis: How Will Ethereum Price End in 2022? ETH Holders’ Conviction at Its Highest per This Metric</a> was first posted on December 18, 2022 at 4:00 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BTC Price Analysis: BTC/USD Downward Pressure Slows Despite Risk of More Losses</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/btc-price-analysis-btc-usd-downward-pressure-slows-despite-risk-of-more-losses/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 09:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC/USD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC/USD Price Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63571</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BTC remains overly optimistic despite the strong two-day sell-off Bitcoin might continue to see dip buying, especially after sharp losses U.S. Federal Reserve increased the benchmark interest rate by 50 basis points The overall crypto market has not made significant changes to its growth outlook after its bearish slide. Although the sentiment will stabilize somewhat [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/btc-price-analysis-btc-usd-downward-pressure-slows-despite-risk-of-more-losses/">BTC Price Analysis: BTC/USD Downward Pressure Slows Despite Risk of More Losses</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/btc-price-analysis-btc-usd-downward-pressure-slows-despite-risk-of-more-losses/">BTC Price Analysis: BTC/USD Downward Pressure Slows Despite Risk of More Losses</a> was first posted on December 18, 2022 at 4:54 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li>BTC remains overly optimistic despite the strong two-day sell-off</li>
<li>Bitcoin might continue to see dip buying, especially after sharp losses</li>
<li>U.S. Federal Reserve increased the benchmark interest rate by 50 basis points</li>
</ul>
<p>The overall <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/here-are-crypto-market-predictions-as-btc-drops-in-wake-of-genesis-ftx-fallout-new-ftx-ceo-dissociates-from-sbf-tweets/">crypto market</a> has not made significant changes to its growth outlook after its bearish slide. Although the sentiment will stabilize somewhat during the festive season, we might also see more selling towards the end of regular trading as fears increase and the slide will continue for the rest of December. BTC remains overly optimistic despite the strong two-day sell-off as the crypto markets still have significant downside potential. Bitcoin (BTC/USD) is still under pressure to fall as the pair continued to struggle in holding the majority of its recent gains over the past week. It traded as low as the $16,529 region which was a test of the retracement of the ascending range from the low level of $15,460 to the $18,385 weekly high. Bitcoin might continue to see dip buying, especially after sharp losses (like in the previous two sessions of the past week), but it might also end more quickly in profit-taking. According to analysts&#8217; predictions, the U.S. Federal Reserve increased the benchmark interest rate by 50 basis points. The <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-falls-back-near-20k-ethereum-drops-7-shib-altcoins-decline-on-feds-powell-speech-in-jackson-hole/">Fed</a> has indicated that it is still planning to raise interest rates next year, which will cause cryptocurrency and stock prices to decline.<br /><br /><strong>Key Levels</strong><br />Resistance Levels: $21,500, $19,000, $17,500<br />Support Levels: $15,500, $13,000, $10,000</p>
<h4>BTC/USD Daily Chart: Bearish</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1436" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-63577 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-Daily-Dec-18.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-Daily-Dec-18.png 1436w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-Daily-Dec-18-300x144.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-Daily-Dec-18-1024x491.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-Daily-Dec-18-768x368.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-Daily-Dec-18-750x359.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-Daily-Dec-18-1140x546.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1436px) 100vw, 1436px" /><em><span style="color: #999999">BTC/USD Daily Chart</span></em></h6>
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/btc-price-analysis-btc-usd-trying-to-extend-consolidation-after-weeks-recovery-attempt/">BTC/USD</a> has been in a downtrend since March, reaching a yearly low of $15,460 before experiencing an upside correction. Even though the pair erased part of its recent pullback during the week, it has been rangebound in the last few hours, with the moving average (MA 50) capping its upside. Piercing through this zone, the spotlight could then turn to the $20,000.<br /><br />The momentum indicators currently suggest that bearish forces are intensifying. Specifically, the daily relative strength index (RSI) is descending after posting a bearish cross past its midline 50, while the moving average (MA 200) seeks to strengthen above price. Should bearish forces persist, the price could edge lower to test the recent support region of $15,500.</p>
<h4>BTC/USD 4-Hour Chart: Ranging</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1436" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-63578 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-4-Hour-Dec-18.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-4-Hour-Dec-18.png 1436w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-4-Hour-Dec-18-300x144.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-4-Hour-Dec-18-1024x491.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-4-Hour-Dec-18-768x368.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-4-Hour-Dec-18-750x359.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-4-Hour-Dec-18-1140x546.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1436px) 100vw, 1436px" /><em><span style="color: #999999">BTC/USD 4-Hour Chart</span></em></h6>
<p>Since November, BTC/USD has been trading in a new lower sideways channel, but over the past few weeks, a slow increase in positive momentum has brought the price nearly to the range ceiling at $18,385 per coin. However, the technical indicators are showing that the bullish bias is waning, making the $18,000 resistance a difficult barrier to overcome.<br /><br />The 4-hour relative strength index (RSI) has crossed the oversold line at 30 and BTC prices remain comfortably below the short-term moving averages (MA 50 and 200). The price has already begun to gently dip lower towards the oversold level. A downside violation might then set the stage for a new yearly low under the $15,000 support zone.</p>
<p><strong>Note:</strong><em> Kryptomoney.com is not a financial advisor. Do your research before investing your funds in any financial asset or presented product or event. We are not responsible for your investing results</em></p>
<p><em>Image Credit: Shutterstock</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/btc-price-analysis-btc-usd-downward-pressure-slows-despite-risk-of-more-losses/">BTC Price Analysis: BTC/USD Downward Pressure Slows Despite Risk of More Losses</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/btc-price-analysis-btc-usd-downward-pressure-slows-despite-risk-of-more-losses/">BTC Price Analysis: BTC/USD Downward Pressure Slows Despite Risk of More Losses</a> was first posted on December 18, 2022 at 4:54 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BNB Price Analysis: Dip Buying Emerges as FUD Lessens; Binance CEO Dismisses Concerns on Clawed Back Funds in FTX Saga</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/bnb-price-analysis-dip-buying-emerges-as-fud-lessens-binance-ceo-dismisses-concerns-on-clawed-back-funds-in-ftx-saga/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 08:43:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin (BNB)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB/USD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB/USD Price Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63562</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance&#8217;s native cryptocurrency, BNB, suddenly gained 7% within a few hours Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao dismissed concerns that his company could have that money clawed in FTX bankruptcy proceedings Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao dismissed these concerns BNB (BNB) suddenly gained 7% within 24 hours, having dropped significantly following the market selloff. At the time of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/bnb-price-analysis-dip-buying-emerges-as-fud-lessens-binance-ceo-dismisses-concerns-on-clawed-back-funds-in-ftx-saga/">BNB Price Analysis: Dip Buying Emerges as FUD Lessens; Binance CEO Dismisses Concerns on Clawed Back Funds in FTX Saga</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bnb-price-analysis-dip-buying-emerges-as-fud-lessens-binance-ceo-dismisses-concerns-on-clawed-back-funds-in-ftx-saga/">BNB Price Analysis: Dip Buying Emerges as FUD Lessens; Binance CEO Dismisses Concerns on Clawed Back Funds in FTX Saga</a> was first posted on December 18, 2022 at 3:43 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li>Binance&#8217;s native cryptocurrency, BNB, suddenly gained 7% within a few hours</li>
<li>Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao dismissed concerns that his company could have that money clawed in FTX bankruptcy proceedings</li>
<li>Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao dismissed these concerns</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bnb-price-analysis-bnb-usd-registers-steady-consolidation-past-17-50-following-binance-bnb-historic-coin-burn/">BNB (BNB)</a> suddenly gained 7% within 24 hours, having dropped significantly following the market selloff. At the time of publication, BNB was changing hands at $247, still down 15% in the last seven days. According to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bnb/">CoinMarketCap</a>, BNB, which was initially issued in 2017, is the world&#8217;s fifth-most valuable cryptocurrency, with a market worth of nearly $38.2 billion. Binance is being questioned about its ability to handle potential $2.1 billion clawback requests in FTX&#8217;s bankruptcy proceedings. In a recent CNBC interview, Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao dismissed these concerns. According to cryptocurrency exchange Binance, auditing company Mazars Group has dismissed cryptocurrency firms as clients. Binance&#8217;s proof of reserves report was heavily criticized since it did not include a thorough or formal audit. It also refers to a snapshot of the exchange&#8217;s assets at a specific point in time without disclosing its liabilities<br /><br /><strong>Key Levels</strong><br />Resistance Levels: $360, $315, $280<br />Support Levels: $220, $183, $150</p>
<h4>BNB/USD Daily Chart: Ranging</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1436" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-63572 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSD-Daily-Dec-18.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSD-Daily-Dec-18.png 1436w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSD-Daily-Dec-18-300x144.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSD-Daily-Dec-18-1024x491.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSD-Daily-Dec-18-768x368.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSD-Daily-Dec-18-750x359.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSD-Daily-Dec-18-1140x546.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1436px) 100vw, 1436px" /><em><span style="color: #999999">BNB/USD Daily Chart</span></em></h6>
<p>BNB/USD <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bnb-price-analysis-mild-pullback-as-bulls-attempt-to-head-north-binance-coin-retains-3rd-largest-cryptocurrency-status/">remains bid</a> from the lower end of its recent range, and it has renewed its upward bias toward the level at $280. In light of the ongoing risk appetite trend in the crypto markets, the pair is now moving higher at the start of the new week. The BNB/USD remains unchanged in its ranging movement and is edging closer to the daily moving averages (MA 50 and MA 200).<br /><br />The price of the pair is currently rising by nearly 7% towards $260, and if this zone is broken, $280 will be reached on the way to setting another upside traction. On the other hand, $220 serves as the first support level, followed by the yearly low of $183.4. Overall the expansion from the level of $220 is viewed as a medium-term phase in a broader context.</p>
<h4>BNB/USD 4-Hour Chart: Ranging</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1436" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-63573 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSD-4-Hour-Dec-18.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSD-4-Hour-Dec-18.png 1436w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSD-4-Hour-Dec-18-300x144.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSD-4-Hour-Dec-18-1024x491.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSD-4-Hour-Dec-18-768x368.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSD-4-Hour-Dec-18-750x359.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSD-4-Hour-Dec-18-1140x546.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1436px) 100vw, 1436px" /><em><span style="color: #999999">BNB/USD 4-Hour Chart</span></em></h6>
<p>The BNB/USD&#8217;s recovery from the $220 level is still taking shape, and the intraday bias is slightly upward toward a retest of the $265 level. We can expect a stronger rebound from $220 levels to continue, with a breach of the $280 mark, as the retracement from the November high of $397.9 to $249.7 has been supported at $220 levels.<br /><br />On the downside, a break of the crucial support level at $220 could indicate that the upward trend from the yearly low of $183.4 level is over. Meanwhile, if the $260 level is breached, the intraday bias may shift back to the upside towards $280.</p>
<p><strong>Note:</strong><em> Kryptomoney.com is not a financial advisor. Do your research before investing your funds in any financial asset or presented product or event. We are not responsible for your investing results</em></p>
<p><em>Image Credit: Shutterstock</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/bnb-price-analysis-dip-buying-emerges-as-fud-lessens-binance-ceo-dismisses-concerns-on-clawed-back-funds-in-ftx-saga/">BNB Price Analysis: Dip Buying Emerges as FUD Lessens; Binance CEO Dismisses Concerns on Clawed Back Funds in FTX Saga</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bnb-price-analysis-dip-buying-emerges-as-fud-lessens-binance-ceo-dismisses-concerns-on-clawed-back-funds-in-ftx-saga/">BNB Price Analysis: Dip Buying Emerges as FUD Lessens; Binance CEO Dismisses Concerns on Clawed Back Funds in FTX Saga</a> was first posted on December 18, 2022 at 3:43 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XLM Price Analysis: What’s Next for Price? Stellar-Based Aid Disbursement Solution Launches for Ukraine</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/xlm-price-analysis-whats-next-for-price-stellar-based-aid-disbursement-solution-launches-for-ukraine/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 23:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar (XLM)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM/USD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM/USD Price Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63559</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stellar (XLM) is down 1.46% at $0.076 at the time of publication Stellar-based aid disbursement solution launches for war-affected individuals in Ukraine The pilot phase is designed specifically for Ukraine but can be adapted worldwide Just like the rest of the crypto markets, Stellar (XLM) is down 1.46% at $0.076 at the time of publication. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/xlm-price-analysis-whats-next-for-price-stellar-based-aid-disbursement-solution-launches-for-ukraine/">XLM Price Analysis: What’s Next for Price? Stellar-Based Aid Disbursement Solution Launches for Ukraine</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/xlm-price-analysis-whats-next-for-price-stellar-based-aid-disbursement-solution-launches-for-ukraine/">XLM Price Analysis: What’s Next for Price? Stellar-Based Aid Disbursement Solution Launches for Ukraine</a> was first posted on December 16, 2022 at 6:17 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li>Stellar (XLM) is down 1.46% at $0.076 at the time of publication</li>
<li>Stellar-based aid disbursement solution launches for war-affected individuals in Ukraine</li>
<li>The pilot phase is designed specifically for Ukraine but can be adapted worldwide</li>
</ul>
<p>Just like the rest of the crypto markets, <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/stellar-xlm-bulls-didnt-hear-the-okex-news-this-prediction-surfaced-when-uniswap-jumped-as-btc-xrp-fell/">Stellar (XLM)</a> is down 1.46% at $0.076 at the time of publication. UNHCR, the UN Refugee Agency, and the Stellar Development Foundation (SDF), the non-profit that supports the growth and development of the Stellar blockchain network, have announced the launch of a pilot first-of-its-kind blockchain payment solution for digital cash distribution to internally displaced persons (IDPs) and other war-affected people in Ukraine. UNHCR, in collaboration with United Nations International Computing Centre (UNICC), the UN’s technology solutions provider, is among the first to pilot the new Stellar-based aid disbursement solution, which ensures the delivery of cash assistance directly into the hands of those being assisted quickly, efficiently, and securely with full value transfer traceability and accountability. The pilot phase of the project is designed specifically for Ukraine but can be adapted worldwide.<br /><br /><strong>Key Levels</strong><br />Resistance Levels: $0.1150, $0.0990, $0.0800<br />Support levels: $0.0769, $0.0500 $0.0350</p>
<h4>XLM/USD Daily Chart: Bearish</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1436" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-63563 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XLMUSD-Daily-Dec-16-1.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XLMUSD-Daily-Dec-16-1.png 1436w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XLMUSD-Daily-Dec-16-1-300x144.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XLMUSD-Daily-Dec-16-1-1024x491.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XLMUSD-Daily-Dec-16-1-768x368.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XLMUSD-Daily-Dec-16-1-750x359.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XLMUSD-Daily-Dec-16-1-1140x546.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1436px) 100vw, 1436px" /><br /><span style="color: #999999"><em>XLM/USD Daily Chart</em></span></h6>
<p>The price of<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/xlm-price-analysis-whats-next-for-xlm-price-wirex-expands-usdc-support-to-the-stellar-network/"> XLM/USD</a> made an attempt to climb back up on the prior day but failed, drifting lower to oscillate under the $0.0800 mark. Since the declines, XLM has had a difficult time fending off bearish pressures. The pair has been trading sideways within a predetermined range even though the decline appears to continue under the moving average (MA 50 and 200).<br /><br />It is noteworthy that the daily relative strength index (RSI) has now touched the oversold line without a sign of stalling. It resembles a continuous bearish pressure, which signals that the bulls are out of steam. However, if the pair can return above support near the $0.0800 mark, the bulls may attempt to push higher.</p>
<h4>XLM/USD 4-Hour Chart: Bearish</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1436" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-63564 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XLMUSD-4-Hour-Dec-16.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XLMUSD-4-Hour-Dec-16.png 1436w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XLMUSD-4-Hour-Dec-16-300x144.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XLMUSD-4-Hour-Dec-16-1024x491.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XLMUSD-4-Hour-Dec-16-768x368.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XLMUSD-4-Hour-Dec-16-750x359.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XLMUSD-4-Hour-Dec-16-1140x546.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1436px) 100vw, 1436px" /><br /><em><span style="color: #999999">XLM/USD 4-Hour Chart</span></em></h6>
<p>The intraday sentiment is uncharted, and the XLM/USD is still trading in a range below $0.0800. On the other hand, the breakout of the $0.0800 low level might support the idea that the decline from the November high at the $0.1162 level will continue toward the $0.0700 level.<br /><br />Possibly a retest of the $0.0800 level and a break into the $0.0990 confluence region would follow a fresh rebound from the current price in the $0.076 area. On the other hand, a break of the $0.0800 support turned resistance level could initially reverse the downtrend and trigger another round of drops as traders sell during rallies.</p>
<p><strong>Note:</strong><em> Kryptomoney.com is not a financial advisor. Do your research before investing your funds in any financial asset or presented product or event. We are not responsible for your investing results</em></p>
<p><em>Image Credit: Shutterstock</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/xlm-price-analysis-whats-next-for-price-stellar-based-aid-disbursement-solution-launches-for-ukraine/">XLM Price Analysis: What’s Next for Price? Stellar-Based Aid Disbursement Solution Launches for Ukraine</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/xlm-price-analysis-whats-next-for-price-stellar-based-aid-disbursement-solution-launches-for-ukraine/">XLM Price Analysis: What’s Next for Price? Stellar-Based Aid Disbursement Solution Launches for Ukraine</a> was first posted on December 16, 2022 at 6:17 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jim Cramer Says He Is Negative on XRP, LTC, DOGE; Binance Announces Giveaway of 1 BTC for New Users</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/jim-cramer-says-he-is-negative-on-xrp-ltc-doge-binance-announce-giveaway-of-1-btc-for-new-users/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 23:09:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin (LTC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP (XRP)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63552</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Longtime CNBC host Jim Cramer, in his usual criticism of cryptocurrencies, says he is negative on XRP, LTC, and DOGE. &#8220;I think you should be negative on crypto.&#8221; &#8220;I&#8217;m negative on XRP, LTC, and DOGE because I haven&#8217;t been able to find anyone that takes them,&#8221; Jim Cramer stated in a recent CNBC Squawk Box [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/jim-cramer-says-he-is-negative-on-xrp-ltc-doge-binance-announce-giveaway-of-1-btc-for-new-users/">Jim Cramer Says He Is Negative on XRP, LTC, DOGE; Binance Announces Giveaway of 1 BTC for New Users</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/jim-cramer-says-he-is-negative-on-xrp-ltc-doge-binance-announce-giveaway-of-1-btc-for-new-users/">Jim Cramer Says He Is Negative on XRP, LTC, DOGE; Binance Announces Giveaway of 1 BTC for New Users</a> was first posted on December 16, 2022 at 6:09 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Longtime CNBC host <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/mad-money-host-jim-cramer-suggests-gamestop-should-convert-3447-stores-to-crypto-information-centres/">Jim Cramer</a>, in his usual criticism of cryptocurrencies, says he is negative on XRP, LTC, and DOGE. &#8220;I think you should be negative on crypto.&#8221; &#8220;I&#8217;m negative on XRP, LTC, and DOGE because I haven&#8217;t been able to find anyone that takes them,&#8221; Jim Cramer stated in a recent CNBC Squawk Box edition. He further added, &#8220;It&#8217;s like $80 billion worth of non-Bitcoin that&#8217;s destined to be wiped out.&#8221;<br /><br />The XRP community won&#8217;t let Cramer’s criticism slide. Crypto Law founder John Deaton responded, &#8220;Jim Cramer continues to talk about XRP, and he is totally clueless about the asset itself or the network—the XRPLedger—in which XRP operates.&#8221;<br /><br />Similarly, the CNBC host claims in a Friday tweet that Binance, the largest cryptocurrency exchange by trading volume, has &#8220;no real legitimacy&#8221; following the collapse of its primary rival FTX. <br /><br />The host of CNBC&#8217;s &#8220;Mad Money&#8221; seemed perplexed by market experts&#8217; refusal to recognize that most cryptocurrencies have no value at all.<br /><br />&#8220;Why aren&#8217;t there strategists saying that most crypto is worthless and should be sold?&#8221; he wonders. Cramer goes on to say that he would rather put his money in DraftKings, a sports betting firm, than Binance. This is not the first time the financial expert has targeted the world&#8217;s largest bitcoin exchange.<br /><br />Jim Cramer is critical of cryptocurrencies, calling them a &#8220;gigantic&#8221; scam. &#8220;The whole thing seems so bottomless that I don&#8217;t know how to fathom it,&#8221; he said. According to Cramer, XRP, Dogecoin (DOGE), and Solana (SOL) are all &#8220;cons.&#8221;<br /><br />Cramer appears to have adopted an often-hard position on cryptocurrency assets, claiming that only blockchain technology is valuable, not cryptocurrency itself. &#8220;No one thinks blockchain is bad,&#8221; the CNBC host said.<br /><br />The CNBC host also reiterated JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon&#8217;s admiration for blockchain while comparing cryptocurrency to &#8220;pet rocks.&#8221; <br /><br />Since 2014, the &#8220;Blockchain, not Bitcoin&#8221; narrative has gained support, with crypto detractors suggesting that the technology has more viable applications beyond speculative trading.</p>
<h2>Binance Announces Give Away of 1 BTC for New Users</h2>
<p>Top crypto exchange<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-receives-clean-bill-of-health-from-cryptoquant/"> Binance</a> Card is launching an exclusive giveaway for its new users. It announces that eligible new Binance Card users&#8217; actions will qualify them to receive a BUSD or BTC coin reward, which is 1 BTC in their Spot wallet.<br /><br />This is if they order their Binance Card during the promotion period and complete a successful transaction or make an ATM withdrawal with their Binance Card during the promotion period from December 1 to December 31, 2022.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/jim-cramer-says-he-is-negative-on-xrp-ltc-doge-binance-announce-giveaway-of-1-btc-for-new-users/">Jim Cramer Says He Is Negative on XRP, LTC, DOGE; Binance Announces Giveaway of 1 BTC for New Users</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/jim-cramer-says-he-is-negative-on-xrp-ltc-doge-binance-announce-giveaway-of-1-btc-for-new-users/">Jim Cramer Says He Is Negative on XRP, LTC, DOGE; Binance Announces Giveaway of 1 BTC for New Users</a> was first posted on December 16, 2022 at 6:09 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana Based DEX, Raydium Suffers $4.4 Million Exploit; Here Are Bitcoin Predictions for 2023</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/solana-based-dex-raydium-loses-nearly-4-4-million-in-exploit-here-are-bitcoin-predictions-for-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 22:20:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin price prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Raydium (RAY)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana (SOL)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63534</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Solana-based DEX, Raydium has been exploited for over $4.4 million, according to the post-mortem analysis carried out by the team. Arkham Crypto Intelligence gave indications about the exploit, ’’It appears that an account on Solana is draining multiple liquidity pools on Raydium. The account has received thousands of Solana in the last few minutes. We [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/solana-based-dex-raydium-loses-nearly-4-4-million-in-exploit-here-are-bitcoin-predictions-for-2023/">Solana Based DEX, Raydium Suffers $4.4 Million Exploit; Here Are Bitcoin Predictions for 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/solana-based-dex-raydium-loses-nearly-4-4-million-in-exploit-here-are-bitcoin-predictions-for-2023/">Solana Based DEX, Raydium Suffers $4.4 Million Exploit; Here Are Bitcoin Predictions for 2023</a> was first posted on December 16, 2022 at 5:20 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Solana-based DEX, <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/raydium-serum-iost-shiba-inu-hedera-lead-altcoin-pack-rebound-is-the-btc-market-setting-up-a-bear-trap/">Raydium</a> has been exploited for over $4.4 million, according to the post-mortem analysis carried out by the team. <br /><br />Arkham Crypto Intelligence gave indications about the exploit, <em>’’It appears that an account on Solana is draining multiple liquidity pools on Raydium. The account has received thousands of Solana in the last few minutes. We would advise withdrawing any liquidity on Raydium until further notice’’,</em> it stated.<br /><br />The exploit was officially confirmed by the Raydium Twitter account,’’ An exploit on Raydium is being investigated that affected liquidity pools. Details to follow as more is known. Its initial knowledge is that the attacker overtook owner authority, but the authority has been halted on AMM and farm programs for now.<br /><br />It gives an Initial Post-Mortem, stating it was working with 3rd-party auditors and teams across Solana to gather additional information. It says that a patch has been deployed to prevent further exploits from the attacker.</p>
<p>Raydium’s upgrade authority is held by a SquadsProtocol multisig so the attack was not related to upgrade authority on the program, it stated. The exploit appears to stem from a trojan attack and compromised private key for the pool owner account, it stated giving the root cause of the incident.</p>
<p>The attacker then accessed the pool owner account and was then able to call the withdrawalPNL function, a function used to collect trading/protocol fees earned by swaps in pools. The hacker was also able to set the parameters to change the settings for both quote and base tokens in the affected pools in order to modify expected fees and then withdraw those amounts.</p>
<p>According to it, the pools affected are SOL-USDC, SOL-USDT, RAY-USDC, RAY-USDT, RAY-SOL, stSOL-USDC, ZBC-USDC, UXP-USDC, whETH-USDC.</p>
<p>The approximate total funds exploited by the attacker are RAY, $1,879,638, stSOL $3,214, whETH $39.3, USDC $1,094,613, SOL $120,512, UXP $21,068,507, ZBC $9,758,647, USDT $110,427. In total, this represents nearly $4,395,237.</p>
<h2>Here Are Bitcoin Predictions for 2023</h2>
<p>While <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/btc-price-analysis-bitcoin-sustains-above-yearly-lows-179250-btc-withdrawn-from-exchanges-since-novembers-start/">Bitcoin</a> may still test a potential low of $10,000-$12,000, it could recover to $30,000 in the second half of 2023, Matthew Sigel, VanEck&#8217;s head of digital assets research predicts. Bitcoin is currently trading down 3.40% at $16,968.</p>
<p>Marion Laboure, a research analyst at Deutsche Bank predicts <em>&#8220;Although investors have suffered significant losses, we believe this second &#8216;crypto winter&#8217; will be a net positive because the FTX collapse will edge the crypto ecosystem closer to the established financial sector.&#8221;</em></p>
<p>Tom Norwood, Co-founder and CEO of LOOP markets predicts, <em>&#8220;Demand for bitcoin should continue to grow regardless of market conditions as it is still better than most currencies in that it at least has a good chance of going up eventually, whereas most currencies are just going to depreciate over time.&#8221;</em> Norwood expects the crypto market to pick up in about six months.</p>
<p>In their<em> &#8220;surprise&#8221;</em> scenario for 2023, Standard Chartered on the other hand forecasts Bitcoin dropping to $5,000 if the present decline continues.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/solana-based-dex-raydium-loses-nearly-4-4-million-in-exploit-here-are-bitcoin-predictions-for-2023/">Solana Based DEX, Raydium Suffers $4.4 Million Exploit; Here Are Bitcoin Predictions for 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/solana-based-dex-raydium-loses-nearly-4-4-million-in-exploit-here-are-bitcoin-predictions-for-2023/">Solana Based DEX, Raydium Suffers $4.4 Million Exploit; Here Are Bitcoin Predictions for 2023</a> was first posted on December 16, 2022 at 5:20 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Receives Clean Bill of Health From CryptoQuant</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/binance-receives-clean-bill-of-health-from-cryptoquant/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 21:18:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63542</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain analytics company CryptoQuant has confirmed that all of Binance&#8217;s reserves are present and accounted for after receiving a lot of bad press for its most recent proof-of-reserves audit. Over the past few days, FUD reports claiming that this or that cryptocurrency platform is about to shut down have roiled the market for cryptocurrencies. Being [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-receives-clean-bill-of-health-from-cryptoquant/">Binance Receives Clean Bill of Health From CryptoQuant</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-receives-clean-bill-of-health-from-cryptoquant/">Binance Receives Clean Bill of Health From CryptoQuant</a> was first posted on December 16, 2022 at 4:18 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Blockchain analytics company <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/dashboard/639937bbfbe454308ff04670">CryptoQuant</a> has confirmed that all of Binance&#8217;s reserves are present and accounted for after receiving a lot of bad press for its most recent proof-of-reserves audit.<br /><br />Over the past few days, FUD reports claiming that this or that cryptocurrency platform is about to shut down have roiled the market for cryptocurrencies. Being the largest trading platform in the industry, Binance has emerged as the primary target of the majority of FUD.<br /><br />Binance&#8217;s overcollateralized Bitcoin reserves were confirmed by the proof-of-reserves report created by Mazars. However, Mazars began to distance itself from the report after it was criticized by some business experts, and as a result, the <a href="https://veritas.mazars.com/binance/">link</a> to it is no longer active.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" width="2446" height="1164" class="alignnone wp-image-63548 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/screenshot-2022-12-16-at-144517.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/screenshot-2022-12-16-at-144517.png 2446w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/screenshot-2022-12-16-at-144517-300x143.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/screenshot-2022-12-16-at-144517-1024x487.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/screenshot-2022-12-16-at-144517-768x365.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/screenshot-2022-12-16-at-144517-1536x731.png 1536w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/screenshot-2022-12-16-at-144517-2048x975.png 2048w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/screenshot-2022-12-16-at-144517-750x357.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/screenshot-2022-12-16-at-144517-1140x543.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2446px) 100vw, 2446px" /></p>
<h6><em>Source: <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/dashboard/639937bbfbe454308ff04670">CryptoQuant</a></em></h6>
<p>Given that the report used an<em> &#8220;agreed-upon procedure&#8221;</em> rather than a complete audit that followed a process imposed by the auditor, the issue seems to have been that the report was not a proper audit.<br /><br />With 30% of its reserves in BTC, Binance is now the largest exchange in the market, according to CryptoQuant&#8217;s analysis of the exchange. With 26% of its reserves held in Bitcoin, Coinbase came in second.<br /><br />The fact that the liabilities reported by <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/asset/btc/chart/exchange-flows/exchange-reserve?exchange=binance&amp;window=BLOCK&amp;sma=0&amp;ema=0&amp;priceScale=log&amp;metricScale=linear&amp;chartStyle=line">Binance</a> and CryptoQuant&#8217;s estimation were so similar was one of the report&#8217;s main messages.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>&#8220;In order to assess the data in Binance’s Proof-of-Reserves report, we compared Binance liabilities expressed in the report to CryptoQuant’s on-chain metric Binance BTC Reserve data (our estimate of Binance’s customers’ deposits). We found out that the liabilities reported by Binance are very close to our estimation (99%).&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<p>According to the report&#8217;s findings, Binance&#8217;s ETH and stablecoin reserves are <em>&#8220;not showing FTX-like behavior,&#8221;</em> and the BNB exchange coin did not make up a significant portion of reserves.<br /><br /><em>&#8220;Binance has an acceptable &#8220;Clean Reserve,” which means its token, BNB, is still a low proportion of its total assets.&#8221;</em></p>
<p><em>Image Credit: Shutterstock</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-receives-clean-bill-of-health-from-cryptoquant/">Binance Receives Clean Bill of Health From CryptoQuant</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-receives-clean-bill-of-health-from-cryptoquant/">Binance Receives Clean Bill of Health From CryptoQuant</a> was first posted on December 16, 2022 at 4:18 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>