<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title/>
	<atom:link href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 09:16:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3</generator>
	<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><itunes:subtitle/><itunes:category text="News &amp; Politics"/><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Business News"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Investing"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Tech News"/></itunes:category><item>
		<title>Why VC Spectra is Winning Over Arbitrum and Monero Investors: The Prospects of 900% ROI</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/why-vc-spectra-is-winning-over-arbitrum-and-monero-investors-the-prospects-of-900-roi/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/why-vc-spectra-is-winning-over-arbitrum-and-monero-investors-the-prospects-of-900-roi/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 09:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VC Spectra (SPCT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65526</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking for a robust network that democratizes access to blockchain and technology projects? Enter VC Spectra (SPCT), a new decentralized asset management protocol offering early [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/why-vc-spectra-is-winning-over-arbitrum-and-monero-investors-the-prospects-of-900-roi/">Why VC Spectra is Winning Over Arbitrum and Monero Investors: The Prospects of 900% ROI</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/why-vc-spectra-is-winning-over-arbitrum-and-monero-investors-the-prospects-of-900-roi/">Why VC Spectra is Winning Over Arbitrum and Monero Investors: The Prospects of 900% ROI</a> was first posted on August 11, 2023 at 9:16 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p align="left">Looking for a robust network that democratizes access to blockchain and technology projects? Enter VC Spectra (SPCT), a new decentralized asset management protocol offering early investors a 900% ROI once it launches on exchanges. Although Arbitrum (ARB) and Monero (XMR) have initiated various system upgrades, VC Spectra (SPCT) blows them off the water, utilizing machine-learning algorithms for profitable trade execution. Discover why SPCT is winning over ARB and XMR.<u><b></b></u></p>
<h2 class="western">VC Spectra (SPCT): The New Sheriff In Town Redefining Blockchain</h2>
<p align="left"><a href="https://vcspectra.io/"><span style="color: #1155cc;"><u>VC Spectra (SPCT)</u></span></a> is the go-to decentralized hedge fund utilizing state-of-the-art technology to execute profitable trading decisions. The platform grants users voting rights, exclusive access to pre-ICOs and early-stage blockchain ventures.</p>
<p align="left">Moreover, VC Spectra&#8217;s native token (SPCT) is a BRC-20 standard token built on the Bitcoin blockchain. The token enables asset management, seamless exchange, and decentralized trading on the Spectra platform. SPCT implements a deflationary model with a burn mechanism that progressively reduces token supply, increasing VC Spectra (SPCT) value.</p>
<p align="left">Through strict risk management principles, VC Spectra (SPCT) strategically allocates 40% of its funds to a carefully curated portfolio and another 40% to specific ICOs.As a user-centric platform, VC Spectra (SPCT) goes beyond buybacks and quarterly dividends linked to investment earnings.</p>
<p align="left">With Stage 2 of the public presale underway, SPCT is valued at $0.011, marking a 37.5% spike from its initial $0.008 price. SPCT is projected to skyrocket by 127.27% to $0.025 once the platform advances to Stage 3.</p>
<p align="left">Market forecasts paint a positive picture, with <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/spct-vs-doge-vs-bnb-future-of-high-returns/">VC Spectra (SPCT)</a> positioned to surge by 900% from its initial $0.008 price to $0.08 once it hits the exchanges. Grab your SPCT tokens today and enjoy a 25% bonus on any deposit.<u><b></b></u></p>
<h2 class="western">Arbitrum’s Evolution Continues: Spotlight on ARB’s the Cutting-Edge Improvements</h2>
<p align="left">Arbitrum Foundation has introduced its long-awaited inaugural grant initiative. Dubbed “Foundation Grants,” this program is dedicated to fostering the expansion of the Arbitrum (ARB) ecosystem by bestowing grants upon partner projects and extending support for educational initiatives.</p>
<p align="left">Each grant furnished via this initiative will follow a structure anchored in milestones and key performance indicators (KPIs), ensuring productive collaboration with chosen recipients to meet predefined objectives. The implementation of the Foundation Grant Program will occur in a series of distinct phases, each catering to applications from specific segments within the Arbitrum ecosystem. Moreover, the inaugural phase will prioritize the development of decentralized applications and infrastructure for both Arbitrum Nova and Arbitrum One.</p>
<p align="left">So, it’s no surprise Arbitrum (ARB) spiked by 4.4% over the past week, from $1.13 to $1.18. Driven by its focus on efficiency and sustainability, Arbitrum’s (ARB) price is expected to increase by 13.6%, from $1.18 to $1.34 in the coming weeks.</p>
<h2 class="western">Momentum Shift: Monero (XMR) Exhibits Promising Bullish Trend</h2>
<p align="left">Monero’s (XMR) price jumped by 2.03% over the past week, from $158.14 to $161.36. Experts point out that the rising demand for spot Bitcoin ETFs positively influenced Monero’s (XMR) price dynamics.</p>
<p align="left">Additionally, Monero&#8217;s (XMR) dynamic fee structure prevents fees from becoming excessively high, regardless of increasing usage. The blockchain operates without any set limits, ensuring flexibility and affordability.</p>
<p align="left">Furthermore, the global competition surrounding the development of CBDCs has further contributed to Monero’s (XMR) growing popularity. Monero’s (XMR) enhanced ring signatures also enable quick and secure validation of private transactions.</p>
<p align="left">As Monero (XMR) bolsters its network capabilities, experts say Monero’s (XMR) price can spike by 5.52%, from $161.36 to $170.27.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/why-vc-spectra-is-winning-over-arbitrum-and-monero-investors-the-prospects-of-900-roi/">Why VC Spectra is Winning Over Arbitrum and Monero Investors: The Prospects of 900% ROI</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/why-vc-spectra-is-winning-over-arbitrum-and-monero-investors-the-prospects-of-900-roi/">Why VC Spectra is Winning Over Arbitrum and Monero Investors: The Prospects of 900% ROI</a> was first posted on August 11, 2023 at 9:16 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/why-vc-spectra-is-winning-over-arbitrum-and-monero-investors-the-prospects-of-900-roi/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bittrex Agrees to $24 Million Settlement with SEC</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/bittrex-agrees-to-24-million-settlement-with-sec/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/bittrex-agrees-to-24-million-settlement-with-sec/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 22:19:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bittrex]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65524</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bankrupt cryptocurrency exchange Bittrex and its CEO have reached a settlement with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for a sum of $24 million. This [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bittrex-agrees-to-24-million-settlement-with-sec/">Bittrex Agrees to $24 Million Settlement with SEC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bittrex-agrees-to-24-million-settlement-with-sec/">Bittrex Agrees to $24 Million Settlement with SEC</a> was first posted on August 10, 2023 at 10:19 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bankrupt cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bittrex-announces-partnership-to-launch-new-crypto-platform-for-middle-east-and-north-africa/">Bittrex</a> and its CEO have reached a settlement with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for a sum of $24 million. This agreement comes after the SEC filed charges against the exchange in April for functioning as an unregistered trading platform.</p>
<p>In the court filing submitted on Thursday, neither the exchange nor its foreign affiliate, along with former CEO William Shihara, admitted or denied the allegations. Bittrex Global GmbH, the foreign affiliate, has also agreed to resolve the accusations, about its failure to register as a national securities exchange, according to an<a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2023-150"> official statement by the SEC</a>.</p>
<p>Gurbir S. Grewal, who heads the SEC&#8217;s enforcement division, emphasized that Bittrex had attempted to eliminate any indications that the token issuers&#8217; online statements were linked to investment contracts, to evade federal securities regulations. This attempt was ultimately unsuccessful, leading to the charges. Grewal noted that the settlement highlights the significance of the economic realities behind such offerings, rather than merely altering labels or descriptions.</p>
<p>William Shihara expressed contentment with the settlement outcome in an emailed statement, regarding it as a positive resolution. He stressed the importance of achieving a balance between fostering innovation, supporting entrepreneurs, and safeguarding consumers. Shihara hoped that this settlement could contribute to advancing these goals.</p>
<p>Bittrex had applied for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in May, disclosing estimated assets and liabilities ranging between $500 million and $1 billion. The company had already revealed plans to withdraw from the U.S. market in March. At its peak, Bittrex accounted for nearly 23% of USD support in the cryptocurrency exchange market during the initial months of 2018.</p>
<p>The SEC has taken a strong stance against unregistered crypto exchanges, as demonstrated by their legal actions against Bittrex and, more recently, Coinbase in June. SEC Chair Gary Gensler has consistently underscored the necessity for compliance within the cryptocurrency sector.</p>
<p>He has highlighted that while trading platforms deal with various crypto tokens, they often lack the established safeguards against fraud and manipulation that are present in traditional financial markets. Gensler reiterated this concern during an interview with Bloomberg last month.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bittrex-agrees-to-24-million-settlement-with-sec/">Bittrex Agrees to $24 Million Settlement with SEC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bittrex-agrees-to-24-million-settlement-with-sec/">Bittrex Agrees to $24 Million Settlement with SEC</a> was first posted on August 10, 2023 at 10:19 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/bittrex-agrees-to-24-million-settlement-with-sec/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bakkt Revenue Surges to $348 Million Despite Falling Trading Volume</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/bakkt-revenue-surges-to-348-million-despite-falling-trading-volume/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/bakkt-revenue-surges-to-348-million-despite-falling-trading-volume/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 21:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BAKKT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65522</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The digital asset platform Bakkt has revealed a remarkable surge in its total revenue for the second quarter of this year, reaching $348 million. This [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bakkt-revenue-surges-to-348-million-despite-falling-trading-volume/">Bakkt Revenue Surges to $348 Million Despite Falling Trading Volume</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bakkt-revenue-surges-to-348-million-despite-falling-trading-volume/">Bakkt Revenue Surges to $348 Million Despite Falling Trading Volume</a> was first posted on August 10, 2023 at 9:54 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The digital asset platform<a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bakkt-to-buy-apex-crypto-for-200-million/"> Bakkt</a> has revealed a remarkable surge in its total revenue for the second quarter of this year, reaching $348 million. This represents a significant leap from the $14 million recorded in the same quarter of the previous year, 2022.</p>
<p>A spokesperson for the company clarified that the current quarter&#8217;s revenue of $348 million is inclusive of gross revenue, adhering to Generally Accepted Accounting Principles (GAAP), while the $14 million reported last year was based on total revenue on a net basis.</p>
<p>Based in New York City, Bakkt attributed its impressive earnings to the acquisition of Apex Crypto in April. The substantial increase in gross crypto services revenue was primarily fueled by the trading activities of Apex Crypto. The company communicated this in an <a href="https://investors.bakkt.com/news/news-details/2023/Bakkt-Reports-Second-Quarter-2023-Results/default.aspx">official earnings statement</a>.</p>
<p>Gavin Michael, the CEO of Bakkt, underlined the significance of acquiring Apex Crypto at the start of the quarter. He stated, &#8220;The completion of our acquisition of Apex Crypto marked a pivotal moment for our company. We&#8217;ve been able to significantly expand our presence within the crypto ecosystem, achieving strong traction by engaging new clients.&#8221;</p>
<p>Apex Crypto has since been rebranded as Bakkt Crypto Solutions. Bakkt further<a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bakkt-set-to-launch-crypto-transaction-app-by-2020/"> bolstered</a> its client portfolio by bringing invstr, Swan Bitcoin, and Blockchain.com into the fold.</p>
<p>While Bakkt&#8217;s traded volume experienced a decline of 51%, amounting to $531 million, the number of transacting accounts also witnessed a 20% drop compared to the previous year. The company attributed these declines in trading to the prevailing &#8220;slowdown&#8221; within the crypto market.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, Bakkt noted a 3% increase in its assets under custody, which reached $660 million. This growth can be attributed to the elevated values of certain cryptocurrencies, as stated by Bakkt.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bakkt-revenue-surges-to-348-million-despite-falling-trading-volume/">Bakkt Revenue Surges to $348 Million Despite Falling Trading Volume</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bakkt-revenue-surges-to-348-million-despite-falling-trading-volume/">Bakkt Revenue Surges to $348 Million Despite Falling Trading Volume</a> was first posted on August 10, 2023 at 9:54 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/bakkt-revenue-surges-to-348-million-despite-falling-trading-volume/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stablecoins Face Supply Crunch Amid Rising Adoption</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/stablecoin-face-supply-crunch-amid-rising-adoption/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/stablecoin-face-supply-crunch-amid-rising-adoption/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 22:48:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stablecoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65518</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Amid the widely applauded launch of a stablecoin by PayPal this week, signaling the entrance of a prominent American payment giant into the blockchain arena, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/stablecoin-face-supply-crunch-amid-rising-adoption/">Stablecoins Face Supply Crunch Amid Rising Adoption</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/stablecoin-face-supply-crunch-amid-rising-adoption/">Stablecoins Face Supply Crunch Amid Rising Adoption</a> was first posted on August 9, 2023 at 10:48 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Amid the widely applauded launch of a stablecoin by <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/paypal-sees-record-high-crypto-deposits-reaching-943m/">PayPal</a> this week, signaling the entrance of a prominent American payment giant into the blockchain arena, the overall supply of this asset category has experienced a prolonged decline spanning more than a year.</p>
<p>Recent <a href="https://www.federalreserve.gov/supervisionreg/srletters/SR2308.htm#:~:text=To%20obtain%20a%20written%20notification,of%20its%20activities%2C%20and%20the">data</a> underscores a steady reduction in the aggregate supply of stablecoins since the midpoint of 2022. The trajectory continued into 2023, witnessing a decline of approximately 12%. The total supply dwindled from $139 billion at the outset of the year to $122 billion by August.</p>
<p>Market analysts are now anticipating a potential reversal of this downturn, particularly given PayPal&#8217;s newfound involvement in the sector. The belief is that PayPal&#8217;s active engagement could validate the utility of stablecoins, not only elucidating their functional value but also compelling traditional financial institutions to embrace these digital assets due to competitive pressures. Mark Lurie, CEO of Shipyard Software, expressed this sentiment, emphasizing that if PayPal effectively demonstrates the practical application of stablecoins, it could trigger a significant wave of adoption.</p>
<p>Concurrently, regulatory frameworks seem to be positioning themselves to accommodate an expansion in<a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/stablecoin-issuer-tethers-q1-profits-surge-to-1-5-billion/"> stablecoin</a> utilization. In a communiqué directed at state member banks with interest in &#8220;issuing, holding, or transacting in dollar tokens to facilitate payments,&#8221; the U.S. Federal Reserve stipulated the necessity for banks to establish robust protocols to manage liquidity and mitigate the risks of illicit financial activities.</p>
<p>The central bank has taken a proactive stance, unveiling the &#8220;Novel Activities Supervision Program&#8221; to bolster oversight over banks engaged in stablecoin activities. This program encompasses a comprehensive supervision enhancement across all financial institutions under its purview. The focus is extended to include cryptocurrency, distributed ledger technology, and novel partnerships between nonbank entities and financial service providers, aimed at delivering technologically-driven financial solutions to consumers.</p>
<p>Simultaneously, the UK Treasury has joined this regulatory trend. They have <a href="https://assets.publishing.service.gov.uk/government/uploads/system/uploads/attachment_data/file/1176540/Payments_Regulation_and_the_Systemic_Perimeter_-_Consultation_Response.pdf">released</a> a consultation response detailing updated propositions for a regulatory framework overseeing systemic stablecoins. The framework delineates the collaborative supervisory approach between the Bank of England and the Financial Conduct Authority, orchestrating stablecoin issuance and usage oversight in tandem.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/stablecoin-face-supply-crunch-amid-rising-adoption/">Stablecoins Face Supply Crunch Amid Rising Adoption</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/stablecoin-face-supply-crunch-amid-rising-adoption/">Stablecoins Face Supply Crunch Amid Rising Adoption</a> was first posted on August 9, 2023 at 10:48 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/stablecoin-face-supply-crunch-amid-rising-adoption/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			<enclosure length="502962" type="application/pdf" url="https://assets.publishing.service.gov.uk/government/uploads/system/uploads/attachment_data/file/1176540/Payments_Regulation_and_the_Systemic_Perimeter_-_Consultation_Response.pdf"/><itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><itunes:subtitle>Amid the widely applauded launch of a stablecoin by PayPal this week, signaling the entrance of a prominent American payment giant into the blockchain arena, [&amp;#8230;] The post Stablecoins Face Supply Crunch Amid Rising Adoption appeared first on . Stablecoins Face Supply Crunch Amid Rising Adoption was first posted on August 9, 2023 at 10:48 pm. &amp;copy;2023 &amp;quot;Kryptomoney&amp;quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at susanta@brishti.in</itunes:subtitle><itunes:summary>Amid the widely applauded launch of a stablecoin by PayPal this week, signaling the entrance of a prominent American payment giant into the blockchain arena, [&amp;#8230;] The post Stablecoins Face Supply Crunch Amid Rising Adoption appeared first on . Stablecoins Face Supply Crunch Amid Rising Adoption was first posted on August 9, 2023 at 10:48 pm. &amp;copy;2023 &amp;quot;Kryptomoney&amp;quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at susanta@brishti.in</itunes:summary><itunes:keywords>News, BUSD, stablecoins, Tether, USDC</itunes:keywords></item>
		<item>
		<title>Aptos Strikes Partnership With Microsoft, Price Soar 10%</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/aptos-strikes-partnership-with-microsoft-price-soar-10/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/aptos-strikes-partnership-with-microsoft-price-soar-10/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 21:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aptos (APT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MICROSOFT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65496</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Aptos (APT) is experiencing a significant surge in bullish momentum today, prompted by the exciting news of its recent collaboration with the esteemed American multinational [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/aptos-strikes-partnership-with-microsoft-price-soar-10/">Aptos Strikes Partnership With Microsoft, Price Soar 10%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/aptos-strikes-partnership-with-microsoft-price-soar-10/">Aptos Strikes Partnership With Microsoft, Price Soar 10%</a> was first posted on August 9, 2023 at 9:31 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/aptos-apt-400-gains-in-january-traced-to-crazy-buying-in-korean-communities-aave-v3-deploys-on-ethereum/">Aptos (APT)</a> is experiencing a significant surge in bullish momentum today, prompted by the exciting news of its recent collaboration with the esteemed American multinational technology behemoth, Microsoft Incorporated. The protocol&#8217;s announcement of this partnership has generated enthusiasm within the broader digital currency landscape. This strategic alliance will encompass ventures into asset tokenization solutions, an intensified focus on digital payments and the exploration of Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs).<br /><br />The Microsoft<a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/08/09/microsoft-aptos-blockchain-ai-web3/?guccounter=1&amp;guce_referrer=aHR0cHM6Ly91LnRvZGF5Lw&amp;guce_referrer_sig=AQAAAByZ9n9jNE4Pxt2_1vNbUTNhI9wiRN-PstU8a2YClet5gPYN1fsN5lSnN8duuS2EWMfLFLct5jXKDxly_sTHi9pCISgUWDTYKiKBLLMgowlEjtCbQojHpKtFPkkyANbWhR9mOOhjzogJnTmW_f3p31hDn5wOSGsbCjekqfldcjcS"> partnership</a> illuminates a constellation of promising growth indicators for Aptos. The project has consistently achieved remarkable milestones since its inception in the past year. With Microsoft&#8217;s involvement, Aptos is set to solidify its status as a Layer 1 blockchain, extending its influence beyond the boundaries of the Web 3.0 ecosystem into the expansive realm of technology at large.<br /><br />By the terms of the Aptos-Microsoft collaboration, Aptos will leverage the capabilities of Microsoft Azure OpenAI services to enhance its offerings comprehensively. In a joint statement issued by both entities, it was emphasized that the diverse array of services from both organizations will be advantageous for Aptos&#8217; &#8220;developers in their endeavors to construct intelligent contracts and decentralized applications.&#8221;<br /><br />This announcement catalyzed a 10% increase in the<a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/aptos/"> price of Aptos (APT)</a>, reaching $7.52 per coin. Despite the prevailing volatility within the cryptocurrency sphere, the recent surge has repositioned APT as a standout contender among high-potential tokens.<br /><br />The strategic agreement between <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/aptos-apt-400-gains-in-january-traced-to-crazy-buying-in-korean-communities-aave-v3-deploys-on-ethereum/">Aptos</a> and Microsoft has been met with applause from stakeholders within the digital currency ecosystem. However, it also underscores a broader trend evident among emerging Web 3.0 protocols. Much like Aptos, Ankr Protocol has solidified a parallel partnership with Microsoft over the past year.<br /><br />Notably, other prominent tech giants, such as Google and Amazon, are similarly intensifying their engagement with the blockchain domain through collaborations with burgeoning Web 3.0 protocols. These partnerships collectively reinforce the notion that blockchain and traditional technology frameworks can harmoniously coexist.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/aptos-strikes-partnership-with-microsoft-price-soar-10/">Aptos Strikes Partnership With Microsoft, Price Soar 10%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/aptos-strikes-partnership-with-microsoft-price-soar-10/">Aptos Strikes Partnership With Microsoft, Price Soar 10%</a> was first posted on August 9, 2023 at 9:31 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/aptos-strikes-partnership-with-microsoft-price-soar-10/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Google Bard’s Golden Trio: VC Spectra (SPCT), Ethereum (ETH), and Optimism (OP) Tipped as 2023’s Investment Powerhouses</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/google-bards-golden-trio-vc-spectra-spct-ethereum-eth-and-optimism-op-tipped-as-2023s-investment-powerhouses/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/google-bards-golden-trio-vc-spectra-spct-ethereum-eth-and-optimism-op-tipped-as-2023s-investment-powerhouses/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 05:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VC Spectra (SPCT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65508</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>While Ethereum (ETH) records a pessimistic outlook, Optimism (OP) and VC Spectra (SPCT) have been building traction over the past weeks. Their performance has prompted [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/google-bards-golden-trio-vc-spectra-spct-ethereum-eth-and-optimism-op-tipped-as-2023s-investment-powerhouses/">Google Bard&#8217;s Golden Trio: VC Spectra (SPCT), Ethereum (ETH), and Optimism (OP) Tipped as 2023&#8217;s Investment Powerhouses</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/google-bards-golden-trio-vc-spectra-spct-ethereum-eth-and-optimism-op-tipped-as-2023s-investment-powerhouses/">Google Bard&#8217;s Golden Trio: VC Spectra (SPCT), Ethereum (ETH), and Optimism (OP) Tipped as 2023&#8217;s Investment Powerhouses</a> was first posted on August 9, 2023 at 5:42 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p align="left">While Ethereum (ETH) records a pessimistic outlook, Optimism (OP) and <span style="color: #1155cc;"><u>VC Spectra (SPCT)</u></span> have been building traction over the past weeks. Their performance has prompted the attention of market analysts and investors alike.</p>
<p align="left">However, though Ethereum (ETH) is currently having a significant price decline, experts suggest this is a perfect &#8220;bag the token&#8221; period as Ethereum (ETH) will yield maximum profits alongside well-performing tokens like VC Spectra (SPCT) and Optimism (OP).</p>
<h2 class="western">VC Spectra (SPCT) Inspires Investors&#8217; Interest With its Unique Feature</h2>
<p align="left"><a href="https://vcspectra.io/"><span style="color: #1155cc;"><u>VC Spectra (SPCT)</u></span></a> has attracted the interest of investors all over the world with its decentralized investment management platform. The VC Spectra (SPCT) platform offers a secure and all-inclusive investment solution with the potential for sustainable returns on investment (ROI) for its customers. The platform enables investments with high-profit potential and minimal risk in the blockchain and technology industries.</p>
<p align="left">VC Spectra (SPCT) is in Stage 2 of its public presale, selling at $0.011 per token. Despite still being in its presale, <span style="color: #1155cc;"><u>VC Spectra (SPCT)</u></span> is proving its profiting potential. During Stage 1 of its presale, VC Spectra (SPCT) was selling each token at $0.008. When it rose to its current price of $0.011, early investors made a 37.5% ROI! The existing thing is that this is not the final increase VC Spectra (SPCT) will make.</p>
<p align="left">The token has been predicted to hit $0.08 at the final stage of its presale. This guarantees investors who partake now a 627% ROI when the presale ends. Furthermore, <span style="color: #1155cc;"><u>VC Spectra&#8217;s (SPCT)</u></span> price increase during its presale is an insight into the price increases it will make when it is launched. The platform&#8217;s unique world utility guarantees it will be a formidable player in the crypto market.</p>
<h2 align="left">Ethereum&#8217;s (ETH) Current Decline Could Be a Perfect Buying Period</h2>
<p align="left">Over the past few weeks, Ethereum&#8217;s (ETH) price has been bouncing in an extremely sluggish spectrum, leaving investors unsure about the next move. The value of <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/ethereum-eth-braces-for-new-wave-of-volatility-data-shows/">Ethereum</a> (ETH) has dropped by 1.89% in the last seven days, falling from $1,870.21 on July 31, 2023, to $1,834.81 at the time of writing. Experts suggest this is a perfect buying period, as Ethereum (ETH) will experience a significant price rally in the coming months.</p>
<p align="left">Ethereum (ETH) is presently preparing for the impending Cancun-Deneb upgrade. Though no date has been selected, the event is expected to take place before the end of 2023. The update is intended to increase the scalability, security, and data storage of the Ethereum (ETH) network while cutting transaction costs.</p>
<p align="left">Furthermore, the highly anticipated EIP-4844 will occur alongside Ethereum&#8217;s (ETH) Dencun upgrade. Ethereum Improvement Proposal 4844 (EIP-4844) aims to significantly reduce transaction costs, which could unlock many new applications in Ethereum&#8217;s (ETH) ecosystem. An increase in network activity might send a spark to Ethereum (ETH), sending it into a price uproar. With this, Ethereum (ETH) could hit significant price levels before the end of 2023.</p>
<h2 class="western">Optimism (OP) Maintains Positive Outlook</h2>
<p align="left">The price of Optimism (OP) has increased by over 20% in recent weeks due to a combination of underlying solid reasons. One of these factors is Zora, a popular Web3 NFT minting platform, which is now connected to the Optimism (OP) network. Optimism&#8217;s (OP) affiliation with Zora has helped its stand out among layer-2 competitors, experiencing a <b>47% increase in daily transactions</b> since July 20, 2023.</p>
<p align="left">Furthermore, Optimism (OP) has issued its first Fault Proof, which is essential for allowing protocol decentralization. This has further expanded Optimism&#8217;s (OP) reach, enabling more activities in its ecosystem. These events have helped Optimism (OP) build and maintain a bullish momentum over the past weeks.</p>
<p align="left">Optimism (OP) has seen a <b>7% </b>increase since the month began, rising from $1.58 on August 1, 2023, to $1.70 at the time of writing. Based on Optimism&#8217;s (OP) previous price movements and Bitcoin&#8217;s halving cycles, market analysts predict that Optimism (OP) will continue on its uptrend, reaching the $2 price level by September 2023.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/google-bards-golden-trio-vc-spectra-spct-ethereum-eth-and-optimism-op-tipped-as-2023s-investment-powerhouses/">Google Bard&#8217;s Golden Trio: VC Spectra (SPCT), Ethereum (ETH), and Optimism (OP) Tipped as 2023&#8217;s Investment Powerhouses</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/google-bards-golden-trio-vc-spectra-spct-ethereum-eth-and-optimism-op-tipped-as-2023s-investment-powerhouses/">Google Bard&#8217;s Golden Trio: VC Spectra (SPCT), Ethereum (ETH), and Optimism (OP) Tipped as 2023&#8217;s Investment Powerhouses</a> was first posted on August 9, 2023 at 5:42 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/google-bards-golden-trio-vc-spectra-spct-ethereum-eth-and-optimism-op-tipped-as-2023s-investment-powerhouses/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Transforms Carbon Market with New Alliance</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/ripple-transforms-carbon-market-with-new-alliance/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/ripple-transforms-carbon-market-with-new-alliance/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 09:44:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65506</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple, a pioneer in blockchain technology, has initiated a far-reaching endeavor to infuse carbon markets with transparency, trustworthiness, and ethical standards. Historically, carbon markets, which [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/ripple-transforms-carbon-market-with-new-alliance/">Ripple Transforms Carbon Market with New Alliance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/ripple-transforms-carbon-market-with-new-alliance/">Ripple Transforms Carbon Market with New Alliance</a> was first posted on August 8, 2023 at 9:44 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/ripple-ceo-states-the-company-is-mostly-recruiting-abroad/">Ripple</a>, a pioneer in blockchain technology, has<a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230807853646/en/Centigrade-Announces-New-Open-Data-Platform-to-Restore-Trust-in-Carbon-Markets"> initiated</a> a far-reaching endeavor to infuse carbon markets with transparency, trustworthiness, and ethical standards.</p>
<p>Historically, carbon markets, which facilitate the trading of carbon credits to counterbalance CO2 emissions, have grappled with issues of opacity and doubt. Demonstrating its unwavering commitment to addressing climate change, Ripple committed a substantial $100 million investment towards this cause last year.</p>
<p>In a strategic collaboration with Centigrade, a technology provider focused on climate solutions, Ripple now seeks to elevate its efforts even further. Centigrade has launched an open data platform designed to cultivate faith in the global voluntary<a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/eco-friendly-bitcoin-mining/"> carbon markets</a>.</p>
<p>The platform&#8217;s primary objective is to offer top-notch data, streamlined accessibility, and heightened transparency, all working together to nurture an equitable, dynamic, and efficient carbon market. However, it&#8217;s important to note that this platform doesn&#8217;t serve as a trading or rating system; rather, its purpose lies in providing indispensable data to all stakeholders within the carbon credit ecosystem, encompassing sellers, buyers, and service providers.</p>
<p>This bold initiative by Ripple and Centigrade positions them as pivotal players in delivering a vital service to the carbon market. By making informed decisions possible for investors, the open data platform could potentially stimulate the availability of high-quality credits, thus ensuring the smooth operation of both carbon and nature markets.</p>
<p>This undertaking stands as a core component of Ripple&#8217;s comprehensive strategy to combat climate change. Having previously invested in the tokenization of carbon credits, Ripple persists in advocating for environmentally conscious practices within the realm of cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/ripple-transforms-carbon-market-with-new-alliance/">Ripple Transforms Carbon Market with New Alliance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/ripple-transforms-carbon-market-with-new-alliance/">Ripple Transforms Carbon Market with New Alliance</a> was first posted on August 8, 2023 at 9:44 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/ripple-transforms-carbon-market-with-new-alliance/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shocking Predictions: Top 3 Coins That Could Outperform Bitcoin This Year</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/shocking-predictions-top-3-coins-that-could-outperform-bitcoin-this-year/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/shocking-predictions-top-3-coins-that-could-outperform-bitcoin-this-year/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 04:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon (MATIC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UniSwap (UNI)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VC Spectra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VC Spectra (SPCT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65503</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In an epic turn of events, experts have named VC Spectra (SPCT), Uniswap (UNI), and Polygon (MATIC) the best investments to make in 2023. With [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/shocking-predictions-top-3-coins-that-could-outperform-bitcoin-this-year/">Shocking Predictions: Top 3 Coins That Could Outperform Bitcoin This Year</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/shocking-predictions-top-3-coins-that-could-outperform-bitcoin-this-year/">Shocking Predictions: Top 3 Coins That Could Outperform Bitcoin This Year</a> was first posted on August 8, 2023 at 4:08 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In an epic turn of events, experts have named VC Spectra (SPCT), Uniswap (UNI), and Polygon (MATIC) the best investments to make in 2023. With VC Spectra (SPCT) scoring high gains in its ongoing presale, investors remain hopeful that VC Spectra (SPCT) will outperform Bitcoin (BTC) this year.</p>
<p>What about Uniswap (UNI) and Polygon (MATIC)? Well, let’s find out!</p>
<h2>Unleashing the Future of Asset Management: VC Spectra (SPCT)</h2>
<p>Prepare to embark on an extraordinary journey into the realm of innovative asset management. <a href="https://vcspectra.io/">VC Spectra (SPCT)</a> is no ordinary platform; it&#8217;s a revolutionary force, <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/matic-price-analysis-matic-jumps-8-as-investment-manager-hamilton-lane-tokenizes-on-ploygon/">reshaping the investment landscape for investors</a> from all walks of life.</p>
<p>At the core of VC Spectra (SPCT) lies the power of Artificial Intelligence, a force that ensures the utmost security and transparency for your valuable assets.</p>
<p>But that&#8217;s not all – VC Spectra takes decentralization to a whole new level. Experience the thrill of exclusive voting rights, where your voice truly matters. The traditional approach to investment management is a thing of the past; VC Spectra (SPCT) empowers you to actively participate in shaping your financial future.</p>
<p>VC Spectra has garnered tremendous interest<strong>.</strong> The ongoing public presale has been a beacon of hope for investors, attracting significant attention at every stage. Stage 2 gave a profit of 37.5% to Stage 1 investors and introduced a new price of $0.011.</p>
<p>Stage 3 plans to take things a bit further by introducing a 127.27% growth and <a href="https://vcspectra.io/">VC Spectra (SPCT)</a> price of $0.025.</p>
<p>VC Spectra&#8217;s enterprising goal is to reach a target price of $0.08 for its tokens, projecting an awe-inspiring 627% growth from the initial Stage 2 price.</p>
<h2>Uniswap (UNI) Just Rose Above Its Support Region: What’s Next?</h2>
<p>Uniswap (UNI) has been in the spotlight lately due to its recent price movements. After reaching an all-time high of $44.97 on May 3, 2021, the cryptocurrency experienced fluctuations but has since gained popularity among crypto investors.</p>
<p>Since June 20, 2023, the price of Uniswap (UNI) has been on a steady upward trend, showing no signs of decline. As of July 31, it stood at $6.50, a modest increase of 1.2% from its 24-hour high of $6.42. Notably, the trading volume spiked to $144.8 million, marking a significant 21.75% increase within 24 hours.</p>
<p>Analysts forecast that Uniswap&#8217;s (UNI) price will fluctuate between $6.15 and $6.98, with an average annual value of $6.41. Uniswap (UNI) is trading at $6.18 on August 4, reflecting a 6.61% decrease in the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>However, despite the rise in Uniswap&#8217;s (UNI) price, Uniswap v3&#8217;s performance declined. The trading volume for Ethereum (ETH) and Optimism (OP) networks decreased after reaching a peak in mid-July.</p>
<h2>Polygon’s (MATIC) Volley Of Losses: Time To Switch?</h2>
<p>Polygon (MATIC) has experienced a rollercoaster ride in its price over the past few weeks. On July 8, Polygon (MATIC) was trading at $0.67, but it quickly jumped to $0.84 on July 14, representing a 25.3% increase. However, the excitement was short-lived, falling by 11.9% to $0.74 on July 20 and dropping to $0.70 on July 26. As of August 2, Polygon (MATIC) is trading at $0.69.</p>
<p>This continuous drop surprised investors, especially considering the decrease in Ethereum&#8217;s network activity. Many had anticipated that Polygon (MATIC) would benefit from this situation and rally, but unfortunately, it disappointed by declining further.</p>
<p>As a result, bearish predictions suggest Polygon (MATIC) could fall by 34% to $0.45. On the other hand, some bullish analysts foresee a rebound in the altcoin sector by the end of the year, leading to an 18% rise in Polygon&#8217;s (MATIC) price to $0.82.</p>
<p>During these fluctuations, Polygon (MATIC) remains a topic of interest for investors, and its future performance will be closely monitored in the coming months.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/shocking-predictions-top-3-coins-that-could-outperform-bitcoin-this-year/">Shocking Predictions: Top 3 Coins That Could Outperform Bitcoin This Year</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/shocking-predictions-top-3-coins-that-could-outperform-bitcoin-this-year/">Shocking Predictions: Top 3 Coins That Could Outperform Bitcoin This Year</a> was first posted on August 8, 2023 at 4:08 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/shocking-predictions-top-3-coins-that-could-outperform-bitcoin-this-year/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>China Breaks Silence on Crypto Matters</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/china-breaks-silence-on-crypto-matters/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/china-breaks-silence-on-crypto-matters/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 22:28:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[China]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65492</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Chinese Communist Party has issued a strong warning to overseas telecommunications and network fraud groups, vowing to take decisive action against their illegal and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/china-breaks-silence-on-crypto-matters/">China Breaks Silence on Crypto Matters</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/china-breaks-silence-on-crypto-matters/">China Breaks Silence on Crypto Matters</a> was first posted on August 6, 2023 at 10:28 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The Chinese Communist Party has issued a strong warning to <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/indian-cryptocurrency-exchange-move-overseas-post-rbi-clampdown/">overseas</a> telecommunications and network fraud groups, vowing to take decisive action against their illegal and criminal activities. <br /><br />The party expressed concern that fraud groups are exploiting new technologies and formats, including Blockchain, metaverse, virtual currencies, and artificial intelligence, to deceive and harm people. In response, the party pledged to collaborate with relevant countries to dismantle electronic fraud centers and rescue victims trapped in these schemes.<br /><br />At a recent plenary meeting of the China Central Political and Legal Committee, the need for systematic management, rule of law, and management at the source was emphasized to prevent overseas telecommunications and network fraud, along with other illegal and criminal activities. <br /><br />The committee highlighted that fraud groups are using deceptive tactics, such as posing as<em> &#8220;high-paying recruiters,&#8221;</em> to lure and coerce innocent individuals into fraudulent activities, leading to a range of nefarious practices like violent detention and human trafficking that jeopardize people&#8217;s safety and property.<br /><br />To combat these threats effectively, the committee will examine the current law enforcement model and explore the establishment of a normalized cooperation mechanism to target overseas telecommunications and network fraud. The goal is to establish a strong, long-term deterrent against criminals while maintaining a friendly cooperative relationship between China and related countries.<br /><br />Additionally, the committee emphasized its commitment to strengthen oversight of new technologies and formats exploited by fraud groups to modernize their criminal tools. Notably, <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/indians-engage-in-international-purchases-using-bitcoins-amidst-tightening-regulations/">Blockchain</a> was specifically highlighted in the statement as a technology requiring increased vigilance.<br /><br />With these measures in place, the Chinese Communist Party aims to tackle the rising challenge of overseas telecom and network fraud effectively and safeguard its citizens from falling victim to these illegal activities.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/china-breaks-silence-on-crypto-matters/">China Breaks Silence on Crypto Matters</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/china-breaks-silence-on-crypto-matters/">China Breaks Silence on Crypto Matters</a> was first posted on August 6, 2023 at 10:28 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/china-breaks-silence-on-crypto-matters/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Block Sees Over 30% Increase in BTC Revenue in Q2</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/block-sees-over-30-increase-in-btc-revenue-in-q2/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/block-sees-over-30-increase-in-btc-revenue-in-q2/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 21:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Block]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Square]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65488</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Block, formerly known as Square and led by former Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey, has revealed impressive growth in its Bitcoin revenue for the second quarter [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/block-sees-over-30-increase-in-btc-revenue-in-q2/">Block Sees Over 30% Increase in BTC Revenue in Q2</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/block-sees-over-30-increase-in-btc-revenue-in-q2/">Block Sees Over 30% Increase in BTC Revenue in Q2</a> was first posted on August 6, 2023 at 9:54 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://block.xyz/">Block</a>, formerly known as Square and led by former Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey, has revealed impressive growth in its Bitcoin revenue for the second quarter of 2023. The payment technology firm reported that its Bitcoin revenue for this period reached approximately $2.39 billion, marking a substantial 34% increase compared to the figure reported in Q2 2022, which was nearly $1.8 billion.<br /><br />The surge in Bitcoin <a href="https://s29.q4cdn.com/628966176/files/doc_financials/2023/q2/2Q23_Block_Shareholder-Letter.pdf">revenue</a> can be attributed to the company&#8217;s mobile application, Cash App, which enables monetary transfers and has become a significant player on the crypto scene. Cash App&#8217;s BTC gross profit also showed promising growth, reaching $44 million, a 7% increase year-over-year.<br /><br />Block <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/SQ/?guccounter=1&amp;guce_referrer=aHR0cHM6Ly9jcnlwdG9wb3RhdG8uY29tLw&amp;guce_referrer_sig=AQAAANllAnch98Hs14joIJt0WW5y10L6DtcREFFOW98cufxp6Q3XAPV8OkOPQbH4XiQNNrqIHyJ_L7lrFw9RVS8tVrXAYa-XzbIw_sjtkBfEnv9YwZQO5nqrn9MXPmvb82YdZzfYg5gMXUqy-ndHaekiQ1a2w1yNHt2AolZdOlLLG2Mh">attributed</a> the year-over-year increase in Bitcoin revenue and gross profit to the higher quantity of Bitcoin sold to customers. However, this growth was partially offset by a decrease in the average market price of Bitcoin compared to the previous year.<br /><br />Despite the surge in <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-off-to-strong-q2-as-it-ends-q1-down-only-10/">Bitcoin</a> revenue, Block did not incur any Bitcoin impairment losses during the period. As of the end of June 2023, the company&#8217;s BTC investment was valued at $245 million. However, due to a slight price decrease in the following weeks, Block&#8217;s stash of 8,027 BTC is currently worth approximately $234 million.<br /><br />With this substantial BTC investment, Block has cemented its position as one of the top 10 largest corporate holders of Bitcoin, according to CoinGecko&#8217;s data. MicroStrategy holds the top job, having recently purchased an additional 420 BTC, bringing its total Bitcoin holdings to 152,800 BTC.<br /><br />In addition to the positive bitcoin revenue, Block&#8217;s overall financial results (excluding bitcoin revenue) were also encouraging. However, the company&#8217;s shares did not experience an immediate uptick, as SQ&#8217;s stock price closed at over $73 on August 3, but subsequently dipped by approximately 6% in after-hours trading.<br /><br />Block had previously reported a decline in bitcoin revenue, with $1.83 billion generated from Cash App in Q4 2022, an 8.5% decrease compared to the figures from Q4 2021. The company explained that this disappointing number was a result of the market crash that occurred last year, which dampened investor interest in the primary cryptocurrency.<br /><br />Despite the decrease in revenue at the time, Block&#8217;s overall financial results were favorable, leading to a 7% spike in its shares. The company&#8217;s strong performance in the crypto and financial sectors continues to attract investors&#8217; attention and interest.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/block-sees-over-30-increase-in-btc-revenue-in-q2/">Block Sees Over 30% Increase in BTC Revenue in Q2</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/block-sees-over-30-increase-in-btc-revenue-in-q2/">Block Sees Over 30% Increase in BTC Revenue in Q2</a> was first posted on August 6, 2023 at 9:54 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/block-sees-over-30-increase-in-btc-revenue-in-q2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			<enclosure length="6832652" type="application/pdf" url="https://s29.q4cdn.com/628966176/files/doc_financials/2023/q2/2Q23_Block_Shareholder-Letter.pdf"/><itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><itunes:subtitle>Block, formerly known as Square and led by former Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey, has revealed impressive growth in its Bitcoin revenue for the second quarter [&amp;#8230;] The post Block Sees Over 30% Increase in BTC Revenue in Q2 appeared first on . Block Sees Over 30% Increase in BTC Revenue in Q2 was first posted on August 6, 2023 at 9:54 pm. &amp;copy;2023 &amp;quot;Kryptomoney&amp;quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at susanta@brishti.in</itunes:subtitle><itunes:summary>Block, formerly known as Square and led by former Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey, has revealed impressive growth in its Bitcoin revenue for the second quarter [&amp;#8230;] The post Block Sees Over 30% Increase in BTC Revenue in Q2 appeared first on . Block Sees Over 30% Increase in BTC Revenue in Q2 was first posted on August 6, 2023 at 9:54 pm. &amp;copy;2023 &amp;quot;Kryptomoney&amp;quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at susanta@brishti.in</itunes:summary><itunes:keywords>News, Bitcoin (BTC), Block, Square</itunes:keywords></item>
		<item>
		<title>Tether Triumphs as US Court Dismisses Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/tether-triumphs-as-us-court-dismisses-lawsuit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/tether-triumphs-as-us-court-dismisses-lawsuit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 16:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65485</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tether and its sister company, Bitfinex, which are both owned by iFinex, have achieved a significant legal victory as a U.S. court has thrown out [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/tether-triumphs-as-us-court-dismisses-lawsuit/">Tether Triumphs as US Court Dismisses Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/tether-triumphs-as-us-court-dismisses-lawsuit/">Tether Triumphs as US Court Dismisses Lawsuit</a> was first posted on August 6, 2023 at 4:54 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/Tether_to/status/1687568481745510400">Tether</a> and its sister company, Bitfinex, which are both owned by iFinex, have achieved a significant legal victory as a U.S. court has thrown out a class-action lawsuit against them. Chief Judge Laura Taylor Swain of the U.S. District Court for the Southern District of New York ordered the complete dismissal of the lawsuit brought by Matthew Anderson and Shawn Dolifka against Tether and Bitfinex.<br /><br />The court ruled that the plaintiffs&#8217; complaint lacked plausible allegations of injury and failed to provide any evidence of diminished actual value for the USDT stablecoin.<br /><br />The lawsuit, initiated in December 2021, centered around allegations concerning Tether&#8217;s <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/tether-supply-increase-amidst-bitcoin-price-hike/">stablecoin</a> backing. However, the court&#8217;s recent decision to dismiss the case at an early stage suggests that the plaintiffs&#8217; claims lacked legal merit.<br /><br />In a similar vein, U.S. crypto exchange Coinbase also sought a dismissal of an SEC complaint against it, citing the recent Ripple ruling that determined XRP was not a security when traded on exchanges.<br /><br />Furthermore, Tether <a href="https://tether.to/en/tether-excess-reserves-increase-by-850m-to-reach-3-3b-as-leading-stablecoin-reveals-72-5b-overall-exposure-in-us-t-bills-and-unveils-energy-related-investments/">reported</a> in a BDO assurance opinion for the second quarter of 2023 that its excess reserves increased by $850 million. <br /><br />Excess reserves represent the company&#8217;s profits not distributed to shareholders, which Tether chose to maintain in addition to the 100% reserves backing all outstanding tokens.<br /><br />Tether noted in the report that its reserves are exceptionally liquid, with 85% of its investments held in cash and cash equivalents. During the period from April to June 2023, the company&#8217;s operational profits exceeded $1 billion, demonstrating a strong 30% quarter-over-quarter growth.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/tether-triumphs-as-us-court-dismisses-lawsuit/">Tether Triumphs as US Court Dismisses Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/tether-triumphs-as-us-court-dismisses-lawsuit/">Tether Triumphs as US Court Dismisses Lawsuit</a> was first posted on August 6, 2023 at 4:54 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/tether-triumphs-as-us-court-dismisses-lawsuit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlockFi Clears Major Hurdle in US Bankruptcy Court</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/blockfi-clears-major-hurdle-in-us-bankruptcy-court/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/blockfi-clears-major-hurdle-in-us-bankruptcy-court/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 16:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlockFI]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65475</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BlockFi, the bankrupt crypto lender, recently announced that the US Bankruptcy Court for the District of New Jersey has conditionally approved its disclosure statement. This [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/blockfi-clears-major-hurdle-in-us-bankruptcy-court/">BlockFi Clears Major Hurdle in US Bankruptcy Court</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/blockfi-clears-major-hurdle-in-us-bankruptcy-court/">BlockFi Clears Major Hurdle in US Bankruptcy Court</a> was first posted on August 6, 2023 at 4:26 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/blockfi-clears-regulatory-hurdle-to-repay-297m-to-specific-customers/">BlockFi</a>, the bankrupt crypto lender, recently announced that the US Bankruptcy Court for the District of New Jersey has conditionally approved its disclosure statement. This marks a significant step in BlockFi&#8217;s reorganization process, which has been underway for eight months since the company filed for relief under Chapter 11 of the United States Bankruptcy Code.<br /><br />In an <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230802310688/en/BlockFi%E2%80%99s-Disclosure-Statement-Conditionally-Approved-by-Court">official statement</a> on August 2nd, Mark Renzi, BlockFi&#8217;s Chief Restructuring Officer, emphasized the lender&#8217;s commitment to maximizing recoveries for its creditors. He expressed his satisfaction with the conditional approval of the Disclosure Statement, stating that it brings BlockFi <em>&#8220;one step closer to accomplishing that goal.&#8221;</em><br /><br />Renzi urged BlockFi&#8217;s <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/blockfi-minces-25-million-in-2-weeks-as-the-bitcoin-and-ether-investors-seek-interest/">clients</a> to support the plan, believing it offers the best route to efficiently return crypto assets to the clients. The company&#8217;s focus, if the bankruptcy plan is approved, will be on recovering funds from other defunct firms, such as Alameda, FTX, 3AC, Emergent, Marex, and Core Scientific. This effort is aimed at maximizing recoveries for clients and defending against claims by third parties that could significantly dilute clients&#8217; assets.<br /><br />However, not everyone is on board with the proposed bankruptcy plans. The disgraced crypto exchange FTX, the fallen hedge fund Three Arrows Capital (3AC), and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) have expressed strong opposition to the plan.<br /><br />The proposed bankruptcy plan provides clients with the option for releases, allowing them to avoid withdrawing from a voluntary third-party release, which would absolve them from any claims and causes of action that BlockFi may have against them. This release is applicable for most clients, except those who withdrew $250,000 or more from BlockFi Interest Accounts (BIA) or BlockFi Private Client (BPC) Accounts on or after November 2, 2022.<br /><br />The scheduled date for voting on the proposed reorganization plan is September 11, when the fate of BlockFi&#8217;s restructuring efforts will be determined.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/blockfi-clears-major-hurdle-in-us-bankruptcy-court/">BlockFi Clears Major Hurdle in US Bankruptcy Court</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/blockfi-clears-major-hurdle-in-us-bankruptcy-court/">BlockFi Clears Major Hurdle in US Bankruptcy Court</a> was first posted on August 6, 2023 at 4:26 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/blockfi-clears-major-hurdle-in-us-bankruptcy-court/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>VC Spectra (SPCT) vs. Dogecoin (DOGE) vs. BNB: A Glimpse into the Future of High Returns!</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/spct-vs-doge-vs-bnb-future-of-high-returns/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/spct-vs-doge-vs-bnb-future-of-high-returns/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 05:38:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VC Spectra (SPCT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65478</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Among the top contenders offering unique opportunities for exponential growth are VC Spectra (SPCT), Dogecoin (DOGE), and BNB. VC Spectra has rapidly gained traction in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/spct-vs-doge-vs-bnb-future-of-high-returns/">VC Spectra (SPCT) vs. Dogecoin (DOGE) vs. BNB: A Glimpse into the Future of High Returns!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/spct-vs-doge-vs-bnb-future-of-high-returns/">VC Spectra (SPCT) vs. Dogecoin (DOGE) vs. BNB: A Glimpse into the Future of High Returns!</a> was first posted on August 6, 2023 at 5:38 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Among the top contenders offering unique opportunities for exponential growth are VC Spectra (SPCT), Dogecoin (DOGE), and BNB. VC Spectra has rapidly gained traction in the market, securing an impressive $2.4 million within a mere two-week period through its private seed sale, thereby setting ambitious growth objectives for the future.</p>
<p>With their diverse potential, these cryptocurrencies present captivating prospects for investors seeking significant returns in the dynamic world of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>BUY SPCT TOKENS NOW</strong></p>
<h2>Discover the Revolutionary Potential of VC Spectra (SPCT)</h2>
<p><a href="https://vcspectra.io/">VC Spectra (SPCT)</a> stands out as a pioneering force, providing investors with a <strong>unique opportunity</strong> to engage in early-stage projects.</p>
<p>What sets <a href="https://vcspectra.io/">VC Spectra (SPCT)</a> apart is its rigorous due diligence process that evaluates the viability and potential of each project meticulously. VC Spectra’s (SPCT) team of experts scrutinizes critical aspects, ensuring that only the most promising ventures make it to the presale stage.</p>
<p>Operating on the BRC-20 standard, the VC Spectra (SPCT) token serves a myriad of functions, including decentralized trading, asset management, and covering transaction fees.</p>
<p>The current public presale in Stage 2 presents a compelling opportunity for investors, with the VC Spectra (SPCT) token available at an attractive price of $0.011.</p>
<p>The allure intensifies as we look ahead to Stage 3, where projections suggest the VC Spectra (SPCT) token could reach <strong>$0.025</strong>. <a href="https://vcspectra.io/"> </a>VC Spectra (SPCT) will deliver its holders a staggering 127.27% increase from the current price and a remarkable 212.5% gain from the initial offering of $0.008.</p>
<h2>Elon Musk&#8217;s Endorsement: Dogecoin (DOGE) in the Spotlight Again</h2>
<p>Dogecoin (DOGE) once again captured the spotlight due to a subtle but meaningful alteration in Elon Musk&#8217;s Twitter bio. Musk has been hinting at the possibility of integrating Dogecoin (DOGE) into his ventures.</p>
<p>The Twitter rebrand on July 25 displayed both an &#8220;X&#8221; and a &#8220;D&#8221; in Musk&#8217;s profile. While the &#8220;X&#8221; represents the platform&#8217;s new branding, the &#8220;D&#8221; was widely interpreted as Dogecoin (DOGE), sparking speculation. This reignited rumors of potential usage of payments with Dogecoin (DOGE) on Musk&#8217;s &#8220;everything app.&#8221;</p>
<p>This seemingly minor development managed to score a small price gain for Dogecoin (DOGE), as it surged by 6% on July 25, rising from $0.77 to $0.82. However, the excitement was short-tempered and Dogecoin’s (DOGE) price quickly started falling. As of August 2, Dogecoin (DOGE) is trading at $0.74, reflecting a decrease of 3.9% compared to its price of $0.77 on July 25.</p>
<p>The revived interest triggered by Musk&#8217;s social media activity holds the potential for a significant positive impact on Dogecoin (DOGE) in the near future.</p>
<h2>BNB Chain Partners with PLANET</h2>
<p>BNB Chain has recently joined forces with PLANET, an innovative blockchain platform dedicated to driving positive change for a sustainable future.</p>
<p>The partnership between BNB Chain and PLANET was officially announced on July 27 through <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bnb-chain-reopens-operations-following-2-million-token-exploit/">BNB Chain</a>&#8216;s official Twitter/X account. PLANET now becomes an ecosystem partner to BNB Chain, establishing a powerful collaboration in the realm of blockchain for environmental good.</p>
<p>The partnership with BNB Chain is a major boost to PLANET&#8217;s mission of using the power of celebrities, fandom, and cutting-edge technology to promote sustainability.</p>
<p>The partnership&#8217;s positive influence is reflected in BNB&#8217;s price performance. Between July 27 and August 2, BNB witnessed a 0.54% price increase, climbing from $238.3 to $240.6.</p>
<p>Analysts are optimistic about market sentiment for BNB, projecting a continued upward trend toward $250.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/spct-vs-doge-vs-bnb-future-of-high-returns/">VC Spectra (SPCT) vs. Dogecoin (DOGE) vs. BNB: A Glimpse into the Future of High Returns!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/spct-vs-doge-vs-bnb-future-of-high-returns/">VC Spectra (SPCT) vs. Dogecoin (DOGE) vs. BNB: A Glimpse into the Future of High Returns!</a> was first posted on August 6, 2023 at 5:38 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/spct-vs-doge-vs-bnb-future-of-high-returns/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Australia’s Financial Regulator Takes Legal Action Against eToro</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/australias-financial-regulator-takes-legal-action-against-etoro/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/australias-financial-regulator-takes-legal-action-against-etoro/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 22:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ASIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Australia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eToro]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65471</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Australian Securities and Investments Commission (ASIC) has taken legal action against trading platform eToro, raising concerns about the potential harm its contract for difference [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/australias-financial-regulator-takes-legal-action-against-etoro/">Australia’s Financial Regulator Takes Legal Action Against eToro</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/australias-financial-regulator-takes-legal-action-against-etoro/">Australia’s Financial Regulator Takes Legal Action Against eToro</a> was first posted on August 4, 2023 at 10:32 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/central-bank-of-australia-voices-support-towards-bitcoin-and-cryptocurrency-usage/">Australian</a> Securities and Investments Commission (ASIC) has taken legal action against trading platform eToro, raising concerns about the potential harm its contract for difference (CFD) product could inflict on investors. CFDs are leveraged derivative contracts that allow customers to speculate on the price movements of equities, commodities, stock market indices, and digital assets.<br /><br /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/etoro-plans-to-launch-cryptocurrency-trading-services-in-31-us-states/">eToro</a>, an early adopter in the cryptocurrency market, introduced trading services with Bitcoin (BTC) in 2013 through CFDs. Over time, it expanded its offerings to include Ethereum (ETH), Cardano (ADA), Bitcoin Cash (BCH), Litecoin (LTC), and other cryptocurrencies.<br /><br />The Australian watchdog <a href="https://asic.gov.au/about-asic/news-centre/find-a-media-release/2023-releases/23-204mr-asic-sues-etoro-in-its-first-design-and-distribution-action-to-protect-consumers-from-high-risk-cfd-products/">announced</a> that it has commenced legal proceedings in the Federal Court against eToro, raising concerns about the adequacy of testing its CFD product before making it available to users. The focus of the case lies on the appropriateness of eToro&#8217;s target market and the screening test used to determine whether a retail client fell within the target market for the CFD product.<br /><br />The ASIC further claims that the financial product is highly dangerous and volatile, criticizing the initial trial as &#8220;wholly inadequate&#8221; in assessing whether a retail client fits the target market. The regulator alleges that eToro&#8217;s conduct led to a significant number of retail clients being exposed to the CFD product, which was not consistent with their investment objectives, financial situation, and needs, consequently posing a significant risk of consumer harm.<br /><br />Based on ASIC&#8217;s estimations, approximately 20,000 eToro customers incurred losses between October 5, 2021, and June 14, 2023, due to trading CFDs on the platform. The lawsuit reflects the regulator&#8217;s concerns about the potential impact of such products on retail investors and seeks to address issues related to customer protection and risk management.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/australias-financial-regulator-takes-legal-action-against-etoro/">Australia’s Financial Regulator Takes Legal Action Against eToro</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/australias-financial-regulator-takes-legal-action-against-etoro/">Australia’s Financial Regulator Takes Legal Action Against eToro</a> was first posted on August 4, 2023 at 10:32 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/australias-financial-regulator-takes-legal-action-against-etoro/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bank of Russia Initiates New Digital Ruble With Zero Transaction Fees Till 2025</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/bank-of-russia-initiates-new-digital-ruble-with-zero-transaction-fees-till-2025/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/bank-of-russia-initiates-new-digital-ruble-with-zero-transaction-fees-till-2025/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 21:37:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bank of Russia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65466</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a recent statement, the Bank of Russia revealed its plans for the country&#8217;s Digital Ruble currency. It declared that transactions using digital currency would [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bank-of-russia-initiates-new-digital-ruble-with-zero-transaction-fees-till-2025/">Bank of Russia Initiates New Digital Ruble With Zero Transaction Fees Till 2025</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bank-of-russia-initiates-new-digital-ruble-with-zero-transaction-fees-till-2025/">Bank of Russia Initiates New Digital Ruble With Zero Transaction Fees Till 2025</a> was first posted on August 4, 2023 at 9:37 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In a<a href="https://cbr.ru/press/event/?id=16982"> recent statement,</a> the Bank of Russia revealed its plans for the country&#8217;s Digital Ruble currency. It declared that transactions using digital currency would be free of charge until the year 2025. <br /><br />However, after this period, businesses and legal entities engaging in transactions with the Central Bank digital currency (CBDC) would incur a small fee for its usage. The Bank specified the fee structure in the statement as follows:<br /><br /><em>“The tariff for businesses for accepting payments for goods and services in digital rubles will be 0.3% of the payment amount (but no more than ?1,500).”</em><br /><br />Companies providing housing and communal services will face a lower tariff of 0.2%, but not exceeding P10. Transfers between legal entities will be subject to a fixed commission of 15 rubles per transaction.<br /><br />Russian citizens, on the other hand, would continue to enjoy free payments and transactions in the digital ruble. The Bank of Russia sees this move as an incentive for the populace to embrace and make extensive use of the national digital currency.<br /><br />As part of the ongoing efforts to promote the CBDC, the Bank of Russia announced the commencement of a pilot scheme this month. The pilot program involves the participation of 13 banks and will progress through different stages over the next two years until the Digital Ruble is fully integrated into wider circulation by 2025.<br /><br />To encourage participation, individuals and companies can open a single digital ruble account on the Bank of Russia&#8217;s official website without incurring any charges.<br /><br />In addition to the fee structure, the Bank of Russia unveiled the <a href="https://www.cbr.ru/press/event/?id=16980">official logo</a> for the digital currency. The logo features two interconnected elements: a ruble sign enveloped by a circular frame. The design resembles a conventional coin and bears a resemblance to the logo of the Bank of Russia. The primary colors of the logo are coral, scarlet (a shade of red), and white. The Bank also mentioned that this logo would be incorporated into mobile banking applications.<br /><br />It is important to note that the digital ruble bill was signed into law by President Vladimir Putin on July 24. The currency, which has been under development for the past two years, will serve as a third means of payment alongside cash and non-cash <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/binance-will-begin-support-for-russian-ruble-in-two-weeks-says-ceo-changpeng-zhao/">Rubles</a>. The implementation of the digital ruble marks a significant step in Russia&#8217;s efforts to modernize its financial infrastructure and embrace digital innovations in the payment system.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bank-of-russia-initiates-new-digital-ruble-with-zero-transaction-fees-till-2025/">Bank of Russia Initiates New Digital Ruble With Zero Transaction Fees Till 2025</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bank-of-russia-initiates-new-digital-ruble-with-zero-transaction-fees-till-2025/">Bank of Russia Initiates New Digital Ruble With Zero Transaction Fees Till 2025</a> was first posted on August 4, 2023 at 9:37 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/bank-of-russia-initiates-new-digital-ruble-with-zero-transaction-fees-till-2025/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Robinhood Shares Tumbles as Crypto Revenue Tanks</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/robinhood-shares-tumbles-as-crypto-revenue-tanks/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/robinhood-shares-tumbles-as-crypto-revenue-tanks/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 20:34:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robinhood]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65468</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a notable development, Robinhood, the online brokerage, achieved its first profitable quarter since its initial public offering, despite facing a continuous decline in its [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/robinhood-shares-tumbles-as-crypto-revenue-tanks/">Robinhood Shares Tumbles as Crypto Revenue Tanks</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/robinhood-shares-tumbles-as-crypto-revenue-tanks/">Robinhood Shares Tumbles as Crypto Revenue Tanks</a> was first posted on August 3, 2023 at 8:34 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a notable development, <a href="https://twitter.com/RobinhoodComms/status/1686834425341018113">Robinhood</a>, the online brokerage, achieved its first profitable quarter since its initial public offering, despite facing a continuous decline in its cryptocurrency-related revenue.</p>
<p>However, concerns among investors were evident as shares of Robinhood plummeted by 9.3% following the report of a decline in its monthly active users. While the revenue from cryptocurrency transactions dropped to $31 million in Q2, Robinhood&#8217;s total revenue managed to increase by 10% to $486 million, leading to a net income of $25 million.</p>
<p>Although the company celebrated higher Q2 revenues and its first profitable quarter as a publicly traded firm, Robinhood&#8217;s shares took a hit, falling an additional 4% in extended trading due to the decline in monthly active users. The online brokerage witnessed a decrease in active users, with the number dropping to 10.8 million, marking a decline of one million from the previous quarter and 3.2 million fewer than the previous year. In response to this user downturn, Robinhood is proactively exploring new revenue streams and implementing cost-cutting measures, including job cuts.</p>
<p>Robinhood initially ventured into the cryptocurrency market in 2018, offering users the ability to trade only <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-btc-ethereum-eth-volatility-at-multiyear-lows/">Bitcoin and Ethereum</a>. Over time, it expanded its offerings to include more digital assets, such as Shiba Inu in 2022. However, the ongoing &#8220;crypto winter&#8221; has led to a substantial decline in crypto trading revenue for the platform.</p>
<p>To add to the challenges, Robinhood recently faced a setback when it had to swiftly remove several newly listed assets, including Cardano after they were deemed securities by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) during a lawsuit against <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/binance-users-sold-bnb-token-in-millions-ahead-of-sec-lawsuits/">Binance</a>. This sudden removal of popular digital tokens may have contributed to the notable decline in the company&#8217;s cryptocurrency revenues.</p>
<p>Amidst the volatile market conditions and regulatory challenges, Robinhood is striving to adapt and find solutions to sustain its growth and profitability, seeking to navigate the ever-changing landscape of the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/robinhood-shares-tumbles-as-crypto-revenue-tanks/">Robinhood Shares Tumbles as Crypto Revenue Tanks</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/robinhood-shares-tumbles-as-crypto-revenue-tanks/">Robinhood Shares Tumbles as Crypto Revenue Tanks</a> was first posted on August 3, 2023 at 8:34 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/robinhood-shares-tumbles-as-crypto-revenue-tanks/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>USDC Market Cap Plummets to Lowest Level in Two Years</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/usdc-market-cap-plummets-to-lowest-level-in-two-years/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/usdc-market-cap-plummets-to-lowest-level-in-two-years/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 20:20:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USD Coin (USDC)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65457</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fintech giant Circle&#8217;s USD Coin (USDC), the second-largest stablecoin, has faced a challenging period with its market capitalization experiencing a downward trend for 13 consecutive [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/usdc-market-cap-plummets-to-lowest-level-in-two-years/">USDC Market Cap Plummets to Lowest Level in Two Years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/usdc-market-cap-plummets-to-lowest-level-in-two-years/">USDC Market Cap Plummets to Lowest Level in Two Years</a> was first posted on August 3, 2023 at 8:20 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Fintech giant Circle&#8217;s<a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1685566649389506560"> USD Coin (USDC)</a>, the second-largest stablecoin, has faced a challenging period with its market capitalization experiencing a downward trend for 13 consecutive months. Rival stablecoins have been encroaching on USDC&#8217;s market share, intensifying the pressure.<br /><br />As of August 3, 2023, the aggregated market capitalization of USDC dropped to $26.1 billion, a significant decline from its peak of nearly $56 billion recorded in late June 2022. Notably, the current market cap is the lowest since July 2021. Despite experiencing a crisis in the first quarter of 2022, USDC managed to limit its losses to only 10%, showing some resilience. Nevertheless, its primary competitor, U.S. Dollar Tether (USDT), the largest stablecoin, has been thriving, reaching a record market cap of $83 billion.<br /><br />The rapid decline in USDC&#8217;s market cap was accentuated after the painful de-pegging incident on March 11, 2023. During this period, rumors of insolvency by banks storing Circle&#8217;s resources led to panic selling by USDC holders, resulting in an $11 billion reduction in its market cap. This represented one of the steepest declines in the <a href="https://research.kaiko.com/insights/the-state-of-stablecoins">stablecoin&#8217;s</a> history.<br /><br />Consequently, USDC slipped out of the top 5 cryptocurrencies by market capitalization, losing its position to XRP, whose rise was fueled by Ripple&#8217;s legal victories against the SEC.<br /><br />However, the third quarter of 2023 was crucial for USDC&#8217;s technical development. Notably, it was natively launched on Arbitrum (ARB), a dominant Ethereum Layer 2 scaling solution. This integration made <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/circle-breaks-boundaries-with-new-cross-chain-usdc-protocol/">USDC transactions</a> more cost-effective and faster, significantly expanding its user base within the Arbitrum ecosystem.<br /><br />Additionally, Coinbase Wallet facilitated zero-gas USDC transfers on <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/matic-price-analysis-matic-up-8-amid-positive-news-polygon-sees-major-integration-with-the-graph-network/">Polygon (MATIC)</a>, the largest Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) blockchain, thanks to the implementation of EIP 4337, or the &#8220;Account Abstraction&#8221; mechanism, which opened up new possibilities for Ethereum-like blockchains.<br /><br />While USDC has faced challenges recently, these technical developments could present an opportunity for its resurgence in the<a href="https://ccdata.io/reports/stablecoins-cbdcs-report-july-2023"> stablecoin segment</a>. Nevertheless, it must strategize effectively to regain its competitive edge against its strong contenders.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/usdc-market-cap-plummets-to-lowest-level-in-two-years/">USDC Market Cap Plummets to Lowest Level in Two Years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/usdc-market-cap-plummets-to-lowest-level-in-two-years/">USDC Market Cap Plummets to Lowest Level in Two Years</a> was first posted on August 3, 2023 at 8:20 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/usdc-market-cap-plummets-to-lowest-level-in-two-years/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chainlink and Optimism Traders Eyeing Potential in VC Spectra</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/chainlink-and-optimism-traders-eyeing-potential-in-vc-spectra/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/chainlink-and-optimism-traders-eyeing-potential-in-vc-spectra/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 03:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chainlink holders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VC Spectra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VC Spectra token]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65460</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chainlink (LINK) holders face difficulty getting the price above the $8 mark yet again and are now worried that getting Chainlink (LINK) to surpass that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/chainlink-and-optimism-traders-eyeing-potential-in-vc-spectra/">Chainlink and Optimism Traders Eyeing Potential in VC Spectra</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/chainlink-and-optimism-traders-eyeing-potential-in-vc-spectra/">Chainlink and Optimism Traders Eyeing Potential in VC Spectra</a> was first posted on August 3, 2023 at 3:52 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chainlink (LINK) holders face difficulty getting the price above the $8 mark yet again and are now worried that getting Chainlink (LINK) to surpass that obstacle won’t be possible anytime soon. Optimism (OP) is currently in the green, but Optimism (OP) holders are hesitant about the token’s ability to break through the $1.7 resistance barrier. Meanwhile, VC Spectra (SPCT) has provided excellent gains and real-world utility to thousands of investors, and many Chainlink (LINK) and Optimism (OP) holders are looking to get in on the action.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">BUY SPCT TOKENS NOW</p>
<h2>VC Spectra (SPCT) Brings Lucrative Investments to Your Doorstep</h2>
<p>The blockchain investment sector has always been a tough market to break into and be successful in, as the blockchain is a foreign concept for many. Also, spotting a good investment out of thousands of potential ones is like finding a needle in a haystack.</p>
<p>However, <a href="https://vcspectra.io/">VC Spectra (SPCT)</a>, a decentralized hedge fund, eliminates all the difficulties that the blockchain investment market has and allows millions of people who have no prior experience to access lucrative investments and make life-changing money on the blockchain.</p>
<p>It does so by providing VC Spectra (SPCT) investors with five investment funds to choose from, with each of them containing <strong>high-potential</strong> projects that have been carefully picked out by industry experts. So, now, thanks to VC Spectra (SPCT), everyone can make successful blockchain investments and make a lot of money while doing so.</p>
<p>VC Spectra (SPCT) chooses its projects by putting every potential project or token through a rigorous selection process, which spits out only the best of the best. Then, VC Spectra (SPCT) lumps the projects into portfolios and allocates capital based on comprehensive risk management principles and investment strategies.</p>
<p>The VC Spectra token, SPCT, is now in Stage 2 of its public presale, trading at $0.011. Before this, VC Spectra (SPCT) was in Stage 1 of its presale, and the VC Spectra token, SPCT, was trading at $0.008. So, even now, VC Spectra (SPCT) has realized returns for holders, and experts believe that it will surge 900%, trading at $0.08 when the VC Spectra (SPCT) presale ends.</p>
<h2>Chainlink (LINK) Struggles to Break the $8 Resistance</h2>
<p>The past few weeks have shown us that Chainlink (LINK) finds it very hard to break out of the $8 price level, as Chainlink (LINK) has continuously failed to reach a price above $8 for quite some time now.</p>
<p>And as it nears the $8 mark again,<a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/link-price-analysis-here-are-price-indications-leading-web3-gaming-company-integrates-chainlink-vrf/"> Chainlink (LINK) holders</a> believe that history will repeat itself and are therefore looking for other investments that’ll bring them better gains than Chainlink (LINK).</p>
<p>Currently, Chainlink (LINK) is trading at $7.57, a 1.18% decrease in the last 24h. Likewise, the Chainlink (LINK) market cap is down by 1.18%, while the Chainlink (LINK) trading volume is up by 36.02%.</p>
<h2>Can Optimism (OP) Go Above $1.7?</h2>
<p>As Optimism (OP) increases from $1.2 to $1.7, Optimism (OP) holders are now wondering if it can brave the resistance and finally break the $1.7 price level. Likewise, crypto analysts state that Optimism (OP) could possibly go back down to $1.54.</p>
<p>So, experts say that now isn’t a good time to buy Optimism (OP), as there is a high chance of the token going further down.</p>
<p>Optimism (OP) is currently trading at $1.64, a 4.25% increase since yesterday. Also, the Optimism (OP) market cap is up by 4.45%, and the Optimism (OP) trading volume is up by 104.42%.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/chainlink-and-optimism-traders-eyeing-potential-in-vc-spectra/">Chainlink and Optimism Traders Eyeing Potential in VC Spectra</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/chainlink-and-optimism-traders-eyeing-potential-in-vc-spectra/">Chainlink and Optimism Traders Eyeing Potential in VC Spectra</a> was first posted on August 3, 2023 at 3:52 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/chainlink-and-optimism-traders-eyeing-potential-in-vc-spectra/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BALD Rugpull Linked to SBF as Base L2 Suffers Liquidity Issues</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/bald-rugpull-linked-to-sbf-as-base-l2-suffers-liquidity-issues/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/bald-rugpull-linked-to-sbf-as-base-l2-suffers-liquidity-issues/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 20:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bald (BALD)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Layer 2]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65453</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The recent meme coin frenzy on Coinbase&#8216;s Layer-2 Base blockchain has been marred by a major rug pull incident. The deployer of the Brian Armstrong-themed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bald-rugpull-linked-to-sbf-as-base-l2-suffers-liquidity-issues/">BALD Rugpull Linked to SBF as Base L2 Suffers Liquidity Issues</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bald-rugpull-linked-to-sbf-as-base-l2-suffers-liquidity-issues/">BALD Rugpull Linked to SBF as Base L2 Suffers Liquidity Issues</a> was first posted on August 2, 2023 at 8:36 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The recent meme coin frenzy on <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/coinbase-soaring-high-with-a-21-spike-amid-lawsuit-dismissal/">Coinbase</a>&#8216;s Layer-2 Base blockchain has been marred by a major rug pull incident. The deployer of the Brian Armstrong-themed Bald (BALD) token unexpectedly removed all liquidity for $BALD, constituting approximately 30% of the entire liquidity on the Base blockchain. This drastic move resulted in a significant crash in $BALD&#8217;s market price within a matter of hours.<br /><br />The meme currency $BALD experienced an astonishing surge, claiming a daily high of $0.093869 with an impressive 30,000% gain in just 13 hours. However, the surge was short-lived, and at the time of publication, $BALD is trading at a meager $0.00628762, as reported by CoinGecko.<br /><br /><a href="https://twitter.com/CertiKAlert/status/1686236502353666048">CertiK</a>, a blockchain security audit company, promptly issued a slippage alert when the price of $BALD plummeted by 88%. The company also cautioned about multiple compromised liquidity pools on LeetSwap.</p>
<p>Remarkably, the deployer of $BALD executed this disastrous rug pull without even needing to sell any tokens. The rug puller simply manipulated two-sided liquidity by adding and removing it while simultaneously buying $BALD. Adding to the severity of the situation, the deployer had been an influential player in the early days of DeFi.<br /><br />Despite the swift evaporation of a staggering $68 million in investors&#8217; funds due to this one-day rug pull, the initiator of the scheme managed to profit over $5 million in less than two days.<br /><br /><a href="https://twitter.com/0xJacket/status/1686138741071699970">Speculation</a> has emerged and Samuel Bankman-Fried (SBF), the founder of FTX, has found himself at the top of the suspect list. <br /><br />Blockchain security and analytics firm Nansen identified interactions between the deployer&#8217;s wallet and a crypto wallet <a href="https://twitter.com/FrankResearcher/status/1686184372485976065">linked</a> to Alameda Research, the sister company of the now-defunct crypto exchange FTX. <br /><br />Additionally, some community members noted that the BALD deployer and SBF shared a similar style of speech, adding to the suspicions.<br /><br />As on-chain detectives of Crypto Twitter delve deeper into the investigation, rumors on the platform have escalated. A prominent <a href="https://twitter.com/WhaleChart/status/1686312071862829056">whale account</a> made allegations that Samuel Bankman-Fried may have collaborated with Gary Gensler to &#8220;prove how fraudulent crypto is&#8221; in support of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission&#8217;s case against Coinbase. However, these rumors remain unverified and should be treated with caution until further evidence surfaces.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bald-rugpull-linked-to-sbf-as-base-l2-suffers-liquidity-issues/">BALD Rugpull Linked to SBF as Base L2 Suffers Liquidity Issues</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/bald-rugpull-linked-to-sbf-as-base-l2-suffers-liquidity-issues/">BALD Rugpull Linked to SBF as Base L2 Suffers Liquidity Issues</a> was first posted on August 2, 2023 at 8:36 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/bald-rugpull-linked-to-sbf-as-base-l2-suffers-liquidity-issues/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>HEX Loses Uniswap UI Support Amid SEC Legal Battle</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/hex-loses-uniswap-ui-support-amid-sec-legal-battle/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/hex-loses-uniswap-ui-support-amid-sec-legal-battle/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 13:51:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hex (HEX)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HEX tokens]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65442</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Richard Heart&#8217;s HEX token has been delisted from the prominent decentralized exchange, Uniswap, just days after the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filed a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/hex-loses-uniswap-ui-support-amid-sec-legal-battle/">HEX Loses Uniswap UI Support Amid SEC Legal Battle</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/hex-loses-uniswap-ui-support-amid-sec-legal-battle/">HEX Loses Uniswap UI Support Amid SEC Legal Battle</a> was first posted on August 2, 2023 at 1:51 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Richard Heart&#8217;s HEX token has been<a href="https://unsupportedtokens.uniswap.org/"> delisted</a> from the prominent decentralized exchange, Uniswap, just days after the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filed a <a href="https://twitter.com/SummersThings/status/1686016484638703616">lawsuit</a> claiming that the token is an unregistered security. The legal action against HEX was initiated on July 31.<br /><br />It&#8217;s important to note that the delisting from Uniswap&#8217;s front-end user interface does not entirely restrict users from trading HEX. Instead, the cryptocurrency has been moved to Uniswap&#8217;s list of unsupported tokens, accompanied by a warning note. Traders can still conduct HEX transactions on the DEX by directly interacting with the token&#8217;s smart contract.<br /><br /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/hex-token-crashes-over-fifty-to-trade-for-less-than-one-satoshi/">HEX</a>&#8216;s inclusion in the list of unsupported tokens implies that Uniswap has taken this measure based on legal considerations and concerns related to potential scams or trademark violations among listed cryptocurrencies.<br /><br />The SEC&#8217;s lawsuit targeted Richard Heart, whose real name is Richard Schueler, accusing him of raising over $1 billion since 2019 through three crypto projects: HEX, PulseChain (PLS), and PulseX (PLSX). Uniswap was also mentioned in the complaint as one of the trading venues for Heart&#8217;s tokens. According to the lawsuit, PulseX was launched as a Uniswap fork, and transactions involving unregistered securities issued by Heart occurred on the DEX.<br /><br />The lawsuit alleges that Heart misused funds invested in his crypto ventures to sustain a luxurious personal lifestyle, thereby defrauding investors of their money. This case is part of the SEC&#8217;s broader efforts to address regulatory concerns and protect investors in the cryptocurrency space, with previous cases against other crypto founders like Alex Mashinsky, Changpeng Zhao and <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/terraform-labs-co-founder-do-kwon-charged-with-fraud-after-arrest/">Do Kwon</a>.<br /><br />As the situation develops, the crypto community is closely monitoring the outcome of the lawsuit and its implications for HEX and other tokens in the market. The delisting from Uniswap may signal a potential setback for the HEX project and could have ramifications for its trading volume and liquidity.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/hex-loses-uniswap-ui-support-amid-sec-legal-battle/">HEX Loses Uniswap UI Support Amid SEC Legal Battle</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/hex-loses-uniswap-ui-support-amid-sec-legal-battle/">HEX Loses Uniswap UI Support Amid SEC Legal Battle</a> was first posted on August 2, 2023 at 1:51 pm.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/hex-loses-uniswap-ui-support-amid-sec-legal-battle/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			<enclosure length="-1" type="application/json" url="https://unsupportedtokens.uniswap.org/"/><itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><itunes:subtitle>Richard Heart&amp;#8217;s HEX token has been delisted from the prominent decentralized exchange, Uniswap, just days after the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filed a [&amp;#8230;] The post HEX Loses Uniswap UI Support Amid SEC Legal Battle appeared first on . HEX Loses Uniswap UI Support Amid SEC Legal Battle was first posted on August 2, 2023 at 1:51 pm. &amp;copy;2023 &amp;quot;Kryptomoney&amp;quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at susanta@brishti.in</itunes:subtitle><itunes:summary>Richard Heart&amp;#8217;s HEX token has been delisted from the prominent decentralized exchange, Uniswap, just days after the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filed a [&amp;#8230;] The post HEX Loses Uniswap UI Support Amid SEC Legal Battle appeared first on . HEX Loses Uniswap UI Support Amid SEC Legal Battle was first posted on August 2, 2023 at 1:51 pm. &amp;copy;2023 &amp;quot;Kryptomoney&amp;quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at susanta@brishti.in</itunes:summary><itunes:keywords>News, Hex (HEX), HEX tokens</itunes:keywords></item>
		<item>
		<title>Compound and Pepe Fade Away As VC Spectra Takes Center Stage</title>
		<link>https://www.kryptomoney.com/compound-and-pepe-fade-away-as-vc-spectra-takes-center-stage/</link>
					<comments>https://www.kryptomoney.com/compound-and-pepe-fade-away-as-vc-spectra-takes-center-stage/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 04:03:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VC Spectra]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.kryptomoney.com/?p=65449</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a shifting cryptocurrency landscape, Compound (COMP) and Pepe (PEPE) are losing their spotlight as VC Spectra (SPCT) emerges as the new star. With its [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/compound-and-pepe-fade-away-as-vc-spectra-takes-center-stage/">Compound and Pepe Fade Away As VC Spectra Takes Center Stage</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/compound-and-pepe-fade-away-as-vc-spectra-takes-center-stage/">Compound and Pepe Fade Away As VC Spectra Takes Center Stage</a> was first posted on August 1, 2023 at 4:03 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a shifting cryptocurrency landscape, Compound (COMP) and Pepe (PEPE) are losing their spotlight as VC Spectra (SPCT) emerges as the new star. With its remarkable performance capturing market attention, VC Spectra (SPCT) is taking center stage, leaving other tokens in the shadows. VC Spectra (SPCT) recently raised over $2.4 million in a private presale.</p>
<p>Will VC Spectra (SPCT) be able to keep Compound (COMP) and Pepe (PEPE) at bay? Let’s find out.</p>
<h2>Compound (COMP): Why Are Investors Leaving?</h2>
<p>Compound (COMP) has displayed an intriguing price pattern, setting up two higher highs on July 2 and July 15 at $71 and $76, respectively. A closer examination reveals potential signals for an impending trend reversal.</p>
<p>On July 7, the Wave Trend indicator flashed a bearish crossover in the overbought region, suggesting it was time to sell. Despite this signal, Compound’s (COMP) price continued its ascent, establishing a higher high on July 15, which resulted in a bearish divergence, marking the second sell signal.</p>
<p>Notably, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) and Awesome Oscillator (AO) have registered lower highs, contrasting Compound’s (COMP) higher highs. This pattern, known as bearish divergence, frequently foreshadows a downtrend.</p>
<p>While the outlook for Compound’s (COMP) price correction is based on multiple sell signals, the crypto market recently experienced an unexpected bullish shift due to SEC vs. Ripple lawsuit developments.</p>
<p>Under these circumstances, the potential bearish thesis for Compound’s (COMP) price can be invalidated if it produces a daily candlestick close above the $76 hurdle and successfully transforms it into a support level. Should this occur, Compound (COMP) bulls could potentially propel the altcoin toward the $80 mark, <a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/3-critical-btc-predictions-from-market-experts-for-2021/">according to market experts</a>.</p>
<h2>PEPE Fighting For Breather: Will It Go Down?</h2>
<p>A newcomer in meme coins, PEPE, has experienced a sharp decline of 17% within just 72 hours. Despite this downtrend, the frog-themed crypto has entered an accumulation zone, presenting a potential opportunity for long-term investors.</p>
<p>This dip caused PEPE to break below the crucial 50-day Moving Average (MA) at $0.0000014923, prompting a selling spree among PEPE holders following its drop below the 50-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA).</p>
<p>While the RSI and EMA indicators currently show a neutral outlook, market analysts view this lower low as the perfect buying spot for PEPE, anticipating a substantial influx of buy action if the market cap increases.</p>
<h2>VC Spectra (SPCT): Moving Towards High Gains In Stage 3 of Public Presale</h2>
<p>VC Spectra (SPCT) is gaining significant traction as a revolutionary asset management platform in cryptocurrencies. <a href="https://vcspectra.io/">VC Spectra (SPCT)</a> provides a transformative opportunity for individuals from diverse financial backgrounds.</p>
<p>With the power of blockchain technology, the platform ensures the safety of investors&#8217; assets, fostering a system of open verification for all transactions. Furthermore, VC Spectra (SPCT) allow exclusive voting rights to its investors using a decentralized investment management system.</p>
<p>The ongoing public presale of <a href="https://vcspectra.io/">VC Spectra (SPCT)</a> tokens has already achieved remarkable milestones, attracting investors, with each stage offering attractive investment prospects. The private presale raised over $2.4 million, reflecting strong investor confidence.</p>
<p>Stage 2 saw an impressive surge in the VC Spectra (SPCT) token price, reaching $0.011 from $0.008 in Stage 1 and delivering a substantial 37.5% ROI to investors participating during this phase.</p>
<p>Moving into Stage 3, the token price rises to $0.025, presenting another opportunity for investors to witness a significant 127.27% price surge compared to Stage 2.</p>
<p>The platform&#8217;s ultimate goal is to reach a target price of $0.08 for VC Spectra&#8217;s (SPCT) tokens, representing a 627% surge from the initial Stage 2 price.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/compound-and-pepe-fade-away-as-vc-spectra-takes-center-stage/">Compound and Pepe Fade Away As VC Spectra Takes Center Stage</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.kryptomoney.com"></a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://www.kryptomoney.com/compound-and-pepe-fade-away-as-vc-spectra-takes-center-stage/">Compound and Pepe Fade Away As VC Spectra Takes Center Stage</a> was first posted on August 1, 2023 at 4:03 am.<br />&copy;2023 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/development">Kryptomoney</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->susanta@brishti.in<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.kryptomoney.com/compound-and-pepe-fade-away-as-vc-spectra-takes-center-stage/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>