<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>Latest Crypto News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://kryptomoney.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<description>Latest Crypto News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 23:11:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/cropped-cropped-favicon_512x512_v2-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Latest Crypto News</title>
	<link>https://kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><itunes:subtitle>Latest Crypto News</itunes:subtitle><itunes:category text="News &amp; Politics"/><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Business News"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Investing"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Tech News"/></itunes:category><item>
		<title>BTC Price Analysis: Bitcoin Clings to $23K as Traders Await Fed’s Next Move; Funding Rates Suggest Not Yet Overheated Market</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/btc-price-analysis-bitcoin-clings-to-23k-as-traders-await-feds-next-move-funding-rates-suggest-not-yet-overheated-market/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 23:11:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC/USD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC/USD Price Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64168</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC) stayed near $23,000 on Saturday Funding rates for BTC are currently around 0.01% Current levels in derivatives show the market is optimistic Bitcoin (BTC) stayed near $23,000 on Saturday in anticipation of the Federal Open Market Committee&#8217;s interest rate decision next week and any signals that policymakers might give regarding when their rate [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/btc-price-analysis-bitcoin-clings-to-23k-as-traders-await-feds-next-move-funding-rates-suggest-not-yet-overheated-market/">BTC Price Analysis: Bitcoin Clings to $23K as Traders Await Fed’s Next Move; Funding Rates Suggest Not Yet Overheated Market</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/btc-price-analysis-bitcoin-clings-to-23k-as-traders-await-feds-next-move-funding-rates-suggest-not-yet-overheated-market/">BTC Price Analysis: Bitcoin Clings to $23K as Traders Await Fed’s Next Move; Funding Rates Suggest Not Yet Overheated Market</a> was first posted on January 28, 2023 at 6:11 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin (BTC) stayed near $23,000 on Saturday</li>
<li>Funding rates for BTC are currently around 0.01%</li>
<li>Current levels in derivatives show the market is optimistic</li>
</ul>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC) stayed near $23,000 on Saturday in anticipation of the Federal Open Market Committee&#8217;s interest rate decision next week and any signals that policymakers might give regarding when their rate hike campaign might cease. The price of the biggest cryptocurrency by market capitalization just dropped to roughly $22,998, representing a 1.14% daily decline. Funding rates for BTC are currently around 0.01%, which indicates that traders&#8217; sentiment toward the market is bullish but is <em>&#8220;still far from the 0.06% levels recorded in February or November of 2021 when traders were paying 80% more annualized to long bitcoin.&#8221;</em> According to Lucas Outumuro, head of analysis firm IntoTheBlock, the current levels in derivatives show the market is optimistic, but at the same time, it has not yet reached an overheated state, which could provide reasons for the current rise to continue.<br /><br /><strong>Key Levels</strong><br />Resistance Levels: $30,000, $27,000, $25,000<br />Support Levels: $22,000, $20,000, $18,000</p>
<h4>BTC/USD Daily Chart: Ranging</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1488" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-64172 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-Daily-Jan-28.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-Daily-Jan-28.png 1488w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-Daily-Jan-28-300x139.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-Daily-Jan-28-1024x473.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-Daily-Jan-28-768x355.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-Daily-Jan-28-750x347.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-Daily-Jan-28-1140x527.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1488px) 100vw, 1488px" /><em><span style="color: #999999">BTC/USD Daily Chart</span></em></h6>
<p>The analysis indicates increasing positive momentum past the daily moving averages (MA 200 &amp; 50), and it also predicts a small correction before bulls continue the upside traction. Bullish sentiment is what is sustaining the run at the upside after a minor retreat under $23,000 as seen on the daily chart. It is noteworthy that if the BTC/USD pair crosses the $21,000 level, a much more significant bullish reversal pattern might be in play.<br /><br />The primary goal of traders will be to exit positions at psychological resistance above the $25,000 region, but they need to exercise caution if these levels are broken because doing so might pave the way for another run and reveal levels around the $30,000 region. Fresh weakness, however, would portend a continuation of the retracement from $23,824 (high of January 25), where greater bulls paused.</p>
<h4>BTC/USD 4-Hour Chart: Ranging</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1488" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-64173 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-4-Hour-jan-28.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-4-Hour-jan-28.png 1488w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-4-Hour-jan-28-300x139.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-4-Hour-jan-28-1024x473.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-4-Hour-jan-28-768x355.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-4-Hour-jan-28-750x347.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-4-Hour-jan-28-1140x527.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1488px) 100vw, 1488px" /><em><span style="color: #999999">BTC/USD 4-Hour Chart</span></em></h6>
<p>The BTC/USD pair has remained in upside consolidation since January 23 rebound, when it bounced from a $20,370 low. On the four-hour chart, the pair is still above all moving averages (MA 50). While indicators like the relative strength index (RSI) are still above their midlines and in the uptrend. Additionally, a higher low pattern has emerged. The pair will therefore keep moving higher as bulls pursue the next psychological level of $25,000.<br /><br />Bitcoin developed strong support against the USD between $21,500 and $20,000, thus the pair may start to move over the $23,000 mark once more. Only when the price of the pair is trading over $24,000 is it considered to return bullish. The primary resistance levels are $25,000 and $30,000.</p>
<p><strong>Note:</strong><em> Kryptomoney.com is not a financial advisor. Do your research before investing your funds in any financial asset or presented product or event. We are not responsible for your investing results</em></p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/btc-price-analysis-bitcoin-clings-to-23k-as-traders-await-feds-next-move-funding-rates-suggest-not-yet-overheated-market/">BTC Price Analysis: Bitcoin Clings to $23K as Traders Await Fed’s Next Move; Funding Rates Suggest Not Yet Overheated Market</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/btc-price-analysis-bitcoin-clings-to-23k-as-traders-await-feds-next-move-funding-rates-suggest-not-yet-overheated-market/">BTC Price Analysis: Bitcoin Clings to $23K as Traders Await Fed’s Next Move; Funding Rates Suggest Not Yet Overheated Market</a> was first posted on January 28, 2023 at 6:11 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu (SHIB) Now Accepted by Top Bahrain’s Real Estate Developer; Cardano Releases New Node Version</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/shiba-inu-shib-now-accepted-by-top-bahrains-real-estate-developer-cardano-releases-new-node-version/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 21:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBA INU (SHIB)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64152</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB) payments are now accepted by Top Bahrain’s Real Estate Developer as adoption continues to grow. Bin Faqeeh, a real estate developer in Bahrain, is the newest business to accept Shiba Inu and other cryptocurrencies supported by Binance pay. In a recent release, Bin Faqeeh stated that its customers could now pay for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/shiba-inu-shib-now-accepted-by-top-bahrains-real-estate-developer-cardano-releases-new-node-version/">Shiba Inu (SHIB) Now Accepted by Top Bahrain’s Real Estate Developer; Cardano Releases New Node Version</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/shiba-inu-shib-now-accepted-by-top-bahrains-real-estate-developer-cardano-releases-new-node-version/">Shiba Inu (SHIB) Now Accepted by Top Bahrain’s Real Estate Developer; Cardano Releases New Node Version</a> was first posted on January 28, 2023 at 4:54 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB) payments are now accepted by Top Bahrain’s Real Estate Developer as adoption continues to grow. Bin Faqeeh, a real estate developer in Bahrain, is the newest business to accept Shiba Inu and other cryptocurrencies supported by Binance pay.</p>
<p>In a recent release, Bin Faqeeh stated that its customers could now pay for real estate properties using cryptocurrencies inclusive of SHIB.<br /><br />The change happens when Bin Faqeeh adopted Binance Pay, a cryptocurrency payment service created by Binance. Clients must use their Binance Pay app to scan a QR code issued by the real estate company to pay for Bin Faqeeh&#8217;s properties with cryptocurrencies. Clients of Bin Faqeeh will also need to choose the cryptocurrency they want to use and the amount they want to spend to purchase the property.<br /><br />Shiba Inu was added to Binance Pay in the past year. It is important to note that more than 80 cryptocurrencies, including Ethereum (ETH), Cardano (ADA), Polygon (MATIC), XRP, Litecoin (LTC), Tether (USDT), and others, are supported by Binance Pay.<br /><br />Leading Bahraini real estate developer Bin Faqeeh offers investors and homeowners opulent flats. The business asserts to be working on more than 30 distinctive real estate projects.<br /><br />Bin Faqeeh is one of many businesses in Bahrain that accept cryptocurrency payments using the Binance Pay platform. Customers of STC can now pay their phone bills with cryptocurrency thanks to a partnership between Binance Pay and Bahraini payment processor EazyPay from last month.</p>
<h2>Cardano Releases New Node Version</h2>
<p>Cardano builder, Input Output has released a new node version in response to the partial degradation the network experienced last weekend.<br /><br />An anomaly happened on the Cardano network while the entire network did not go down. There was a brief period of degradation. Most nodes impacted gracefully recovered while no network restart was required. 50% of the Cardano nodes disconnected and restarted.<br /><br />Cardano founder Charles Hoskinson took to Twitter to share the GitHub release of node 1.35.5, urging stake pool operators (SPOs) to upgrade their nodes while announcing that the issue that caused the partial degradation has been fixed.<br /><br />According to the Cardano creator, while responding to a user, the new node version is not a patch but tackles the root cause of the brief outage experienced last weekend. He named the root cause ‘’Fatality.’’</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/shiba-inu-shib-now-accepted-by-top-bahrains-real-estate-developer-cardano-releases-new-node-version/">Shiba Inu (SHIB) Now Accepted by Top Bahrain’s Real Estate Developer; Cardano Releases New Node Version</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/shiba-inu-shib-now-accepted-by-top-bahrains-real-estate-developer-cardano-releases-new-node-version/">Shiba Inu (SHIB) Now Accepted by Top Bahrain’s Real Estate Developer; Cardano Releases New Node Version</a> was first posted on January 28, 2023 at 4:54 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Investors Place High Bets on Upcoming Upgrade</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/ethereum-investors-place-high-bets-on-upcoming-upgrade/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 17:45:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64158</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Shanghai upgrade of Ethereum has generated yet another token frenzy, with speculators banking on the upgrade&#8217;s success. According to Bloomberg, speculators are increasingly betting on tokens tied to the next Ethereum network upgrade, known as Shanghai. The much-anticipated upgrade is scheduled for March. It will enable Ether holders to withdraw their staked currencies. Prices [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/ethereum-investors-place-high-bets-on-upcoming-upgrade/">Ethereum Investors Place High Bets on Upcoming Upgrade</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ethereum-investors-place-high-bets-on-upcoming-upgrade/">Ethereum Investors Place High Bets on Upcoming Upgrade</a> was first posted on January 28, 2023 at 12:45 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The Shanghai upgrade of Ethereum has generated yet another token frenzy, with speculators banking on the upgrade&#8217;s success. According to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-01-27/crypto-s-hottest-trade-risks-spurring-another-leverage-bubble?utm_source=website&amp;utm_medium=share&amp;utm_campaign=twitter">Bloomberg</a>, speculators are increasingly betting on tokens tied to the next Ethereum network upgrade, known as Shanghai.<br /><br />The much-anticipated upgrade is scheduled for March. It will enable Ether holders to withdraw their staked currencies. Prices of several cryptocurrencies have risen dramatically in recent weeks, just months after the historic FTX crash, which forced analysts to reconsider their most pessimistic predictions for the young crypto market. Liquid staking apps received a lot of attention from investors, with the coins of Lido and Rocket Pool seeing considerable price increases. Such apps enable Ethereum holders to earn interest without having to sell their tokens.<br /><br />The rapid surge is similar to the one that occurred in September ahead of the much-anticipated software upgrade known as the<em> &#8220;merge,&#8221;</em> which enabled the second-largest blockchain to convert to a new consensus mechanism known as <em>&#8220;proof-of-stake.&#8221;</em> According to Henry Elder, Wave Financial&#8217;s head of decentralized finance, many are expecting an increase in adoption following <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ethereum-staking-tokens-surge-in-anticipation-of-shanghai-upgrade/">Shanghai</a>. <br /><br />Since early November, when the whole cryptocurrency market witnessed a big slump owing to the collapse of the FTX exchange, the LDO token, which serves as the Lido app&#8217;s governance token, has seen a triple-digit surge. Lido is now the most popular decentralized finance platform, with over $8 billion invested in the protocol.<br /><br />By the end of 2023, when withdrawals are authorized, about one-fifth of all Ether tokens in circulation will have been staked. After Shanghai, it can still take a while to withdraw staked Ether from the Ethereum network.<br /><br />Although the tokens&#8217; liquidity is probably going to increase, there is a chance that they could become stranded. Additionally, there is a chance that investors who drove up the cost of governance tokens for liquid-staking apps will unload them just before Shanghai goes into effect.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/ethereum-investors-place-high-bets-on-upcoming-upgrade/">Ethereum Investors Place High Bets on Upcoming Upgrade</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ethereum-investors-place-high-bets-on-upcoming-upgrade/">Ethereum Investors Place High Bets on Upcoming Upgrade</a> was first posted on January 28, 2023 at 12:45 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Luno Crypto Exchange Trims Workforce by 35% Globally</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/luno-crypto-exchange-trims-workforce-by-35-globally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 16:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto companies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Luno Cryptocurrency Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64139</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Luno cryptocurrency exchange, based in London, warned its staff on Wednesday that 35% of its global workers would be laid off. The company employs roughly 960 people; thus, 330 positions would be impacted, according to Luno&#8217;s LinkedIn profile. According to reports by CNBC, the company&#8217;s CEO, Marcus Swanepoel, informed staff members of the layoffs [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/luno-crypto-exchange-trims-workforce-by-35-globally/">Luno Crypto Exchange Trims Workforce by 35% Globally</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/luno-crypto-exchange-trims-workforce-by-35-globally/">Luno Crypto Exchange Trims Workforce by 35% Globally</a> was first posted on January 28, 2023 at 11:44 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The Luno cryptocurrency exchange, based in London, warned its staff on Wednesday that 35% of its global workers would be laid off. The company employs roughly 960 people; thus, 330 positions would be impacted, according to Luno&#8217;s<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lunoglobal/about/?src=aff-ref&amp;trk=aff-ir_progid.8005_partid.10078_sid._adid.449670&amp;clickid=XiRQrpyzUxyNU%3Ae3n50BGQccUkA1qgXPD1fhyI0&amp;mcid=6851962469594763264&amp;irgwc=1"> LinkedIn profile</a>. According to reports by <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/25/dcg-owned-crypto-exchange-luno-axes-35percent-of-staff.html">CNBC</a>, the company&#8217;s CEO, Marcus Swanepoel, informed staff members of the layoffs via a live-streamed town hall. Swanepoel wrote to CNBC in an internal memo:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>2022 has been an incredibly tough year for the broader tech industry and, in particular the crypto market. Luno unfortunately hasn’t been immune to this turbulence, which has affected our overall growth and revenue numbers</p>
</blockquote>
<p>According to a Luno spokeswoman, the redundancies would mostly affect the company&#8217;s marketing teams and have<em> “minimal or no impact on key operating and compliance teams.”</em></p>
<p>The exchange, which has its headquarters in London and has offices there as well as in Singapore, Lagos, Sydney, and Cape Town, South Africa, is a division of the DCG conglomerate. The collapse of Sam Bankman-crypto Fried&#8217;s empire, FTX, left DCG in the dust. As a result, DCG&#8217;s lending arm, Genesis, filed for bankruptcy last week.<br /><br />Since the algorithmic stablecoin TerraUSD&#8217;s demise in May last year, the cryptocurrency sector has endured a string of setbacks. Swanepoel stated in a message distributed to staff members this week that the cryptocurrency industry has had a &#8220;series of shocks,&#8221; adding:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>While we anticipated a downturn and proactively planned ahead with a business and funding model that can be resilient to some of these factors, the sheer scale and speed of all of this happening, and all at the same time has put significant strain on our original plan.</p>
<p>What this means in practice is that in addition to streamlining our strategy to focus on our core strengths, we need to also substantially decrease our cost base &#8211; which includes employee headcount in all of our markets &#8211; in order for us to be set up for success going forward.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Almost 11 cryptocurrency companies reported layoffs in January 2023 alone, resulting in the loss of close to 2000 jobs.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/luno-crypto-exchange-trims-workforce-by-35-globally/">Luno Crypto Exchange Trims Workforce by 35% Globally</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/luno-crypto-exchange-trims-workforce-by-35-globally/">Luno Crypto Exchange Trims Workforce by 35% Globally</a> was first posted on January 28, 2023 at 11:44 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LINK Price Analysis: LINK Prepares for Next Move as Chainlink Sets New Network Milestone</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/link-price-analysis-link-prepares-for-next-move-as-chainlink-sets-new-network-milestone/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 23:17:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chainlink (LINK)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LINK/USD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LINK/USD Price Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64149</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At the time of this Analysis, LINK was up 2.45% in the last 24 hours at $7.36 The Chainlink network has surpassed $7 trillion in &#8220;transaction value enabled&#8221; (TVE) Chainlink&#8217;s social volume blasted off to all-time highs Most of the major cryptocurrencies by market capitalization continued to hold on to where they stood earlier. Flat [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/link-price-analysis-link-prepares-for-next-move-as-chainlink-sets-new-network-milestone/">LINK Price Analysis: LINK Prepares for Next Move as Chainlink Sets New Network Milestone</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/link-price-analysis-link-prepares-for-next-move-as-chainlink-sets-new-network-milestone/">LINK Price Analysis: LINK Prepares for Next Move as Chainlink Sets New Network Milestone</a> was first posted on January 27, 2023 at 6:17 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li>At the time of this Analysis, LINK was up 2.45% in the last 24 hours at $7.36</li>
<li>The Chainlink network has surpassed $7 trillion in &#8220;transaction value enabled&#8221; (TVE)</li>
<li>Chainlink&#8217;s social volume blasted off to all-time highs</li>
</ul>
<p>Most of the major cryptocurrencies by market capitalization continued to hold on to where they stood earlier. Flat prices, however, signal that bullish and bearish investors are both actively expressing their market views. At the time of this analysis, <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/link-price-analysis-how-will-link-price-react-after-chainlink-staking-v0-1-early-access-goes-live/">LINK</a> was up 2.45% in the last 24 hours to $7.31. In a recent tweet, the decentralized blockchain oracle network Chainlink celebrated a new milestone. According to it, the Chainlink network has surpassed $7 trillion in &#8220;transaction value enabled&#8221; (TVE)—a measure of the aggregate USD value of on-chain transactions facilitated by Chainlink oracles across 12 blockchains since 2022. Chainlink&#8217;s social volume blasted off to all-time highs, according to on-chain analytics firm Santiment, after it put out a tweet on its proof-of-reserve advantages. The increased crowd interest may have a positive price impact, Santiment predicts.<br /><br /><strong>Key Levels</strong><br />Resistance Levels: $9.50, $8.00, $7.50<br />Support Levels: $7.00, $6.00, $5.00</p>
<h4><br />LINK/USD Daily Chart: Ranging</h4>
<p><img loading="lazy" width="1488" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-64153 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LINKUSD-Daily-Jan-27.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LINKUSD-Daily-Jan-27.png 1488w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LINKUSD-Daily-Jan-27-300x139.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LINKUSD-Daily-Jan-27-1024x473.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LINKUSD-Daily-Jan-27-768x355.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LINKUSD-Daily-Jan-27-750x347.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LINKUSD-Daily-Jan-27-1140x527.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1488px) 100vw, 1488px" /><br />The price of LINK reached a low of $5.386 on Dec 31 but has since remained in a rebound trend, however beginning the year with a <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/gala-alitas-celr-ride-to-all-time-highs-amid-bitcoin-and-altcoins-consolidation-here-are-the-predictions/">positive consolidation</a>. The LINK price is currently above the MA 200 barrier at $7.00. The LINK price might rise to the $8.00 level before the next barrier at $9.50, with a successful effort above its immediate support at $7.00.<br /><br />The barrier at $8.00 could stymie bullish moves above this region. However, a move upward would enable LINK&#8217;s price to surpass the $9.50 level. However, selling interest below current levels may find support around the $8.50 level. The RSI indicator has risen above the neutral 50 level, which points to potential consolidation.</p>
<h4>LINK/USD 4-Hour Chart: Ranging</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1488" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-64154 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LINKUSD-4-Hour-Chart-Jan-27.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LINKUSD-4-Hour-Chart-Jan-27.png 1488w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LINKUSD-4-Hour-Chart-Jan-27-300x139.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LINKUSD-4-Hour-Chart-Jan-27-1024x473.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LINKUSD-4-Hour-Chart-Jan-27-768x355.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LINKUSD-4-Hour-Chart-Jan-27-750x347.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/LINKUSD-4-Hour-Chart-Jan-27-1140x527.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1488px) 100vw, 1488px" /><em><span style="color: #999999">LINK/USD 4-Hour Chart</span></em></h6>
<p>On the 4-hour chart, LINK is maintaining its position above $7.00, well above the rising MA 50 after reaching a high of $7.50 earlier today. Looking at the technical indicators, the RSI is getting close to the 80 level, indicating a bullish advantage. Stronger upward trends may encounter the $8.00. Above this, the $9.50 resistance level, which comes before the highs of $8.0, maybe a critical one for the bulls.<br /><br />If not, a decline below the MA 50 ($6.90) might first strike the $6.50 support before tumbling to the $6.00 level. The bullish mood may come into play as a result of additional positive pressures, with support at the $7.00 level. LINK/USD is attempting to consolidate at its upper price boundary.</p>
<p><strong>Note:</strong><em> Kryptomoney.com is not a financial advisor. Do your research before investing your funds in any financial asset or presented product or event. We are not responsible for your investing results</em></p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/link-price-analysis-link-prepares-for-next-move-as-chainlink-sets-new-network-milestone/">LINK Price Analysis: LINK Prepares for Next Move as Chainlink Sets New Network Milestone</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/link-price-analysis-link-prepares-for-next-move-as-chainlink-sets-new-network-milestone/">LINK Price Analysis: LINK Prepares for Next Move as Chainlink Sets New Network Milestone</a> was first posted on January 27, 2023 at 6:17 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EGLD Now Available to More Users Through New Listings; 11 Million Businesses in Brazil Accept USDT Through SWAPiX</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/egld-now-available-to-more-users-through-new-listings-11-million-businesses-in-brazil-accept-usdt-through-swapix/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 22:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MultiversX (EGLD)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64146</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>MultiversX (EGLD) would now be available to millions of users as the Morningstar Ventures-developed hybrid exchange, EXBI, which recently launched in &#8220;public beta,&#8221; has added EGLD, the native token of the MultiversX blockchain, to its list of tradable tokens. The EGLD listing on EXBI held on January 26, 16:00 UTC is expected to be followed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/egld-now-available-to-more-users-through-new-listings-11-million-businesses-in-brazil-accept-usdt-through-swapix/">EGLD Now Available to More Users Through New Listings; 11 Million Businesses in Brazil Accept USDT Through SWAPiX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/egld-now-available-to-more-users-through-new-listings-11-million-businesses-in-brazil-accept-usdt-through-swapix/">EGLD Now Available to More Users Through New Listings; 11 Million Businesses in Brazil Accept USDT Through SWAPiX</a> was first posted on January 27, 2023 at 5:26 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>MultiversX (EGLD) would now be available to millions of users as the Morningstar Ventures-developed hybrid exchange, EXBI, which recently launched in<em> &#8220;public beta,&#8221;</em> has added EGLD, the native token of the MultiversX blockchain, to its list of tradable tokens.<br /><br />The<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/egld-now-available-to-more-users-through-new-listings-11-million-businesses-in-brazil-accept-usdt-through-swapix/"> EGLD</a> listing on EXBI held on January 26, 16:00 UTC is expected to be followed by a soon-to-be-announced trading competition aiming to incentivize EGLD trading on the platform and reward the most dedicated traders with a host of EGLD prizes.<br /><br />First introduced at X Day, EXBI is a Morningstar Ventures-developed hybrid exchange, aiming to combine the advantages of centralized and decentralized exchanges into a single platform.<br /><br />The MultiversX NFT ecosystem has harnessed creativity and turned it into tools for value exchange and social coordination. Motivated by the values of self-sovereignty, open exploration, and transparency, this dynamic creative environment has grown significantly and presently has more than 1.3 million NFTs issued.<br /><br />Frontier Wallet has expanded an integration that began to take shape in mid-2020 and introduced support for MultiversX NFTs in its Android app. The most recent iteration of its iOS software is still awaiting approval from the App Store.</p>
<h2>11 Million Businesses in Brazil Accept Tether USDT Through SWAPIX</h2>
<p>According to a recent announcement on Twitter, 11 million businesses in Brazil now accept Tether USDT through SWAPiX. <br /><br />SWAPiX is a solution from SmartPay that enables users to quickly convert BRL into USDt via PiX, a payment infrastructure in Brazil. Bitfinex customers can convert USDt within SWAPiX and send BRL through Pix directly to the local banking app.<br /><br /><em>“SWAPiX is popular in Brazil, and we are delighted to provide our customers in the country with easy access to this fiat on and off-ramp service,”</em> said Paolo Ardoino, CTO at Tether and Bitfinex.<br /><br />SmartPay’s SWAPiX fiat on and off-ramp service is executed using just a smartphone device and without the need for a bank account, a critical consideration in a country where an estimated 34 million people (almost 1 in 5 adults) still lack access to traditional financial services.<br /><br />In October 2022, <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitfinex-launches-perpetual-contract-to-speculate-bitcoin-dominance/">Bitfinex</a> crypto exchange announced it had provided customers in Brazil with a connection to SWAPiX by Smartpay, offering an easy and convenient on-and-off ramp between the Brazilian Real (BRL) and Tether tokens (USDt). <br /><br />The initiative forms part of Bitfinex’s mission to enhance financial inclusion and promote financial freedom in Brazil and across Latin America.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/egld-now-available-to-more-users-through-new-listings-11-million-businesses-in-brazil-accept-usdt-through-swapix/">EGLD Now Available to More Users Through New Listings; 11 Million Businesses in Brazil Accept USDT Through SWAPiX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/egld-now-available-to-more-users-through-new-listings-11-million-businesses-in-brazil-accept-usdt-through-swapix/">EGLD Now Available to More Users Through New Listings; 11 Million Businesses in Brazil Accept USDT Through SWAPiX</a> was first posted on January 27, 2023 at 5:26 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aptos (APT) 400% Gains in January Traced to “ Crazy Buying” in Korean Communities; Aave V3 Deploys on Ethereum</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/aptos-apt-400-gains-in-january-traced-to-crazy-buying-in-korean-communities-aave-v3-deploys-on-ethereum/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 21:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AAVE (AAVE)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aptos (APT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64143</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Since the beginning of the year, APT, the token driving the layer-1 blockchain Aptos, has been on a tear, increasing in value by as much as 150% just in the past week. In the past 30 days, the token has increased by 407%. This is true even if APT&#8217;s price has dropped by 8.5% in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/aptos-apt-400-gains-in-january-traced-to-crazy-buying-in-korean-communities-aave-v3-deploys-on-ethereum/">Aptos (APT) 400% Gains in January Traced to “ Crazy Buying” in Korean Communities; Aave V3 Deploys on Ethereum</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/aptos-apt-400-gains-in-january-traced-to-crazy-buying-in-korean-communities-aave-v3-deploys-on-ethereum/">Aptos (APT) 400% Gains in January Traced to “ Crazy Buying” in Korean Communities; Aave V3 Deploys on Ethereum</a> was first posted on January 27, 2023 at 4:55 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Since the beginning of the year, <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/aptos-sets-new-all-time-highs-here-is-what-to-know-on-meme-tokens-the-and-die-created-after-vitalik-buterins-tweets/">APT</a>, the token driving the layer-1 blockchain Aptos, has been on a tear, increasing in value by as much as 150% just in the past week. In the past 30 days, the token has increased by 407%.<br /><br />This is true even if APT&#8217;s price has dropped by 8.5% in the last day, from its record high of $19.92 on Thursday to its current level of $18.21, according to statistics from CoinGecko.<br /><br />Aptos, which debuted in October 2022 amidst much fanfare and criticism, has a market capitalization of about $2.92 billion, ranking it as the 28th most valuable network in the cryptocurrency sector.<br /><br />After the well-known decentralized exchange (DEX) PancakeSwap held a community vote to continue its deployment on Aptos, A price increase was initiated. <br /><br />The recent inclusion into Atomic Wallet, a non-custodial multi-chain cryptocurrency wallet, as well as the rising interest in Aptos-based NFT collections, have had a beneficial effect on the price of the APT token.<br /><br />According to Chinese crypto journalist, Collin Wu: ‘’The recent surge of APT may be related to the crazy buying in the Korean community. The 24-hour trading volume of Korean APT/KRW on Upbit, South Korea’s largest exchange, exceeded the sum of Binance’s multiple trading pairs, reaching $566 million, he stated.<br /><br />Wu further added, ’’Pumping up altcoins is also one of the traditions in the Korean community. Aptos officials attach great importance to the Korean community. It released a Korean language white paper, which is the only language other than English. It plans to launch a global hackathon and the first is in Seoul. Korean companies Hashed, Hive and YG are investors in Aptos. ’’</p>
<h2>Aave Protocol V3 Now Live on the Ethereum Market</h2>
<p>In a recent announcement, Aave Protocol V3 is now live on the Ethereum market. ”The most exciting aspect of V3 is its flexible design, which enables a variety of new risk mitigation features, and its improved capital efficiency &amp; decentralized liquidity – all while reducing gas costs.” <br /><br />Stani Kulechov, <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/aave-aave-now-listed-on-trading-app-robinhood/">AAVE</a> CEO stated. With the deployment of V3 on Ethereum mainnet, Aave’s first and largest market, new technical features and benefits have been unlocked including: <br /><strong>High-Efficiency Mode:</strong> This allows users to increase their capital efficiency when supplying and borrowing correlated assets like stablecoins and liquid staking derivates (LSDs).<br /><br /><strong>Isolation Mode:</strong> enables more assets to be listed on Aave as collateral while maintaining the security of the protocol. Liquidity risks can be siloed by listing assets in isolation mode.<br /><br />And lastly, Gas Optimization reduces gas costs associated with all the functions across the board by almost 20-25%.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/aptos-apt-400-gains-in-january-traced-to-crazy-buying-in-korean-communities-aave-v3-deploys-on-ethereum/">Aptos (APT) 400% Gains in January Traced to “ Crazy Buying” in Korean Communities; Aave V3 Deploys on Ethereum</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/aptos-apt-400-gains-in-january-traced-to-crazy-buying-in-korean-communities-aave-v3-deploys-on-ethereum/">Aptos (APT) 400% Gains in January Traced to “ Crazy Buying” in Korean Communities; Aave V3 Deploys on Ethereum</a> was first posted on January 27, 2023 at 4:55 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin on Track for Best January Ever Since 2013 As Price Returns Above $23K; Holo (HOT) Spikes Higher on New Release</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-on-track-for-best-january-ever-since-2013-as-price-returns-above-23k-holo-hot-spikes-higher-on-new-release/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 21:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Holo (HOT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64131</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Since January 1, Bitcoin has increased by about 40%, putting it on pace for its best year-to-date start since it soared 51% in 2013. The leading cryptocurrency is off to its best start since 2013. As the value of the U.S. dollar has fallen this month, the price of the largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-on-track-for-best-january-ever-since-2013-as-price-returns-above-23k-holo-hot-spikes-higher-on-new-release/">Bitcoin on Track for Best January Ever Since 2013 As Price Returns Above $23K; Holo (HOT) Spikes Higher on New Release</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-on-track-for-best-january-ever-since-2013-as-price-returns-above-23k-holo-hot-spikes-higher-on-new-release/">Bitcoin on Track for Best January Ever Since 2013 As Price Returns Above $23K; Holo (HOT) Spikes Higher on New Release</a> was first posted on January 27, 2023 at 4:42 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Since January 1, <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/btc-price-analysis-early-bull-cycle-signal-beckons-as-bitcoin-rallies-64638-btc-bought-by-whales-in-weeks/">Bitcoin</a> has increased by about 40%, putting it on pace for its best year-to-date start since it soared 51% in 2013. <br /><br />The leading cryptocurrency is off to its best start since 2013. As the value of the U.S. dollar has fallen this month, the price of the largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization has increased by 40%. The majority of U.S. buyers, according to analysts, have driven the rally.<br /><br /><em>&#8220;Bitcoin has increased by 40% so far this year, with 35% of those gains coming during American market hours. &#8220;That&#8217;s an 85% participation of the rally linked with US-based investors,&#8221;</em> says Markus Thielen, head of research and strategy at cryptocurrency services provider Matrixport.<br /><br />Bitcoin, and cryptocurrencies in general, trade continuously, unlike equities, making it possible for observers to watch order flows across time zones and determine the source of purchasing or selling pressure.<br /><br />The renewed premium in bitcoin futures listed on the Chicago Mercantile Exchange further demonstrates institutions&#8217; bullish positioning.<br /><br />Similar findings were made earlier this month by Deutsche Digital Assets, which cited the rise in the Coinbase premium as proof of high buying interest among seasoned U.S.-based investors as opposed to retail investors.<br /><br />David Guong, the head of research at Coinbase Institutional, stated in a weekly market analysis released on January 20 that &#8220;conventional and crypto-focused hedge funds, corporates, and traditional asset managers have been buying.&#8221;<br /><br />Since institutions are driving the bullish turnaround in Bitcoin, it may be a positive indicator for the U.S. equity market. Bitcoin has recovered above $23,000 after its price dipped a few days earlier. At the time of writing, Bitcoin was slightly up at $23,188.</p>
<h2>Holo (HOT) Spikes Higher on New Release</h2>
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/enjin-coin-holo-hot-vechain-refresh-new-all-time-highs-as-crypto-market-tumbles-to-selling-pressure/">Holochain</a> has published Holochain Beta 0.1.0, an app-stable beta release, which it says marks the next step of its Holochain Beta release sequence.<br /><br />In a blog post, it says: &#8220;This is a major leap in the Holochain development roadmap.&#8221; Over the past years of development as a rapidly iterating project, it says it has constantly introduced new fixes, features, and optimizations to its code. <br /><br />The Holochain alpha releases have typically pushed new features, structural changes, fixes, and updates, many of which would break functionality in an existing application. <br /><br />With Holochain Beta,’’ the days of us regularly breaking your code are behind us.&#8221; Now we will be updating a beta 0.1.0 branch of Holochain with non-breaking fixes and features for six months,’’ Holochain stated.<br /><br />In related news, Least Authority, a respected security firm that focuses on decentralized technology, recently completed another audit for Holochain. Their first audit, conducted in December 2022, was of the Lair Keystore. In this second security audit, the Holochain Deterministic Integrity library was reviewed.<br /><br />At the time of publication, HOT was trading up 9% in the last 24 hours at $0.0002. the token is likewise up 15% on the weekly.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-on-track-for-best-january-ever-since-2013-as-price-returns-above-23k-holo-hot-spikes-higher-on-new-release/">Bitcoin on Track for Best January Ever Since 2013 As Price Returns Above $23K; Holo (HOT) Spikes Higher on New Release</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-on-track-for-best-january-ever-since-2013-as-price-returns-above-23k-holo-hot-spikes-higher-on-new-release/">Bitcoin on Track for Best January Ever Since 2013 As Price Returns Above $23K; Holo (HOT) Spikes Higher on New Release</a> was first posted on January 27, 2023 at 4:42 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Rejects Bitcoin ETF Proposal by Ark and 21 Shares: Details</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/sec-rejects-bitcoin-etf-proposal-by-ark-and-21-shares-details/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 23:22:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BitcoinETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64136</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has once again rejected an application from Ark Investment Management and 21Shares to list a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) on the Cboe BZX Exchange, a decision that comes as little surprise to those familiar with the regulatory landscape surrounding the nascent crypto industry. The idea has now [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/sec-rejects-bitcoin-etf-proposal-by-ark-and-21-shares-details/">SEC Rejects Bitcoin ETF Proposal by Ark and 21 Shares: Details</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/sec-rejects-bitcoin-etf-proposal-by-ark-and-21-shares-details/">SEC Rejects Bitcoin ETF Proposal by Ark and 21 Shares: Details</a> was first posted on January 26, 2023 at 6:22 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has once again <a href="https://www.sec.gov/rules/sro/cboebzx/2023/34-96751.pdf">rejected</a> an application from Ark Investment Management and 21Shares to list a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) on the Cboe BZX Exchange, a decision that comes as little surprise to those familiar with the regulatory landscape surrounding the nascent crypto industry.<br /><br />The idea has now been rejected by the dreaded regulator twice; the first time was in April, when a similar effort was also thwarted. Undaunted, the pair submitted a new application in May of last year, but the organization once again cited fraud and manipulation concerns as the main factors in making its decision. The SEC emphasized that <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/defi-platform-bzx-loses-8-million-in-third-hack-in-2020/">BZX</a> had not shown that their plan complied with the rules governing the avoidance of dishonest practices.<br /><br />The agency&#8217;s choice is supported by its conviction that the<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-market-sees-heavy-collapse-as-price-corrects-below-48000/"> Bitcoin market</a> is still vulnerable to fraud and manipulation and that, to identify and discourage such behavior, a thorough surveillance-sharing agreement with a regulated market of scale is required. <br /><br />According to the SEC, BZX neglected to address risk considerations unique to Bitcoin. It is unknown if Ark and 21Shares will attempt to list a spot bitcoin ETF again, but given the regulatory environment at the moment, it appears unlikely that the SEC would change its position very soon.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/sec-rejects-bitcoin-etf-proposal-by-ark-and-21-shares-details/">SEC Rejects Bitcoin ETF Proposal by Ark and 21 Shares: Details</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/sec-rejects-bitcoin-etf-proposal-by-ark-and-21-shares-details/">SEC Rejects Bitcoin ETF Proposal by Ark and 21 Shares: Details</a> was first posted on January 26, 2023 at 6:22 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			<enclosure length="442374" type="application/pdf" url="https://www.sec.gov/rules/sro/cboebzx/2023/34-96751.pdf"/><itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><itunes:subtitle>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has once again rejected an application from Ark Investment Management and 21Shares to list a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) on the Cboe BZX Exchange, a decision that comes as little surprise to those familiar with the regulatory landscape surrounding the nascent crypto industry. The idea has now [&amp;#8230;] The post SEC Rejects Bitcoin ETF Proposal by Ark and 21 Shares: Details appeared first on Latest Crypto News. SEC Rejects Bitcoin ETF Proposal by Ark and 21 Shares: Details was first posted on January 26, 2023 at 6:22 pm. &amp;copy;2021 &amp;quot;Latest Crypto News&amp;quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at info@kryptomoney.com</itunes:subtitle><itunes:summary>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has once again rejected an application from Ark Investment Management and 21Shares to list a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) on the Cboe BZX Exchange, a decision that comes as little surprise to those familiar with the regulatory landscape surrounding the nascent crypto industry. The idea has now [&amp;#8230;] The post SEC Rejects Bitcoin ETF Proposal by Ark and 21 Shares: Details appeared first on Latest Crypto News. SEC Rejects Bitcoin ETF Proposal by Ark and 21 Shares: Details was first posted on January 26, 2023 at 6:22 pm. &amp;copy;2021 &amp;quot;Latest Crypto News&amp;quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at info@kryptomoney.com</itunes:summary><itunes:keywords>News, bitcoin, BitcoinETF, SEC</itunes:keywords></item>
		<item>
		<title>E-Commerce Giant Amazon Joins NFT Frenzy, Unveils New Initiative</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/e-commerce-giant-amazon-joins-nft-frenzy-unveils-new-initiative/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 22:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64126</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Amazon is advancing its efforts to establish a presence in the cryptocurrency market. A non-fungible token (NFT) proposal would reportedly be introduced by the firm sometime in the spring of 2023. Six people with knowledge of the situation are cited in the report. It states that to assist its NFT strategy, Amazon has collaborated with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/e-commerce-giant-amazon-joins-nft-frenzy-unveils-new-initiative/">E-Commerce Giant Amazon Joins NFT Frenzy, Unveils New Initiative</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/e-commerce-giant-amazon-joins-nft-frenzy-unveils-new-initiative/">E-Commerce Giant Amazon Joins NFT Frenzy, Unveils New Initiative</a> was first posted on January 26, 2023 at 5:56 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/amazon-partners-with-avalanche-avax-price-up-17-in-barely-an-hour/">Amazon</a> is advancing its efforts to establish a presence in the cryptocurrency market. A non-fungible token (NFT) proposal would reportedly be introduced by the firm sometime in the spring of 2023.<br /><br />Six people with knowledge of the situation are cited in the report. It states that to assist its NFT strategy, Amazon has collaborated with more than ten cryptocurrency initiatives. Following a fall in the NFT market from its peak in 2021, the initiative might reinforce and resuscitate the industry.<br /><br />The e-commerce giant would reportedly concentrate on several sectors and dabble in NFT gaming. Players who use the platform will receive special NFT rewards.<br /><br />Amazon already provides access to a videogame platform to customers of its Prime service. Members of this service have access to the platform&#8217;s library and are given prizes each month that can be used to buy AAA games. By providing additional incentives and drawing in new customers, the new NFT project could strengthen the service.<br /><br />According to news reports, the NFT platform is currently under development and may operate directly on Amazon rather than through Amazon Web Services (AWS). There is no formal announcement from Amazon or its management, although the firm may disclose further details in April 2023.<br /><br />To reach a<em> “much bigger audience” </em>the e-commerce site aims to reach a <em> “truly worldwide platform.” </em>Amazon might be working toward such goals.<br /><br />The business garnered interest in the cryptocurrency sector two weeks ago when it disclosed cooperation with Ava Labs, the organization in charge of the <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/avalanche-raises-42m-from-token-sale-in-4-5-hours/">Avalanche blockchain</a>. To grant access to this network to thousands of businesses, the cryptocurrency company teamed up with AWS.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/e-commerce-giant-amazon-joins-nft-frenzy-unveils-new-initiative/">E-Commerce Giant Amazon Joins NFT Frenzy, Unveils New Initiative</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/e-commerce-giant-amazon-joins-nft-frenzy-unveils-new-initiative/">E-Commerce Giant Amazon Joins NFT Frenzy, Unveils New Initiative</a> was first posted on January 26, 2023 at 5:56 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>