<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>Latest Crypto News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://kryptomoney.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<description>Latest Crypto News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 22:54:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/cropped-cropped-favicon_512x512_v2-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Latest Crypto News</title>
	<link>https://kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><itunes:subtitle>Latest Crypto News</itunes:subtitle><itunes:category text="News &amp; Politics"/><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Business News"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Investing"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Tech News"/></itunes:category><item>
		<title>HBAR Price Analysis: HBAR Positions for 2023, Hedera Wins Innovation Awards Category in DLT, Blockchain and Crypto</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/hbar-price-analysis-hbar-positions-for-2023-hedera-wins-innovation-awards-category-in-dlt-blockchain-and-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 22:54:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HBAR/USD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HBAR/USD Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hedera Hashgraph (HBAR)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64023</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hedera is up 5.07% in the last 24 hours at $0.059 Hedera has been named winner of The Innovation Awards, in the category &#8220;Innovation in DLT, Blockchain, and Crypto&#8221; The hedera community is rocking so hard at World Economic Forum (WEF) Davos 2023 Hedera (HBAR) is up 5.07% in the last 24 hours at $0.059 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/hbar-price-analysis-hbar-positions-for-2023-hedera-wins-innovation-awards-category-in-dlt-blockchain-and-crypto/">HBAR Price Analysis: HBAR Positions for 2023, Hedera Wins Innovation Awards Category in DLT, Blockchain and Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/hbar-price-analysis-hbar-positions-for-2023-hedera-wins-innovation-awards-category-in-dlt-blockchain-and-crypto/">HBAR Price Analysis: HBAR Positions for 2023, Hedera Wins Innovation Awards Category in DLT, Blockchain and Crypto</a> was first posted on January 19, 2023 at 5:54 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li>Hedera is up 5.07% in the last 24 hours at $0.059</li>
<li>Hedera has been named winner of The Innovation Awards, in the category <em>&#8220;Innovation in DLT, Blockchain, and Crypto&#8221;</em></li>
<li>The hedera community is rocking so hard at World Economic Forum (WEF) Davos 2023</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-influencer-reveals-why-he-moved-from-solana-to-hedera-hbar-internet-computericp-and-algorand/">Hedera (HBAR)</a> is up 5.07% in the last 24 hours at $0.059 and up 21.11% in the last seven days. Hedera has been named the winner of The Innovation Awards in the categor<em>y &#8220;Innovation in DLT, Blockchain, and Crypto&#8221;</em> per a Dmagazine report. Avery Dennison, one of the most important material sciences companies in the world, confirmed Hedera’s attendance at the World Economic Forum this year. The same company is currently one of Hedera’s partners, which means the network is already attracting partners that are aligned with the WEF’s efficiency and sustainability plans. The Hedera community is rocking so hard at World Economic Forum (WEF) Davos 2023. Hedera says it ranks the 12th highest by influence on Twitter. As stated in a blog post, smart contracts will pay rent on Hedera starting in February 2023. As defined, <em>&#8220;rent&#8221;</em> is the recurring payment required for contracts to remain active on the network and is comprised of auto-renewal and storage fees. Smart contracts on Hedera can pay for rent in two ways: with external funds or contract funds.<br /><br /><strong>Key Levels</strong><br />Resistance Levels: $0.0850, $0.0750, $0.0600<br />Support Levels: $0.0550, $0.0450, $0.0350</p>
<h4>HBAR/USD Daily Chart: Ranging</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1488" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-64034 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-Daily-Jan-19.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-Daily-Jan-19.png 1488w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-Daily-Jan-19-300x139.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-Daily-Jan-19-1024x473.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-Daily-Jan-19-768x355.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-Daily-Jan-19-750x347.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-Daily-Jan-19-1140x527.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1488px) 100vw, 1488px" /><em><span style="color: #999999">HBAR/USD Daily Chart</span></em></h6>
<p>A price break of the moving average (MA 200) on the daily chart indicates a mild price breakout region. Near-term range trading is likely to continue as the 36th-largest cryptocurrency battles to stay above the $0.0500 region, which serves as a critical zone. Because of a surge in positive bias, positive momentum is increasing while negative momentum is declining.<br /><br />Hedera has regained some of its losses after plunging to the $0.0355 level. Buyers may come through around the $0.0600 handle in an attempt to strengthen the positive bounce after recovering from the loss. The Relative Strength Index, which indicates a surge in upward momentum, contributes to the bullish traction from the yearly low of $0.0355.</p>
<h4>HBAR/USD 4-Hour Chart: Bullish</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1488" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-64035 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19.png 1488w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19-300x139.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19-1024x473.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19-768x355.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19-750x347.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19-1140x527.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1488px) 100vw, 1488px" /><em><span style="color: #999999">HBAR/USD 4-Hour Chart</span></em></h6>
<p><br />According to the short-term oscillators, bulls are currently backing additional gains in the pair toward the $0.0600 level. Bears, on the other hand, may sell on rallies that fall below the 4-hour moving average (MA 50) at $0.0522. If investors keep the surge going above this mark, the $0.0700 barrier could represent the first point of resistance on the upside.<br /><br />If favorable forces start to weaken, preliminary support might be at $0.0550. If the bearish trend persists, the price may target the short-term MA 200 at about $0.0440. <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/hbar-price-analysis-hedera-crosses-the-2-5-billion-transaction-mark-in-a-major-milestone-what-happens-to-price/">HBAR/USD</a> is showing an upward tendency, and bulls must push the price above the $0.0600 level to oppose bears.</p>
<p><strong>Note:</strong><em> Kryptomoney.com is not a financial advisor. Do your research before investing your funds in any financial asset or presented product or event. We are not responsible for your investing results</em></p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/hbar-price-analysis-hbar-positions-for-2023-hedera-wins-innovation-awards-category-in-dlt-blockchain-and-crypto/">HBAR Price Analysis: HBAR Positions for 2023, Hedera Wins Innovation Awards Category in DLT, Blockchain and Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/hbar-price-analysis-hbar-positions-for-2023-hedera-wins-innovation-awards-category-in-dlt-blockchain-and-crypto/">HBAR Price Analysis: HBAR Positions for 2023, Hedera Wins Innovation Awards Category in DLT, Blockchain and Crypto</a> was first posted on January 19, 2023 at 5:54 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CoinDesk: Rumors of a Potential Sale Surface as It Considers Options</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/coindesk-rumors-of-a-potential-sale-surface-as-it-considers-options/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 21:34:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64025</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Genesis came first, then Coindesk. Barry Silbert&#8217;s empire seems to be in peril; reportedly, it is thinking about selling some of its subsidiaries to deal with cash flow problems. On January 18, 2023, Kevin Worth, the CEO of CoinDesk, a division of Digital Currency Group that publishes news on cryptocurrencies, announced that the company has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/coindesk-rumors-of-a-potential-sale-surface-as-it-considers-options/">CoinDesk: Rumors of a Potential Sale Surface as It Considers Options</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/coindesk-rumors-of-a-potential-sale-surface-as-it-considers-options/">CoinDesk: Rumors of a Potential Sale Surface as It Considers Options</a> was first posted on January 19, 2023 at 4:34 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-firm-genesis-to-file-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy-details/">Genesis</a> came first, then Coindesk. Barry Silbert&#8217;s empire seems to be in peril; reportedly, it is thinking about selling some of its subsidiaries to deal with cash flow problems.<br /><br />On January 18, 2023, Kevin Worth, the CEO of CoinDesk, a division of Digital Currency Group that publishes news on cryptocurrencies, announced that the company has hired investment bankers from Lazard LTD to assist them in exploring alternatives for a partial or full sale of the business.<br /><br />According to <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/crypto-media-outlet-coindesk-taps-bankers-for-potential-sale-11674076000">The Wall Street Journal</a>, Worth discussed how prospective investors were enthusiastic about owning the online website:<br /><br /><em>“Over the last few months, we have received numerous inbound indications of interest in CoinDesk,”</em><br /><br />The <em>&#8220;Consensus&#8221;</em> summit, one of the largest crypto events in the United States, is organized by<a href="https://www.coindesk.com/advertise/"> Coindesk</a>, which boasts over 5 million monthly visitors on its website (<a href="https://www.similarweb.com/website/coindesk.com/#overview">Similarweb</a> claims over 10 million visitors). Coindesk has also expanded to other products, such as a newsletter and a YouTube channel.<br /><br />CoinDesk seems to be a success, but the parent company&#8217;s liquidity problems aren&#8217;t caused by a media site that isn&#8217;t performing well; rather, they are primarily the result of the <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/cardano-network-receives-bullish-catalysts-heres-what-might-be-next-for-bitcoin-ethereum-altcoins-after-ftx-collapse/">FTX contagion</a> and a dispute with the Winklevoss twins, who founded the Gemini cryptocurrency exchange after DCG-owned crypto lender Genesis stopped allowing withdrawals and messed with Gemini&#8217;s<em> &#8220;Earn&#8221;</em> program.<br /><br />The Winklevii have openly demanded DCG CEO Barry Silbert&#8217;s resignation and charged the business with ignoring their attempts to come to a mutually beneficial agreement. Additionally, Genesis and DCG were both recently sued by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for allegedly marketing unregistered securities.<br /><br />After failing to raise money, Genesis may be ready to declare bankruptcy this week. The cryptocurrency fund was left with a liquidity shortfall of more than $175 million as a result of FTX&#8217;s demise, which prevented it from restarting customer withdrawals.<br /><br />CoinDesk or Genesis, as well as other prominent DCG-owned cryptocurrency companies like Foundry, Grayscale Investments, and Luno, may be sold in the future. While this could help with some or all of DCG&#8217;s financial problems, it could also have a large effect on the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/coindesk-rumors-of-a-potential-sale-surface-as-it-considers-options/">CoinDesk: Rumors of a Potential Sale Surface as It Considers Options</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/coindesk-rumors-of-a-potential-sale-surface-as-it-considers-options/">CoinDesk: Rumors of a Potential Sale Surface as It Considers Options</a> was first posted on January 19, 2023 at 4:34 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>National Australia Bank Unveils Stablecoin on Ethereum and Algorand</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/national-australia-bank-unveils-stablecoin-on-ethereum-and-algorand/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 20:42:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorand]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National Australia Bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64012</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Given recent reluctance and more recent implosion of Terra, other nations have been intending to investigate stablecoins. One of Australia&#8217;s four main financial institutions, the National Australia Bank (NAB), is the most recent to join the bandwagon. The Ethereum and Algorand blockchain networks will soon host the NAB-created AUDN stablecoin, which is tethered to the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/national-australia-bank-unveils-stablecoin-on-ethereum-and-algorand/">National Australia Bank Unveils Stablecoin on Ethereum and Algorand</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/national-australia-bank-unveils-stablecoin-on-ethereum-and-algorand/">National Australia Bank Unveils Stablecoin on Ethereum and Algorand</a> was first posted on January 19, 2023 at 3:42 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Given recent reluctance and more recent implosion of Terra, other nations have been intending to investigate <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/stablecoins-might-soon-be-officially-categorized-as-securities/">stablecoins</a>. One of Australia&#8217;s four main financial institutions, the National Australia Bank (NAB), is the most recent to join the bandwagon.<br /><br />The Ethereum and Algorand blockchain networks will soon host the NAB-created AUDN stablecoin, which is tethered to the Australian dollar. By the middle of 2023, completion is anticipated.<br /><br />The AUDN would allow users to settle transactions on blockchain technology in real-time using Australian dollars, according to a report from the <a href="https://www.afr.com/companies/financial-services/nab-creates-a-stablecoin-in-boost-for-digital-economy-20230117-p5cd8f">Australian Financial Review (AFR)</a>. According to the NAB, the stablecoin is intended to be used for a variety of tasks, including the trade of carbon credits, international money transfers, and repurchase agreements. The bank will also be in charge of keeping the Australian stablecoin backed by currency.<br /><br />NAB Chief Innovation Officer Howard Silby was cited as stating in a release,</p>
<blockquote>
<p>“We certainly believe there are elements of blockchain technology that will form part of the future of finance […] From our point of view, we see [blockchain] has the potential to deliver instantaneous, transparent, inclusive, financial outcomes.”</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The SWIFT network, an antiquated system, dominates the existing infrastructure for international transactions. However, many users may find the launch of AUDN to be a worthwhile substitute.<br /><br />The change occurs four months after Australian Senator Andrew Bragg introduced a bill attempting to strictly regulate the domestic bitcoin market. The measure mandated that stablecoin issuers and exchanges for digital assets report to authorities about their business practices. It also targeted Chinese banks operating in the nation that deal with digital yuan.<br /><br />NAB has launched AUDN, an Australian dollar-pegged stablecoin on the Ethereum network, making it the second major bank in the nation to do so. In partnership with cryptocurrency custodian Fireblocks, Australia and New Zealand Banking Group (ANZ) created a stablecoin that was tethered to the Australian dollar last year.<br /><br />Russia and Iran reportedly discussed the introduction of a new cryptocurrency backed by gold this week. The token would be produced as a stablecoin, according to Alexander Brazhnikov, executive director of the Russian Association of the Crypto Industry and Blockchain.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/national-australia-bank-unveils-stablecoin-on-ethereum-and-algorand/">National Australia Bank Unveils Stablecoin on Ethereum and Algorand</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/national-australia-bank-unveils-stablecoin-on-ethereum-and-algorand/">National Australia Bank Unveils Stablecoin on Ethereum and Algorand</a> was first posted on January 19, 2023 at 3:42 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XTZ Price Analysis: XTZ Steadies Above Key Psychological Level; Tezos Set To Undergo Its Most “Transformative” Update</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/xtz-price-analysis-xtz-steadies-above-key-psychological-level-tezos-set-to-undergo-its-most-transformative-update/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:53:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tezos (XTZ)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XTZ/USD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XTZ/USD Price Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64005</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tezos (XTZ) is up 2% in the last 24 hours as its price steadies near psychological $1 mark A whole new level of scaling capabilities within the Tezos network and beyond are expected to be introduced with the Mumbai upgrade plan This is one of the most &#8220;transformative&#8221; updates for the well-known proof-of-stake blockchain Tezos [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/xtz-price-analysis-xtz-steadies-above-key-psychological-level-tezos-set-to-undergo-its-most-transformative-update/">XTZ Price Analysis: XTZ Steadies Above Key Psychological Level; Tezos Set To Undergo Its Most “Transformative” Update</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/xtz-price-analysis-xtz-steadies-above-key-psychological-level-tezos-set-to-undergo-its-most-transformative-update/">XTZ Price Analysis: XTZ Steadies Above Key Psychological Level; Tezos Set To Undergo Its Most “Transformative” Update</a> was first posted on January 18, 2023 at 7:53 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li>Tezos (XTZ) is up 2% in the last 24 hours as its price steadies near psychological $1 mark</li>
<li>A whole new level of scaling capabilities within the Tezos network and beyond are expected to be introduced with the Mumbai upgrade plan</li>
<li>This is one of the most <em>&#8220;transformative&#8221;</em> updates for the well-known proof-of-stake blockchain</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/xtz-price-analysis-tezos-xtz-up-19-as-crypto-market-recovers-binance-us-announces-tezos-giveaway/">Tezos (XTZ)</a> is up 2% in the last 24 hours as its price steadies near psychological $1 mark. A whole new level of scaling capabilities within the Tezos network and beyond are expected to be introduced with the Mumbai upgrade plan, which was presented by Nomadic Labs, the top blockchain developer in the Tezos community. This is one of the most <em>&#8220;transformative&#8221;</em> updates for the well-known proof-of-stake blockchain, according to Tezos co-founder Arthur Breitman. The main features made public by Nomadic Labs include the activation of smart rollups, the introduction of Epoxy on Mainnet, which will further strengthen instant finality due to SNARKs proof-of-validity, a 15-second block time reduction, ticket transfers between accounts, and the addition of two new RPC endpoints for better visibility into ticket ownership. All of these improvements are anticipated to significantly increase scalability, resulting in more productive transactions and processing power for Tezos network users. The faster transaction assurance and extensive ticket transfer functionality between user accounts will both depend on the reduced block time feature.<br /><br /><strong>Key Levels</strong><br />Resistance Levels: $2.00, %1.50, $1.00<br />Support Levels: $0.92, $0.70, $0.500</p>
<h4>XTZ/USD Daily Chart: Ranging</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1488" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-64018 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-Daily-Jan-19.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-Daily-Jan-19.png 1488w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-Daily-Jan-19-300x139.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-Daily-Jan-19-1024x473.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-Daily-Jan-19-768x355.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-Daily-Jan-19-750x347.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-Daily-Jan-19-1140x527.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1488px) 100vw, 1488px" /><em><span style="color: #999999">XTZ/USD Daily Chart</span></em></h6>
<p>Following a brief consolidation, <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/xtz-price-analysis-striking-rally-holds-back-beneath-4-43-on-xtz-usd-tezos-q2-growth-remains-positive-on-etoro/">XTZ/USD</a> recorded a mild retracement after breaking above the $1.00 barrier to approach daily moving average (MA 200). The near-term oscillators are supporting the move higher, with the RSI strengthening inside the bullish zone despite the lack of confirmation of overbought conditions. <br /><br />If buying demand remains strong, initial resistance might come from the $1.50 level before the bulls target the $2.0 handle. If the price falls below the psychological level of $1.00 and approaches the previous range low of $0.70, a critical support zone could form between the $0.70 and the daily MA 50 at $0.90. Tezos aims to return to an ascending trend pattern.</p>
<h4>XTZ/USD 4-Hour Chart: Ranging</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1488" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-64019 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19.png 1488w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19-300x139.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19-1024x473.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19-768x355.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19-750x347.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19-1140x527.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1488px) 100vw, 1488px" /><em><span style="color: #999999">XTZ/USD 4-Hour Chart</span></em></h6>
<p>XTZ/USD recorded fresh selling above the 4-hour moving average (MA 50) near the $1.08 level, extending its retracement impulse to a new low of $0.964 on Wednesday. The market&#8217;s enthusiasm pushed the RSI into the overbought zone, while the indicator showed no symptoms of weakness. <br /><br />Currently, the price appears to be under pressure near the $0.950 mark. If the bulls take that level, the path to $1.50 and $2.00 will open up. Higher, the surge could go to the $2.50 level. On the downside, initial constraints may arise near $0.90, a break of which may result in some consolidation near the MA 200 at $0.825. The $0.70 low and the neighboring MA 200 at $0.825 may also be important levels to monitor.</p>
<p><strong>Note:</strong><em> Kryptomoney.com is not a financial advisor. Do your research before investing your funds in any financial asset or presented product or event. We are not responsible for your investing results</em></p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/xtz-price-analysis-xtz-steadies-above-key-psychological-level-tezos-set-to-undergo-its-most-transformative-update/">XTZ Price Analysis: XTZ Steadies Above Key Psychological Level; Tezos Set To Undergo Its Most “Transformative” Update</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/xtz-price-analysis-xtz-steadies-above-key-psychological-level-tezos-set-to-undergo-its-most-transformative-update/">XTZ Price Analysis: XTZ Steadies Above Key Psychological Level; Tezos Set To Undergo Its Most “Transformative” Update</a> was first posted on January 18, 2023 at 7:53 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ConsenSys To Cut 11% of Its Workforce Amidst Crypto Market Slowdown</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/consensys-to-cut-11-of-its-workforce-amidst-crypto-market-slowdown/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 23:26:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consensys]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64008</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ConsenSys, the founder of MetaMask and an Ethereum development company, has revealed plans to lay off 11% of its personnel. CEO Joseph Lubin confirmed the decision in a blog post today. ConsenSys will lay off 97 employees as part of its attempts to fight &#8220;challenging and uncertain market conditions,&#8221; according to Lubin. Furthermore, the decision [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/consensys-to-cut-11-of-its-workforce-amidst-crypto-market-slowdown/">ConsenSys To Cut 11% of Its Workforce Amidst Crypto Market Slowdown</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/consensys-to-cut-11-of-its-workforce-amidst-crypto-market-slowdown/">ConsenSys To Cut 11% of Its Workforce Amidst Crypto Market Slowdown</a> was first posted on January 18, 2023 at 6:26 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/01/10/ethereum-software-firm-consensys-to-cut-upwards-of-100-staff-as-crypto-bear-market-takes-another-casualty/">ConsenSys</a>, the founder of MetaMask and an Ethereum development company, has revealed plans to lay off 11% of its personnel. CEO Joseph Lubin confirmed the decision in a blog post today.<br /><br />ConsenSys will lay off 97 employees as part of its attempts to fight <em>&#8220;challenging and uncertain market conditions,&#8221;</em> according to Lubin. Furthermore, the decision continues a pattern that has been prevalent in 2023, as companies prepare for a likely economic recession.<br /><br />Although it is only about a month into 2023, the <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/cryptocurrency-hacks-increase-as-north-korea-focuses-on-defi/">cryptocurrency sector</a> has already seen several ups and downs. Prices of popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin have rebounded from the disastrous 2022, which harmed the sector. Despite this, Bitcoin companies have shed 27,000 positions since April 2022.<br /><br />That figure is about to rise, as ConsenSy announced plans to lay off 11% of its workforce in a blog post by CEO Joseph Lubin.<em> “Today we need to make the extremely difficult decision to streamline some of ConsenSys’ teams to adjust to challenging and uncertain market conditions,”</em> Lubin said.<br /><br />Furthermore, <em>“This decision will impact a total of 97 employees, which represents 11% of ConsenSys’ total workforce.”</em> Furthermore, the post noted that departing employees had access to severance compensation based on tenure, with an exercise window ranging from 12 to 36 months. ConsenSys, on the other hand, is providing<em> “personalized support from an external placement agency and extension of healthcare benefits in relevant jurisdictions.”</em></p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/consensys-to-cut-11-of-its-workforce-amidst-crypto-market-slowdown/">ConsenSys To Cut 11% of Its Workforce Amidst Crypto Market Slowdown</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/consensys-to-cut-11-of-its-workforce-amidst-crypto-market-slowdown/">ConsenSys To Cut 11% of Its Workforce Amidst Crypto Market Slowdown</a> was first posted on January 18, 2023 at 6:26 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Firm Genesis To File for Chapter 11 Bankruptcy: Details</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-firm-genesis-to-file-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy-details/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 22:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genesis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64002</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Amid a legal battle with the SEC, cryptocurrency startup Genesis is considering filing for Chapter 11 bankruptcy. The firm has been involved in a dispute with the Securities and Exchange Commission, which charged it last week with marketing unregistered securities. The conflict between Genesis and Gemini has been a major headline in 2023, culminating with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-firm-genesis-to-file-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy-details/">Crypto Firm Genesis To File for Chapter 11 Bankruptcy: Details</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-firm-genesis-to-file-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy-details/">Crypto Firm Genesis To File for Chapter 11 Bankruptcy: Details</a> was first posted on January 18, 2023 at 5:42 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Amid a legal battle with the SEC, cryptocurrency startup Genesis is <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-01-18/crypto-firm-genesis-said-to-prepare-bankruptcy-filing-as-soon-as-this-week">considering filing</a> for Chapter 11 bankruptcy. The firm has been involved in a dispute with the Securities and Exchange Commission, which charged it last week with marketing unregistered securities.<br /><br />The conflict between Genesis and Gemini has been a major headline in 2023, culminating with last week&#8217;s allegations. Following the circumstances of the past month, Genesis appears to be obliged to seek Chapter 11 protection.<br /><br />This month, the platform has been a consistent narrative in the cryptocurrency world. Following a 30% layoff in early January and its well-publicized struggle with the SEC and Gemini. Genesis, a Bitcoin lender, has now been forced to file for Chapter 11 bankruptcy.<br /><br /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/gemini-and-genesis-hit-with-sec-charges-for-earn-program-violations/">Gemini</a> has publicly attacked Genesis, which is owned by the Digital Currency Group and Barry Silbert. Publicly declaring the cryptocurrency firm&#8217;s accounting irregularities and deceptive actions concerning its former collaborator. All of this followed the two platforms&#8217; collaboration in February 2021, which resulted in the SEC&#8217;s allegations last week.<br /><br />Gary Gensler and the regulatory body both charged both platforms with selling unregistered securities. As a result, it is also tied to the collaboratively designed Gemini Earn program.<br /><br />The cryptocurrency startup is now said to be filing for Chapter 11 bankruptcy this week. Furthermore, Bloomberg claims that the company has been in <em>&#8220;confidential negotiations with various creditor groups amid liquidity crunch.&#8221;</em></p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-firm-genesis-to-file-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy-details/">Crypto Firm Genesis To File for Chapter 11 Bankruptcy: Details</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-firm-genesis-to-file-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy-details/">Crypto Firm Genesis To File for Chapter 11 Bankruptcy: Details</a> was first posted on January 18, 2023 at 5:42 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Ripple Lawsuit May Not Settle? Here Are Expectations of Ripple CEO and Legal Experts as Ruling Looms</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/why-ripple-lawsuit-may-not-settle-here-are-expectations-of-ripple-ceo-and-legal-experts-as-ruling-looms/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 21:51:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple lawsuit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP (XRP)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63993</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In an interview with CNBC&#8217;s &#8220;Squawk Box Europe&#8221; on Wednesday at the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland, Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse expressed his hopes for Ripple’s ongoing lawsuit with the SEC. A decision should come &#8220;sometime in the coming single digit months,&#8221; maybe as soon as June, Garlinghouse says on the lawsuit. He continued [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/why-ripple-lawsuit-may-not-settle-here-are-expectations-of-ripple-ceo-and-legal-experts-as-ruling-looms/">Why Ripple Lawsuit May Not Settle? Here Are Expectations of Ripple CEO and Legal Experts as Ruling Looms</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/why-ripple-lawsuit-may-not-settle-here-are-expectations-of-ripple-ceo-and-legal-experts-as-ruling-looms/">Why Ripple Lawsuit May Not Settle? Here Are Expectations of Ripple CEO and Legal Experts as Ruling Looms</a> was first posted on January 18, 2023 at 4:51 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In an interview with CNBC&#8217;s &#8220;Squawk Box Europe&#8221; on Wednesday at the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland, Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse expressed his hopes for Ripple’s ongoing lawsuit with the SEC. <br /><br />A decision should come <em>&#8220;sometime in the coming single digit months,&#8221;</em> maybe as soon as June, Garlinghouse says on the lawsuit. He continued by saying that although he is still open to the idea, he doesn&#8217;t think the company will settle the case.<br /><br />According to Garlinghouse,<em> “We have always said that we would love to settle, but it requires one very important thing, and that is that, on a going-forward basis, it’s clear that XRP is not a security.”</em><br /><br /><em>&#8220;The SEC and Gary Gensler have publicly said that they consider practically all cryptocurrencies to be securities. In the Venn diagram, that leaves very little room for settlement’’.</em><br /><br />If<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/xrp-might-be-the-next-big-thing-in-2023-here-are-five-reasons-per-santiment/"> XRP</a> is declared to be a security, Ripple may be subject to far harsher restrictions with regard to the token. This could include demands for better investor protections and transparency disclosures, similar to those imposed on registered broker-dealers.<br /><br />It might also serve as a model for numerous other blockchain and cryptocurrency projects that might later be categorized as securities.</p>
<h2>Expectations remain</h2>
<p>According to Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse and General Counsel Stuart Alderoty, a ruling on the action is anticipated in the first half of 2023. <br /><br />According to James K. Filan, the decision could be made in March 2023 or earlier. Stuart Alderoty believes that the decision, whenever it is announced, will have a significant impact on the development of cryptocurrencies in the US.<br /><br />Bloomberg presents some observers&#8217; viewpoints. According to Joseph Hall, a partner at Davis Polk &amp; Wardwell who served as an SEC employee from 2003 to 2005, &#8220;the recent upheaval in the crypto markets might taint the court&#8217;s view.&#8221; You simply have to assume that the judge&#8217;s decision might be impacted by the investment losses they have witnessed, according to Hall.<br /><br /><em>‘’And the SEC will make it obvious to them that if they opt for a different decision, they won&#8217;t have the tools they need to stop this kind of activity’’.</em><br /><br />Even if Ripple wins, it might not be the ticker-tape celebration that cryptocurrency enthusiasts are hoping for, according to Andrew Stoltmann, a securities lawsuit attorney based in Chicago.<br /><br />According to Stoltmann, <em>&#8220;I anticipate Congress will step in over the above and essentially decide who gets jurisdiction with regard to enforcement.&#8221;</em></p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/why-ripple-lawsuit-may-not-settle-here-are-expectations-of-ripple-ceo-and-legal-experts-as-ruling-looms/">Why Ripple Lawsuit May Not Settle? Here Are Expectations of Ripple CEO and Legal Experts as Ruling Looms</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/why-ripple-lawsuit-may-not-settle-here-are-expectations-of-ripple-ceo-and-legal-experts-as-ruling-looms/">Why Ripple Lawsuit May Not Settle? Here Are Expectations of Ripple CEO and Legal Experts as Ruling Looms</a> was first posted on January 18, 2023 at 4:51 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Hit With New Class Action Lawsuit, Here’s Reason</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-hit-with-new-class-action-lawsuit-heres-reason/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 22:11:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Flare]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63998</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase Global Inc., an American publicly traded trading platform, has been named in a new class action lawsuit for failing to provide two airdrops including Flare Network&#8217;s native token, FLR, and the accompanying Songbird (SGB) token. The lawsuit was filed in the United States District Court for the Northern District of California. According to the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-hit-with-new-class-action-lawsuit-heres-reason/">Coinbase Hit With New Class Action Lawsuit, Here’s Reason</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-hit-with-new-class-action-lawsuit-heres-reason/">Coinbase Hit With New Class Action Lawsuit, Here’s Reason</a> was first posted on January 17, 2023 at 5:11 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Coinbase Global Inc., an American publicly traded trading platform, has been named in a new<a href="https://www.dropbox.com/sh/koqcuqyj47fvhlv/AADXxp8HCyvwKFQtd1wws_WVa?dl=0&amp;preview=001_2023.01.13_complaint.pdf"> class action lawsuit</a> for failing to provide two airdrops including Flare Network&#8217;s native token, FLR, and the accompanying Songbird (SGB) token. The lawsuit was filed in the United States District Court for the Northern District of California.<br /><br />According to the case filed by HODL LAW CALI, the plaintiff&#8217;s attorney, Dallas Woody, and anyone who may join in, Coinbase has broken its agreement to participate in the Flare Network airdrop, which it promised in December 2021. According to the lawsuit, the Flare Network airdrop was supposed to be dispersed to every XRP holder based on a snapshot of account balances. <br /><br />The terms noted that the Songbird token would be distributed first, followed by the deposit of FLR tokens for all users. According to the lawsuit, despite receiving distribution of both SGB and FLR tokens before the latter&#8217;s distribution on January 9 of this year, the trading platform has refused to give it to all qualified clients.<br /><br />As seen in the lawsuit, rival exchanges have transferred their received FLR and SGB tokens to eligible users, and Coinbase&#8217;s delay or failure to do so on time has cost clients some money. The defendant is requesting that the court order Coinbase to credit customers&#8217; tokens and compensate them for any losses they may have suffered.<br /><br />The<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/flare-networks-to-bridge-ripple-and-ethereum-ecosystems/"> Flare Network</a> airdrop has recently become one of the most acclaimed in the digital currency industry, with several trading firms expressing support. Despite the participation of exchanges such as Binance, the Flare Token experienced a large drop as many beneficiaries sold the tokens as soon as they received them.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-hit-with-new-class-action-lawsuit-heres-reason/">Coinbase Hit With New Class Action Lawsuit, Here’s Reason</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-hit-with-new-class-action-lawsuit-heres-reason/">Coinbase Hit With New Class Action Lawsuit, Here’s Reason</a> was first posted on January 17, 2023 at 5:11 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			<enclosure length="-1" type="application/json" url="https://www.dropbox.com/sh/koqcuqyj47fvhlv/AADXxp8HCyvwKFQtd1wws_WVa?dl=0&amp;amp;preview=001_2023.01.13_complaint.pdf"/><itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><itunes:subtitle>Coinbase Global Inc., an American publicly traded trading platform, has been named in a new class action lawsuit for failing to provide two airdrops including Flare Network&amp;#8217;s native token, FLR, and the accompanying Songbird (SGB) token. The lawsuit was filed in the United States District Court for the Northern District of California. According to the [&amp;#8230;] The post Coinbase Hit With New Class Action Lawsuit, Here’s Reason appeared first on Latest Crypto News. Coinbase Hit With New Class Action Lawsuit, Here’s Reason was first posted on January 17, 2023 at 5:11 pm. &amp;copy;2021 &amp;quot;Latest Crypto News&amp;quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at info@kryptomoney.com</itunes:subtitle><itunes:summary>Coinbase Global Inc., an American publicly traded trading platform, has been named in a new class action lawsuit for failing to provide two airdrops including Flare Network&amp;#8217;s native token, FLR, and the accompanying Songbird (SGB) token. The lawsuit was filed in the United States District Court for the Northern District of California. According to the [&amp;#8230;] The post Coinbase Hit With New Class Action Lawsuit, Here’s Reason appeared first on Latest Crypto News. Coinbase Hit With New Class Action Lawsuit, Here’s Reason was first posted on January 17, 2023 at 5:11 pm. &amp;copy;2021 &amp;quot;Latest Crypto News&amp;quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at info@kryptomoney.com</itunes:summary><itunes:keywords>News, Coinbase, Flare</itunes:keywords></item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Burns $620 Million Worth of Native Crypto BNB From Circulation</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/binance-burns-620-million-worth-of-native-crypto-bnb-from-circulation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 21:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance (BNB)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63989</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange Binance is still aiming to lower the total number of BNB in circulation to 100 million. To accomplish this, the firm announced the completion of the 22nd burn of its native token. According to Binance&#8217;s statement, it has pulled 2.064 million BNB from circulation, which is worth over $620 million [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-burns-620-million-worth-of-native-crypto-bnb-from-circulation/">Binance Burns $620 Million Worth of Native Crypto BNB From Circulation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-burns-620-million-worth-of-native-crypto-bnb-from-circulation/">Binance Burns $620 Million Worth of Native Crypto BNB From Circulation</a> was first posted on January 17, 2023 at 4:30 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-acknowledges-busd-peg-issues-says-not-always-been-fully-backed/"> Binance</a> is still aiming to lower the total number of BNB in circulation to 100 million. To accomplish this, the firm announced the completion of the 22nd burn of its native token.<br /><br />According to Binance&#8217;s statement, it has pulled 2.064 million BNB from circulation, which is worth over $620 million at today&#8217;s prices.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">The 22nd quarterly <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BNB&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$BNB</a> token burn has been completed through <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BNB?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#BNB</a> Auto-Burn. <br /><br />Here’s everything you need to know about the first quarterly burn of 2023 and some words from <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@cz_binance</a> ??<a href="https://t.co/sIrWpnUxIL">https://t.co/sIrWpnUxIL</a></p>
— Binance (@binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1615272723885727745?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 17, 2023</a></blockquote>
<p>The<a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1615272723885727745"> 22nd burn</a> was the largest in terms of BNB tokens since the record-breaking 14th two years ago. The Pioneer Burn Program was responsible for 7,181 of the 2.064 burns that occurred today. The service, which was introduced in 2020, intends to assist customers who have lost access to their BNB tokens when they submit requests through the customer service page and are accepted by the exchange.<br /><br />The <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-completes-quarterly-burn-with-over-2-million-bnb-burned/">Pioneer Burn Program</a> operates in tandem with the other BNB burning processes. Binance&#8217;s native crypto, like the rest of the market, has been on a run since the beginning of the year. It began in 2023 at roughly $240 but quickly skyrocketed by double digits.<br /><br />This resulted in a rise of $315 on Saturday, marking the highest price for BNB since late November 2022. Barring a modest retracement, the asset is currently trading above $300.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-burns-620-million-worth-of-native-crypto-bnb-from-circulation/">Binance Burns $620 Million Worth of Native Crypto BNB From Circulation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-burns-620-million-worth-of-native-crypto-bnb-from-circulation/">Binance Burns $620 Million Worth of Native Crypto BNB From Circulation</a> was first posted on January 17, 2023 at 4:30 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CHZ Price Analysis: How High Will Launch of Socios Collectibles Push CHZ Price; Chiliz Chain 2.0 Smashes New Milestone</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/chz-price-analysis-how-high-will-launch-of-socios-collectibles-push-chz-price-chiliz-chain-2-0-smashes-new-milestone/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 13:54:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chiliz (CHZ)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CHZ/USD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CHZ/USD Price Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63978</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chiliz (CHZ) is up 20.5% in the past seven days at $0.136 The 10,000,000th transaction on the Chiliz Scoville Testnet has been surpassed Users can now own the game-scored balls from the SerieA Super Cup Chiliz (CHZ) is up 20.5% in the past seven days at $0.136, but trades down at 1.49% in the last [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/chz-price-analysis-how-high-will-launch-of-socios-collectibles-push-chz-price-chiliz-chain-2-0-smashes-new-milestone/">CHZ Price Analysis: How High Will Launch of Socios Collectibles Push CHZ Price; Chiliz Chain 2.0 Smashes New Milestone</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/chz-price-analysis-how-high-will-launch-of-socios-collectibles-push-chz-price-chiliz-chain-2-0-smashes-new-milestone/">CHZ Price Analysis: How High Will Launch of Socios Collectibles Push CHZ Price; Chiliz Chain 2.0 Smashes New Milestone</a> was first posted on January 17, 2023 at 8:54 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li>Chiliz (CHZ) is up 20.5% in the past seven days at $0.136</li>
<li>The 10,000,000th transaction on the Chiliz Scoville Testnet has been surpassed</li>
<li>Users can now own the game-scored balls from the SerieA Super Cup</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/chz-price-analysis-chiliz-price-jumps-15-in-week-amid-fresh-wave-of-hype-ahead-of-fifa-world-cup-2022/">Chiliz (CHZ)</a> is up 20.5% in the past seven days at $0.136, but trades down at 1.49% in the last 24 hours. Chilizle Chain 2.0 has reached a new milestone ahead of its release. In a Twitter announcement, the 10,000,000th transaction on the Chiliz Scoville Testnet has been surpassed. In March 2022, Chiliz announced the launch of <em>&#8220;Scoville,&#8221;</em> the public testnet for Chiliz Chain 2.0 and the first Layer-1 blockchain created especially for the sports and entertainment industries. Developed in collaboration with Ankr, a leading provider of decentralized infrastructure, CC2 is EVM compatible with gas fees up to 200x cheaper than ETH. In a move that is deemed the world’s first, users can now own the game-scored balls from the Serie A Super Cup as the Socios collectibles launch. According to the announcement, only fan token holders will be able to win the real balls from the goals. The first drop gives fans a chance to own a game-scored ball from the EA Sports Super Cup Final between AC Milan and Inter. The EA Sports Supercup final paves the way for the first-ever Socios.com collectibles, and its final will be played on Wednesday, January 18.</p>
<p><strong>Key Levels</strong><br />Resistance Levels: $0.2400, $0.2000, $0.1500<br />Support Levels: $0.1000, $0.0761, $0.0500</p>
<h4>CHZ/USD Daily Chart: Ranging</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1488" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-63994 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CHZUSD-Daily-Jan-17.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CHZUSD-Daily-Jan-17.png 1488w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CHZUSD-Daily-Jan-17-300x139.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CHZUSD-Daily-Jan-17-1024x473.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CHZUSD-Daily-Jan-17-768x355.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CHZUSD-Daily-Jan-17-750x347.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CHZUSD-Daily-Jan-17-1140x527.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1488px) 100vw, 1488px" /><em><span style="color: #808080">CHZ/USD Daily Chart</span></em></h6>
<p>Chiliz (CHZ) achieved a daily high of $0.1443 in the prior week before retracing to $0.1314 on Monday as bulls aim to convert this $0.1500 zone into support ahead of a move higher. A break of the moving average (MA 200) threshold near $0.1700 could provide market players with the impetus needed to move the pair higher. Daily, the RSI indicator is currently above 60, indicating a buy signal.<br /><br />If the market confirms overbought conditions, a minor retreat is not out of the question shortly. This, however, may present a buy-the-dip opportunity. In the event of a pullback below the moving average (MA 500), the $0.1000 might provide quick support to the CHZ price. Otherwise, the bears may target the $0.076 low if they continue to push lower in unfamiliar terrain.</p>
<h4>CHZ/USD 4-Hour Chart: Ranging</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1488" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-63995 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CHZUSD-4-Hour-Jan-17.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CHZUSD-4-Hour-Jan-17.png 1488w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CHZUSD-4-Hour-Jan-17-300x139.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CHZUSD-4-Hour-Jan-17-1024x473.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CHZUSD-4-Hour-Jan-17-768x355.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CHZUSD-4-Hour-Jan-17-750x347.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CHZUSD-4-Hour-Jan-17-1140x527.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1488px) 100vw, 1488px" /><em><span style="color: #999999">CHZ/USD 4-Hour Chart</span></em></h6>
<p>On the 4-hour chart, the <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/chz-price-analysis-chiliz-rebounds-from-lows-fc-barcelona-fan-token-powered-by-chiliz-goes-live-on-binance/">CHZ/USD</a> pair is rising in a positive trend. It&#8217;s upside resistance is yet to be broken, as the CHZ price is rising. A break over the $0.1500 barrier should signal a continued rise toward the $0.200 level. Otherwise, if the price retraces to the psychological level of $0.100, we may witness another push to the low, impacting the current trend negatively.<br /><br />If the price continues to fall, the $0.076 level may provide support. Only a break below this support would give bears greater momentum to target the $0.05 level. Overall, Chiliz is still on the rise, aided by good fundamentals in the fan token sector. A retreat may produce a consolidation pattern before the continuation of the trend.</p>
<p><strong>Note:</strong><em> Kryptomoney.com is not a financial advisor. Do your research before investing your funds in any financial asset or presented product or event. We are not responsible for your investing results</em></p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/chz-price-analysis-how-high-will-launch-of-socios-collectibles-push-chz-price-chiliz-chain-2-0-smashes-new-milestone/">CHZ Price Analysis: How High Will Launch of Socios Collectibles Push CHZ Price; Chiliz Chain 2.0 Smashes New Milestone</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/chz-price-analysis-how-high-will-launch-of-socios-collectibles-push-chz-price-chiliz-chain-2-0-smashes-new-milestone/">CHZ Price Analysis: How High Will Launch of Socios Collectibles Push CHZ Price; Chiliz Chain 2.0 Smashes New Milestone</a> was first posted on January 17, 2023 at 8:54 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>