<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>Latest Crypto News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://kryptomoney.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<description>Latest Crypto News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 23:43:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/cropped-cropped-favicon_512x512_v2-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Latest Crypto News</title>
	<link>https://kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><itunes:subtitle>Latest Crypto News</itunes:subtitle><itunes:category text="News &amp; Politics"/><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Business News"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Investing"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Tech News"/></itunes:category><item>
		<title>Ripple Executive Applauds EU’s Progressive Stance on Crypto</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/ripple-executive-applauds-eus-progressive-stance-on-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 23:43:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64952</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Susan Friedman, a Ripple executive, has praised the European Union&#8217;s (EU) progressive approach to cryptocurrency regulation following the passage of the Markets in Crypto-Assets (MiCA) legislation by the EU Parliament. In a tweet, Friedman expressed her enthusiasm for the EU&#8216;s sensible regulatory measures, which stand in contrast to the United States&#8217; enforcement-focused approach. She also [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/ripple-executive-applauds-eus-progressive-stance-on-crypto/">Ripple Executive Applauds EU&#8217;s Progressive Stance on Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ripple-executive-applauds-eus-progressive-stance-on-crypto/">Ripple Executive Applauds EU&#8217;s Progressive Stance on Crypto</a> was first posted on April 20, 2023 at 7:43 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/ss_friedman/status/1649122957954777099">Susan Friedman</a>, a Ripple executive, has praised the European Union&#8217;s (EU) progressive approach to cryptocurrency regulation following the passage of the Markets in Crypto-Assets (MiCA) legislation by the EU Parliament. <br /><br />In a tweet, Friedman expressed her enthusiasm for the <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/eu-report-central-banks-likely-safe-cryptocurrencies/">EU</a>&#8216;s sensible regulatory measures, which stand in contrast to the United States&#8217; enforcement-focused approach. She also highlighted Ripple&#8217;s eagerness to expand in the European market, joining other major <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/new-york-attorney-general-moves-to-shut-down-unregistered-crypto-firms/">crypto firms</a> such as Binance, Coinbase, and Kraken in welcoming the new legislation.<br /><br />MiCA aims to provide regulatory clarity and harmonization for crypto firms operating across Europe. With a significant majority of 517 Members of the European Parliament (MEPs) voting in favor and only 38 voting against, the legislation now moves to its final formal vote in the Council of the EU on May 16.<br /><br />According to Circle&#8217;s <a href="https://twitter.com/paddi_hansen/status/1649014582009110533">Patrick Hansen</a>, the regulation will take effect for stablecoin issuers in June 2024 and for all other crypto-asset service providers in December 2024, upon publication in the Official Journal of the EU.<br /><br />The EU&#8217;s primary objectives with MiCA are to protect consumers engaging in crypto transactions, create regulatory harmonization to allow companies to operate on an EU-wide basis, provide legal certainty for companies and institutions entering the space, and establish a leading role in global crypto regulation. This comprehensive framework offers companies a clear rulebook for various services, including token issuance, exchange, and custody, enabling fair competition and innovation.<br /><br />With the passage of MiCA, the EU is poised to become a global hub for crypto projects due to regulatory clarity and its large single market of 450 million consumers.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/ripple-executive-applauds-eus-progressive-stance-on-crypto/">Ripple Executive Applauds EU&#8217;s Progressive Stance on Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ripple-executive-applauds-eus-progressive-stance-on-crypto/">Ripple Executive Applauds EU&#8217;s Progressive Stance on Crypto</a> was first posted on April 20, 2023 at 7:43 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Gains Regulatory Approval To Operate in Bermuda</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-gains-regulatory-approval-to-operate-in-bermuda/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 07:58:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64944</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase, a major cryptocurrency exchange, has announced that it has been granted a Class F License under the Digital Asset Business Act by the Bermuda Monetary Authority (BMA). Bermuda was one of the first countries to implement full digital asset regulation in 2018, and Coinbase has praised the BMA&#8217;s &#8220;level of rigor, transparency, compliance, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-gains-regulatory-approval-to-operate-in-bermuda/">Coinbase Gains Regulatory Approval To Operate in Bermuda</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-gains-regulatory-approval-to-operate-in-bermuda/">Coinbase Gains Regulatory Approval To Operate in Bermuda</a> was first posted on April 20, 2023 at 3:58 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-set-to-receive-470k-from-wahi-brothers/">Coinbase</a>, a major cryptocurrency exchange, has announced that it has been granted a Class F License under the Digital Asset Business Act by the Bermuda Monetary Authority (BMA). Bermuda was one of the first countries to implement full digital asset regulation in 2018, and Coinbase has praised the BMA&#8217;s <em>&#8220;level of rigor, transparency, compliance, and cooperation.&#8221;</em> The company has chosen Bermuda as an international hub due to the BMA&#8217;s world-class leadership and involvement in global regulation.<br /><br />Coinbase is set to launch its offshore derivatives exchange in Bermuda by the end of this month, according to reports from <a href="https://fortune.com/crypto/2023/04/19/coinbase-gets-bermuda-license-plans-to-launch-offshore-exchange-in-coming-weeks/">Fortune</a>. In addition to its expansion in Bermuda, Coinbase has also provided updates on its progress in expanding to Singapore, Brazil, Canada, the United Arab Emirates, and Europe in a recent <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/an-update-to-coinbases-global-scale-to-go-broad-and-deep">blog post.</a><br /><br />Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong had previously stated that the company might consider leaving the US to operate in the UK due to regulatory challenges in the US. Coinbase has faced various actions in the US, including receiving a Wells notice from the Securities and Exchange Commission in March. The company settled with the New York Department of Financial Services on an unrelated issue in January and settled with the Commodity Futures Trading Commission in 2021.<br /><br />While the Bermuda license and other expansions do not signify a complete move away from the US or address the aforementioned issues, Coinbase is taking a <em>&#8220;go broad and go deep approach&#8221;</em> to ensure that it can serve users globally. Kraken, another cryptocurrency exchange, has also recently obtained regulatory approval in Ireland, while Binance expanded to Sweden in January, indicating a growing trend of cryptocurrency exchanges expanding their global reach.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-gains-regulatory-approval-to-operate-in-bermuda/">Coinbase Gains Regulatory Approval To Operate in Bermuda</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-gains-regulatory-approval-to-operate-in-bermuda/">Coinbase Gains Regulatory Approval To Operate in Bermuda</a> was first posted on April 20, 2023 at 3:58 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Best Ways to Sell USDT in Dubai</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/best-ways-to-sell-usdt-in-dubai/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 06:45:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sponsored]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sell USDT in Dubai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT in Dubai]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64948</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There are several places in Dubai in which there are the best ways to Sell USDT in Dubai. As a stablecoin tied to the value of the US dollar, USDT is widely used in financial dealings and investments. But, if you need to sell your USDT in Dubai, you&#8217;ll want to be familiar with the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/best-ways-to-sell-usdt-in-dubai/">Best Ways to Sell USDT in Dubai</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/best-ways-to-sell-usdt-in-dubai/">Best Ways to Sell USDT in Dubai</a> was first posted on April 20, 2023 at 2:45 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are several places in Dubai in which there are the best ways to <a href="https://cryptodesk.ae/sell-usdt-in-dubai">Sell USDT in Dubai</a>. As a stablecoin tied to the value of the US dollar, USDT is widely used in financial dealings and investments. But, if you need to sell your USDT in Dubai, you&#8217;ll want to be familiar with the best options available to you. Here, we&#8217;ll go over some of the most effective strategies for selling USDT in Dubai, along with some helpful hints and advice.</p>
<h3>Cryptocurrency exchanges</h3>
<p>The role of cryptocurrency exchanges in buying and selling cryptocurrencies is crucial. These marketplaces allow users to trade and invest in various coins and tokens by exchanging them for fiat currency or other digital assets. Particularly notable is Crypto Desk, one of the leading cryptocurrency exchanges today to Sell tether in Dubai.</p>
<p>The trading platform provided by Crypto Desk, a registered exchange, is both safe and simple to use. Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Litecoin are some cryptocurrencies accepted on the exchange. One of the most promising features of the crypto desk is that you can sell tether coin, USDT crypto, exchange USDT for cash, and exchange USDT For Dirhams. It&#8217;s easy to purchase, sell, and trade and supports various currency pairs. The security measures at Crypto Desk prevent unauthorized access to customer funds or private data. Its superb customer service is another reason investors and traders should consider it.</p>
<h3>Over-the-counter (OTC) trading</h3>
<p>Trading cryptocurrencies directly between individuals, as opposed to through an exchange, is known as over-the-counter (OTC) trading. The benefits of over-the-counter (OTC) trading benefits include shorter processing times, reduced fees, and higher levels of individual attention. High-net-worth individuals, institutional investors, and major trading businesses sometimes engage in off-exchange (OTC) trading when they need to buy or sell substantial amounts of cryptocurrencies without affecting the market price.</p>
<p>In addition to Bitcoin and Ethereum, OTC trading desks offer access to many other cryptocurrencies. Over-the-counter (OTC) transactions are handled at a trading desk, where parties can discuss pricing and terms of the settlement. Although over-the-counter trading has many benefits, working with a trustworthy OTC trading desk that prioritizes safety and regulation is essential.</p>
<p>If you&#8217;re looking for a trustworthy and safe OTC trading platform, go no further than <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/goldman-sachs-launches-crypto-trading-desk-focused-on-btc-derivatives/">Crypto Desk</a>. Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin, and many other cryptocurrencies and altcoins are all available on the platform. Clients are assigned their personal account managers at the Crypto Desk, who are there to facilitate transactions and offer analysis of the market. Customers may feel at ease knowing their money and data are secure on the platform. In addition, all transactions are done openly and responsibly thanks to Crypto Desk&#8217;s adherence to regulatory regulations.</p>
<h3>Peer-to-peer (P2P)</h3>
<p>Without the participation of a central authority, P2P trading allows users to trade cryptocurrencies directly with one another. Buyers and sellers meet each other online, negotiate a price, and complete the transaction in a P2P trade. Peer-to-peer (P2P) trade benefits include reduced costs, shortened processing times, and enhanced confidentiality. It&#8217;s also a common choice in places with weak or underdeveloped banking infrastructures. For this reason, peer-to-peer (P2P) trading in the cryptocurrency market has exploded in popularity.</p>
<h3>Crypto ATM Machine</h3>
<p>In Dubai, you can use a crypto ATM to purchase and trade cryptocurrencies quickly and easily. Like standard ATMs, crypto ATMs let customers purchase cryptocurrency using cash or a debit/credit card. Due to the increasing demand for easy and quick access to buying and selling cryptocurrency, crypto ATMs have become increasingly popular in Dubai.</p>
<p>In Dubai, you can use cryptocurrencies from ATMs from several providers, including BCB ATM, Bitaccess, and Bitcoin Depot. Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin, and Bitcoin Cash are just some of the cryptocurrencies that may be purchased and traded at these ATMs. Several Dubai crypto ATMs also feature stringent Know Your Customer (KYC) and Anti-Money Laundering (AML) standards that must be met before any transactions can be processed.</p>
<p>Cryptocurrency ATMs provide a quick and easy way to purchase and sell digital currency, but their costs exceed regular exchanges. Before utilizing a cryptocurrency ATM, comparing costs is a good idea. To ensure a safe and secure transaction, use encrypted wallet addresses.</p>
<h3>Conclusion</h3>
<p>One of the wisest financial moves you can make in Dubai is to include crypto assets in your portfolio. To acquire cryptocurrency, you need only use a trusted and regulated crypto exchange platform, such as Crypto Desk. It won&#8217;t take you more than a few minutes to complete the purchase procedure. A final invoice is issued as evidence of the transaction. Get on the bandwagon now by purchasing or selling USDT in Dubai through Crypto Desk.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/best-ways-to-sell-usdt-in-dubai/">Best Ways to Sell USDT in Dubai</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/best-ways-to-sell-usdt-in-dubai/">Best Ways to Sell USDT in Dubai</a> was first posted on April 20, 2023 at 2:45 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BTC: Here’s a Quick Summary of Tesla’s Bitcoin Holdings in Q1</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/btc-heres-a-quick-summary-of-teslas-bitcoin-holdings-in-q1/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 23:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tesla]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64940</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In its Q1 report, Tesla revealed that it had not made any changes to its Bitcoin holdings, which remained at around 11,950 BTC, equivalent to approximately $350 million. This news comes after the e-car maker sold 75% of its Bitcoin holdings in June 2022, converting them into fiat currency and adding $936 million to its [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/btc-heres-a-quick-summary-of-teslas-bitcoin-holdings-in-q1/">BTC: Here’s a Quick Summary of Tesla’s Bitcoin Holdings in Q1</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/btc-heres-a-quick-summary-of-teslas-bitcoin-holdings-in-q1/">BTC: Here’s a Quick Summary of Tesla’s Bitcoin Holdings in Q1</a> was first posted on April 19, 2023 at 7:58 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In its Q1 <a href="https://tesla-cdn.thron.com/static/ZXSBN8_TSLA_Q1_2023_Update_ABMJPG.pdf?xseo=&amp;response-content-disposition=inline%3Bfilename%3D%22e826b065-cc14-467c-8c9c-e1feb7189ba8.pdf">report</a>, Tesla revealed that it had not made any changes to its Bitcoin holdings, which remained at around 11,950 BTC, equivalent to approximately $350 million. This news comes after the e-car maker sold 75% of its Bitcoin holdings in June 2022, converting them into fiat currency and adding $936 million to its cash reserves.<br /><br /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/tesla-completed-bitcoin-sales-worth-936-million-in-q2-2022/">Tesla</a>&#8216;s initial investment in Bitcoin, made in February 2021, was a bold move that significantly impacted the cryptocurrency market. The investment saw Tesla purchase $1.5 billion worth of Bitcoin, which pushed the price of the cryptocurrency to new heights.<br /><br />However, the bet on<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-holds-steady-above-28000-despite-regulatory-crackdowns/"> Bitcoin</a> did not pay off as Tesla had hoped. The company&#8217;s Q1 earnings report revealed a slight dip in sales, which came in at $23.33 billion compared to the estimated $23.39 billion. Despite this, the company still met earnings per share (EPS) expectations of $0.85.<br /><br />Despite the sales miss, investors seemed unfazed, with Tesla&#8217;s shares trading only marginally lower in after-hours trading. This is likely since Tesla&#8217;s overall financial position remains strong, with the company&#8217;s cash reserves bolstered by the sale of its Bitcoin holdings.<br /><br />It remains to be seen whether Tesla will make any further investments in Bitcoin or other cryptocurrencies in the future. While the initial investment had a significant impact on the market, the subsequent sale of the majority of Tesla&#8217;s Bitcoin holdings suggests that the company may not view cryptocurrency as a viable long-term investment option.<br /><br />In any case, Tesla&#8217;s Q1 earnings report serves as a reminder that even the most audacious bets can sometimes fail to pay off and that businesses must carefully consider the risks and benefits of any investment decisions they make.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/btc-heres-a-quick-summary-of-teslas-bitcoin-holdings-in-q1/">BTC: Here’s a Quick Summary of Tesla’s Bitcoin Holdings in Q1</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/btc-heres-a-quick-summary-of-teslas-bitcoin-holdings-in-q1/">BTC: Here’s a Quick Summary of Tesla’s Bitcoin Holdings in Q1</a> was first posted on April 19, 2023 at 7:58 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			<enclosure length="5935644" type="application/pdf" url="https://tesla-cdn.thron.com/static/ZXSBN8_TSLA_Q1_2023_Update_ABMJPG.pdf?xseo=&amp;amp;response-content-disposition=inline%3Bfilename%3D%22e826b065-cc14-467c-8c9c-e1feb7189ba8.pdf"/><itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><itunes:subtitle>In its Q1 report, Tesla revealed that it had not made any changes to its Bitcoin holdings, which remained at around 11,950 BTC, equivalent to approximately $350 million. This news comes after the e-car maker sold 75% of its Bitcoin holdings in June 2022, converting them into fiat currency and adding $936 million to its [&amp;#8230;] The post BTC: Here’s a Quick Summary of Tesla’s Bitcoin Holdings in Q1 appeared first on Latest Crypto News. BTC: Here’s a Quick Summary of Tesla’s Bitcoin Holdings in Q1 was first posted on April 19, 2023 at 7:58 pm. &amp;copy;2021 &amp;quot;Latest Crypto News&amp;quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at info@kryptomoney.com</itunes:subtitle><itunes:summary>In its Q1 report, Tesla revealed that it had not made any changes to its Bitcoin holdings, which remained at around 11,950 BTC, equivalent to approximately $350 million. This news comes after the e-car maker sold 75% of its Bitcoin holdings in June 2022, converting them into fiat currency and adding $936 million to its [&amp;#8230;] The post BTC: Here’s a Quick Summary of Tesla’s Bitcoin Holdings in Q1 appeared first on Latest Crypto News. BTC: Here’s a Quick Summary of Tesla’s Bitcoin Holdings in Q1 was first posted on April 19, 2023 at 7:58 pm. &amp;copy;2021 &amp;quot;Latest Crypto News&amp;quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at info@kryptomoney.com</itunes:summary><itunes:keywords>News, bitcoin, Tesla</itunes:keywords></item>
		<item>
		<title>SafeMoon Hacker To Return Majority of Stolen Funds: Details</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/safemoon-hacker-to-return-majority-of-stolen-funds-details/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 23:37:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SafeMoon (SAFEMOON)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64936</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The SafeMoon community can breathe a sigh of relief as the hacker responsible for last month&#8217;s liquidity hack has agreed to return 80% of the stolen funds, amounting to $7.2 million in tokens. The hacker exploited a smart contract vulnerability on March 28, resulting in a $9 million liquidity drain. In the weeks following the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/safemoon-hacker-to-return-majority-of-stolen-funds-details/">SafeMoon Hacker To Return Majority of Stolen Funds: Details</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/safemoon-hacker-to-return-majority-of-stolen-funds-details/">SafeMoon Hacker To Return Majority of Stolen Funds: Details</a> was first posted on April 18, 2023 at 7:37 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The <a href="https://twitter.com/SafeMoonSpidey/status/1648319024395169796">SafeMoon</a> community can breathe a sigh of relief as the hacker responsible for last month&#8217;s liquidity hack has agreed to return 80% of the stolen funds, amounting to $7.2 million in tokens. The hacker exploited a smart contract vulnerability on March 28, resulting in a $9 million liquidity drain.<br /><br />In the weeks following the <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/robinhood-twitter-account-hacked-as-scammers-trick-investors-into-buying-phony-crypto-2/">hack</a>, the community expressed their frustration over the lack of updates and progress in recovering the stolen funds. SafeMoon CEO John Karony&#8217;s calls for patience were criticized as repetitive and avoidant, while a recent announcement about &#8220;New #SAFEMOON app builds submitted!&#8221; was labeled as a distraction.<br /><br />However, according to <a href="https://twitter.com/SafeMoonSpidey/status/1648320150045704192">@SafeMoonSpidey</a>, a deal was struck between both parties, with the hacker returning 80% of the stolen funds and keeping the remaining 20%, with no charges filed against them. <br /><br />An on-chain message explained that, after careful consideration, it was believed that this was in the best interest of SafeMoon and the community. While some raised concerns that the hacker was being rewarded for criminal behavior, @SafeMoonSpidey called the 20% reward a white hat bounty reward.<br /><br />The resolution of this issue comes as a relief to the SafeMoon community, which has been eagerly awaiting updates and progress on recovering the stolen funds. @SafeMoonSpidey suggested that the team may have been holding out for this resolution before &#8220;updating the app,&#8221; indicating that progress may finally be made toward recovery and improving the platform&#8217;s security. <br /><br />Despite some concerns, the return of 80% of the stolen funds is a positive development, providing some closure to the community and signaling a step forward for SafeMoon.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/safemoon-hacker-to-return-majority-of-stolen-funds-details/">SafeMoon Hacker To Return Majority of Stolen Funds: Details</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/safemoon-hacker-to-return-majority-of-stolen-funds-details/">SafeMoon Hacker To Return Majority of Stolen Funds: Details</a> was first posted on April 18, 2023 at 7:37 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kraken Secures Regulatory Nod To Run Operations in Ireland</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/kraken-secures-regulatory-nod-to-run-operations-in-ireland/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 23:23:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kraken]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64932</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Kraken, a popular cryptocurrency exchange, has received a Virtual Asset Service Provider (VASP) license from the Central Bank of Ireland. This license allows the exchange to operate legally in the country, and Kraken believes it demonstrates their adherence to strict anti-money laundering and counterterrorism financing rules. The exchange&#8217;s Head of European Operations, Mark Jennings, emphasized [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/kraken-secures-regulatory-nod-to-run-operations-in-ireland/">Kraken Secures Regulatory Nod To Run Operations in Ireland</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/kraken-secures-regulatory-nod-to-run-operations-in-ireland/">Kraken Secures Regulatory Nod To Run Operations in Ireland</a> was first posted on April 18, 2023 at 7:23 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/krakenfx/status/1648341661926211586">Kraken,</a> a popular cryptocurrency exchange, has received a Virtual Asset Service Provider (VASP) license from the Central Bank of Ireland. This license allows the exchange to operate legally in the country, and Kraken believes it demonstrates their adherence to strict anti-money laundering and counterterrorism financing rules.<br /><br />The exchange&#8217;s Head of European Operations, Mark Jennings, emphasized the importance of clear and effective regulation for the mainstream adoption of cryptocurrencies. He added that Kraken remains committed to working with European regulators to ensure compliance.<br /><br />The need for regulatory clarity in the crypto industry has been apparent for years, particularly in the top economies such as the United States and China. While China has banned digital assets altogether, the US regulatory landscape is not closed off, but regulatory bodies have largely approached the topic through enforcement.<br /><br />In recent months, the <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/u-s-congress-to-address-stablecoin-legislation-and-sec-oversight/">Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)</a> has taken multiple enforcement actions against established exchanges such as Kraken and Coinbase. This has pushed crypto firms to seek more solid footing, resulting in an exodus and cross-border expansion to locations such as Europe and Hong Kong, which have a proactive approach to regulation.<br /><br />Europe is on the verge of implementing the Markets in Crypto-Assets (MiCA) framework, which establishes rules for cryptocurrencies and the industry. The framework places various regulatory requirements on crypto firms and mandates disclosures to bring them up to par with traditional financial institutions. Additionally, the European Parliament has introduced the Data Act, which supplements the MiCA regulation and establishes protocols for handling sensitive personal and business data.<br /><br />While the MiCA framework and Data Act have yet to come into force, companies have already begun applying for necessary approvals, and more announcements are expected in the coming months. Similarly, Hong Kong is also establishing a full regulatory net for the crypto industry and is already processing applications from VASP hopefuls. Officials have reported that over 80 firms have shown interest in setting up shop in the city-state, while around 20 firms have applied for a license already.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/kraken-secures-regulatory-nod-to-run-operations-in-ireland/">Kraken Secures Regulatory Nod To Run Operations in Ireland</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/kraken-secures-regulatory-nod-to-run-operations-in-ireland/">Kraken Secures Regulatory Nod To Run Operations in Ireland</a> was first posted on April 18, 2023 at 7:23 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Grayscale Solana Trust Starts Trading on OTC Markets: Details</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/grayscale-solana-trust-starts-trading-on-otc-markets-details/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 21:43:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grayscale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana (SOL)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64929</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Grayscale&#8217;s Solana (SOL) trust is now available for trading on the OTC Markets platform, according to a press release. It is the 60th crypto trust offered by the company and will trade under the ticker GSOL. SOL is the native cryptocurrency of Solana, which aims to expand blockchain&#8217;s utility beyond payments by allowing developers to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/grayscale-solana-trust-starts-trading-on-otc-markets-details/">Grayscale Solana Trust Starts Trading on OTC Markets: Details</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/grayscale-solana-trust-starts-trading-on-otc-markets-details/">Grayscale Solana Trust Starts Trading on OTC Markets: Details</a> was first posted on April 17, 2023 at 5:43 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/en/news-release/2023/04/17/2647933/0/en/Grayscale-Solana-Trust-Now-Trading-on-OTC-Markets.html">Grayscale&#8217;s Solana (SOL)</a> trust is now available for trading on the OTC Markets platform, according to a press release. <br /><br />It is the 60th crypto trust offered by the company and will trade under the ticker GSOL. SOL is the native cryptocurrency of Solana, which aims to expand blockchain&#8217;s utility beyond payments by allowing developers to create smart contracts that work on the <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/solana-network-goes-down-again-reportedly-as-a-result-of-ddos-attack/">Solana Network</a> powered by SOL tokens.<br /><br />Grayscale&#8217;s crypto trusts are like shares backed by cryptocurrencies stored by the company, which allows investors to get exposure to digital assets without the hassle of buying and storing them directly.<br /><br />The GSOL ticker is used for trading the SOL trust, and there are over 304 shares available. U.S.-based investors can buy them directly, along with other crypto trust shares, on OTC Markets.<br /><br />All of Grayscale&#8217;s crypto trusts, including GSOL, are regulated by the Securities Act of 1933 and can be bought directly by U.S.-based investors, along with other securities.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/grayscale-solana-trust-starts-trading-on-otc-markets-details/">Grayscale Solana Trust Starts Trading on OTC Markets: Details</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/grayscale-solana-trust-starts-trading-on-otc-markets-details/">Grayscale Solana Trust Starts Trading on OTC Markets: Details</a> was first posted on April 17, 2023 at 5:43 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Plunges Below $30,000 Amid Economic Concerns</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-plunges-below-30000-amid-economic-concerns/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 21:10:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64925</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>On Monday, cryptocurrency prices experienced a decline as investors shifted their focus to upcoming bank earnings and recession concerns, leaving behind the excitement around Ethereum&#8217;s &#8220;Shapella&#8221; upgrade. According to CoinMetrics, Bitcoin dropped over 3.5% to $29,251, falling below the crucial $30,000 level that it had achieved last week for the first time since June. In [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-plunges-below-30000-amid-economic-concerns/">Bitcoin Plunges Below $30,000 Amid Economic Concerns</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-plunges-below-30000-amid-economic-concerns/">Bitcoin Plunges Below $30,000 Amid Economic Concerns</a> was first posted on April 17, 2023 at 5:10 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>On Monday, cryptocurrency <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/04/17/bitcoin-dips-below-30000-as-investors-await-bank-earnings.html?&amp;qsearchterm=bitcoin">prices</a> experienced a decline as investors shifted their focus to upcoming bank earnings and recession concerns, leaving behind the excitement around Ethereum&#8217;s &#8220;Shapella&#8221; upgrade. <br /><br />According to CoinMetrics, <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoins-price-action-forms-pennant-pattern-near-crucial-30000-level/">Bitcoin</a> dropped over 3.5% to $29,251, falling below the crucial $30,000 level that it had achieved last week for the first time since June. In contrast, Ether decreased by 2.4%, but it managed to maintain its $2,000 mark, which it had surpassed the previous week.<br /><br />Last week was a good one for cryptocurrencies, with prices rising due to optimism surrounding Ethereum&#8217;s latest technical upgrade, which is expected to bring greater liquidity to the network by enabling &#8220;locked up&#8221; Ether to be withdrawn. This is anticipated to attract more institutional interest in the long run, with Bitcoin and Ether rising 8% and 12%, respectively, for the week.<br /><br />According to Yuya Hasegawa, a crypto market analyst at the Japanese bitcoin exchange Bitbank, a small correction in prices is expected this week, and some investors may want to take profits from the previous week, causing some selling pressure. However, macro factors are not expected to have a significant impact on the price of Bitcoin, as the Fed Funds futures market has already priced in more than an 80% chance of a 25 bp hike in May.<br /><br />Crypto investors are keeping an eye on bank earnings this week for more insight into the health of the sector and the possibility of an upcoming recession. <br /><br />Several other Fed officials are also scheduled to speak this week. Callie Cox, an analyst at investing company eToro, believes that it is uncertain how cryptocurrencies will perform during a recession since they have not yet performed well in a high-rate, slow-growth environment.<br /><br />Despite the potential downside this week, Hasegawa believes that it should not severely affect Bitcoin&#8217;s upward trend.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-plunges-below-30000-amid-economic-concerns/">Bitcoin Plunges Below $30,000 Amid Economic Concerns</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-plunges-below-30000-amid-economic-concerns/">Bitcoin Plunges Below $30,000 Amid Economic Concerns</a> was first posted on April 17, 2023 at 5:10 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>U.S. Congress to Address Stablecoin Legislation and SEC Oversight</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/u-s-congress-to-address-stablecoin-legislation-and-sec-oversight/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 23:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64921</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. House Committee on Financial Services will hold a hearing on Tuesday with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair, Gary Gensler, as the star witness, to discuss the &#8220;Oversight of the Securities and Exchange Commission.&#8221; The following day, the Subcommittee on Digital Assets, Financial Technology and Inclusion will discuss draft legislation related to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/u-s-congress-to-address-stablecoin-legislation-and-sec-oversight/">U.S. Congress to Address Stablecoin Legislation and SEC Oversight</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/u-s-congress-to-address-stablecoin-legislation-and-sec-oversight/">U.S. Congress to Address Stablecoin Legislation and SEC Oversight</a> was first posted on April 16, 2023 at 7:02 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The U.S. House Committee on Financial Services will hold a hearing on Tuesday with the <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/sec-classifies-nine-digital-tokens-as-securities/">Securities and Exchange Commission</a> (SEC) Chair, Gary Gensler, as the star witness, to discuss the <em>&#8220;Oversight of the Securities and Exchange Commission.&#8221;</em> The following day, the Subcommittee on Digital Assets, Financial Technology and Inclusion will discuss draft legislation related to stablecoins.<br /><br />One of the<a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/statement/peirce-rendering-inovation-2023-04-12"> issues</a> on the table is Gensler&#8217;s latest <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2023-77">policy move</a> to change the statutory definition of a securities exchange, which SEC Commissioner Hester Peirce opposes. Gensler argues that the amendment is necessary to address platforms trading crypto asset securities, including <em>&#8220;DeFi systems,&#8221;</em> while Peirce argues that the proposed change undermines innovation and the First Amendment.<br /><br />Other topics up for discussion include the SEC&#8217;s regulatory developments, rulemaking, and activities, as well as the potential expansion of the SEC&#8217;s authority over digital asset trading platforms. The committee will also <a href="https://docs.house.gov/meetings/BA/BA00/20230418/115751/HHRG-118-BA00-20230418-SD002.pdf">revisit</a> the SEC proposal calling for registered investment advisors to include Bitcoin holdings among other assets held by<em> &#8220;qualified custodians,&#8221;</em> which Peirce says the Commission does not have the authority to regulate directly.<br /><br />On Wednesday, the Subcommittee will address<em> &#8220;Understanding Stablecoins’ Role in Payments and the Need for Legislation&#8221;</em> and review a 72-page draft of<a href="https://docs.house.gov/meetings/BA/BA21/20230419/115753/BILLS-118pih-Toproviderequirementsforpaymentstablecoinissuersresearchonadigitaldollarandforotherpurposes.pdf"> legislation</a> proposing requirements for payment stablecoin issuers, research on a digital dollar, and other purposes. The draft bill includes extensive definitions, sets up standards for interoperability, reporting, and enforcement, and calls for a two-year moratorium on new stablecoins until a study can be completed by the U.S. Treasury.<br /><br />Various industry leaders are expected to testify, including Dante Disparte, chief strategy officer and global policy head at Circle, and Jake Chervinsky, chief policy officer at the Blockchain Association. While the proposed bill is a product of bipartisan efforts, it still requires further work to address open and challenging issues. The role of the dollar in the world and currency on the internet is at stake, and political leaders must work to get it right.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/u-s-congress-to-address-stablecoin-legislation-and-sec-oversight/">U.S. Congress to Address Stablecoin Legislation and SEC Oversight</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/u-s-congress-to-address-stablecoin-legislation-and-sec-oversight/">U.S. Congress to Address Stablecoin Legislation and SEC Oversight</a> was first posted on April 16, 2023 at 7:02 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			<enclosure length="224732" type="application/pdf" url="https://docs.house.gov/meetings/BA/BA00/20230418/115751/HHRG-118-BA00-20230418-SD002.pdf"/><itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><itunes:subtitle>The U.S. House Committee on Financial Services will hold a hearing on Tuesday with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair, Gary Gensler, as the star witness, to discuss the &amp;#8220;Oversight of the Securities and Exchange Commission.&amp;#8221; The following day, the Subcommittee on Digital Assets, Financial Technology and Inclusion will discuss draft legislation related to [&amp;#8230;] The post U.S. Congress to Address Stablecoin Legislation and SEC Oversight appeared first on Latest Crypto News. U.S. Congress to Address Stablecoin Legislation and SEC Oversight was first posted on April 16, 2023 at 7:02 pm. &amp;copy;2021 &amp;quot;Latest Crypto News&amp;quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at info@kryptomoney.com</itunes:subtitle><itunes:summary>The U.S. House Committee on Financial Services will hold a hearing on Tuesday with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair, Gary Gensler, as the star witness, to discuss the &amp;#8220;Oversight of the Securities and Exchange Commission.&amp;#8221; The following day, the Subcommittee on Digital Assets, Financial Technology and Inclusion will discuss draft legislation related to [&amp;#8230;] The post U.S. Congress to Address Stablecoin Legislation and SEC Oversight appeared first on Latest Crypto News. U.S. Congress to Address Stablecoin Legislation and SEC Oversight was first posted on April 16, 2023 at 7:02 pm. &amp;copy;2021 &amp;quot;Latest Crypto News&amp;quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at info@kryptomoney.com</itunes:summary><itunes:keywords>News, Crypto Regulation, Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Stablecoin</itunes:keywords></item>
		<item>
		<title>Uniswap Users at Risk of a Phishing Scam</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/uniswap-users-at-risk-of-a-phishing-scam/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 22:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Decentralized finance (DeFi)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UniSwap (UNI)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64918</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Uniswap, the popular decentralized exchange (DEX), has recently become the target of a phishing scam that is spreading false information about a supposed exploit. Cybersecurity firm PeckShield has issued a warning to Uniswap users about a fraudulent account impersonating Pocket Universe. The phishing account claims that there is a bug in the Permit2 Contract that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/uniswap-users-at-risk-of-a-phishing-scam/">Uniswap Users at Risk of a Phishing Scam</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/uniswap-users-at-risk-of-a-phishing-scam/">Uniswap Users at Risk of a Phishing Scam</a> was first posted on April 14, 2023 at 6:13 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/peckshield/status/1646963495047667712">Uniswap</a>, the popular decentralized exchange (DEX), has recently become the target of a phishing scam that is spreading false information about a supposed exploit. Cybersecurity firm PeckShield has issued a warning to Uniswap users about a fraudulent account impersonating Pocket Universe. The phishing account claims that there is a bug in the Permit2 Contract that makes Uniswap users&#8217; coins unsafe.<br /><br />According to reports, the scam involves a fraudulent account prompting users to revoke their current approvals on a platform called Revoke Cash. <br /><br />PeckShield has taken to Twitter to alert users about the phishing attempt and urged them to stay vigilant and not fall prey to the scam. The company emphasized that the tweets contain false statements intended to entice users to click the phishing link and ultimately steal their tokens.<br /><br />To protect themselves, users should verify the authenticity of accounts and information sources before taking any action. The real Pocket Universe account, @PocketUniverseZ, offers an extension that protects users from scams. Users must use such protective measures and stay alert to phishing attempts that aim to steal their tokens.<br /><br />Uniswap is a leading <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/dex-volume-climbs-from-1-billion-to-over-25-billion-in-2020/">DEX</a> that operates on the Ethereum blockchain. It allows users to trade cryptocurrencies without relying on a centralized exchange. As the popularity of decentralized finance (DeFi) grows, the risk of phishing scams and other fraudulent activities also increases. Users need to take the necessary precautions and stay informed to avoid falling victim to such scams.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/uniswap-users-at-risk-of-a-phishing-scam/">Uniswap Users at Risk of a Phishing Scam</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/uniswap-users-at-risk-of-a-phishing-scam/">Uniswap Users at Risk of a Phishing Scam</a> was first posted on April 14, 2023 at 6:13 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>