<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>Latest Crypto News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://kryptomoney.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<description>Latest Crypto News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 07:44:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/cropped-cropped-favicon_512x512_v2-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Latest Crypto News</title>
	<link>https://kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><itunes:subtitle>Latest Crypto News</itunes:subtitle><itunes:category text="News &amp; Politics"/><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Business News"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Investing"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Tech News"/></itunes:category><item>
		<title>Gbitcoins: Simplifying Passive Income with Cloud Mining – Easy, Safe, and Profitable</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/gbitcoins-simplifying-passive-income-with-cloud-mining/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 07:43:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sponsored]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cloud mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gbitcoins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65093</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With everything that is going around, having a stable source of passive income comes with many advantages. If you are wondering which is the best method to do so in the sense of being secured, the answer is cloud mining. And when it comes to finding the world&#8217;s best cloud mining services to help you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/gbitcoins-simplifying-passive-income-with-cloud-mining/">Gbitcoins: Simplifying Passive Income with Cloud Mining &#8211; Easy, Safe, and Profitable</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/gbitcoins-simplifying-passive-income-with-cloud-mining/">Gbitcoins: Simplifying Passive Income with Cloud Mining &#8211; Easy, Safe, and Profitable</a> was first posted on May 13, 2023 at 3:43 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With everything that is going around, having a stable source of passive income comes with many advantages. If you are wondering which is the best method to do so in the sense of being secured, the answer is cloud mining. And when it comes to finding the world&#8217;s best cloud mining services to help you out, look no further than the trusted and effective Gbitcoins!</p>
<p>Want to learn how to use <a href="https://gbitcoins.net/?kryptomoney">Gbitcoins</a> for effective cloud mining to acquire a desired passive income? Great!<br />
You are in the right place as everything you need to know about this is mentioned below in detail for your better understanding. So, do keep on reading!</p>
<h3>Why do so many new investors choose Gbitcoins?</h3>
<p>Currently, Gbitcoins (operating from America) is popular among investors from all over because the company is known for being an excellent cloud mining service provider. From renting extra resources to successfully broadening your hashing power, everything you need to optimize the entire process can be done easily with the help of Gbitcoins.</p>
<p>Learn how to open a Gbitcoins account in 3 easy-to-follow steps</p>
<h4>Step 1:</h4>
<p>Go to the company&#8217;s official website to open an account or register and click on the &#8220;Sign Up&#8221; tab visible on your screen.</p>
<h4>Step 2:</h4>
<p>You will receive a verification code on the official email address you provided when signing up. Input this code within the allotted time and proceed by clicking on the &#8220;Submit&#8221; tab.</p>
<h4>Step 3:</h4>
<p>Your account will be activated instantly. As soon as it gets activated, $15 will be added to your account by the company so that you can effectively kickstart your passive income-earning process via cloud mining.</p>
<p>Is cloud mining right for investors?</p>
<p>Anyone interested in effectively earning passive income knows about the benefits of <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/jpmorgan-maintains-bearish-stance-on-cryptocurrencies/">cryptocurrency</a> cloud mining.</p>
<p>With cloud mining (standard cryptocurrency mining using the shared computing power of a datacenter remotely), you can mine all profitable cryptocurrencies, such as Ethereum, Dogecoin, Bitcoin, and other similar cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>If you are interested in Bitcoin cloud mining, the service provider Gbitcoins will be the right fit as their miners focus mainly on Bitcoin mining for free. The company is known for investing in only cutting-edge technologies to provide all the required cloud mining services that can drastically increase your profit margin.</p>
<p>Besides the instant $15 deposit discussed above, Gbitcoins is also known for its lucrative affiliate program that offers an incentive of up to 5.5%. Earning passive income via cloud mining becomes an easy and effective process with the company&#8217;s many beneficial services.</p>
<h3>Is Gbitcoins legit?</h3>
<p>Do not confuse Gbitcoins as a scam website as the difference between such a site and Gbitcoins are far too many to count.</p>
<p>Unlike scam websites, the official website of Gbitcoins is licensed by the respected American government. The company can also provide legit cloud mining certification to prove its legitimacy. On the other hand, fake or scam websites are not certified cloud mining companies like Gbitcoins.</p>
<p>A tell-tale sign of a scam website is the fact you can open an account with a fake email address. When you deal with a scam website, you end up losing your valuable personal information and money. No such worries are associated with this well-loved cloud mining service provider. Customers feel safe cloud mining with Gbitcoins as they are known for offering the following benefits that are always absent in all scam websites:</p>
<ul>
<li>Account for cloud mining can be opened only with a legit or registered email id</li>
<li>Guaranteed payouts within 24 hours</li>
<li>SSL protection for all customers&#8217; vulnerable personal and banking information</li>
</ul>
<p>Hopefully, these major differences between Gbitcoins and standard scam websites have helped you to understand that this cloud mining service provider is legit and can effectively help out. Both you and your earnings will be safeguarded well if only Gbitcoins for cloud mining and passive income earning is considered.</p>
<h3>Gbitcoins Packages for Cloud Mining</h3>
<p>The company offers many different packages and every one of them offers a different set of advantages, contract length, and Return on Investment (ROI). However, no matter which package you go for, the profit will remain fixed and you will receive daily payouts. Once your contract term comes to an end, you can either continue with the same package or withdraw your collected fund.</p>
<p>Some fruitful Gbitcoins packages and their offers are the following:</p>
<ul>
<li>Package/Contract costing $6000</li>
</ul>
<p>The Contract Term or validity period of this package is 30 days. With this package, you will get a Daily Rate (DR) of 3% with a $6,000+$5,400 Fixed Return (FR).</p>
<ul>
<li>Package/Contract costing $3000</li>
</ul>
<p>The Contract Term of this package from Gbitcoins is 21 days with a $3,000+$1,638 Fixed Return at a Daily Rate of 2.6%.</p>
<ul>
<li>Package/Contract costing $1,500</li>
</ul>
<p>With a 2.25% Daily Rate and a 14 day Contract Term, customers can enjoy a $1,500+$472.5 Fixed Return from this package.</p>
<ul>
<li>Package/Contract costing $500</li>
</ul>
<p>The Contract Term of this package is 7 days with a $500+$70 Fixed Return at a Daily Rate of 2%.</p>
<ul>
<li>Package/Contract costing $100</li>
</ul>
<p>This package comes with a 3 day Contract Term and a Fixed Return of $100+$5.45 at a 1.82% Daily Rate.</p>
<ul>
<li>Package/Contract costing $15</li>
</ul>
<p>This one is valid for a day only and offers a $15+$0.9 Fixed Return</p>
<p>The process to withdraw your passive income from Gbitcoins</p>
<p>You can withdraw the fund that you earned via cloud mining with Gbitcoins into your account quickly and with minimum effort as the process is quite straightforward.</p>
<p>Here is what you need to do to withdraw your fund from the company&#8217;s <a href="https://gbitcoins.net/?kryptomoney">official website</a> (for first-timers):</p>
<ul>
<li>Browse your account to find the &#8220;Withdraw&#8221; tab and click on it</li>
<li>After getting access, you have to pick a wallet of your choice to continue</li>
<li>Enter the amount you want to withdraw from your account in the designated field (the minimum withdrawal limit is $100)</li>
<li>Shortly, your registered or chosen wallet will receive the requested amount of withdrawal (this process may take a couple of minutes to complete)</li>
</ul>
<h3>To Conclude</h3>
<p>Earning passive income becomes an easy process when cloud mining is selected. If you are interested in an effective cloud mining service performance, consider the trusted and helpful service provider Gbitcoins. They make the process profitable, secure, and faster.</p>
<p>To learn more about cloud mining and earning passive income securely, click on this link for the required official assistance &#8211; https://gbitcoins.net/?kryptomoney</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/gbitcoins-simplifying-passive-income-with-cloud-mining/">Gbitcoins: Simplifying Passive Income with Cloud Mining &#8211; Easy, Safe, and Profitable</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/gbitcoins-simplifying-passive-income-with-cloud-mining/">Gbitcoins: Simplifying Passive Income with Cloud Mining &#8211; Easy, Safe, and Profitable</a> was first posted on May 13, 2023 at 3:43 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Bids Farewell to Canada, Temporarily Halts Operations</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/binance-bids-farewell-to-canada-temporarily-halts-operations/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 22:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Canada]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65086</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a tweet on May 12, Binance announced its decision to halt operations in Canada, following the footsteps of other proactive crypto companies that have withdrawn from the Canadian marketplace. While acknowledging Canada&#8217;s sentimental value and expressing optimism for the country&#8217;s crypto sector, Binance cited recent regulatory guidance as the reason for its departure, deeming [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-bids-farewell-to-canada-temporarily-halts-operations/">Binance Bids Farewell to Canada, Temporarily Halts Operations</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-bids-farewell-to-canada-temporarily-halts-operations/">Binance Bids Farewell to Canada, Temporarily Halts Operations</a> was first posted on May 12, 2023 at 6:59 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In a tweet on <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1657099651210969088">May 12</a>, Binance announced its decision to halt operations in Canada, following the footsteps of other proactive crypto companies that have withdrawn from the Canadian marketplace.</p>
<p>While acknowledging Canada&#8217;s sentimental value and expressing optimism for the country&#8217;s crypto sector,<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-accused-of-deliberately-flouting-laws-by-cftc-chief/"> Binance</a> cited recent regulatory guidance as the reason for its departure, deeming it unfeasible to continue operating under the new conditions.</p>
<p>Despite disagreeing with the new guidelines, Binance expressed its intention to maintain engagement with Canadian regulators and return to the market when users regain the freedom to access a broader range of digital assets.</p>
<p>The regulatory landscape changed in February when Canadian securities regulators introduced new guidelines, mandating pre-registration filings and imposing specific rules on crypto companies.</p>
<p>Notably, companies operating in Canada are now required to segregate funds belonging to Canadian users and withhold margin or leverage trading from them.</p>
<p>Binance joins the ranks of Paxos, dYdX, Blockchain.com, and OKX, all of which have withdrawn their services from the Canadian market.</p>
<p>On the other hand, Kraken, Coinbase, Crypto.com, and Gemini have expressed their intent to continue operating in Canada.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-bids-farewell-to-canada-temporarily-halts-operations/">Binance Bids Farewell to Canada, Temporarily Halts Operations</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-bids-farewell-to-canada-temporarily-halts-operations/">Binance Bids Farewell to Canada, Temporarily Halts Operations</a> was first posted on May 12, 2023 at 6:59 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nexo to Exit UK Market as Part of Reorganization Strategy</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/nexo-to-exit-uk-market-as-part-of-reorganization-strategy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 22:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nexo]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65082</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nexo, a prominent cryptocurrency lending platform, has decided to dissolve two of its business units based in the United Kingdom as it grapples with regulatory challenges in various parts of Europe and North America. This move is part of a broader restructuring effort, although Nexo will continue its operations within the country. According to filings [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/nexo-to-exit-uk-market-as-part-of-reorganization-strategy/">Nexo to Exit UK Market as Part of Reorganization Strategy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/nexo-to-exit-uk-market-as-part-of-reorganization-strategy/">Nexo to Exit UK Market as Part of Reorganization Strategy</a> was first posted on May 11, 2023 at 6:56 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/nexo-settles-with-sec-for-45-million/">Nexo</a>, a prominent cryptocurrency lending platform, has decided to dissolve two of its business units based in the United Kingdom as it grapples with regulatory challenges in various parts of Europe and North America. This move is part of a broader restructuring effort, although Nexo will continue its operations within the country.<br /><br />According to filings reported by<a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/crypto-lender-nexo-takes-steps-to-dissolve-uk-units-1.1918939"> BNN Bloomberg</a>, Nexo has applied to remove Nexo Financial Services Ltd. and Nexo Clearing and Custody Ltd. from the UK company register. In a message to Bloomberg, Antoni Trenchev, co-founder of Nexo, explained that the company is undergoing restructuring and reevaluating its approach to client services.<br /><br />Aside from crypto trading and custody, Nexo offers a range of crypto-based financial products, including debit card services, borrowing, and savings accounts. The savings accounts, as advertised on their website, can yield &#8220;up to 15% APR on your crypto,&#8221; with Bitcoin reaching as high as 7% and USDC up to 12%.<br /><br />Regulators in the United States have expressed skepticism towards crypto-based interest-bearing accounts, highlighting their unusually high savings rates compared to traditional accounts. Unlike chartered banks, crypto financial platforms are not covered by federal deposit insurance. Scrutiny heightened in mid-2022 after several crypto lending platforms, including Celsius, Voyager, and later BlockFi, encountered financial difficulties.<br /><br />Nexo clarified that it is not facing the same dire financial situation as those firms. However, it continues to face ongoing scrutiny and charges from the Securities and Exchange Commission in the coming months. In December, Nexo announced its departure from the United States due to regulatory obstacles.<br /><br />Furthermore, Nexo&#8217;s Earn product is currently inaccessible in Canada due to the complete ban on crypto margin trading imposed by regulators in the country. The company&#8217;s troubles also extend to Bulgaria, where its offices were raided in January on allegations of money laundering, tax fraud, and computer fraud related to unlicensed banking services.</p>
<p>Trenchev dismissed these accusations as &#8220;ludicrous&#8221; and responded by filing a $1 million lawsuit against Bulgaria.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/nexo-to-exit-uk-market-as-part-of-reorganization-strategy/">Nexo to Exit UK Market as Part of Reorganization Strategy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/nexo-to-exit-uk-market-as-part-of-reorganization-strategy/">Nexo to Exit UK Market as Part of Reorganization Strategy</a> was first posted on May 11, 2023 at 6:56 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlockFi Clears Regulatory Hurdle To Repay $297M to Specific Customers</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/blockfi-clears-regulatory-hurdle-to-repay-297m-to-specific-customers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 22:24:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlockFI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65078</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a significant development within its ongoing bankruptcy proceedings, BlockFi has been granted authorization to refund $297 million to select customers, as reported by Reuters on May 11. This decision pertains specifically to customers who held funds in BlockFi&#8217;s Wallet rather than its interest-bearing accounts. The ruling was delivered by Judge Michael Kaplan, who determined [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/blockfi-clears-regulatory-hurdle-to-repay-297m-to-specific-customers/">BlockFi Clears Regulatory Hurdle To Repay $297M to Specific Customers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/blockfi-clears-regulatory-hurdle-to-repay-297m-to-specific-customers/">BlockFi Clears Regulatory Hurdle To Repay $297M to Specific Customers</a> was first posted on May 11, 2023 at 6:24 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In a significant development within its ongoing bankruptcy proceedings, <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/blockfi-set-to-pay-back-over-100000-to-california-users/">BlockFi</a> has been granted authorization to refund $297 million to select customers, as reported by <a href="https://www.reuters.com/legal/blockfi-gets-court-permission-return-297-million-wallet-customers-2023-05-11/">Reuters</a> on May 11. This decision pertains specifically to customers who held funds in BlockFi&#8217;s Wallet rather than its interest-bearing accounts.<br /><br />The ruling was delivered by Judge Michael Kaplan, who determined that while wallet users maintained ownership of their deposits, customers who stored funds in interest-bearing accounts relinquished ownership and granted control to BlockFi. Subsequently, the company utilized those assets for its lending activities.<br /><br />However, customers who transferred their funds to the wallet accounts as a last-minute measure when BlockFi filed for<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-lender-blockfi-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy-protection/"> bankruptcy</a> in November last year will not be eligible for the refund. Approximately 48,000 users attempted to move a total of $375 million from interest accounts to wallet accounts during that period.<br /><br />Although customer lawyers contended that this amount should also be returned, Judge Kaplan dismissed the claim, citing BlockFi&#8217;s failure to finalize those transactions and its prerogative to block such transfers during the service halt.<br /><br />BlockFi&#8217;s legal representatives previously argued that returning the $375 million sum would dilute the value of funds recoverable by wallet users. They further asserted that such a payout could impede BlockFi from refunding any funds altogether due to a lack of fund segregation.<br /><br />The tumultuous series of events began when BlockFi temporarily suspended user withdrawals and activity on November 10, 2022, in response to the collapse of the crypto exchange FTX. Subsequently, the company filed for bankruptcy on November 28.<br /><br />Earlier in March, BlockFi had already initiated refunds of $100,000 to users in California.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/blockfi-clears-regulatory-hurdle-to-repay-297m-to-specific-customers/">BlockFi Clears Regulatory Hurdle To Repay $297M to Specific Customers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/blockfi-clears-regulatory-hurdle-to-repay-297m-to-specific-customers/">BlockFi Clears Regulatory Hurdle To Repay $297M to Specific Customers</a> was first posted on May 11, 2023 at 6:24 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Shifts Voyager, FTX Tokens to Innovation Zone Amid Bankruptcy</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/binance-shifts-voyager-ftx-tokens-to-innovation-zone-amid-bankruptcy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 23:33:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng “CZ” Zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX token (FTT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Voyager Token (VGX)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65074</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance, a prominent cryptocurrency exchange, has made a strategic move by relocating the native tokens of bankrupt crypto firms Voyager (VGX) and FTX (FTT) to its newly established innovation zone. This decision was part of a broader action that involved transferring 16 other struggling digital assets, including JasmyCoin (JASMY), OMG Network (OMG), WazirX (WRX), Serum [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-shifts-voyager-ftx-tokens-to-innovation-zone-amid-bankruptcy/">Binance Shifts Voyager, FTX Tokens to Innovation Zone Amid Bankruptcy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-shifts-voyager-ftx-tokens-to-innovation-zone-amid-bankruptcy/">Binance Shifts Voyager, FTX Tokens to Innovation Zone Amid Bankruptcy</a> was first posted on May 10, 2023 at 7:33 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/binance-will-move-amb-ark-bts-drep-ftt-gft-jasmy-loom-mln-oax-omg-perl-pnt-snm-srm-vgx-wrx-and-yfii-into-the-innovation-zone-on-2023-05-10-2f420fa36bcd4fe89dc6855b857b7ea9">Binance</a>, a prominent cryptocurrency exchange, has made a strategic move by relocating the native tokens of bankrupt crypto firms Voyager (VGX) and FTX (FTT) to its newly established innovation zone. This decision was part of a broader action that involved transferring 16 other struggling digital assets, including JasmyCoin (JASMY), OMG Network (OMG), WazirX (WRX), Serum (SRM), OAX (OAX), and more.<br /><br />Binance <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1656231470959063041?s=20">CEO Changpeng</a> &#8220;CZ&#8221; Zhao explained that rather than directly delisting these tokens, the exchange opted to move them to the innovation zone based on a suggestion from a community member. CZ emphasized that this relocation serves as a prelude, allowing the failing projects to improve. However, CZ made it clear that if these projects fail to demonstrate progress, delisting remains a possibility.<br /><br />The innovation zone on Binance was specifically designed to provide users with a platform to trade innovative projects characterized by higher volatility and risks compared to other tokens. Binance will periodically review and assess projects that meet these criteria, monitoring their development closely. If deemed appropriate, these projects could be migrated to Binance&#8217;s main platform.<br /><br />Both Voyager (VGX) and FTX (FTT) have experienced a significant decline in interest since filing for bankruptcy in 2022. VGX, for instance, has dropped from over $1 to approximately $0.15911 at the time of writing, representing an 83% decline over the past year. Its market capitalization has also plummeted to around $40 million from a peak of over $300 million, with a daily trading volume below $10 million.<br /><br />Similarly, FTX&#8217;s FTT has witnessed a rapid decline from its previous heights. The token, associated with the bankrupt exchange, has fallen by over 96% to $1.18594 after reaching an all-time high of over $84 in 2021. Currently, its market capitalization stands at $390.05 million, with a trading volume of $11 million.<br /><br />As the situation unfolds, Binance&#8217;s move to the innovation zone provides a new opportunity for these struggling tokens to potentially turn their fortunes around.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-shifts-voyager-ftx-tokens-to-innovation-zone-amid-bankruptcy/">Binance Shifts Voyager, FTX Tokens to Innovation Zone Amid Bankruptcy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-shifts-voyager-ftx-tokens-to-innovation-zone-amid-bankruptcy/">Binance Shifts Voyager, FTX Tokens to Innovation Zone Amid Bankruptcy</a> was first posted on May 10, 2023 at 7:33 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stablecoin Issuer Tether’s Q1 Profits Surge to $1.5 Billion</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/stablecoin-issuer-tethers-q1-profits-surge-to-1-5-billion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 22:52:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65070</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tether, the dominant player in the stablecoin market, recently released its Q1 2023 financial report, revealing an impressive net profit of $1.5 billion. BDO Italia, an auditing firm, attested to the accuracy of the report, adding credibility to the figures. The reserves report provided a comprehensive breakdown of Tether&#8217;s assets as of March 31, showcasing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/stablecoin-issuer-tethers-q1-profits-surge-to-1-5-billion/">Stablecoin Issuer Tether’s Q1 Profits Surge to $1.5 Billion</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/stablecoin-issuer-tethers-q1-profits-surge-to-1-5-billion/">Stablecoin Issuer Tether’s Q1 Profits Surge to $1.5 Billion</a> was first posted on May 10, 2023 at 6:52 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/tether-predicts-700-million-q1-profit-cto-reveals/">Tether</a>, the dominant player in the stablecoin market, recently <a href="https://tether.to/en/tethers-latest-q1-2023-assurance-report-shows-reserves-surplus-at-all-time-high-of-244b-up-148b-in-net-profit-new-categories-for-additional-transparency-reveals-bitcoin-and-gold-allocations/">released</a> its Q1 2023 financial report, revealing an impressive net profit of $1.5 billion. BDO Italia, an auditing firm, attested to the accuracy of the report, adding credibility to the figures.<br /><br />The reserves report provided a comprehensive breakdown of Tether&#8217;s assets as of March 31, showcasing a significant increase in reserves to $2.44 billion. Notably, the report introduced new asset categories, such as physical gold, diversifying Tether&#8217;s holdings. Additionally, the first quarter witnessed remarkable growth in both profit and token circulation, with a 20% increase.<br /><br />Tether&#8217;s total consolidated assets amounted to a staggering $81.8 billion, with a substantial portion invested in US Treasury bills. In a strategic move to enhance security and liquidity for its users, Tether revealed its plan to reduce reliance on traditional bank deposits and instead engage with the repo market.<br /><br />Paolo Ardoino, the CTO of Tether, expressed satisfaction with the net profits, highlighting how they underscored the platform&#8217;s stability. Ardoino emphasized Tether&#8217;s continuous monitoring of the global economic landscape to safeguard customer funds. However, concerns have been raised by former SEC official John Reed Stark regarding Tether&#8217;s operations.<br /><br />Stark cautioned that an attestation report should not be equated with a conventional financial audit, casting doubt on the financial stability of a firm like Tether that operates without a certified financial audit. He also raised concerns about Tether&#8217;s regulatory status, pointing out its lack of SEC registration and investor protection. Stark&#8217;s remarks highlight the importance of ongoing scrutiny of Tether&#8217;s operations and regulatory compliance.<br /><br />While Tether&#8217;s Q1 performance paints a lucrative picture, the company must address the concerns raised by industry experts and regulatory bodies to ensure transparency and build trust within the crypto community.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/stablecoin-issuer-tethers-q1-profits-surge-to-1-5-billion/">Stablecoin Issuer Tether’s Q1 Profits Surge to $1.5 Billion</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/stablecoin-issuer-tethers-q1-profits-surge-to-1-5-billion/">Stablecoin Issuer Tether’s Q1 Profits Surge to $1.5 Billion</a> was first posted on May 10, 2023 at 6:52 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Transaction Fees Skyrocket to a 2-Year High Amid BRC-20 Memecoin Craze</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-transaction-fees-skyrocket-to-a-2-year-high-amid-brc-20-memecoin-craze/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 22:36:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Transaction Fees]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65068</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Data from ycharts.com shows that the average transaction fee for Bitcoin has spiked to $30.91, a level not seen since April 2021. The period leading up to April 2021 was marked by Bitcoin&#8217;s surge to $64,900, fueled by Coinbase&#8217;s NASDAQ listing and the narrative that crypto was going mainstream. However, this run came to an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-transaction-fees-skyrocket-to-a-2-year-high-amid-brc-20-memecoin-craze/">Bitcoin Transaction Fees Skyrocket to a 2-Year High Amid BRC-20 Memecoin Craze</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-transaction-fees-skyrocket-to-a-2-year-high-amid-brc-20-memecoin-craze/">Bitcoin Transaction Fees Skyrocket to a 2-Year High Amid BRC-20 Memecoin Craze</a> was first posted on May 9, 2023 at 6:36 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Data from <a href="https://ycharts.com/indicators/bitcoin_average_transaction_fee">ycharts.com</a> shows that the average transaction fee for Bitcoin has spiked to $30.91, a level not seen since April 2021. The period leading up to April 2021 was marked by Bitcoin&#8217;s surge to $64,900, fueled by Coinbase&#8217;s NASDAQ listing and the narrative that crypto was going mainstream. <br /><br />However, this run came to an abrupt end when China extended its anti-crypto policy to ban proof-of-work mining and Tesla <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/12/elon-musk-says-tesla-will-stop-accepting-bitcoin-for-car-purchases.html">announced</a> it would stop accepting BTC for vehicle purchases due to environmental concerns.<br /><br />Currently, <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/dogecoin-real-life-currency-or-meme-coin-only/">meme coin</a> mania is driving activity on the Bitcoin network via the recently released BRC-20 standard. BRC-20 was created in March by an anonymous individual known as &#8220;<a href="https://www.makeuseof.com/what-are-bitcoin-brc-20-tokens/">Domo</a>&#8221; and allows fungible assets to operate on the Bitcoin chain. Taproot, launched in November 2021, enabled this by making transactions quicker and more cost-effective, laying the groundwork for smart contracts and dApps. However, this has led to higher transaction fees and chain bloat, as warned by commentators at the time.<br /><br />The top three BRC-20 tokens by market cap are Ordi, Nals, and Pepe, valued at $411.3 million, $42.3 million, and $34.7 million, respectively, according to the <a href="https://brc-20.io/">brc-20.io</a> website. Despite the triviality of some token names, some experts believe that BRC-20 tokens will be a significant factor in driving Bitcoin dominance and rendering Ethereum irrelevant in the next bull market.<br /><br />Willy Woo points out that while there are pros and cons to the current situation, an alternative source of mining revenue is needed to keep miners incentivized as block rewards will be zero one day. However, the trade-off is &#8220;bad for nodes and decentralization,&#8221; especially since the impact of Ordinals is happening at a time when mining rewards are still high.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-transaction-fees-skyrocket-to-a-2-year-high-amid-brc-20-memecoin-craze/">Bitcoin Transaction Fees Skyrocket to a 2-Year High Amid BRC-20 Memecoin Craze</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-transaction-fees-skyrocket-to-a-2-year-high-amid-brc-20-memecoin-craze/">Bitcoin Transaction Fees Skyrocket to a 2-Year High Amid BRC-20 Memecoin Craze</a> was first posted on May 9, 2023 at 6:36 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PayPal Sees Record-High Crypto Deposits, Reaching $943M</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/paypal-sees-record-high-crypto-deposits-reaching-943m/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 22:08:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65060</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>PayPal has announced that it now holds $943 million in customers&#8217; crypto assets, representing a 56% increase from the previous quarter. The company allows users in some regions to buy, hold, sell, and pay for purchases using cryptocurrency. However, PayPal doesn&#8217;t hold any cryptocurrencies on its balance sheet other than those belonging to its customers. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/paypal-sees-record-high-crypto-deposits-reaching-943m/">PayPal Sees Record-High Crypto Deposits, Reaching $943M</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/paypal-sees-record-high-crypto-deposits-reaching-943m/">PayPal Sees Record-High Crypto Deposits, Reaching $943M</a> was first posted on May 9, 2023 at 6:08 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/paypals-crypto-cache-surges-to-604-million-by-2022-end/">PayPal</a> has announced that it now holds $943 million in customers&#8217; crypto assets, representing a 56% increase from the previous quarter. The company allows users in some regions to buy, hold, sell, and pay for purchases using cryptocurrency. However, PayPal doesn&#8217;t hold any cryptocurrencies on its balance sheet other than those belonging to its customers.<br /><br />According to the latest Q1 2023<a href="https://d18rn0p25nwr6d.cloudfront.net/CIK-0001633917/195d9afa-779f-4932-b227-90f0a170923e.pdf"> Form 10-Q SEC filing,</a> customers&#8217; crypto deposits surged from $604 million in the prior quarter to $943 million as of March 31. Bitcoin was the most popular cryptocurrency in terms of current holdings and quarter-over-quarter percentage increase, spiking 71% to just short of half a billion dollars. Ethereum, the second-most held cryptocurrency, saw a 45% increase in deposits, while &#8220;Other,&#8221; consisting of Bitcoin Cash and Litecoin, saw gains of plus 30%.<br /><br />PayPal noted that accounting for cryptocurrency involves several risks, including technological, legal, and regulatory risks, which is why crypto assets are recorded as both a liability and an asset on their books.<br /><br />Although the total crypto market experienced a significant increase of 49%, rising from $796 billion on December 31, 2022, to $1,183 billion on March 31, 2023, the exact <a href="https://investor.pypl.com/financials/sec-filings/default.aspx">breakdown</a> of PayPal customers&#8217; holdings is unclear. <br /><br />Therefore, it is uncertain precisely how much of the 56% quarter-over-quarter increase in deposits relates to increased crypto holdings or the increase in dollar value over that period. However, the majority of the increase likely relates to an increase in the dollar value of holdings rather than a jump in customers&#8217; deposits.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/paypal-sees-record-high-crypto-deposits-reaching-943m/">PayPal Sees Record-High Crypto Deposits, Reaching $943M</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/paypal-sees-record-high-crypto-deposits-reaching-943m/">PayPal Sees Record-High Crypto Deposits, Reaching $943M</a> was first posted on May 9, 2023 at 6:08 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			<enclosure length="1014417" type="application/pdf" url="https://d18rn0p25nwr6d.cloudfront.net/CIK-0001633917/195d9afa-779f-4932-b227-90f0a170923e.pdf"/><itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><itunes:subtitle>PayPal has announced that it now holds $943 million in customers&amp;#8217; crypto assets, representing a 56% increase from the previous quarter. The company allows users in some regions to buy, hold, sell, and pay for purchases using cryptocurrency. However, PayPal doesn&amp;#8217;t hold any cryptocurrencies on its balance sheet other than those belonging to its customers. [&amp;#8230;] The post PayPal Sees Record-High Crypto Deposits, Reaching $943M appeared first on Latest Crypto News. PayPal Sees Record-High Crypto Deposits, Reaching $943M was first posted on May 9, 2023 at 6:08 pm. &amp;copy;2021 &amp;quot;Latest Crypto News&amp;quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at info@kryptomoney.com</itunes:subtitle><itunes:summary>PayPal has announced that it now holds $943 million in customers&amp;#8217; crypto assets, representing a 56% increase from the previous quarter. The company allows users in some regions to buy, hold, sell, and pay for purchases using cryptocurrency. However, PayPal doesn&amp;#8217;t hold any cryptocurrencies on its balance sheet other than those belonging to its customers. [&amp;#8230;] The post PayPal Sees Record-High Crypto Deposits, Reaching $943M appeared first on Latest Crypto News. PayPal Sees Record-High Crypto Deposits, Reaching $943M was first posted on May 9, 2023 at 6:08 pm. &amp;copy;2021 &amp;quot;Latest Crypto News&amp;quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at info@kryptomoney.com</itunes:summary><itunes:keywords>News, Crypto Adoption, paypal</itunes:keywords></item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Might Be Accepted as Payment Option for Government Services in Liechtenstein – PM</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-might-be-accepted-as-payment-option-for-government-services-in-liechtenstein-pm/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 23:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65057</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Liechtenstein&#8217;s Prime Minister, Daniel Risch, has announced plans to enable Bitcoin payments for various government services. While he did not disclose whether the country plans to adopt the cryptocurrency as legal tender, citizens will be allowed to settle government services in Bitcoin, with the option for authorities to swap the crypto assets for Swiss francs. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-might-be-accepted-as-payment-option-for-government-services-in-liechtenstein-pm/">Bitcoin Might Be Accepted as Payment Option for Government Services in Liechtenstein – PM</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-might-be-accepted-as-payment-option-for-government-services-in-liechtenstein-pm/">Bitcoin Might Be Accepted as Payment Option for Government Services in Liechtenstein – PM</a> was first posted on May 8, 2023 at 7:59 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Liechtenstein&#8217;s Prime Minister, Daniel Risch, has <a href="https://www.handelsblatt.com/politik/international/kryptowaehrung-liechtenstein-will-staatliche-dienstleistungen-kuenftig-auch-in-bitcoin-bezahlen-lassen/29134712.html">announced</a> plans to enable Bitcoin payments for various government services. While he did not disclose whether the country plans to adopt the cryptocurrency as legal tender, citizens will be allowed to settle government services in Bitcoin, with the option for authorities to swap the crypto assets for Swiss francs. <br /><br />This move<a href="https://www.liechtensteinusa.org/article/liechtensteins-parliament-approves-blockchain-act-unanimously"> follows</a> the passage of the <em>&#8220;Blockchain Act,&#8221;</em> which set clear standards in the sector and provided maximum protection to users. Additionally, Liechtenstein&#8217;s leading private bank, LGT Bank, partnered with SEBA Bank in 2022 to enable direct investments in digital currencies for its clients.<br /><br />Switzerland&#8217;s city of Lugano, Liechtenstein&#8217;s western neighbor, has also made moves toward adopting cryptocurrencies. The domestic authorities have developed an infrastructure to make Bitcoin, Tether, and LVGA tokens official means of settlement in the region. This initiative, called PlanB, aims to enable locals to pay taxes or public service fees via the aforementioned assets. <br /><br /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/tether-utilized-signature-bank-to-gain-access-to-us-financial-market/">Tether</a> outlined in March this year that the initiative has been quite successful during the first year of its existence, with more than 150 domestic merchants accepting BTC, USDT, and LVGA as payment methods, while the total number could surpass 2,500 by the end of 2023.<br /><br />The move towards cryptocurrencies in Liechtenstein and Switzerland highlights the increasing acceptance and mainstream adoption of digital assets worldwide. However, it remains to be seen if Liechtenstein will follow in the footsteps of El Salvador and the Central African Republic and adopt BTC as legal tender.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-might-be-accepted-as-payment-option-for-government-services-in-liechtenstein-pm/">Bitcoin Might Be Accepted as Payment Option for Government Services in Liechtenstein – PM</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-might-be-accepted-as-payment-option-for-government-services-in-liechtenstein-pm/">Bitcoin Might Be Accepted as Payment Option for Government Services in Liechtenstein – PM</a> was first posted on May 8, 2023 at 7:59 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Anticipates $200M Price Tag for SEC Lawsuit, Eyes Dubai Expansion</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/ripple-anticipates-200m-price-tag-for-sec-lawsuit-eyes-dubai-expansion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 23:09:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65053</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>According to a CNBC report on May 8, Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse discussed the regulatory hurdles his company is facing during the Dubai Fintech Summit. Garlinghouse revealed that Ripple has spent a whopping $200 million defending itself against the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) lawsuit, which he claims &#8220;doesn&#8217;t make a lot of sense&#8221; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/ripple-anticipates-200m-price-tag-for-sec-lawsuit-eyes-dubai-expansion/">Ripple Anticipates $200M Price Tag for SEC Lawsuit, Eyes Dubai Expansion</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ripple-anticipates-200m-price-tag-for-sec-lawsuit-eyes-dubai-expansion/">Ripple Anticipates $200M Price Tag for SEC Lawsuit, Eyes Dubai Expansion</a> was first posted on May 8, 2023 at 7:09 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>According to a <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/08/ripple-will-have-spent-200-million-fighting-sec-lawsuit-ceo-says.html">CNBC report</a> on May 8, Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse discussed the regulatory hurdles his company is facing during the Dubai Fintech Summit. <br /><br />Garlinghouse revealed that <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ripple-president-responds-to-multibillion-dollar-win-in-crucial-market/">Ripple</a> has spent a whopping $200 million defending itself against the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) lawsuit, which he claims &#8220;doesn&#8217;t make a lot of sense&#8221; from its inception. <br /><br />This was the first time Garlinghouse has publicly disclosed the cost of the legal conflict, and he argues that the U.S. is<em> &#8220;definitely stuck&#8221;</em> when it comes to regulation.<br /><br />In response to the regulatory landscape in the U.S., Garlinghouse announced via <a href="https://twitter.com/bgarlinghouse/status/1655563716795170818">Twitter</a> that Ripple plans to expand to Dubai. He highlighted that the MENA region, where 20% of Ripple&#8217;s customers are based, has<em> &#8220;clear regulatory regimes&#8221;</em> and is on its way to becoming a global financial hub.<br /><br />Ripple has been facing regulatory challenges since December 2020, when the SEC accused Ripple and its executives of breaching securities regulations by selling XRP tokens.<br /><br />Ripple isn&#8217;t the only company attempting to challenge the SEC, with cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase also preparing to take on the regulator after receiving a Wells notice. It remains unclear whether Ripple&#8217;s or Coinbase&#8217;s challenge will succeed.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/ripple-anticipates-200m-price-tag-for-sec-lawsuit-eyes-dubai-expansion/">Ripple Anticipates $200M Price Tag for SEC Lawsuit, Eyes Dubai Expansion</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ripple-anticipates-200m-price-tag-for-sec-lawsuit-eyes-dubai-expansion/">Ripple Anticipates $200M Price Tag for SEC Lawsuit, Eyes Dubai Expansion</a> was first posted on May 8, 2023 at 7:09 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>