<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>Latest Crypto News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://kryptomoney.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<description>Latest Crypto News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 23:00:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/cropped-cropped-favicon_512x512_v2-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Latest Crypto News</title>
	<link>https://kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><itunes:subtitle>Latest Crypto News</itunes:subtitle><itunes:category text="News &amp; Politics"/><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Business News"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Investing"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Tech News"/></itunes:category><item>
		<title>Three Catalysts That Might Propel SHIB in 2023; Helium Migrating to Solana in Q1 Next Year</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/three-catalysts-that-might-propel-shib-in-2023-helium-migrating-to-solana-in-q1-next-year/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 23:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Helium (HNT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBA INU (SHIB)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana (SOL)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63524</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>According to Coinswitch analysts, Shiba Inu (SHIB) might have three secret moves up its sleeve. This might suggest the presence of catalysts that might propel it higher come 2023. First is its growing address list. Analysts at Coinswitch note that addresses holding SHIB tokens have peaked over the past 30 days, indicating constant accumulation. Second, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/three-catalysts-that-might-propel-shib-in-2023-helium-migrating-to-solana-in-q1-next-year/">Three Catalysts That Might Propel SHIB in 2023; Helium Migrating to Solana in Q1 Next Year</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/three-catalysts-that-might-propel-shib-in-2023-helium-migrating-to-solana-in-q1-next-year/">Three Catalysts That Might Propel SHIB in 2023; Helium Migrating to Solana in Q1 Next Year</a> was first posted on December 15, 2022 at 6:00 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>According to Coinswitch analysts, Shiba Inu (SHIB) might have three secret moves up its sleeve. This might suggest the presence of catalysts that might propel it higher come 2023.<br /><br />First is its growing address list. Analysts at Coinswitch note that addresses holding SHIB tokens have peaked over the past 30 days, indicating constant accumulation.<br /><br />Second, SHIB has a low MVRV. The term MVRV refers to the ratio of market capitalization to realized capitalization. Simply put, if the realized capitalization is higher than the market capitalization, the price action of an asset can see a surge.<br /><br />The third is increasing whale movements. Large SHIB-specific transactions have started looking up over the past week or so. The surge in whale activity might be a positive thing, as in the case of SHIB, whales hold almost 70% of the token supply.<br /><br />Shiba Inu adoption, which has experienced noticeable growth since 2022, might sustain this in the forthcoming year. Through Binance Pay&#8217;s partnership with leading Bahraini payment provider EazyPay, STC customers can now pay their phone bills with Shiba Inu.<br /><br />STC Bahrain has become the first telecom operator in Bahrain to expand its payment options amid the partnership to meet the growing demand for easy-to-use crypto payments. Also, the collaboration indicates Bahrain’s commitment to advancing the country’s fintech landscape.<br /><br />Likewise, the growing trend of listings might continue. Crypto exchange, Huobi Global sparked speculations about the potential listing of Shiba Inu’s ecosystem token, Bone ShibaSwap (BONE), as it recently posted a tweet containing a picture of a cute Shiba Inu dog wearing a Santa dress with a blurry Christmas tree in the background. The caption reads “Huobi (handshake) Christmas.”</p>
<h2>Helium Migrating to Solana in Q1 Next Year</h2>
<p>Helium is migrating onto the Solana blockchain by Q1 2023, the team revealed in a recent tweet. Helium hotspots will each be represented by an NFT on Solana, creating almost 1 million new Solana NFTs.<br /><br />In September, the Helium core developer team released a proposal (HIP 70) to greatly increase the operating efficiency of the Helium blockchain.<br /><br />To do this, the core developer team suggested shifting data transfer accounting and proof-of-coverage (“PoC”) to Oracles, which streamlines the system architecture and enables the use of a more scalable Layer 1 (“L1”), notably Solana. By utilizing the extensive selection of composable Solana developer tools, features, and applications, such a shift would result in significant economies of scale, as stated by the team.<br /><br />With almost a million hotspots installed worldwide and increased data throughput thanks to an ever-growing number of use cases, the Helium Network has experienced phenomenal growth.<br /><br />During the cryptocurrency run-up of last year, investors who had been mostly focused on Ethereum started diversifying into Solana and other alternative blockchains.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/three-catalysts-that-might-propel-shib-in-2023-helium-migrating-to-solana-in-q1-next-year/">Three Catalysts That Might Propel SHIB in 2023; Helium Migrating to Solana in Q1 Next Year</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/three-catalysts-that-might-propel-shib-in-2023-helium-migrating-to-solana-in-q1-next-year/">Three Catalysts That Might Propel SHIB in 2023; Helium Migrating to Solana in Q1 Next Year</a> was first posted on December 15, 2022 at 6:00 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase To Recover Any ERC-20 Tokens Sent Inadvertently</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-to-recover-any-erc-20-tokens-sent-inadvertently/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 22:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ERC-20 Token]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63527</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase, the largest cryptocurrency exchange in the United States, has launched an asset recovery tool that will allow users to recover over 4000 unsupported ERC-20 tokens that were accidentally sent to the exchange. Non-supported assets will be returned to user addresses in exchange for a small fee. The tool only needs the Ethereum transaction ID [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-to-recover-any-erc-20-tokens-sent-inadvertently/">Coinbase To Recover Any ERC-20 Tokens Sent Inadvertently</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-to-recover-any-erc-20-tokens-sent-inadvertently/">Coinbase To Recover Any ERC-20 Tokens Sent Inadvertently</a> was first posted on December 15, 2022 at 5:32 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-reveals-over-33000000000-worth-of-bitcoin-in-its-reserves/">Coinbase</a>, the largest cryptocurrency exchange in the United States, has launched an asset recovery tool that will allow users to recover over 4000 unsupported ERC-20 tokens that were accidentally sent to the exchange. Non-supported assets will be returned to user addresses in exchange for a small fee.<br /><br />The tool only needs the Ethereum transaction ID of the lost funds and the incorrect Coinbase address where the tokens were sent, according to a <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/coinbase-announces-new-asset-recovery-tool-for-erc-20-tokens">blog post</a> from Coinbase on Thursday. At no point does it reveal any user&#8217;s private keys.</p>
<blockquote>
<p><em>“We did this by using patent-pending technology to send the funds directly from your inbound address without processing the funds through our centralized exchange infrastructure,”</em> said the company.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Only a few ERC-20 tokens, such as wETH, TUSD, and STETH, are eligible for recovery. Each eligible asset must pass the listing review process at Coinbase.<br /><br />The first significant exchange to permit <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/erc-20-tokens-protocol-explained/">ERC-20 token</a> recoveries at scale while upholding the security of its users&#8217; deposit addresses is Coinbase, which claims to be true. According to its website, <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/faq/frequently-asked-questions-on-incorrect-deposits-115003798632">Binance</a> does not provide the same service, but it may offer customized assistance to users who have lost &#8220;significant funds&#8221; as a result of unintentional transfers.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>“We’re reducing the points of friction and focusing on improving usability to better serve and earn the trust of our customers,” added Coinbase.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The service is still not available in Japan, nor for Coinbase Prime.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-to-recover-any-erc-20-tokens-sent-inadvertently/">Coinbase To Recover Any ERC-20 Tokens Sent Inadvertently</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/coinbase-to-recover-any-erc-20-tokens-sent-inadvertently/">Coinbase To Recover Any ERC-20 Tokens Sent Inadvertently</a> was first posted on December 15, 2022 at 5:32 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Microsoft Subtly Prohibits Crypto Mining From Cloud Services</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/microsoft-subtly-prohibits-crypto-mining-from-cloud-services/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 22:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MICROSOFT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63515</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>To maintain its cloud services, Microsoft&#8217;s updated terms restrict access to Bitcoin and crypto mining. Any users who intend to do so now must receive pre-written approval from the company. In an attempt to maintain its cloud services, Microsoft&#8217;s updated terms are restricting access to Bitcoin and crypto mining. Any users who intend to do [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/microsoft-subtly-prohibits-crypto-mining-from-cloud-services/">Microsoft Subtly Prohibits Crypto Mining From Cloud Services</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/microsoft-subtly-prohibits-crypto-mining-from-cloud-services/">Microsoft Subtly Prohibits Crypto Mining From Cloud Services</a> was first posted on December 15, 2022 at 5:06 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>To maintain its cloud services,<a href="https://www.microsoft.com/licensing/terms/product/changes/MCA"> Microsoft&#8217;s updated terms</a> restrict access to Bitcoin and crypto mining. Any users who intend to do so now must receive pre-written approval from the company.<br /><br />In an attempt to maintain its cloud services, Microsoft&#8217;s updated terms are restricting access to Bitcoin and crypto mining. Any users who intend to do so now must receive pre-written approval from the company.<br /><br /><em>“We suggest seeking written pre-approval from Microsoft before using Microsoft Online Services for mining cryptocurrencies, regardless of the term of a subscription,”</em> it added. <br /><br />Microsoft has claimed that crypto mining can <em>&#8220;cause disruption or even impairment to online services,&#8221;</em> according to the British tech site <a href="https://www.theregister.com/2022/12/15/microsoft_online_services_cryptomining_ban/#:~:text=Updated%20Microsoft%20has%20quietly%20banned,into%20effect%20on%20December%201.">The Register</a>. Furthermore, its users are frequently associated with<em> &#8220;cyber fraud&#8221;</em> and <em>&#8220;abuse attacks,&#8221;</em> which involve the unauthorized use of customer resources.<br /><br /><em>&#8220;We made this change to further protect our customers and reduce the risk of disrupting or impairing Microsoft Cloud,&#8221;</em> the company said. One scenario in which it may allow a customer to mine is for testing and research purposes. <br /><br />Google Cloud also prohibited the use of its servers for crypto mining without written permission, whereas Oracle and OVH outright prohibited it. Amazon Web Services (AWS), on the other hand, only allows crypto mining within its paid tiers.<br /><br /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-announces-500-million-fund-to-lend-to-bitcoin-miners/">Miners</a> have been struggling to stay afloat in recent months due to Bitcoin&#8217;s increasing difficulty adjustment and collapsing price. North Computer has already declared bankruptcy, and companies such as Iris Energy and Argo Blockchain have stated that they will be unable to make their interest payments.<br /><br />Core Scientific was in a similar situation in October, but has since agreed to restructure its debt with B.Riley, receiving a $72 million loan from the company.<br /><br />Many private companies have taken issue with crypto mining over its energy footprint, prompting them to disassociate from the industry. Mozilla, for example, stopped accepting donations from Proof of Work-based cryptos in January.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/microsoft-subtly-prohibits-crypto-mining-from-cloud-services/">Microsoft Subtly Prohibits Crypto Mining From Cloud Services</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/microsoft-subtly-prohibits-crypto-mining-from-cloud-services/">Microsoft Subtly Prohibits Crypto Mining From Cloud Services</a> was first posted on December 15, 2022 at 5:06 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>40,700 BTC Settle in Whales’ Wallets in Anticipation of End of Year Move; J.P.Morgan Predicts Big Catalyst for ETH Price</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/40700-btc-settle-in-whales-wallets-in-anticipation-of-end-of-year-move-j-p-morgan-predicts-big-catalyst-for-eth-price/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 21:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance USD (BUSD)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Price Prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63519</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Market observers expect the cryptocurrency market to pick up in 2023 after a brutal year that saw bitcoin sink around 75% from its all-time high in November last year. Bitcoin appears to be preparing for this major move, as Santiment, an Onchain analytics firm, has noticed an interesting trend in Bitcoin whale accumulation. Santiment observed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/40700-btc-settle-in-whales-wallets-in-anticipation-of-end-of-year-move-j-p-morgan-predicts-big-catalyst-for-eth-price/">40,700 BTC Settle in Whales’ Wallets in Anticipation of End of Year Move; J.P.Morgan Predicts Big Catalyst for ETH Price</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/40700-btc-settle-in-whales-wallets-in-anticipation-of-end-of-year-move-j-p-morgan-predicts-big-catalyst-for-eth-price/">40,700 BTC Settle in Whales’ Wallets in Anticipation of End of Year Move; J.P.Morgan Predicts Big Catalyst for ETH Price</a> was first posted on December 15, 2022 at 4:37 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Market observers expect the cryptocurrency market to pick up in 2023 after a brutal year that saw bitcoin sink around 75% from its all-time high in November last year. Bitcoin appears to be preparing for this major move, as Santiment, an Onchain analytics firm, has noticed an interesting trend in Bitcoin whale accumulation.<br /><br />Santiment observed that Bitcoin&#8217;s whales have been reducing their supply held and dumping in profit-taking after the 2020 to 2021 bull run for approximately 14 months. Prices have been falling in tandem with these dump-offs.<br /><br />However, there has been a recent improvement. Not necessarily in terms of prices, but at least in terms of whales finally accumulating rather than dumping. Santiment observes that the largest streak of new BTC whale addresses has been created in 10 months.<br /><br />159 new addresses holding between 100 and 10,000 bitcoins have been created in just three weeks. This is the fastest growth of these addresses in 10 months, Santiment observes. The number of BTC whale addresses holding 100 to 10,000 BTC is now 15,848.<br /><br />But additionally, 40,747 more bitcoins worth $726 million have collectively entered key whale wallets in just the past 9 days.<br /><br />Also, Tether&#8217;s key addresses have collectively accumulated $817.5 million more in buying power in just the past three days, a 7% increase from what they were holding before the start of the week. Binance USD&#8217;s key addresses have also collectively accumulated $104.9 million more in buying power in the same timeframe. This represents a 9% increase.</p>
<h2>J.P.Morgan predicts big catalyst for ETH price</h2>
<p>The Ethereum merge occurred in mid-September and ushered in a transition to a proof-of-stake mechanism for the second-largest cryptocurrency. JP Morgan&#8217;s analysts believe this and an upcoming upgrade might be a catalyst for Ethereum&#8217;s price.<br /><br />&#8220;We believe that the Ethereum Merge and really the Ethereum Surge could be a big factor in terms of increasing the use-cases for blockchain into new areas, including financial services,&#8221; JP Morgan analysts wrote in an early December note.<br /><br />The Surge, an upcoming upgrade, might reduce costs, make the ETH network safer, and process transactions faster.<br /><br />&#8220;We continue to see the Ethereum Surge as a catalyst for development in the cryptocurrency markets, which appears at least 6-12 months away.&#8221;</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/40700-btc-settle-in-whales-wallets-in-anticipation-of-end-of-year-move-j-p-morgan-predicts-big-catalyst-for-eth-price/">40,700 BTC Settle in Whales’ Wallets in Anticipation of End of Year Move; J.P.Morgan Predicts Big Catalyst for ETH Price</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/40700-btc-settle-in-whales-wallets-in-anticipation-of-end-of-year-move-j-p-morgan-predicts-big-catalyst-for-eth-price/">40,700 BTC Settle in Whales’ Wallets in Anticipation of End of Year Move; J.P.Morgan Predicts Big Catalyst for ETH Price</a> was first posted on December 15, 2022 at 4:37 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LTC Price Analysis: How Far Will Rapid Whale Accumulation Take LTC Price? Litecoin Ranks Top Payment Option on BitPay</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/ltc-price-analysis-how-far-will-rapid-whale-accumulation-take-ltc-price-litecoin-ranks-top-payment-option-on-bitpay/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 23:45:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin (LTC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC/USD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC/USD Price Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63497</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin (LTC) is up 1.74% at $75.42 as the crypto market rebounded Millionaire LTC whales upped their supply held from 11.3% to 15.6%. BitPay reports that Litecoin (LTC) has gained significant traction as a go-to coin for purchases Litecoin (LTC) is up 1.74% at $75.42 as the crypto market rebounded following lower-than-expected CPI data. Litecoin [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/ltc-price-analysis-how-far-will-rapid-whale-accumulation-take-ltc-price-litecoin-ranks-top-payment-option-on-bitpay/">LTC Price Analysis: How Far Will Rapid Whale Accumulation Take LTC Price? Litecoin Ranks Top Payment Option on BitPay</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ltc-price-analysis-how-far-will-rapid-whale-accumulation-take-ltc-price-litecoin-ranks-top-payment-option-on-bitpay/">LTC Price Analysis: How Far Will Rapid Whale Accumulation Take LTC Price? Litecoin Ranks Top Payment Option on BitPay</a> was first posted on December 14, 2022 at 6:45 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li>Litecoin (LTC) is up 1.74% at $75.42 as the crypto market rebounded</li>
<li>Millionaire LTC whales upped their supply held from 11.3% to 15.6%.</li>
<li>BitPay reports that Litecoin (LTC) has gained significant traction as a go-to coin for purchases</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/litecoin-ltc-surges-past-220-why-the-altcoin-market-may-just-be-starting-the-new-bull-cycle/">Litecoin (LTC)</a> is up 1.74% at $75.42 as the crypto market rebounded following lower-than-expected CPI data. Litecoin has been on quite an independent run over the past month as Bitcoin and Ethereum have trodden water. According to Onchain analytics firm, Santiment, large whales holding between 1 million to 10 million LTC have increased coincidentally with LTC price against BTC over the past year. Just about 5 weeks ago, these addresses rapidly upped their supply held from 11.3% to 15.6%. Crypto payments processor, BitPay reports that Litecoin (LTC) has gained significant traction as a go-to coin for purchases at leading electronics, video games, gold and jewelry, and other eCommerce websites. BitPay began supporting Litecoin in June 2021 to fanfare from merchants and the Litecoin community. In just one year, monthly Litecoin payments increased by 109%. The<em> &#8220;digital silver&#8221;</em> also makes up over 25% of all cryptocurrency payments processed by BitPay.<br /><br /><strong>Key Levels</strong><br />Resistance Levels: $105.00, $95.00, $85.00<br />Support Levels: $75.00, $65.00, $55.00</p>
<h4>LTC/USD Daily Chart: Ranging</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1436" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-63520 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LTCUSD-Daily-Dec-15.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LTCUSD-Daily-Dec-15.png 1436w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LTCUSD-Daily-Dec-15-300x144.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LTCUSD-Daily-Dec-15-1024x491.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LTCUSD-Daily-Dec-15-768x368.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LTCUSD-Daily-Dec-15-750x359.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LTCUSD-Daily-Dec-15-1140x546.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1436px) 100vw, 1436px" /><span style="color: #999999">LTC/USD Daily Chart</span></h6>
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ltc-price-analysis-here-are-key-levels-to-watch-on-price-litecoin-processes-33-million-transactions-in-11-years-of-existence/">LTC/USD</a> pivoted at $75.00 before entering what appears to be a sideways market. Resistance was met near $85.00, forcing the pair to reverse lower. On Wednesday, LTC hit intraday lows of $74.18, extending the previous day&#8217;s losses. The RSI also losing traction towards the mid-level of 50. <br /><br />If prices continue to fall, support should come from the $65.00 level before falling further to the $60.00 level. Should an upside reversal occur, immediate resistance would most likely come from the horizontal level of $85.00. A break above these levels could propel the LTC/USD pair to $95.00, and even higher.</p>
<h4>LTC/USD 4-Hour Chart: Ranging</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1436" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-63521 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LTCUSD-Daily-Dec-15-1.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LTCUSD-Daily-Dec-15-1.png 1436w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LTCUSD-Daily-Dec-15-1-300x144.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LTCUSD-Daily-Dec-15-1-1024x491.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LTCUSD-Daily-Dec-15-1-768x368.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LTCUSD-Daily-Dec-15-1-750x359.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LTCUSD-Daily-Dec-15-1-1140x546.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1436px) 100vw, 1436px" /><span style="color: #999999">LTC/USD 4-Hour Chart</span></h6>
<p>LTC is still oscillating around the MA 50 ($75.00) and needs to stay above $77.00 to keep the chances of reaching the horizontal barrier ($85.00) on the upside. Meanwhile, bears are eyeing the MA 200 support at $71.50, a breach of which would risk a move toward the next key level at $60.00. The momentum indicators show a neutral to negative bias, with the RSI falling below the 50 mark.<br /><br />If the price moves above the MA 50 ($75.00), the $85.00 resistance could act as a barrier before it can challenge the $90.00 and then $95.00 levels. A break above this level would change the outlook to bullish, as it would take the pair to a yearly high of $153.91, which was reached in January 2022.</p>
<p><strong>Note:</strong><em> Kryptomoney.com is not a financial advisor. Do your research before investing your funds in any financial asset or presented product or event. We are not responsible for your investing results</em></p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/ltc-price-analysis-how-far-will-rapid-whale-accumulation-take-ltc-price-litecoin-ranks-top-payment-option-on-bitpay/">LTC Price Analysis: How Far Will Rapid Whale Accumulation Take LTC Price? Litecoin Ranks Top Payment Option on BitPay</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ltc-price-analysis-how-far-will-rapid-whale-accumulation-take-ltc-price-litecoin-ranks-top-payment-option-on-bitpay/">LTC Price Analysis: How Far Will Rapid Whale Accumulation Take LTC Price? Litecoin Ranks Top Payment Option on BitPay</a> was first posted on December 14, 2022 at 6:45 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Margin Trading Banned by Canadian Securities Regulators</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-margin-trading-banned-by-canadian-securities-regulators/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 22:54:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[margin trading]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63511</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto trading platforms in Canada are no longer permitted to provide leverage to their clients and must instead segregate their assets with a qualified custodian. The collapse of FTX has prompted global regulators to take action against the crypto industry, and the Canadian Securities Administrators (CSA) are no exception. The association announced an expanded set [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-margin-trading-banned-by-canadian-securities-regulators/">Crypto Margin Trading Banned by Canadian Securities Regulators</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-margin-trading-banned-by-canadian-securities-regulators/">Crypto Margin Trading Banned by Canadian Securities Regulators</a> was first posted on December 14, 2022 at 5:54 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Crypto trading platforms in Canada are no longer permitted to provide leverage to their clients and must instead segregate their assets with a qualified custodian. The <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/amazon-to-produce-tv-show-about-ftx-collapse-details/">collapse of FTX</a> has prompted global regulators to take action against the crypto industry, and the Canadian Securities Administrators (CSA) are no exception.<br /><br />The association <a href="https://www.osc.ca/en/news-events/news/csa-provides-update-crypto-trading-platforms-operating-canada">announced</a> an expanded set of rules for crypto trading platforms in Canada on Monday, prohibiting them from offering margin or leveraged trading to Canadian clients. According to the regulator&#8217;s announcement on Wednesday, the new rules will apply to any platform in the country subject to securities legislation, including cryptocurrency trading platforms that have yet to register.<br /><br />Unregistered platforms will soon face a deadline for submitting a pre-registration undertaking (PRU) to their principal regulator, in which they promise to comply with the requirements expected of already registered entities. If they do not, they may face legal action.<br /><br />The expanded terms for compliant platforms include obligations to keep Canadian clients&#8217; assets with an <em>&#8220;appropriate custodian&#8221;</em> and to keep those assets separate from the company&#8217;s proprietary business. They also prohibit <em>“offering margin or leverage to any Canadian client.”</em></p>
<blockquote>
<p><em>“Custodians will generally be considered qualified if they are regulated by a financial regulator in Canada, the U.S., or a similar jurisdiction with a supervisory regime for conduct and financial regulation,”</em> read the regulator’s statement.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Though the regulator did not name FTX, it is widely assumed that custodial and margin trading issues were major contributors to the exchange&#8217;s demise. Under oath on Tuesday, bankruptcy lawyer John Ray claimed that FTX commingled client assets with Alameda Research, where they were traded and lost on margin.<br /><br />Several crypto firms, including Celsius, Voyager, and BlockFi, have gone bankrupt this year after using client assets to margin trade, contributing to some larger-than-expected losses in the crypto market.<br /><br />The CSA also stated that stablecoins, which are tokens with prices tied to fiat currencies such as USDC and USDT, are regarded as securities by the regulator.</p>
<blockquote>
<p><em>“Crypto trading platforms… are reminded that they are prohibited from permitting Canadian clients to trade, or obtain exposure to, any crypto asset that is itself a security and/or a derivative,”</em> it stated.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-margin-trading-banned-by-canadian-securities-regulators/">Crypto Margin Trading Banned by Canadian Securities Regulators</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-margin-trading-banned-by-canadian-securities-regulators/">Crypto Margin Trading Banned by Canadian Securities Regulators</a> was first posted on December 14, 2022 at 5:54 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PayPal Teams Up With Cryptocurrency Wallet MetaMask</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/paypal-teams-up-with-cryptocurrency-wallet-metamask/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 22:28:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Metamask]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63507</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Two of the industry&#8217;s biggest names are collaborating to make purchasing cryptocurrencies even easier. According to the news, PayPal is collaborating with cryptocurrency wallet MetaMask to develop a new and more efficient cryptocurrency purchasing experience. Per the announcement, the two entities are looking into different options for users to transfer their digital assets. The two [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/paypal-teams-up-with-cryptocurrency-wallet-metamask/">PayPal Teams Up With Cryptocurrency Wallet MetaMask</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/paypal-teams-up-with-cryptocurrency-wallet-metamask/">PayPal Teams Up With Cryptocurrency Wallet MetaMask</a> was first posted on December 14, 2022 at 5:28 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Two of the industry&#8217;s biggest names are collaborating to make purchasing cryptocurrencies even easier. According to the <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2022/12/14/paypal-partners-with-crypto-wallet-metamask-to-offer-easy-way-to-buy-crypto/">news</a>, PayPal is collaborating with cryptocurrency wallet MetaMask to develop a new and more efficient cryptocurrency purchasing experience.<br /><br />Per the announcement, the two entities are looking into different options for users to transfer their digital assets. The two companies announced their collaboration today in a press release, according to the news.<br /><br />The collaboration between PayPal and MetaMask is fantastic news for users looking for a simpler way to purchase cryptocurrencies. The collaboration was formed with the intention of supporting a simpler and more mainstream approach for PayPal users who want to enter the industry.<br /><br />According to the press release,<a href="https://kryptomoney.com/metamask-integrates-with-bitfinex-pay-to-further-serve-growing-demand-for-crypto-payments/"> MetaMask</a> developer ConsenSys plans to allow users to choose PayPal as a payment option when purchasing Ethereum through the MetaMask platform. Furthermore, this advancement incorporates a seamless transfer of digital assets between the two platforms.<br /><br />The application has features that are similar to those found on popular platforms such as Etsy and eBay. Furthermore, this replicates the checkout feature, which allows customers to pay with their PayPal account. The same will now be true when purchasing cryptocurrency through MetaMask.<br /><br />Lorenzo Santos, MetaMask product manager, stated that this development will benefit customers by introducing them to Web3. <em>&#8220;With this integration with PayPal, our US users will be able to not only buy cryptocurrency seamlessly through MetaMask, but also easily explore the Web3 ecosystem,&#8221;</em> Santos explained.<br /><br />The development represents yet another moment of acceptance for PayPal and cryptocurrency. The collaboration continues the integration of digital assets, which has been a focus of the financial firm since 2020.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/paypal-teams-up-with-cryptocurrency-wallet-metamask/">PayPal Teams Up With Cryptocurrency Wallet MetaMask</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/paypal-teams-up-with-cryptocurrency-wallet-metamask/">PayPal Teams Up With Cryptocurrency Wallet MetaMask</a> was first posted on December 14, 2022 at 5:28 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Sam Bankman-Fried Charged With Eight Criminal Offenses</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/ftx-sam-bankman-fried-charged-with-eight-criminal-offenses/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 22:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63503</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Prosecutors in the United States charged ex-FTX CEO and founder Sam Bankman-Fried with eight criminal counts today, including wire fraud and conspiracy to commit money laundering. The disgraced crypto mogul was arrested yesterday in the Bahamas at the request of US authorities seeking his extradition. Bankman-Fried is charged by the US Attorney&#8217;s Office for the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/ftx-sam-bankman-fried-charged-with-eight-criminal-offenses/">FTX Sam Bankman-Fried Charged With Eight Criminal Offenses</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ftx-sam-bankman-fried-charged-with-eight-criminal-offenses/">FTX Sam Bankman-Fried Charged With Eight Criminal Offenses</a> was first posted on December 13, 2022 at 5:22 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Prosecutors in the United States charged ex-FTX CEO and founder <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ftx-sam-bankman-fried-transferred-assets-to-bahamas-government-after-bankruptcy/">Sam Bankman-Fried</a> with eight criminal counts today, including wire fraud and conspiracy to commit money laundering.<br /><br />The disgraced crypto mogul was arrested yesterday in the Bahamas at the request of US authorities seeking his extradition.<br /><br />Bankman-Fried is charged by the US Attorney&#8217;s Office for the Southern District of New York with conspiracy to commit wire fraud on customers, wire fraud on customers, conspiracy to commit wire fraud on lenders, wire fraud on lenders, conspiracy to commit commodities fraud, conspiracy to commit securities fraud, conspiracy to commit money laundering, and conspiracy to defraud the United States and violate campaign finance laws.<br /><br />In addition, the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) filed a lawsuit against Bankman-Fried today for alleged violations of federal commodities laws.<br /><br /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ftx-token-trading-volume-jumps-1060-as-price-rises-on-ftx-revival-proposal-supported-by-sam-bankman-fried/">FTX</a> crashed spectacularly last month, in what was by far the sharpest decline in the cryptocurrency industry&#8217;s 13-year history.<br /><br />The company, which allowed customers to buy, sell, and store a variety of digital assets as well as speculate on the future prices of cryptocurrency via derivative products, was one of the most popular in the world.<br /><br />However, it failed when it became clear that the company lacked sufficient funds to back customers&#8217; assets. According to newly appointed FTX CEO John J. Ray III, this was due to Alameda Research, a sister company also founded by Bankman-Fried, having the ability to use FTX customer assets for its purposes without oversight.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/ftx-sam-bankman-fried-charged-with-eight-criminal-offenses/">FTX Sam Bankman-Fried Charged With Eight Criminal Offenses</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ftx-sam-bankman-fried-charged-with-eight-criminal-offenses/">FTX Sam Bankman-Fried Charged With Eight Criminal Offenses</a> was first posted on December 13, 2022 at 5:22 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Resumes USDC Withdrawals; $3 Billion Taken Off Within 24 Hours</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/binance-resumes-usdc-withdrawals-3-billion-taken-off-within-24-hours/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 21:46:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDCoin (USDC)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63493</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>After pausing them for a while, Binance is once again processing withdrawal requests for the USD Coin (USDC) stablecoin. According to Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao, the insufficient USDC reserves on the platform caused a temporary halt in the processing of USDC withdrawals at the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange platform by daily volume, Binance. Binance, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-resumes-usdc-withdrawals-3-billion-taken-off-within-24-hours/">Binance Resumes USDC Withdrawals; $3 Billion Taken Off Within 24 Hours</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-resumes-usdc-withdrawals-3-billion-taken-off-within-24-hours/">Binance Resumes USDC Withdrawals; $3 Billion Taken Off Within 24 Hours</a> was first posted on December 13, 2022 at 4:46 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>After pausing them for a while, Binance is once again processing withdrawal requests for the USD Coin (USDC) stablecoin.</p>
<p>According to Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao, the insufficient USDC reserves on the platform caused a temporary halt in the processing of USDC withdrawals at the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange platform by daily volume, Binance.</p>
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binances-auditor-confirms-bitcoin-reserves-are-101-backed/">Binance</a>, the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange, announced on Tuesday that withdrawals of the stablecoin USDC will be halted until a token swap involving the asset is completed.<br /><br />This change does not affect other tokens tied to the value of the dollar, such as tether and BUSD, a stablecoin created by Binance and the blockchain-focused company Paxos.<br /><br />The chief executive of Binance, Changpeng Zhao, also stated on <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1602579499903852544">Twitter</a>: <em>&#8220;On USDC, we have seen an increase in withdrawals. However, the channel to swap from PAX/BUSD to USDC calls for using a New York-based bank that deals in USD. For a few more hours, the banks are closed. We expect the situation will be restored when the banks open.&#8221;</em><br /><br />According to blockchain analytics firm<a href="https://twitter.com/nansen_ai/status/1602673823651864577"> Nansen</a>, Binance has seen the highest daily amount of withdrawals since June. On the previous day, there were $3 billion in net outflows. <a href="https://twitter.com/Blockanalia/status/1602337143048781826">Jump Trading</a>, one of the biggest cryptocurrency market makers, was mentioned in a tweet by Nansen analyst Andrew Thurman as one of the biggest redeemers.<br /><br />Investors are uneasy because they fear that the collapse of rival exchange FTX last month will spread to the rest of the industry. Sam Bankman-Fried, the former CEO of FTX, was detained in the Bahamas late on Monday after criminal charges were brought by American prosecutors.<br /><br />In recent weeks, concern has also grown regarding Binance. The exchange released its first proof-of-reserves report, an audit designed to make sure that a platform has enough assets to cover all of its client balances and reassure customers about the security of their holdings.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-resumes-usdc-withdrawals-3-billion-taken-off-within-24-hours/">Binance Resumes USDC Withdrawals; $3 Billion Taken Off Within 24 Hours</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-resumes-usdc-withdrawals-3-billion-taken-off-within-24-hours/">Binance Resumes USDC Withdrawals; $3 Billion Taken Off Within 24 Hours</a> was first posted on December 13, 2022 at 4:46 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SHIB Price Analysis: How Will SHIB Price Fare as 2022 Ends? 19.4 Million SHIB Burned at Once With Burn Rate Up 107%</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/shib-price-analysis-how-will-shib-price-fare-as-2022-ends-19-4-million-shib-burned-at-once-with-burn-rate-up-107/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 10:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB/USD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB/USD Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=63478</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A whopping 19,400,000 SHIB was transferred to a dead wallet in a single transaction Shiba Inu&#8217;s burn rate has subsequently increased by 107% Shiba Inu is currently trading at $0.0000089, seeing a 2.34% decrease Cryptocurrencies, including Shiba Inu (SHIB), are attempting to recover from selling pressure brought on at the start of the week. In [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/shib-price-analysis-how-will-shib-price-fare-as-2022-ends-19-4-million-shib-burned-at-once-with-burn-rate-up-107/">SHIB Price Analysis: How Will SHIB Price Fare as 2022 Ends? 19.4 Million SHIB Burned at Once With Burn Rate Up 107%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/shib-price-analysis-how-will-shib-price-fare-as-2022-ends-19-4-million-shib-burned-at-once-with-burn-rate-up-107/">SHIB Price Analysis: How Will SHIB Price Fare as 2022 Ends? 19.4 Million SHIB Burned at Once With Burn Rate Up 107%</a> was first posted on December 13, 2022 at 5:21 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li>A whopping 19,400,000 SHIB was transferred to a dead wallet in a single transaction</li>
<li>Shiba Inu&#8217;s burn rate has subsequently increased by 107%</li>
<li>Shiba Inu is currently trading at $0.0000089, seeing a 2.34% decrease</li>
</ul>
<p>Cryptocurrencies, including <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/shib-price-analysis-shiba-inu-price-rebounds-shib-up-for-grabs-as-welly-launches-shiba-eternity-tournament/">Shiba Inu (SHIB)</a>, are attempting to recover from selling pressure brought on at the start of the week. In recent hours, the Shibburn website reported a large SHIB burn transaction. According to the data, a whopping 19,400,000 SHIB was transferred to a dead wallet in a single transaction. According to Etherscan.io, the transaction was completed through one of the Cryptocom-associated wallets labeled <em>&#8220;Crypto.com 2.&#8221;</em> Shiba Inu&#8217;s burn rate has subsequently increased by 107% in the last 24 hours, and the total amount of SHIB tokens burned within this timeframe now stands at 31,019,774. In the last seven days, the Shiba Inu Community has eliminated a massive 90,061,737 SHIB with 44 transactions. Shiba Inu pared some of its intraday losses. At the time of publication, Shiba Inu is currently trading at $0.0000089, a 2.34% decrease from the previous day.<br /><br /><strong>Key Levels</strong><br />Resistance Levels: $0.00001518, $0.00001000, $0.00000925<br />Support Levels: $0.00000900, $0.00000800, $0.00000700</p>
<h4>SHIB/USD Daily Chart: Bearish</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1436" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-63498 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-Daily-Dec-13.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-Daily-Dec-13.png 1436w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-Daily-Dec-13-300x144.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-Daily-Dec-13-1024x491.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-Daily-Dec-13-768x368.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-Daily-Dec-13-750x359.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-Daily-Dec-13-1140x546.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1436px) 100vw, 1436px" /><span style="color: #808080">SHIB/USD Daily Chart</span></h6>
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/shib-price-analysis-shiba-inu-bulls-await-launch-of-shibaeternity-on-october-1-price-returns-to-crucial-level/">SHIB/USD</a> attempted to climb back up past $0.00000925 and failed on December 12, drifting lower to oscillate beneath the $00000900 mark. Since the declines, SHIB has had a difficult time fending off bearish pressures. The pair has been trading sideways within a predetermined range even though the decline appears to have ended above the support level of $0.00000800.<br /><br />It is noteworthy that the daily relative strength index (RSI) has been making lower turns and moving against the daily moving averages of 50 and 200 since the beginning of the month. It resembles a bearish divergence, which signals that the bulls are out of steam. However, if the pair can establish support near the $0.00000850 mark, the bulls may attempt to push higher.</p>
<h4>SHIB/USD 4-Hour chart: Bearish</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1436" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-63499 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-4-Hour-Dec-13.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-4-Hour-Dec-13.png 1436w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-4-Hour-Dec-13-300x144.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-4-Hour-Dec-13-1024x491.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-4-Hour-Dec-13-768x368.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-4-Hour-Dec-13-750x359.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SHIBUSD-4-Hour-Dec-13-1140x546.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1436px) 100vw, 1436px" /><span style="color: #999999">SHIB/USD 4-Hour Chart</span></h6>
<p>Right now, the short-term outlook for SHIB/USD is uncertain. Sellers may continue to hold the upper hand unless the price corrects above the $0.00000900 mark and the 4-hour moving average (MA 50 &amp; MA 200) at $0.00000925. The pair was able to hold its support at $0.00000900 while avoiding the next closest support area at $0.00000800.<br /><br />The buyers&#8217; attempts above $0.00000900 and the sellers&#8217; struggle to push prices lower indicate that things might be looking up. Lacking a more definitive direction signal and with the outlook remaining uncertain, price action is still within a consolidation range above the $0.00000800 low. Although SHIB has received support since the June crash, it&#8217;s now at a crucial zone as it attempts to rediscover its rhythm.</p>
<p><strong>Note:</strong><em> Kryptomoney.com is not a financial advisor. Do your research before investing your funds in any financial asset or presented product or event. We are not responsible for your investing results</em></p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/shib-price-analysis-how-will-shib-price-fare-as-2022-ends-19-4-million-shib-burned-at-once-with-burn-rate-up-107/">SHIB Price Analysis: How Will SHIB Price Fare as 2022 Ends? 19.4 Million SHIB Burned at Once With Burn Rate Up 107%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/shib-price-analysis-how-will-shib-price-fare-as-2022-ends-19-4-million-shib-burned-at-once-with-burn-rate-up-107/">SHIB Price Analysis: How Will SHIB Price Fare as 2022 Ends? 19.4 Million SHIB Burned at Once With Burn Rate Up 107%</a> was first posted on December 13, 2022 at 5:21 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>