<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>Latest Crypto News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://kryptomoney.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<description>Latest Crypto News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 20:33:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.7</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/cropped-cropped-favicon_512x512_v2-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Latest Crypto News</title>
	<link>https://kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><itunes:subtitle>Latest Crypto News</itunes:subtitle><itunes:category text="News &amp; Politics"/><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Business News"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Investing"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Tech News"/></itunes:category><item>
		<title>Gate.io Refutes Rumors of Its Collapse Amid Multichain Crisis</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/gate-io-refutes-rumors-of-its-collapse-amid-multichain-crisis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 20:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gate.io]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65216</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Last week witnessed a devastating 20% crash in the price of the Multichain token, triggered by reports of problematic withdrawals. The precise cause of the transaction backlog in the Multichain token remains a mystery, although two theories have emerged. Initially, it was believed that a poorly executed system update was responsible for the deposits and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/gate-io-refutes-rumors-of-its-collapse-amid-multichain-crisis/">Gate.io Refutes Rumors of Its Collapse Amid Multichain Crisis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/gate-io-refutes-rumors-of-its-collapse-amid-multichain-crisis/">Gate.io Refutes Rumors of Its Collapse Amid Multichain Crisis</a> was first posted on June 1, 2023 at 4:33 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Last week witnessed a devastating 20% crash in the price of the Multichain token, triggered by reports of problematic withdrawals. The precise cause of the transaction backlog in the Multichain token remains a mystery, although two theories have emerged.<br /><br />Initially, it was believed that a poorly executed system update was responsible for the deposits and withdrawals of MULTI getting stuck, causing significant delays. However, rumors began circulating like wildfire, suggesting that the development team had been arrested in Shanghai.<br /><br />While these speculations are yet to be confirmed, the Multichain team has since acknowledged that their CEO is <a href="https://twitter.com/MultichainOrg/status/1663941611380965376">missing,</a> leaving the developers without the necessary access to conduct server maintenance, which could account for the prolonged downtime.<br /><br />During this period, an unknown user transferred $2.75 million worth of MULTI to Gate.io, raising concerns about a potential connection between the two platforms.<br /><br />In the following week, additional assets purportedly belonging to members of the Multichain team were reportedly transferred to Gate.io. Notably, a series of transactions involving approximately $10 million worth of Fantom took place.<br /><br />As the Multichain team finds itself in a precarious situation, wild accusations have been thrown around, with Gate.io being singled out for allegedly assisting and harboring the Multichain team.<br /><br />To address these mounting concerns, Gate.io released a statement to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-05-31/crypto-exchange-gate-io-rejects-rumors-that-sank-related-token">Bloomberg</a>, denying any involvement in the matter and clarifying their recent activities. According to Gate.io&#8217;s spokesperson, the platform&#8217;s employees are primarily focused on preparations for the platform&#8217;s upcoming 10th anniversary and handling essential paperwork, particularly obtaining a Virtual Asset Service Provider (VASP) license required for their new Hong Kong-focused trading platform.<br /><br />The <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/gate-io-launches-crypto-exchange-gatetr-in-turkey/">Gate.io</a> spokesperson also took the opportunity to provide a glimpse of upcoming plans for the Gate community, including a series of &#8220;user campaigns&#8221; to celebrate the platform&#8217;s decade-long existence.<br /><br />Following the controversy, the analytics platform Lookonchain decided to publish an updated report on the assets stored on Gate.io&#8217;s platform, aiming to shed light on the situation.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/gate-io-refutes-rumors-of-its-collapse-amid-multichain-crisis/">Gate.io Refutes Rumors of Its Collapse Amid Multichain Crisis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/gate-io-refutes-rumors-of-its-collapse-amid-multichain-crisis/">Gate.io Refutes Rumors of Its Collapse Amid Multichain Crisis</a> was first posted on June 1, 2023 at 4:33 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Mining Difficulty Achieved New Record of 50 Trillion for First Time</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-mining-difficulty-achieved-new-record-of-50-trillion-for-first-time/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 19:37:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65212</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>While Bitcoin&#8216;s price remains trapped within a narrow range, the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency is witnessing an unprecedented challenge in its mining arena. Network fundamentals are painting an overwhelmingly bullish picture for Bitcoin. Recent data from BTC.com reveals a surge in Bitcoin mining difficulty, reaching a remarkable milestone of 50.68 trillion. This new all-time high was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-mining-difficulty-achieved-new-record-of-50-trillion-for-first-time/">Bitcoin Mining Difficulty Achieved New Record of 50 Trillion for First Time</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-mining-difficulty-achieved-new-record-of-50-trillion-for-first-time/">Bitcoin Mining Difficulty Achieved New Record of 50 Trillion for First Time</a> was first posted on June 1, 2023 at 3:37 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>While <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-soars-past-28000-amid-renewed-banking-concerns-from-first-republic/">Bitcoin</a>&#8216;s price remains trapped within a narrow range, the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency is witnessing an unprecedented challenge in its mining arena. Network fundamentals are painting an overwhelmingly bullish picture for Bitcoin.<br /><br />Recent data from <a href="https://btc.com/stats/diff">BTC.com</a> reveals a surge in Bitcoin mining difficulty, reaching a remarkable milestone of 50.68 trillion. This new all-time high was achieved through a 3.4% increase at block height 792,288 on May 31st. It marks the first time Bitcoin has surpassed the 50 trillion difficulty level.<br /><br />The robust conviction and competition among miners are further underscored by the network&#8217;s hash rate, which is hovering near its peak at 400 EH/s. Leading the pack is Foundry USA, contributing the highest market share of 28.9% in hash rate, followed by Antpool at 22.6% and F2Pool with a dominant 14.1% share.<br /><br />This surge in mining difficulty comes as a relief for Bitcoin miners, who faced significant challenges during the market turmoil of the previous year. The recent craze around NFTs contributed to their respite by driving transaction fees.<br /><br />Mining revenue hit a five-year high last month in an extraordinary turn of events. Driven by the popularity of NFTs, miners are now actively deploying more mining machines, thus boosting the network&#8217;s computational power. <br /><br />Additionally, Bitcoin mining-related stocks in the United States experienced gains this week as President Joe Biden agreed to abandon the proposed 30% tax on electricity used by these companies.<br /><br />Riot Platforms emerged as the leading gainer among major mining stocks, followed closely by Iris Energy, Hive Blockchain, Cleanspark, Hut 8 Mining and Marathon Digital Holding.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-mining-difficulty-achieved-new-record-of-50-trillion-for-first-time/">Bitcoin Mining Difficulty Achieved New Record of 50 Trillion for First Time</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-mining-difficulty-achieved-new-record-of-50-trillion-for-first-time/">Bitcoin Mining Difficulty Achieved New Record of 50 Trillion for First Time</a> was first posted on June 1, 2023 at 3:37 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Cuts Off Underperforming Staff Amid Market Share Decline</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/binance-cuts-off-underperforming-staff-amid-market-share-decline/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 21:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65208</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance, the leading cryptocurrency exchange, has recently laid off a portion of its workforce amidst a decline in its market share. In response to a tweet by Wu Blockchain regarding the layoffs, a Binance spokesperson explained that the company periodically reviews its talent allocation to ensure optimal team composition and resource allocation. Consequently, some employees [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-cuts-off-underperforming-staff-amid-market-share-decline/">Binance Cuts Off Underperforming Staff Amid Market Share Decline</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-cuts-off-underperforming-staff-amid-market-share-decline/">Binance Cuts Off Underperforming Staff Amid Market Share Decline</a> was first posted on May 31, 2023 at 5:08 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-accused-of-deliberately-flouting-laws-by-cftc-chief/">Binance</a>, the leading cryptocurrency exchange, has recently laid off a portion of its workforce amidst a decline in its market share. In response to a tweet by <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1663890209526927373">Wu Blockchain</a> regarding the layoffs, a Binance spokesperson explained that the company periodically reviews its talent allocation to ensure optimal team composition and resource allocation. <br /><br />Consequently, some employees who are underperforming or not fitting the organizational culture may be let go.<br /><br />The spokesperson clarified that this move is not a case of rightsizing, but rather a reevaluation of the expertise and talent required in critical roles. <br /><br />Binance intends to fill hundreds of open positions to align with the evolving demands of users and regulators. Although the exact number of employees affected was not disclosed, the exchange confirmed that it had a headcount of around 8,000 before the layoffs.<br /><br />Interestingly, these layoffs follow Binance&#8217;s previous statement in March, where they stated they had no plans for layoffs and were actively seeking to fill 500 additional positions by the end of June. Even now, Binance still has over 300 open positions advertised on its website.<br /><br />In January, Binance&#8217;s CEO, Changpeng Zhao, expressed plans to increase staff numbers by 15% to 30% in 2023, stating their commitment to building and preparing for the next bull market. However, recent reports have indicated a declining market share for Binance, coinciding with decreasing trading volumes. It is worth noting that regulatory actions taken against Binance and Zhao in the United States in March might have contributed to this decline.<br /><br />Responding to concerns about the layoffs, Zhao mentioned on <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1663945939482968075">Twitter</a> that Binance follows a program called &#8216;bottom out,&#8217; which involves parting ways with individuals who do not align with the company&#8217;s unique culture or situation. He emphasized that this program is an ongoing process and that the company does not have specific targets for employee departures.<br /><br />Despite the layoffs, Binance remains optimistic about the future. The company&#8217;s spokesperson reiterated their commitment to delivering for users and expressed excitement about the growth and innovation within the Binance ecosystem. They also clarified that the layoffs were not cost-cutting measures.<br /><br />Binance spokesperson<a href="https://twitter.com/PRHillmann/status/1663925657611403264?s=20"> Patrick Hillmann</a> further explained on Twitter that the company regularly conducts talent density audits and resource allocation exercises every six months or so. He emphasized that these exercises aim to streamline operations and ensure efficiency within the organization. However, he did not provide a specific number of layoffs, highlighting that the focus is on directing resources where they are needed most.<br /><br />In summary, Binance has decided to lay off a portion of its workforce as it evaluates talent allocation and streamlines operations. Despite the decline in market share and recent regulatory challenges, the company remains committed to its users and is optimistic about its future growth and innovation.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-cuts-off-underperforming-staff-amid-market-share-decline/">Binance Cuts Off Underperforming Staff Amid Market Share Decline</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-cuts-off-underperforming-staff-amid-market-share-decline/">Binance Cuts Off Underperforming Staff Amid Market Share Decline</a> was first posted on May 31, 2023 at 5:08 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin Network Activity Rises Before Halving Event</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/litecoin-network-activity-rises-before-halving-event/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 20:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin (LTC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin halving]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65204</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin is gearing up for its highly anticipated third mining reward halving scheduled for early August. Following this event, the per-block reward paid to miners will be reduced by 50%, from 12.5 LTC to 6.25 LTC. In anticipation of the halving, the twelfth largest cryptocurrency by market value has witnessed significant gains, pushing its price [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/litecoin-network-activity-rises-before-halving-event/">Litecoin Network Activity Rises Before Halving Event</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/litecoin-network-activity-rises-before-halving-event/">Litecoin Network Activity Rises Before Halving Event</a> was first posted on May 31, 2023 at 4:06 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ltc-price-analysis-how-far-will-rapid-whale-accumulation-take-ltc-price-litecoin-ranks-top-payment-option-on-bitpay/">Litecoin</a> is gearing up for its highly anticipated third mining reward halving scheduled for early August. Following this event, the per-block reward paid to miners will be reduced by 50%, from 12.5 LTC to 6.25 LTC. In anticipation of the halving, the twelfth largest cryptocurrency by market value has witnessed significant gains, pushing its price to $92.58.<br /><br />On-chain metrics have also shown positive trends for Litecoin. Data from <a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1663472029050306560">IntoTheBlock</a> reveals a surge in the total address count with a balance since the end of April, reaching an impressive 8.5 million LTC addresses with a balance last week. <br /><br />Both new and active address counts have hovered near all-time highs established in February, with new addresses briefly surpassing those of Bitcoin.<br /><br />Crypto-analytic platform<a href="https://insights.santiment.net/read/litecoin-s-ltc20-is-less-than-3-months-out-how-big-of-a-deal-is-it-7307"> Santiment</a> highlights the increased on-chain volume as a strong indicator that significant players are entering the LTC market in anticipation of the halving. They believe this event will have a positive impact on Litecoin&#8217;s price.<br /><br />Furthermore, Litecoin&#8217;s hash rate has remained consistent, experiencing a growth of over 24% since the beginning of the year, reaching 712 TH/s. The mining difficulty stands at 25.12 million hashes, closely aligned with the hash rate.<br /><br />The upcoming halving has also influenced Litecoin&#8217;s futures derivatives contracts, which have <a href="https://www.coinglass.com/currencies/LTC">surged</a> by over $420 million globally, resulting in a year-to-date growth of over 20%. This surge in interest has pushed Litecoin Futures&#8217; open interest to its highest level since the beginning of last year.<br /><br />As the halving approaches, Litecoin continues to show promising signs in its on-chain metrics and futures contracts, building anticipation for the event and its potential impact on the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/litecoin-network-activity-rises-before-halving-event/">Litecoin Network Activity Rises Before Halving Event</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/litecoin-network-activity-rises-before-halving-event/">Litecoin Network Activity Rises Before Halving Event</a> was first posted on May 31, 2023 at 4:06 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin (BTC) to Break Equilibrium and Trigger Volatility: Glassnode</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-btc-to-break-equilibrium-and-trigger-volatility-glassnode/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 13:26:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Glassnode]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65200</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Analytics provider Glassnode has issued a cautionary report in its weekly on-chain analysis, suggesting that Bitcoin (BTC) is poised for a significant movement after a period of low volume and volatility. Glassnode noted that the recent extended period of minimal volatility and narrow trading ranges is likely to be disrupted shortly. The news of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-btc-to-break-equilibrium-and-trigger-volatility-glassnode/">Bitcoin (BTC) to Break Equilibrium and Trigger Volatility: Glassnode</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-btc-to-break-equilibrium-and-trigger-volatility-glassnode/">Bitcoin (BTC) to Break Equilibrium and Trigger Volatility: Glassnode</a> was first posted on May 30, 2023 at 9:26 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Analytics provider Glassnode has issued a cautionary<a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1663173812781830146"> report</a> in its weekly on-chain analysis, suggesting that <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-btc-might-drop-near-22k-analyst-says-shiba-inu-among-most-searched-cryptocurrencies-in-us/">Bitcoin (BTC)</a> is poised for a significant movement after a period of low volume and volatility. Glassnode noted that the recent extended period of minimal volatility and narrow trading ranges is likely to be disrupted shortly.<br /><br />The news of the U.S. government reaching an agreement on the debt ceiling prompted a 4% surge in Bitcoin&#8217;s price. However, this increase was insufficient to break BTC out of its current tight, range-bound channel that has persisted over the past few weeks. BTC has already started retracing from its minor burst of activity.<br /><br /><a href="https://insights.glassnode.com/the-week-onchain-week-22-2023/">Glassnode</a>&#8216;s report also highlighted that digital assets and commodities are undergoing their second corrective upswing of the year, and it observed a closer correlation between these two asset classes in 2023.</p>
<p>The report disclosed that Monthly Realized Volatility has dropped to 34%, falling below the 1-standard deviation Bollinger Band. This level of low volatility has been seen in less than 20% of historical market activity, leading to the logical expectation of increased volatility in the near term.<br /><br />Additionally, transfer volumes remain low, indicating reduced exchange flows. Recent exchange activity has decreased by 27.3% compared to the past six months, further supporting the notion of a phase of equilibrium.<br /><br />The Net Unrealized Profit/Loss (NUPL) metric, which currently sits at 0.29, reinforces this equilibrium phase. A drop below 0.25 would signify a decline in market profitability, potentially entering the capitulation and recovery phase.<br /><br />Glassnode concluded that the market currently lacks a clear directional pull, suggesting a state of indecisiveness.<br /><br />As of now, BTC has retreated by 0.7% and is cooling off from its Monday high of just over $28,000. Presently, the cryptocurrency is trading at $27,775.<br /><br />Immediate support is anticipated at $27,200, with further support at $26,600. If the expected volatility materializes and leads to another downward movement, the ongoing trend that started in mid-April could result in more short-term losses.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-btc-to-break-equilibrium-and-trigger-volatility-glassnode/">Bitcoin (BTC) to Break Equilibrium and Trigger Volatility: Glassnode</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-btc-to-break-equilibrium-and-trigger-volatility-glassnode/">Bitcoin (BTC) to Break Equilibrium and Trigger Volatility: Glassnode</a> was first posted on May 30, 2023 at 9:26 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gemini Faces Market Share Loss Amid Regulatory and Financial Issues</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/gemini-faces-market-share-loss-amid-regulatory-and-financial-issues/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto exchanges]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gemini]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65192</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Gemini, a prominent cryptocurrency exchange, finds itself in a challenging position as it grapples with a decline in market share. The exchange&#8217;s troubles came to light in November 2022 when its partner in the Earn Program, Genesis, filed for bankruptcy, leaving Gemini owed a staggering $765 million. Consequently, on January 10, Gemini decided to discontinue [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/gemini-faces-market-share-loss-amid-regulatory-and-financial-issues/">Gemini Faces Market Share Loss Amid Regulatory and Financial Issues</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/gemini-faces-market-share-loss-amid-regulatory-and-financial-issues/">Gemini Faces Market Share Loss Amid Regulatory and Financial Issues</a> was first posted on May 30, 2023 at 8:14 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/gemini-launches-global-platform-amidst-us-regulatory-challenges/">Gemini</a>, a prominent cryptocurrency exchange, finds itself in a challenging position as it grapples with a decline in market share. The exchange&#8217;s troubles came to light in November 2022 when its partner in the Earn Program, Genesis, filed for bankruptcy, leaving Gemini owed a staggering $765 million. Consequently, on January 10, Gemini decided to discontinue the program.<br /><br />Shortly after, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filed a lawsuit against both Gemini and Genesis, claiming that the Earn Program involved the sale of unregistered securities. However, Gemini and Genesis recently <a href="https://jfblegal.egnyte.com/dl/EgiiPyjDym">filed</a> to have the SEC&#8217;s case dismissed, arguing that the program does not constitute a security offering.<br /><br />To alleviate financial strain, the Winklevoss twins, the founders of Gemini, <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/crypto-gemini-exchange-winklevoss-twins-loan-100-million-ftx-funding-2023-4">extended</a> a $100 million loan to the exchange, highlighting the adverse impact of the broader market downturn on Gemini&#8217;s financial performance. While rumors circulated that JPMorgan intended to terminate its partnership with Gemini due to profitability concerns, Gemini Trust Lawyer Charles Harder refuted the claims, stating that the relationship between Gemini and JPMorgan remains intact.<br /><br />In addition to these challenges, an analysis conducted by CCData and reported by <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-05-29/winklevoss-twins-gemini-crypto-exchange-pivots-after-layoffs-losses-earn">Bloomberg</a> revealed that Gemini&#8217;s cumulative trading volume between January and April 2023 declined by almost 50% compared to the period from September to December 2022. February marked a record low for the company&#8217;s monthly trading volume, accounting for a mere 0.07% of the global spot trading volume. However, this figure improved to 0.12% ($747 million) in April. Despite the recovery, Gemini&#8217;s trading volume in April remained nearly half of what it was a year ago.<br /><br />Meanwhile, competitors such as Coinbase, Kraken, and Binance experienced growth in their market share in April compared to the previous year. Binance, in particular, dominated the global market with a 46% share, up from 31% a year earlier.<br /><br />Recognizing the challenging regulatory landscape in the United States, Gemini has been actively expanding its presence overseas. In recent developments, the exchange launched its derivatives platform, Gemini Foundation, in 30 countries. Additionally, the Winklevoss twins announced that Dublin, Ireland, will serve as the new European base for the exchange.<br /><br />However, Gemini continues to face regulatory obstacles abroad. Just last week, the Securities and Exchange Commission in the Philippines cautioned that Gemini&#8217;s newly launched derivatives platform is operating without proper approval.<br /><br />Campbell Harvey, a Finance Professor at Duke University, suggested that Gemini could potentially benefit from being acquired by a larger competitor. Harvey emphasized the strong brand associated with the Winklevoss twins and speculated that a merger with Coinbase or Kraken could be conceivable. Nonetheless, the exchange&#8217;s regulatory challenges may impede any such potential deal.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/gemini-faces-market-share-loss-amid-regulatory-and-financial-issues/">Gemini Faces Market Share Loss Amid Regulatory and Financial Issues</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/gemini-faces-market-share-loss-amid-regulatory-and-financial-issues/">Gemini Faces Market Share Loss Amid Regulatory and Financial Issues</a> was first posted on May 30, 2023 at 8:14 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Your $100 Investment in blockbank Could Moon When BBANK Hits $1!</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/how-your-100-investment-in-blockbank-could-moon-when-bbank-hits-1/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 03:51:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sponsored]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BBANK]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockbank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockbank Price Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65195</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As an emerging player in the rapidly evolving financial landscape, blockbank is spearheading an integration of the best features of traditional banking, decentralized finance (DeFi), and centralized finance (CeFi) into a single platform. This groundbreaking approach addresses inefficiencies in conventional banking and complexity in DeFi while also emulating the structure and security of CeFi, aiming [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/how-your-100-investment-in-blockbank-could-moon-when-bbank-hits-1/">How Your $100 Investment in blockbank Could Moon When BBANK Hits $1!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/how-your-100-investment-in-blockbank-could-moon-when-bbank-hits-1/">How Your $100 Investment in blockbank Could Moon When BBANK Hits $1!</a> was first posted on May 29, 2023 at 11:51 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As an emerging player in the rapidly evolving financial landscape, blockbank is spearheading an integration of the best features of traditional banking, decentralized finance (DeFi), and centralized finance (CeFi) into a single platform. This groundbreaking approach addresses inefficiencies in conventional banking and complexity in DeFi while also emulating the structure and security of CeFi, aiming to fill gaps in each system while capitalizing on their strengths.</p>
<p>blockbank’s unique amalgamation promises a revolutionary shift in our interaction with <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ncfa-and-kabn-na-announced-a-collaborative-partnership/">financial systems,</a> creating a more transparent, and efficient financial infrastructure. By packaging these varied services into one application, it meets a wide range of financial needs and caters to both new and experienced users in the digital age.</p>
<p>With this fusion, blockbank enhances convenience, and security in the financial ecosystem. It offers users the flexibility to navigate between traditional banking, DeFi, and CeFi, tailoring their financial management based on comfort, risk tolerance, and specific needs. In doing so, blockbank signifies a considerable stride in the digital transformation of finance, truly placing financial control in users&#8217; hands.</p>
<p>Among its many features, the standout element is undoubtedly its native utility token, $BBANK. This token forms the backbone of the blockbank ecosystem, offering users compelling benefits through a tiered reward system.</p>
<h2>The Power of $BBANK Token</h2>
<p>Users who lock $BBANK tokens can unlock various reward tiers, each offering increased annual percentage yields (APY) and enhanced cashback rewards (up to 8%) for transactions using blockbank&#8217;s debit card. The structure encourages active user engagement, making $BBANK more than just a digital asset—it becomes a key to unlocking enhanced benefits within the blockbank ecosystem.</p>
<h2>blockbank (BBANK) Price Analysis</h2>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-65197" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/blockbank-300x159.png" alt="blockbank Price Analysis" width="300" height="159" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/blockbank-300x159.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/blockbank-768x407.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/blockbank-750x398.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/blockbank.png 960w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /></p>
<p>The current price of blockbank tokens stands at $0.0022, with a market capitalization of $880,000. Over the past 24 hours, the trading volume has surged by 99% to reach $35,416. Meanwhile, the circulating supply of blockbank tokens is approximately 400 million, which aligns with the total supply of 400 million tokens which means there are no more token unlocks.</p>
<h2>Looking at the Future: Exciting Developments on the Horizon</h2>
<p>blockbank has some exciting features in its pipeline that could potentially stimulate the demand for $BBANK tokens, potentially propelling its price upwards. The most imminent is the launch of the blockbank card, expected to roll out in the next two months. This development could spur increased usage of $BBANK, as users lock tokens to climb the reward tiers and maximize their debit card benefits.</p>
<p>Further, there are also rumors of a lending and borrowing feature being added to blockbank. If realized, this feature would solidify blockbank&#8217;s standing in the DeFi space, potentially driving further demand for $BBANK as users look to take advantage of borrowing and lending opportunities.</p>
<h2>Projecting Potential Returns</h2>
<p>Now, let&#8217;s delve into the hypothetical scenario of a $100 investment in $BBANK, assuming the token price eventually rises to $1. At the current token price of $0.0022, your $100 would get you approximately 45,454 $BBANK tokens. Should $BBANK reach $1, your initial investment would surge to a whopping $45,454.</p>
<p>This means you could pocket a 45,354% profit on your investment.</p>
<h2>The Path Forward: blockbank and Its Promising Prospects</h2>
<p>blockbank represents a significant evolution in the fintech industry, offering a complete financial solution that bridges the gap between traditional banking and DeFi. With the anticipated release of its debit card and potential lending and borrowing features, <a href="https://blockbank.ai/">blockbank</a> is poised to secure its position as a leading player in the digital banking revolution.</p>
<p>However, as with all investments, it&#8217;s essential to conduct thorough research and consider seeking advice from a financial advisor. The potential returns may be exciting, but it&#8217;s equally vital to assess the inherent risks. Only invest within your means, and remember the golden rule of investing: never invest more than you&#8217;re prepared to lose.</p>
<p>And last but not the least, <a href="https://bbank.onelink.me/s0LE/ddbitvnm">download the blockbank mobile app</a> or <a href="https://app.blockbank.ai/sign-in">access the blockbank application</a> directly from your browser. Get your KYCs done and start trading like a boss!</p>
<p><em><strong>Disclaimer:</strong></em> This is not investment advice. Please do your due diligence before investing in any asset.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/how-your-100-investment-in-blockbank-could-moon-when-bbank-hits-1/">How Your $100 Investment in blockbank Could Moon When BBANK Hits $1!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/how-your-100-investment-in-blockbank-could-moon-when-bbank-hits-1/">How Your $100 Investment in blockbank Could Moon When BBANK Hits $1!</a> was first posted on May 29, 2023 at 11:51 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano Experiences 91% Increase in DEX Volume</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/cardano-experiences-91-increase-in-dex-volume/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 20:58:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65188</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cardano, a well-known blockchain platform, has experienced an impressive surge of 91% in decentralized exchange (DEX) volume within the past week, as reported by DeFiLlama data. The DEX volume on Cardano has now reached a substantial $68.5 million, primarily driven by a notable increase in activity on Cardano-based DEX platforms, particularly Minswap. Minswap, which is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/cardano-experiences-91-increase-in-dex-volume/">Cardano Experiences 91% Increase in DEX Volume</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/cardano-experiences-91-increase-in-dex-volume/">Cardano Experiences 91% Increase in DEX Volume</a> was first posted on May 28, 2023 at 4:58 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/cardanos-defi-industry-might-expand-rapidly-in-2023/">Cardano</a>, a well-known blockchain platform, has experienced an impressive surge of 91% in decentralized exchange (DEX) volume within the past week, as reported by <a href="https://defillama.com/dexs/chains/cardano">DeFiLlama</a> data.<br /><br />The DEX volume on Cardano has now reached a substantial $68.5 million, primarily driven by a notable increase in activity on Cardano-based DEX platforms, particularly Minswap. Minswap, which is the leading DEX on Cardano, witnessed a staggering weekly change of 99.72%.<br /><br />In terms of volume, Minswap accounted for the majority, with $6.91 million in the last 24 hours and $60.52 million over seven days. This impressive figure represents a significant 90.4% of the total DEX volume on the Cardano platform.<br /><br />While other <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/cardano-defi-acardex-launches-car-nfts-grants-higher-opportunities-to-its-token-holders/">DEX</a> platforms on Cardano, like WingRiders and SundaeSwap, also contributed to the overall volume, their impact was relatively smaller. Despite the remarkable growth in DEX volume, Cardano&#8217;s total value locked (TVL) currently stands at $91.27 million, which only represents 0.69% of the combined TVL across all platforms.<br /><br />Ethereum maintains its dominance in the DeFi landscape with a TVL of $7.8 billion, accounting for 37.6% of the total. Binance Smart Chain (BSC) and Arbitrum follow suit with 27.98% and 14.67%, respectively.<br /><br />The surge in DEX volume aligns with a 4.6% increase in the price of Cardano&#8217;s native token, ADA, over the past week. This positive price movement, coupled with the substantial growth in DEX volume, highlights the growing interest and activity within the Cardano ecosystem.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/cardano-experiences-91-increase-in-dex-volume/">Cardano Experiences 91% Increase in DEX Volume</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/cardano-experiences-91-increase-in-dex-volume/">Cardano Experiences 91% Increase in DEX Volume</a> was first posted on May 28, 2023 at 4:58 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>China Unveils White Paper To Support Web3 Growth</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/china-unveils-white-paper-to-support-web3-growth/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 22:44:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65184</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a surprising turn of events, the Chinese government appears to be shifting its perspective on cryptocurrencies and is now eager to explore the possibilities offered by related sectors. According to local news outlet The Paper, the government has released a white paper aimed at fostering innovation and development within the Web3 industry. Titled &#8220;Web3 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/china-unveils-white-paper-to-support-web3-growth/">China Unveils White Paper To Support Web3 Growth</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/china-unveils-white-paper-to-support-web3-growth/">China Unveils White Paper To Support Web3 Growth</a> was first posted on May 27, 2023 at 6:44 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In a surprising turn of events, the <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/chinese-law-enforcement-freezes-4000-crypto-bank-accounts-over-illicit-transactions/">Chinese</a> government appears to be shifting its perspective on cryptocurrencies and is now eager to explore the possibilities offered by related sectors. According to local news outlet <a href="https://www.thepaper.cn/newsDetail_forward_23250778">The Paper</a>, the government has released a white paper aimed at fostering innovation and development within the <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/how-web3-is-shaping-the-future-of-finance/">Web3</a> industry.<br /><br />Titled <em>&#8220;Web3 Innovation and Development White Paper (2023),&#8221;</em> the document was unveiled by the Beijing Municipal Science and Technology Commission (Zhongguancun Chaoyang Park). It emphasizes the inevitability of web3 technology as a future trend in the Internet industry.<br /><br />The white paper focuses on key research areas such as artificial intelligence (AI), XR interactive terminals, and content production tools. It also acknowledges the rapid growth of emerging applications like digital populations and collections.<br /><br />While recognizing the challenges faced in the development of the Internet 3.0 industry in Beijing, including technical capabilities, talent support, and legal norms, the white paper proposes policy changes to address these issues.<br /><br />Yang Hongfu, the director of the Zhongguancun Chaoyang Park management committee, revealed that the Chaoyang district plans to allocate a minimum of 100 million yuan ($14 million) annually until 2025 to support this initiative. Zhongguancun, known as China&#8217;s Silicon Valley, will play a crucial role in driving this ambitious endeavor.<br /><br />The release of the white paper has caught attention, given China&#8217;s history with the cryptocurrency sector. Changpeng Zhao, the CEO of Binance, expressed his interest in a <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1662334590332153868">tweet</a>, highlighting the interesting timing of the white paper&#8217;s release alongside the upcoming implementation of crypto regulations in Hong Kong.<br /><br />Recent developments suggest a potential shift in China&#8217;s stance on cryptocurrencies, fueling speculation about a policy change after years of bans. <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1661391542504902664">Zhao noted</a> that the state broadcaster, China Central Television (CCTV), aired a segment featuring the Bitcoin logo, which is seen as a significant event. In the past, such coverage has been associated with increased market activity and price surges.<br /><br />The CCTV segment showcased a Bitcoin ATM in Hong Kong, featuring a prominent blue Bitcoin logo and the option to <em>&#8220;Buy Bitcoins,&#8221;</em> further fueling speculation about China&#8217;s evolving perspective on cryptocurrencies.<br /><br />This news is significant, considering the profound impact it carries. In 2021, China implemented a major crackdown on digital assets, particularly mining, which had a substantial impact on the crypto market. However, the market eventually recovered, with Bitcoin reaching an all-time high in late 2021.<br /><br />Despite other factors affecting Bitcoin&#8217;s value, such as macroeconomic elements, the cryptocurrency continues to trade below $27,000 and is currently valued at $26,700.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/china-unveils-white-paper-to-support-web3-growth/">China Unveils White Paper To Support Web3 Growth</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/china-unveils-white-paper-to-support-web3-growth/">China Unveils White Paper To Support Web3 Growth</a> was first posted on May 27, 2023 at 6:44 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DCG Closes Crypto Institutional Services Subsidiary TradeBlock</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/dcg-closes-crypto-institutional-services-subsidiary-tradeblock/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 22:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DCG]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Currency Group]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65180</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TradeBlock, a subsidiary of Digital Currency Group (DCG), is set to cease operations, as reported by Bloomberg. A spokesperson from DCG explained that the decision to close down the institutional trading platform side of the business was influenced by the challenging regulatory environment for digital assets in the United States, compounded by the state of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/dcg-closes-crypto-institutional-services-subsidiary-tradeblock/">DCG Closes Crypto Institutional Services Subsidiary TradeBlock</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/dcg-closes-crypto-institutional-services-subsidiary-tradeblock/">DCG Closes Crypto Institutional Services Subsidiary TradeBlock</a> was first posted on May 26, 2023 at 6:39 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>TradeBlock, a subsidiary of Digital Currency Group (DCG), is set to cease operations, as reported by <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-05-25/digital-currency-group-closes-tradeblock-institutional-platform?utm_source=google&amp;utm_medium=bd&amp;cmpId=google&amp;sref=3REHEaVI">Bloomberg.</a> <br /><br />A spokesperson from <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/digital-currency-groups-2022-balance-sheet-in-red-with-1-1-billion-loss/">DCG</a> explained that the decision to close down the institutional trading platform side of the business was influenced by the challenging regulatory environment for digital assets in the United States, compounded by the state of the broader economy and the prolonged crypto winter.<br /><br />CoinDesk, another subsidiary of DCG, <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20210105005308/en/CoinDesk-Acquires-TradeBlock-the-World%E2%80%99s-Leading-Crypto-Index-Provider">acquired</a> TradeBlock in January 2021. Following the acquisition, some aspects of TradeBlock&#8217;s operations were integrated into CoinDesk, while other components were spun off into a separate entity, according to Bloomberg.<br /><br />DCG has faced other setbacks this year, including the closure of its wealth management unit, HQ Digital, due to economic headwinds. Additionally, DCG&#8217;s subsidiary, Genesis, has encountered difficulties with its lending arm, which filed for bankruptcy in January. With a significant debt of $3.5 billion owed to creditors, Genesis has been engaged in discussions with capital providers to address the situation.<br /><br />Furthermore, Genesis has been involved in a dispute with Gemini, a former collaborator, over a missed payment of $630 million related to their Earn product, which enabled users to earn interest on their cryptocurrency investments.<br /><br />DCG&#8217;s other subsidiaries have also been impacted by various circumstances. HQ Digital, the wealth management subsidiary, was closed down in January, while Luno, DCG&#8217;s cryptocurrency exchange, discontinued interest-bearing savings wallets in November 2022.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/dcg-closes-crypto-institutional-services-subsidiary-tradeblock/">DCG Closes Crypto Institutional Services Subsidiary TradeBlock</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/dcg-closes-crypto-institutional-services-subsidiary-tradeblock/">DCG Closes Crypto Institutional Services Subsidiary TradeBlock</a> was first posted on May 26, 2023 at 6:39 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>