<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>Latest Crypto News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://kryptomoney.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<description>Latest Crypto News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 22:37:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/cropped-cropped-favicon_512x512_v2-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Latest Crypto News</title>
	<link>https://kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><itunes:subtitle>Latest Crypto News</itunes:subtitle><itunes:category text="News &amp; Politics"/><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Business News"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Investing"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Tech News"/></itunes:category><item>
		<title>Stellar Shines as CFTC’s Top Blockchain Advisor</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/stellar-shines-as-cftcs-top-blockchain-advisor/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 22:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar (XLM)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar Development Foundation (SDF)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64049</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>According to reports, the Stellar Development Foundation will join a new advisory council for the US Commodity Futures Trading Commission. In the new entity, the SDF will be in charge of blockchain and digital assets, advising the CFTC on these concerns. Along with Stellar representatives, officials from the Chamber of Digital Commerce, Uniswap Labs, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/stellar-shines-as-cftcs-top-blockchain-advisor/">Stellar Shines as CFTC’s Top Blockchain Advisor</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/stellar-shines-as-cftcs-top-blockchain-advisor/">Stellar Shines as CFTC’s Top Blockchain Advisor</a> was first posted on January 20, 2023 at 5:27 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>According to reports, the S<a href="https://stellar.org/blog/representing-blockchain-on-the-commodity-futures-trading-commissions-global-market-advisory-committee">tellar Development Foundation</a> will join a new advisory council for the US Commodity Futures Trading Commission. In the new entity, the SDF will be in charge of blockchain and digital assets, advising the CFTC on these concerns.<br /><br />Along with Stellar representatives, officials from the Chamber of Digital Commerce, <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/us-sec-opens-investigation-into-decentralized-crypto-exchange-developer-uniswap-labs/">Uniswap Labs,</a> and CoinFund will be on the side of the new digital economy. However, Stellar will be solely responsible for the blockchain&#8217;s direction.<br /><br />J.P. Morgan, Goldman Sachs, and BlackRock have also joined the Global Market Advisory Committee, indicating Stellar&#8217;s optimism for beneficial collaboration with traditional financial market representatives. Stellar (XLM), as a decentralized cross-border money transfer provider in particular, wishes to give special attention to the issue of remittances and stablecoins. <br /><br /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ripple-rival-stellar-releases-impressive-annual-results/">SDF</a> intends to bring up the topic of stablecoins on the digital asset market and their uses in real life, including humanitarian relief, as part of their Stellar Aid Assist initiative on this occasion.<br /><br />Ironically, the event seems almost the exact opposite of what is going on in the other corner between Ripple and the SEC. It turns out that while Stellar, together with the traditional finance giants, oversees crypto policy under the wing of the CFTC, Ripple continues to fight the SEC in court. We have two competing companies, two competing regulators, and two opposing situations.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/stellar-shines-as-cftcs-top-blockchain-advisor/">Stellar Shines as CFTC’s Top Blockchain Advisor</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/stellar-shines-as-cftcs-top-blockchain-advisor/">Stellar Shines as CFTC’s Top Blockchain Advisor</a> was first posted on January 20, 2023 at 5:27 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nexo Settles With SEC for $45 Million</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/nexo-settles-with-sec-for-45-million/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 21:44:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nexo (NEXO)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64029</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The SEC charged Nexo on Thursday with failing to register its Earn Interest Product retail crypto asset lending product. Nexo agreed to pay a $45 million penalty to satisfy the charges brought against the company. Nexo has agreed to pay the SEC $22.5 million in fines, as well as state authorities $22.5 million in fines. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/nexo-settles-with-sec-for-45-million/">Nexo Settles With SEC for $45 Million</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/nexo-settles-with-sec-for-45-million/">Nexo Settles With SEC for $45 Million</a> was first posted on January 20, 2023 at 4:44 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The SEC charged <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/nexo-crypto-lending-platform-adds-bitcoin-cash-support/">Nexo</a> on Thursday with failing to register its Earn Interest Product retail crypto asset lending product. Nexo agreed to pay a $45 million penalty to satisfy the charges brought against the company. Nexo has agreed to pay the SEC $22.5 million in fines, as well as state authorities $22.5 million in fines. <br /><br />Nexo faced regulatory scrutiny for its EIP in September 2022 from eight states in the United States, including California, Kentucky, New York, Maryland, Oklahoma, South Carolina, Washington, and Vermont. State officials said that Nexo sold its products without registering them as securities and without properly disclosing them to customers.<br /><br />According to the SEC, Nexo began providing its EIP in June 2020, allowing US investors to surrender their crypto holdings in exchange for a promise of interest. After the SEC filed similar accusations against another company in February 2022, Nexo discontinued marketing its product to new investors. According to a <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2023-11">press release</a> issued by the SEC:<br /><br />According to the SEC’s order, in or around June 2020, Nexo began to offer and sell the EIP in the United States. The EIP allowed U.S. investors to tender their crypto assets to Nexo in exchange for Nexo’s promise to pay interest.<br /><br />The order states that Nexo marketed the EIP as a means for investors to earn interest on their crypto assets, and Nexo exercised its discretion to use investors’ crypto assets in various ways to generate income for its own business and to fund interest payments to EIP investors. The order finds that the EIP is a security and that the offer and sale of the EIP did not qualify for an exemption from SEC registration. Therefore, Nexo was required to register its offer and sale of the EIP, which it failed to do.<br /><br />Despite the SEC and state regulators&#8217; claims, Nexo is also the focus of a large-scale investigation in Bulgaria for suspicions of money laundering, computer fraud, tax evasion, and other offenses. Over 300 police officers searched the company&#8217;s offices in Bulgaria.<br /><br />Nexo also sued the Cayman Islands Monetary Authority (CIMA) for denying its application to become a virtual asset service provider (VASP) in the jurisdiction. Nexo&#8217;s plan to sue CIMA comes after the regulator denied the lender&#8217;s registration as a VASP due to regulatory and enforcement concerns. <br /><br />According to CIMA, <em>&#8220;Nexo posed a risk to market confidence, consumer protection and the reputation of the Islands as a financial centre.&#8221;</em> Nexo is requesting that CIMA&#8217;s judgment be reversed and that the lender be granted VASP registration.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/nexo-settles-with-sec-for-45-million/">Nexo Settles With SEC for $45 Million</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/nexo-settles-with-sec-for-45-million/">Nexo Settles With SEC for $45 Million</a> was first posted on January 20, 2023 at 4:44 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BREAKING: Bitcoin Surpasses $22K, Hedera (HBAR) Rallies 35% Within Hours, Here Is the Reason for the Rise and What Analysts Say</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/breaking-bitcoin-surpasses-22k-hedera-hbar-rallies-35-within-hours-here-is-the-reason-for-the-rise-and-what-analysts-say/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 21:38:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hedera (HBAR)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64042</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>After falling the previous day, Bitcoin rose once more to a comfortable level substantially above $21,000. The action caused bitcoin to rise to intraday highs of $22,456, which was last reached in September 2022. The lead cryptocurrency was recently trading at over $22,276, up 5.76% over the previous 24 hours, as investors ignored the most [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/breaking-bitcoin-surpasses-22k-hedera-hbar-rallies-35-within-hours-here-is-the-reason-for-the-rise-and-what-analysts-say/">BREAKING: Bitcoin Surpasses $22K, Hedera (HBAR) Rallies 35% Within Hours, Here Is the Reason for the Rise and What Analysts Say</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/breaking-bitcoin-surpasses-22k-hedera-hbar-rallies-35-within-hours-here-is-the-reason-for-the-rise-and-what-analysts-say/">BREAKING: Bitcoin Surpasses $22K, Hedera (HBAR) Rallies 35% Within Hours, Here Is the Reason for the Rise and What Analysts Say</a> was first posted on January 20, 2023 at 4:38 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>After falling the previous day, Bitcoin rose once more to a comfortable level substantially above $21,000. The action caused bitcoin to rise to intraday highs of $22,456, which was last reached in September 2022.<br /><br />The <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-mining-difficulty-soars-to-new-heights-with-10-increase-as-miners-return/">lead cryptocurrency</a> was recently trading at over $22,276, up 5.76% over the previous 24 hours, as investors ignored the most recent consequences of the disgraced crypto exchange FTX and conflicting economic statistics. BTC kept following the more optimistic course throughout 2023.<br /><br />The Crypto market is showing a decoupling from equities. The tech-heavy Nasdaq fell 1% this week, while the S&amp;P 500 and Dow Jones Industrial Average (DJIA) also fell by more than a percentage point. Equities markets also continued to lose ground this week.<br /><br />Investors struggled to square declines in housing starts and building permits with the publication of jobs data showing that the strong job market had not cooled, which showed a 15,000 weekly fall in Americans applying for unemployment. <br /><br />The former suggested that the economy is not cooling sufficiently to appease central bankers, which is bad news for cryptocurrency, while the latter implied the opposite.<br /><br /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/hbar-price-analysis-what-to-watch-in-hbar-as-it-ticks-higher-hedera-set-to-launch-its-first-defi-project/">Hedera (HBAR)</a> is up 33% in the last 24 hours at $0.076 and up 51% in the last seven days. Hedera has been named the winner of The Innovation Awards in the category “Innovation in DLT, Blockchain, and Crypto” per a Dmagazine report. <br /><br />Avery Dennison, one of the most important material sciences companies in the world, confirmed Hedera’s attendance at the World Economic Forum this year. The same company is currently one of Hedera’s partners, which means the network is already attracting partners that are aligned with the WEF’s efficiency and sustainability plans.<br /><br />Over the past seven days, the Hedera network has set new milestones, processing more than 323 million transactions, averaging 535 TPS. It also reached a new throughput ATH of 8,061 TPS while Achieving transaction finality in 3.56 seconds (avg).</p>
<h2>Here Is What Analysts Say About the Bullish Scenario</h2>
<p>The resilience of bitcoin in the wake of the Genesis bankruptcy news didn&#8217;t come as a surprise to traders. The GBTC discount immediately widened again as the market seems to have been anticipating the Genesis bankruptcy filing for the previous 48 hours. <br /><br /><em>&#8221;Genesis declaring bankruptcy removes a cloud of doom from the market, allowing cryptocurrency investors to concentrate on the fundamentals,&#8221;</em> Markus Thielen, head of strategy and research at cryptocurrency services provider Matrixport stated.<br /><br /><em>&#8220;In 2023, there is a good chance for a breakthrough that might start a new bull market. The development of layer 2 solutions, ZK-rollups, privacy solutions, and many other emerging cryptographic capabilities excite us,&#8221;</em> Bitwise&#8217;s analysts under the direction of Chief Investment Officer Matthew Hougan noted.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/breaking-bitcoin-surpasses-22k-hedera-hbar-rallies-35-within-hours-here-is-the-reason-for-the-rise-and-what-analysts-say/">BREAKING: Bitcoin Surpasses $22K, Hedera (HBAR) Rallies 35% Within Hours, Here Is the Reason for the Rise and What Analysts Say</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/breaking-bitcoin-surpasses-22k-hedera-hbar-rallies-35-within-hours-here-is-the-reason-for-the-rise-and-what-analysts-say/">BREAKING: Bitcoin Surpasses $22K, Hedera (HBAR) Rallies 35% Within Hours, Here Is the Reason for the Rise and What Analysts Say</a> was first posted on January 20, 2023 at 4:38 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Verasity (VRA) Rallied 150%? Five On-Chain Indicators Signal Early Bull Cycle Might Be Near for Bitcoin and Altcoins</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/why-verasity-vra-rallied-150-five-on-chain-indicators-signal-early-bull-cycle-might-be-near-for-bitcoin-and-altcoins/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 21:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto market prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Verasity (VRA)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64033</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Verasity (VRA) has rallied over 65% in the last 24 hours. At the time of writing, VRA was trading at $0.0071 at press time and is up 150% since the past week. Founded on May 18, 2018, Verasity (VRA) is the next generation of video-sharing aimed at creating a fair system for creators to earn [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/why-verasity-vra-rallied-150-five-on-chain-indicators-signal-early-bull-cycle-might-be-near-for-bitcoin-and-altcoins/">Why Verasity (VRA) Rallied 150%? Five On-Chain Indicators Signal Early Bull Cycle Might Be Near for Bitcoin and Altcoins</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/why-verasity-vra-rallied-150-five-on-chain-indicators-signal-early-bull-cycle-might-be-near-for-bitcoin-and-altcoins/">Why Verasity (VRA) Rallied 150%? Five On-Chain Indicators Signal Early Bull Cycle Might Be Near for Bitcoin and Altcoins</a> was first posted on January 20, 2023 at 4:00 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/verasitys-vra-token-increases-300-because-of-its-product-and-sales-strategy/">Verasity (VRA)</a> has rallied over 65% in the last 24 hours. At the time of writing, VRA was trading at $0.0071 at press time and is up 150% since the past week. <br /><br />Founded on May 18, 2018, Verasity (VRA) is the next generation of video-sharing aimed at creating a fair system for creators to earn from their work and for advertisers to gain value for their ad spend.<br /><br />Since the start of 2023, Verasity has steadily climbed higher. The rally picked up the pace on January 10 when a base was formed at $0.002. Since then, VRA has marked 10 days out of 11 in green. Specifically, it has marked five consecutive days in green since January 16.<br /><br />Today’s rise to intraday highs of $0.0077 was the biggest daily gain since then. Verasity’s rally seemed to be buoyed by technical factors as it saw a breakout above key barriers. The rally might have also been buoyed by the fact that Verasity as a project built on its successes in the previous year. <br /><br />Verasity announced it has an exciting and jam-packed roadmap for 2023 that it will soon release. In 2022, Verasity inked a partnership with Nasdaq-listed marketplace Brightcove; a major video technology provider to some 3,000 publishers and over 30,000 web publishers worldwide.</p>
<p>Verasity’s Proof of View patent also passed the examination by the Chinese Patent Office, securing PoV’s intellectual property rights in the world’s second-largest—and fastest-growing—advertising market.<br /><br />The VRA staking program was also extended through 2023, locking in VRA staking at 18.25% through to April 2023, when the next phase of staking would be announced.<br /><br />In October 2022 VeraViews became an Amazon Ads Partner, officially joining the Amazon Ads Partner Program.<br /><br />Having passed Amazon verification, VeraViews is listed as a tool provider in the Amazon Ads Partner Directory, offering video measurement, brand safety, advertising effectiveness, and reporting and analytics tools. Amazon Ads Partner status is based on merit and independent review following application, and cannot be paid for. Commercial success for VeraViews is now the key focus for 2023.</p>
<h2>Five On-Chain Indicators Signal Early Bull Market Cycle Might Be Near</h2>
<p>On-chain analytics provider, Cryptoquant has provided an analysis of five on-chain indicators that signal an early bull market.</p>
<p>First are the flows between spot and derivative exchanges. Bitcoin movements from spot to derivative exchanges exhibit that investors have entered &#8220;risk-on&#8221; mode, signaling the beginning of a new bull cycle.</p>
<p>Second, the MVRV ratio is above 1 (1.07), close to its 365-day moving average (orange line), showing that bitcoin is about to start a new uptrend.<br /><br />Third, is the NUPL (Net Unrealized Profit/Loss) metric, which is the average profit margin of bitcoin holders. Like the MVRV ratio, the NUPL is close to its 365-day moving average (orange line), which could mean that bitcoin is about to start a new uptrend.<br /><br />Fourth, Puell Multiple is showing a shift to a positive trend because bitcoin&#8217;s price has passed its 365-day moving average to the upside for the first time in a significant way since November 2020. CryptoQuant&#8217;s P&amp;L Index combines the MVRV ratio, NUPL, and LTH/STH SOPR into a single <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/something-is-brewing-on-bitcoin-btc-and-ethereum-eth-this-is-what-key-and-on-chain-indicators-are-insinuating/">bitcoin</a> value indicator.<br /><br />The PnL Index is close to giving a buying signal for BTC, which happens when the index (dark purple line) crosses its 365-day moving average (light purple line).</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/why-verasity-vra-rallied-150-five-on-chain-indicators-signal-early-bull-cycle-might-be-near-for-bitcoin-and-altcoins/">Why Verasity (VRA) Rallied 150%? Five On-Chain Indicators Signal Early Bull Cycle Might Be Near for Bitcoin and Altcoins</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/why-verasity-vra-rallied-150-five-on-chain-indicators-signal-early-bull-cycle-might-be-near-for-bitcoin-and-altcoins/">Why Verasity (VRA) Rallied 150%? Five On-Chain Indicators Signal Early Bull Cycle Might Be Near for Bitcoin and Altcoins</a> was first posted on January 20, 2023 at 4:00 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top 5 Altcoins To Invest In 2023</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/top-5-altcoins-to-invest-in-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 07:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sponsored]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64038</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What altcoins to buy in a new year? We are ready to present you a small guide to the altcoin world and a brief overview of the best altcoins to invest in. What Is Altcoin? Before you buy altcoins, let’s find out what the word itself means. &#8220;Altcoin&#8221; is a combination of the two words [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/top-5-altcoins-to-invest-in-2023/">Top 5 Altcoins To Invest In 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/top-5-altcoins-to-invest-in-2023/">Top 5 Altcoins To Invest In 2023</a> was first posted on January 20, 2023 at 2:03 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What altcoins to buy in a new year? We are ready to present you a small guide to the altcoin world and a brief overview of the best altcoins to invest in.</p>
<h2>What Is Altcoin?</h2>
<p>Before you buy altcoins, let’s find out what the word itself means.</p>
<p>&#8220;Altcoin&#8221; is a combination of the two words &#8220;alternative&#8221; and &#8220;coin.&#8221; Altcoins are all the cryptocurrencies other than Bitcoin. Some investors even point out that altcoins may be those coins that are not Ethereum as well because most cryptocurrencies are usually forked from either Bitcoin or Ethereum.</p>
<p>Usually altcoins try to distinguish themselves from these two by using other consensus mechanisms and opening new blocks. Developers do it as they have different visions on crypto and its utility. Many altcoins are developed to compete with Bitcoin as means of payment.</p>
<p>By the way, get an <a href="https://cryptomus.com/blog/post/cryptocurrency-merchant-account-solutions-international-business-merchant-account">international merchant service</a> to accept payments in altcoins.</p>
<h2>Types Of Altcoins</h2>
<p>Here is a brief description of every altcoin type:</p>
<h3>Payment Token</h3>
<p>These altcoins are designed to be used as currency. <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/whats-happening-with-bitcoin-ethereum-classic-shiba-inu-and-bitcoin-cash/">Bitcoin Cash</a> is an example of such coins.</p>
<h3>Stablecoins</h3>
<p>Cryptocurrencies are volatile and the only way to use crypto without the fear of price change is to use stablecoins. The volatility is reduced by pegging the price of the crypto to other assets, such as physical currencies and values, such as fiat, precious metals, or even other cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Tether&#8217;s <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/tether-usdt-to-be-offered-in-24000-brazilian-atms/">USDT</a> is the most notable stablecoin out there. It is pegged to the USD and is widely used to save crypto assets from volatility.</p>
<h3>Security Tokens</h3>
<p>These assets are tokenized stock market securities. The process of tokenization is a transfer of value from an asset to a token. Anything can be tokenized – from stocks to real estate. Although, the asset tokenized must be secured and held, as it adds value to the token.</p>
<h3>Utility Tokens</h3>
<p>Utility tokens are used to provide services within a network. Use them to pay network fees, purchase services, or redeem rewards. The tokens can be purchased on exchanges and held, but they are meant to be used in the blockchain network to keep it functioning.</p>
<h3>Meme Coins</h3>
<p>Meme coins are inspired by jokes or a silly take on other cryptocurrencies. They usually get hyped on the internet and gain a short period of popularity. This allows the investors to obtain short-term gains.</p>
<h3>Governance Tokens</h3>
<p>The rights for voting for changing a protocol or having a say in decisions are what is allowed for the holders of governance tokens. They are not the same as utility tokens as they are native to a private blockchain and are used for blockchain purposes.</p>
<h2>What New Altcoins to Buy in 2023?</h2>
<p>Which new altcoins are worth buying this year? Here is a list of new good altcoins with potential for growth:</p>
<p>Tamadoge (TAMA): It is a memecoin that has its own purpose. Tamadoge is a part of a Play-to-Earn crypto NFT platform that allows users to mint, train and take care of their virtual puppies.</p>
<p>Battle Infinity (IBAT): Another P2E gaming ecosystem that exists in NFT, DeFi, and Metaverse forms. The IBAT is a native altcoin that covers all needs of users.</p>
<p>Lucky Block (LBLOCK): The biggest altcoin to reach $1 billion market cap value.</p>
<p>Enecuum (ENQ): It works on a unique protocol that unites all mobile devices in a single network offering vast reserves of computing power to its users.</p>
<h2>The Best Altcoins To Invest In</h2>
<p>We compiled a list of the best altcoins for you:</p>
<h3>Ether (ETH)</h3>
<p>Ethereum is the second largest coin after Bitcoin and the biggest altcoin. The digital asset has all the potential to become even bigger.</p>
<p>It is an open-sourced and distributed computing network. Being a favorite of program developers because of its potential applications: non-fungible tokens (NFTs), smart contracts hosting and dApps creation.</p>
<h3>Litecoin (LTC)</h3>
<p>One of the oldest altcoins. It’s just a peer-to-peer digital asset. The uniqueness of it is in Litecoin’s fully decentralized nature. The coin aims to overcome Bitcoin by its fast confirmation speed.</p>
<h3>Dogecoin (DOGE)</h3>
<p>Dogecoin is one of the most popular cryptocurrencies to buy this year. The open-sourced digital currency works on a Proof-of-work consensus. It is an original meme coin that started as a joke in 2013. The token became popular because of the social media backing led by Elon Musk. Gaining a huge amount of attention, Doge soon became a prominent cryptocurrency.</p>
<h3>Bitcoin Cash (BCH)</h3>
<p>Bitcoin Cash is a faster and cheaper fork of Bitcoin. While Bitcoin is regarded as a store of value like gold, Bitcoin Cash is treated as a payment provider.</p>
<h3>Tether (USDT)</h3>
<p>Tether is not like the other cryptocurrencies in the list. It is a stablecoin, which means that the asset is backed up by fiat currencies and keeps a value equal to the currency it is pegged to. Tether value is supposed to be more stable than the value of other currencies. Investors who are wary of the extreme volatility of other coins prefer it to other coins.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/top-5-altcoins-to-invest-in-2023/">Top 5 Altcoins To Invest In 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/top-5-altcoins-to-invest-in-2023/">Top 5 Altcoins To Invest In 2023</a> was first posted on January 20, 2023 at 2:03 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>HBAR Price Analysis: HBAR Positions for 2023, Hedera Wins Innovation Awards Category in DLT, Blockchain and Crypto</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/hbar-price-analysis-hbar-positions-for-2023-hedera-wins-innovation-awards-category-in-dlt-blockchain-and-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 22:54:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HBAR/USD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HBAR/USD Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hedera Hashgraph (HBAR)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64023</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hedera is up 5.07% in the last 24 hours at $0.059 Hedera has been named winner of The Innovation Awards, in the category &#8220;Innovation in DLT, Blockchain, and Crypto&#8221; The hedera community is rocking so hard at World Economic Forum (WEF) Davos 2023 Hedera (HBAR) is up 5.07% in the last 24 hours at $0.059 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/hbar-price-analysis-hbar-positions-for-2023-hedera-wins-innovation-awards-category-in-dlt-blockchain-and-crypto/">HBAR Price Analysis: HBAR Positions for 2023, Hedera Wins Innovation Awards Category in DLT, Blockchain and Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/hbar-price-analysis-hbar-positions-for-2023-hedera-wins-innovation-awards-category-in-dlt-blockchain-and-crypto/">HBAR Price Analysis: HBAR Positions for 2023, Hedera Wins Innovation Awards Category in DLT, Blockchain and Crypto</a> was first posted on January 19, 2023 at 5:54 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li>Hedera is up 5.07% in the last 24 hours at $0.059</li>
<li>Hedera has been named winner of The Innovation Awards, in the category <em>&#8220;Innovation in DLT, Blockchain, and Crypto&#8221;</em></li>
<li>The hedera community is rocking so hard at World Economic Forum (WEF) Davos 2023</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-influencer-reveals-why-he-moved-from-solana-to-hedera-hbar-internet-computericp-and-algorand/">Hedera (HBAR)</a> is up 5.07% in the last 24 hours at $0.059 and up 21.11% in the last seven days. Hedera has been named the winner of The Innovation Awards in the categor<em>y &#8220;Innovation in DLT, Blockchain, and Crypto&#8221;</em> per a Dmagazine report. Avery Dennison, one of the most important material sciences companies in the world, confirmed Hedera’s attendance at the World Economic Forum this year. The same company is currently one of Hedera’s partners, which means the network is already attracting partners that are aligned with the WEF’s efficiency and sustainability plans. The Hedera community is rocking so hard at World Economic Forum (WEF) Davos 2023. Hedera says it ranks the 12th highest by influence on Twitter. As stated in a blog post, smart contracts will pay rent on Hedera starting in February 2023. As defined, <em>&#8220;rent&#8221;</em> is the recurring payment required for contracts to remain active on the network and is comprised of auto-renewal and storage fees. Smart contracts on Hedera can pay for rent in two ways: with external funds or contract funds.<br /><br /><strong>Key Levels</strong><br />Resistance Levels: $0.0850, $0.0750, $0.0600<br />Support Levels: $0.0550, $0.0450, $0.0350</p>
<h4>HBAR/USD Daily Chart: Ranging</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1488" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-64034 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-Daily-Jan-19.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-Daily-Jan-19.png 1488w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-Daily-Jan-19-300x139.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-Daily-Jan-19-1024x473.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-Daily-Jan-19-768x355.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-Daily-Jan-19-750x347.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-Daily-Jan-19-1140x527.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1488px) 100vw, 1488px" /><em><span style="color: #999999">HBAR/USD Daily Chart</span></em></h6>
<p>A price break of the moving average (MA 200) on the daily chart indicates a mild price breakout region. Near-term range trading is likely to continue as the 36th-largest cryptocurrency battles to stay above the $0.0500 region, which serves as a critical zone. Because of a surge in positive bias, positive momentum is increasing while negative momentum is declining.<br /><br />Hedera has regained some of its losses after plunging to the $0.0355 level. Buyers may come through around the $0.0600 handle in an attempt to strengthen the positive bounce after recovering from the loss. The Relative Strength Index, which indicates a surge in upward momentum, contributes to the bullish traction from the yearly low of $0.0355.</p>
<h4>HBAR/USD 4-Hour Chart: Bullish</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1488" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-64035 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19.png 1488w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19-300x139.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19-1024x473.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19-768x355.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19-750x347.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HBARUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19-1140x527.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1488px) 100vw, 1488px" /><em><span style="color: #999999">HBAR/USD 4-Hour Chart</span></em></h6>
<p><br />According to the short-term oscillators, bulls are currently backing additional gains in the pair toward the $0.0600 level. Bears, on the other hand, may sell on rallies that fall below the 4-hour moving average (MA 50) at $0.0522. If investors keep the surge going above this mark, the $0.0700 barrier could represent the first point of resistance on the upside.<br /><br />If favorable forces start to weaken, preliminary support might be at $0.0550. If the bearish trend persists, the price may target the short-term MA 200 at about $0.0440. <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/hbar-price-analysis-hedera-crosses-the-2-5-billion-transaction-mark-in-a-major-milestone-what-happens-to-price/">HBAR/USD</a> is showing an upward tendency, and bulls must push the price above the $0.0600 level to oppose bears.</p>
<p><strong>Note:</strong><em> Kryptomoney.com is not a financial advisor. Do your research before investing your funds in any financial asset or presented product or event. We are not responsible for your investing results</em></p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/hbar-price-analysis-hbar-positions-for-2023-hedera-wins-innovation-awards-category-in-dlt-blockchain-and-crypto/">HBAR Price Analysis: HBAR Positions for 2023, Hedera Wins Innovation Awards Category in DLT, Blockchain and Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/hbar-price-analysis-hbar-positions-for-2023-hedera-wins-innovation-awards-category-in-dlt-blockchain-and-crypto/">HBAR Price Analysis: HBAR Positions for 2023, Hedera Wins Innovation Awards Category in DLT, Blockchain and Crypto</a> was first posted on January 19, 2023 at 5:54 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CoinDesk: Rumors of a Potential Sale Surface as It Considers Options</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/coindesk-rumors-of-a-potential-sale-surface-as-it-considers-options/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 21:34:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64025</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Genesis came first, then Coindesk. Barry Silbert&#8217;s empire seems to be in peril; reportedly, it is thinking about selling some of its subsidiaries to deal with cash flow problems. On January 18, 2023, Kevin Worth, the CEO of CoinDesk, a division of Digital Currency Group that publishes news on cryptocurrencies, announced that the company has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/coindesk-rumors-of-a-potential-sale-surface-as-it-considers-options/">CoinDesk: Rumors of a Potential Sale Surface as It Considers Options</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/coindesk-rumors-of-a-potential-sale-surface-as-it-considers-options/">CoinDesk: Rumors of a Potential Sale Surface as It Considers Options</a> was first posted on January 19, 2023 at 4:34 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-firm-genesis-to-file-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy-details/">Genesis</a> came first, then Coindesk. Barry Silbert&#8217;s empire seems to be in peril; reportedly, it is thinking about selling some of its subsidiaries to deal with cash flow problems.<br /><br />On January 18, 2023, Kevin Worth, the CEO of CoinDesk, a division of Digital Currency Group that publishes news on cryptocurrencies, announced that the company has hired investment bankers from Lazard LTD to assist them in exploring alternatives for a partial or full sale of the business.<br /><br />According to <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/crypto-media-outlet-coindesk-taps-bankers-for-potential-sale-11674076000">The Wall Street Journal</a>, Worth discussed how prospective investors were enthusiastic about owning the online website:<br /><br /><em>“Over the last few months, we have received numerous inbound indications of interest in CoinDesk,”</em><br /><br />The <em>&#8220;Consensus&#8221;</em> summit, one of the largest crypto events in the United States, is organized by<a href="https://www.coindesk.com/advertise/"> Coindesk</a>, which boasts over 5 million monthly visitors on its website (<a href="https://www.similarweb.com/website/coindesk.com/#overview">Similarweb</a> claims over 10 million visitors). Coindesk has also expanded to other products, such as a newsletter and a YouTube channel.<br /><br />CoinDesk seems to be a success, but the parent company&#8217;s liquidity problems aren&#8217;t caused by a media site that isn&#8217;t performing well; rather, they are primarily the result of the <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/cardano-network-receives-bullish-catalysts-heres-what-might-be-next-for-bitcoin-ethereum-altcoins-after-ftx-collapse/">FTX contagion</a> and a dispute with the Winklevoss twins, who founded the Gemini cryptocurrency exchange after DCG-owned crypto lender Genesis stopped allowing withdrawals and messed with Gemini&#8217;s<em> &#8220;Earn&#8221;</em> program.<br /><br />The Winklevii have openly demanded DCG CEO Barry Silbert&#8217;s resignation and charged the business with ignoring their attempts to come to a mutually beneficial agreement. Additionally, Genesis and DCG were both recently sued by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for allegedly marketing unregistered securities.<br /><br />After failing to raise money, Genesis may be ready to declare bankruptcy this week. The cryptocurrency fund was left with a liquidity shortfall of more than $175 million as a result of FTX&#8217;s demise, which prevented it from restarting customer withdrawals.<br /><br />CoinDesk or Genesis, as well as other prominent DCG-owned cryptocurrency companies like Foundry, Grayscale Investments, and Luno, may be sold in the future. While this could help with some or all of DCG&#8217;s financial problems, it could also have a large effect on the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/coindesk-rumors-of-a-potential-sale-surface-as-it-considers-options/">CoinDesk: Rumors of a Potential Sale Surface as It Considers Options</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/coindesk-rumors-of-a-potential-sale-surface-as-it-considers-options/">CoinDesk: Rumors of a Potential Sale Surface as It Considers Options</a> was first posted on January 19, 2023 at 4:34 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>National Australia Bank Unveils Stablecoin on Ethereum and Algorand</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/national-australia-bank-unveils-stablecoin-on-ethereum-and-algorand/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 20:42:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorand]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National Australia Bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64012</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Given recent reluctance and more recent implosion of Terra, other nations have been intending to investigate stablecoins. One of Australia&#8217;s four main financial institutions, the National Australia Bank (NAB), is the most recent to join the bandwagon. The Ethereum and Algorand blockchain networks will soon host the NAB-created AUDN stablecoin, which is tethered to the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/national-australia-bank-unveils-stablecoin-on-ethereum-and-algorand/">National Australia Bank Unveils Stablecoin on Ethereum and Algorand</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/national-australia-bank-unveils-stablecoin-on-ethereum-and-algorand/">National Australia Bank Unveils Stablecoin on Ethereum and Algorand</a> was first posted on January 19, 2023 at 3:42 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Given recent reluctance and more recent implosion of Terra, other nations have been intending to investigate <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/stablecoins-might-soon-be-officially-categorized-as-securities/">stablecoins</a>. One of Australia&#8217;s four main financial institutions, the National Australia Bank (NAB), is the most recent to join the bandwagon.<br /><br />The Ethereum and Algorand blockchain networks will soon host the NAB-created AUDN stablecoin, which is tethered to the Australian dollar. By the middle of 2023, completion is anticipated.<br /><br />The AUDN would allow users to settle transactions on blockchain technology in real-time using Australian dollars, according to a report from the <a href="https://www.afr.com/companies/financial-services/nab-creates-a-stablecoin-in-boost-for-digital-economy-20230117-p5cd8f">Australian Financial Review (AFR)</a>. According to the NAB, the stablecoin is intended to be used for a variety of tasks, including the trade of carbon credits, international money transfers, and repurchase agreements. The bank will also be in charge of keeping the Australian stablecoin backed by currency.<br /><br />NAB Chief Innovation Officer Howard Silby was cited as stating in a release,</p>
<blockquote>
<p>“We certainly believe there are elements of blockchain technology that will form part of the future of finance […] From our point of view, we see [blockchain] has the potential to deliver instantaneous, transparent, inclusive, financial outcomes.”</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The SWIFT network, an antiquated system, dominates the existing infrastructure for international transactions. However, many users may find the launch of AUDN to be a worthwhile substitute.<br /><br />The change occurs four months after Australian Senator Andrew Bragg introduced a bill attempting to strictly regulate the domestic bitcoin market. The measure mandated that stablecoin issuers and exchanges for digital assets report to authorities about their business practices. It also targeted Chinese banks operating in the nation that deal with digital yuan.<br /><br />NAB has launched AUDN, an Australian dollar-pegged stablecoin on the Ethereum network, making it the second major bank in the nation to do so. In partnership with cryptocurrency custodian Fireblocks, Australia and New Zealand Banking Group (ANZ) created a stablecoin that was tethered to the Australian dollar last year.<br /><br />Russia and Iran reportedly discussed the introduction of a new cryptocurrency backed by gold this week. The token would be produced as a stablecoin, according to Alexander Brazhnikov, executive director of the Russian Association of the Crypto Industry and Blockchain.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/national-australia-bank-unveils-stablecoin-on-ethereum-and-algorand/">National Australia Bank Unveils Stablecoin on Ethereum and Algorand</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/national-australia-bank-unveils-stablecoin-on-ethereum-and-algorand/">National Australia Bank Unveils Stablecoin on Ethereum and Algorand</a> was first posted on January 19, 2023 at 3:42 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XTZ Price Analysis: XTZ Steadies Above Key Psychological Level; Tezos Set To Undergo Its Most “Transformative” Update</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/xtz-price-analysis-xtz-steadies-above-key-psychological-level-tezos-set-to-undergo-its-most-transformative-update/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:53:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tezos (XTZ)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XTZ/USD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XTZ/USD Price Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64005</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tezos (XTZ) is up 2% in the last 24 hours as its price steadies near psychological $1 mark A whole new level of scaling capabilities within the Tezos network and beyond are expected to be introduced with the Mumbai upgrade plan This is one of the most &#8220;transformative&#8221; updates for the well-known proof-of-stake blockchain Tezos [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/xtz-price-analysis-xtz-steadies-above-key-psychological-level-tezos-set-to-undergo-its-most-transformative-update/">XTZ Price Analysis: XTZ Steadies Above Key Psychological Level; Tezos Set To Undergo Its Most “Transformative” Update</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/xtz-price-analysis-xtz-steadies-above-key-psychological-level-tezos-set-to-undergo-its-most-transformative-update/">XTZ Price Analysis: XTZ Steadies Above Key Psychological Level; Tezos Set To Undergo Its Most “Transformative” Update</a> was first posted on January 18, 2023 at 7:53 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li>Tezos (XTZ) is up 2% in the last 24 hours as its price steadies near psychological $1 mark</li>
<li>A whole new level of scaling capabilities within the Tezos network and beyond are expected to be introduced with the Mumbai upgrade plan</li>
<li>This is one of the most <em>&#8220;transformative&#8221;</em> updates for the well-known proof-of-stake blockchain</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/xtz-price-analysis-tezos-xtz-up-19-as-crypto-market-recovers-binance-us-announces-tezos-giveaway/">Tezos (XTZ)</a> is up 2% in the last 24 hours as its price steadies near psychological $1 mark. A whole new level of scaling capabilities within the Tezos network and beyond are expected to be introduced with the Mumbai upgrade plan, which was presented by Nomadic Labs, the top blockchain developer in the Tezos community. This is one of the most <em>&#8220;transformative&#8221;</em> updates for the well-known proof-of-stake blockchain, according to Tezos co-founder Arthur Breitman. The main features made public by Nomadic Labs include the activation of smart rollups, the introduction of Epoxy on Mainnet, which will further strengthen instant finality due to SNARKs proof-of-validity, a 15-second block time reduction, ticket transfers between accounts, and the addition of two new RPC endpoints for better visibility into ticket ownership. All of these improvements are anticipated to significantly increase scalability, resulting in more productive transactions and processing power for Tezos network users. The faster transaction assurance and extensive ticket transfer functionality between user accounts will both depend on the reduced block time feature.<br /><br /><strong>Key Levels</strong><br />Resistance Levels: $2.00, %1.50, $1.00<br />Support Levels: $0.92, $0.70, $0.500</p>
<h4>XTZ/USD Daily Chart: Ranging</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1488" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-64018 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-Daily-Jan-19.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-Daily-Jan-19.png 1488w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-Daily-Jan-19-300x139.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-Daily-Jan-19-1024x473.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-Daily-Jan-19-768x355.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-Daily-Jan-19-750x347.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-Daily-Jan-19-1140x527.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1488px) 100vw, 1488px" /><em><span style="color: #999999">XTZ/USD Daily Chart</span></em></h6>
<p>Following a brief consolidation, <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/xtz-price-analysis-striking-rally-holds-back-beneath-4-43-on-xtz-usd-tezos-q2-growth-remains-positive-on-etoro/">XTZ/USD</a> recorded a mild retracement after breaking above the $1.00 barrier to approach daily moving average (MA 200). The near-term oscillators are supporting the move higher, with the RSI strengthening inside the bullish zone despite the lack of confirmation of overbought conditions. <br /><br />If buying demand remains strong, initial resistance might come from the $1.50 level before the bulls target the $2.0 handle. If the price falls below the psychological level of $1.00 and approaches the previous range low of $0.70, a critical support zone could form between the $0.70 and the daily MA 50 at $0.90. Tezos aims to return to an ascending trend pattern.</p>
<h4>XTZ/USD 4-Hour Chart: Ranging</h4>
<h6><img loading="lazy" width="1488" height="688" class="alignnone wp-image-64019 size-full" src="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19.png" alt="" srcset="https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19.png 1488w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19-300x139.png 300w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19-1024x473.png 1024w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19-768x355.png 768w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19-750x347.png 750w, https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XTZUSD-4-Hour-Jan-19-1140x527.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1488px) 100vw, 1488px" /><em><span style="color: #999999">XTZ/USD 4-Hour Chart</span></em></h6>
<p>XTZ/USD recorded fresh selling above the 4-hour moving average (MA 50) near the $1.08 level, extending its retracement impulse to a new low of $0.964 on Wednesday. The market&#8217;s enthusiasm pushed the RSI into the overbought zone, while the indicator showed no symptoms of weakness. <br /><br />Currently, the price appears to be under pressure near the $0.950 mark. If the bulls take that level, the path to $1.50 and $2.00 will open up. Higher, the surge could go to the $2.50 level. On the downside, initial constraints may arise near $0.90, a break of which may result in some consolidation near the MA 200 at $0.825. The $0.70 low and the neighboring MA 200 at $0.825 may also be important levels to monitor.</p>
<p><strong>Note:</strong><em> Kryptomoney.com is not a financial advisor. Do your research before investing your funds in any financial asset or presented product or event. We are not responsible for your investing results</em></p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/xtz-price-analysis-xtz-steadies-above-key-psychological-level-tezos-set-to-undergo-its-most-transformative-update/">XTZ Price Analysis: XTZ Steadies Above Key Psychological Level; Tezos Set To Undergo Its Most “Transformative” Update</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/xtz-price-analysis-xtz-steadies-above-key-psychological-level-tezos-set-to-undergo-its-most-transformative-update/">XTZ Price Analysis: XTZ Steadies Above Key Psychological Level; Tezos Set To Undergo Its Most “Transformative” Update</a> was first posted on January 18, 2023 at 7:53 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ConsenSys To Cut 11% of Its Workforce Amidst Crypto Market Slowdown</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/consensys-to-cut-11-of-its-workforce-amidst-crypto-market-slowdown/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinuola Wealth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 23:26:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consensys]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=64008</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ConsenSys, the founder of MetaMask and an Ethereum development company, has revealed plans to lay off 11% of its personnel. CEO Joseph Lubin confirmed the decision in a blog post today. ConsenSys will lay off 97 employees as part of its attempts to fight &#8220;challenging and uncertain market conditions,&#8221; according to Lubin. Furthermore, the decision [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/consensys-to-cut-11-of-its-workforce-amidst-crypto-market-slowdown/">ConsenSys To Cut 11% of Its Workforce Amidst Crypto Market Slowdown</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/consensys-to-cut-11-of-its-workforce-amidst-crypto-market-slowdown/">ConsenSys To Cut 11% of Its Workforce Amidst Crypto Market Slowdown</a> was first posted on January 18, 2023 at 6:26 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/01/10/ethereum-software-firm-consensys-to-cut-upwards-of-100-staff-as-crypto-bear-market-takes-another-casualty/">ConsenSys</a>, the founder of MetaMask and an Ethereum development company, has revealed plans to lay off 11% of its personnel. CEO Joseph Lubin confirmed the decision in a blog post today.<br /><br />ConsenSys will lay off 97 employees as part of its attempts to fight <em>&#8220;challenging and uncertain market conditions,&#8221;</em> according to Lubin. Furthermore, the decision continues a pattern that has been prevalent in 2023, as companies prepare for a likely economic recession.<br /><br />Although it is only about a month into 2023, the <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/cryptocurrency-hacks-increase-as-north-korea-focuses-on-defi/">cryptocurrency sector</a> has already seen several ups and downs. Prices of popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin have rebounded from the disastrous 2022, which harmed the sector. Despite this, Bitcoin companies have shed 27,000 positions since April 2022.<br /><br />That figure is about to rise, as ConsenSy announced plans to lay off 11% of its workforce in a blog post by CEO Joseph Lubin.<em> “Today we need to make the extremely difficult decision to streamline some of ConsenSys’ teams to adjust to challenging and uncertain market conditions,”</em> Lubin said.<br /><br />Furthermore, <em>“This decision will impact a total of 97 employees, which represents 11% of ConsenSys’ total workforce.”</em> Furthermore, the post noted that departing employees had access to severance compensation based on tenure, with an exercise window ranging from 12 to 36 months. ConsenSys, on the other hand, is providing<em> “personalized support from an external placement agency and extension of healthcare benefits in relevant jurisdictions.”</em></p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/consensys-to-cut-11-of-its-workforce-amidst-crypto-market-slowdown/">ConsenSys To Cut 11% of Its Workforce Amidst Crypto Market Slowdown</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top:black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/consensys-to-cut-11-of-its-workforce-amidst-crypto-market-slowdown/">ConsenSys To Cut 11% of Its Workforce Amidst Crypto Market Slowdown</a> was first posted on January 18, 2023 at 6:26 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>