<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>Latest Crypto News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://kryptomoney.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<description>Latest Crypto News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 14:40:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://kryptomoney.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/cropped-cropped-favicon_512x512_v2-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Latest Crypto News</title>
	<link>https://kryptomoney.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><itunes:subtitle>Latest Crypto News</itunes:subtitle><itunes:category text="News &amp; Politics"/><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Business News"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Investing"/></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Tech News"/></itunes:category><item>
		<title>Chibi Finance $1M “Rug Pull” on Arbitrum Network: ARB Rises Thanks to a Whale, Smart Investors Move to A New Token with A 900% Potential</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/chibi-finance-rug-pull-on-arbitrum-network/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 14:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65290</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>DeFi project Chibi Finance deleted its online presence after redistributing nearly $1 million worth of tokens staked on Arbitrum’s (ARB) network. Although Arbitrum (ARB) is currently surging because of a recent massive withdrawal by an Arbitrum (ARB) whale, smart crypto investors are choosing VC Spectra (SPCT) as a permanent solution because of its amazing 900% [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/chibi-finance-rug-pull-on-arbitrum-network/">Chibi Finance $1M “Rug Pull” on Arbitrum Network: ARB Rises Thanks to a Whale, Smart Investors Move to A New Token with A 900% Potential</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/chibi-finance-rug-pull-on-arbitrum-network/">Chibi Finance $1M “Rug Pull” on Arbitrum Network: ARB Rises Thanks to a Whale, Smart Investors Move to A New Token with A 900% Potential</a> was first posted on June 30, 2023 at 2:32 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>DeFi project Chibi Finance deleted its online presence after redistributing nearly $1 million worth of tokens staked on Arbitrum’s (ARB) network. Although Arbitrum (ARB) is currently surging because of a recent massive withdrawal by an 
Arbitrum (ARB) whale, smart crypto investors are choosing VC Spectra (SPCT) as a permanent solution because of its <strong>amazing 900% potential</strong> and <strong>incredible real-life utility.</strong></p>

<strong><a href="https://vcspectra.io/">BUY SPECTRA TOKENS NOW</a></strong>

<p>Chibi Finance Vanishes After Stealing Over 90,000 Arbitrum (ARB) Tokens</p>

<p>The team behind <strong>Arbitrum (ARB) based DeFi project Chibi Finance</strong> disappeared after stealing user deposits worth approximately $1 million. The rug pull involved <strong>90,563.95</strong> Arbitrum (ARB) tokens staked by Chibi Finance’s users.</p> 

<p>The perpetrators allegedly bridged the funds from Arbitrum’s (ARB) to Ethereum’s (ETH) network and used <strong>Tornado Cash</strong> to cover their tracks. Hence, analysts have advised crypto traders to always do their due diligence and conduct proper research before investing in DeFi projects.</p>

<p>Arbitrum (ARB) is currently priced at <strong>$1.1440</strong>, surging by <strong>17.71%</strong> in the last two weeks. This increase in Arbitrum’s (ARB) price reflects the June 25 massive Binance <strong>withdrawal of 450,881 Arbitrum (ARB) tokens</strong> (worth approximately $507,000) by previously dormant Arbitrum (ARB) whale ‘0x1b67’.</p>

<p>Arbitrum (ARB) enthusiasts believe that the token will manage to uphold its uptrend in the following term. However, bears advise traders to <strong>invest elsewhere</strong> since Chibi Finance is the 12th Arbitrum (ARB) based project to perform a rug pull in 2023.</p>

<h3>VC Spectra (SPCT) Outshines Competitors as a Hidden Crypto Gem</h3>

<p>VC Spectra’s (SPCT) <strong>outstanding stability</strong> and <strong>growth potential</strong> have inspired many investors to move away from unreliable tokens like Arbitrum (ARB). Due to its <strong>advanced real-world utility</strong>, this new crypto gem has attracted a large following in the crypto community while still in the public presale phase.</p>

<p>VC Spectra (SPCT) is a <strong>decentralized hedge fund</strong> that provides optimal gains at a minimal risk via the best investment possibilities in the current market space. VC Spectra (SPCT) explores the most lucrative options in current blockchain projects and technology startups and additionally brings users numerous unique benefits.</p>

<p>VC Spectra (SPCT) token holders can delve into a wide array of tokens and niche markets. The platform’s highly precise <strong>AI systems</strong> detect which projects have the highest chances to succeed through a <strong>rigorous risk analysis</strong> process. Thus, VC Spectra (SPCT) holders can diversify their portfolio with the most viable investments and receive <strong>quarterly dividends and buybacks</strong> from the profits.</p>

<p>Furthermore, VC Spectra (SPCT) convenient interface and visual tools empower users to detect recurring market trends and track their portfolio’s performance. The VC Spectra (SPCT) deflationary token grants exclusive access to pre-ICO discounts and voting rights for future investments.</p>

<p>In other words, VC Spectra (SPCT) token holders can benefit from the platform’s successful core funds while having an active say in its <strong>democratic community</strong>.</p>

<p>Currently priced at <strong>$0.008</strong>, the VC Spectra (SPCT) token will bring investors 37.5% returns once it enters the 2nd presale stage and surges to <strong>$0.011</strong>. However, early adopters will obtain as much as <strong>10x gains</</strong> during the next presale stages and unbelievably more after <a href="https://vcspectra.io/">VC Spectra (SPCT)</a> official launch!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/chibi-finance-rug-pull-on-arbitrum-network/">Chibi Finance $1M “Rug Pull” on Arbitrum Network: ARB Rises Thanks to a Whale, Smart Investors Move to A New Token with A 900% Potential</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/chibi-finance-rug-pull-on-arbitrum-network/">Chibi Finance $1M “Rug Pull” on Arbitrum Network: ARB Rises Thanks to a Whale, Smart Investors Move to A New Token with A 900% Potential</a> was first posted on June 30, 2023 at 2:32 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chainlink Bulls Break The $6 Barrier – Can LINK Copy SPCT and Continue Its Upward Trajectory?</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/chainlink-bulls-break-barrier-continue/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 11:45:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65288</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chainlink (LINK) has seen quite some action in the past few weeks. Finally, it has garnered enough bulls to break out. Yet, there are multiple strong resistance points (places where many people are selling the token), and LINK needs serious bulls to copy SPCT’s 900% surge potential. So, the question remains: can LINK copy VC [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/chainlink-bulls-break-barrier-continue/">Chainlink Bulls Break The $6 Barrier – Can LINK Copy SPCT and Continue Its Upward Trajectory?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/chainlink-bulls-break-barrier-continue/">Chainlink Bulls Break The $6 Barrier – Can LINK Copy SPCT and Continue Its Upward Trajectory?</a> was first posted on June 29, 2023 at 11:38 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Chainlink (LINK) has seen quite some action in the past few weeks. Finally, it has garnered enough bulls to break out. Yet, there are multiple strong resistance points (places where many people are selling the token), and <strong>LINK needs serious bulls to copy SPCT’s 900% surge potential</strong>. So, the question remains: can LINK copy VC Spectra (SPCT) as it has previously copied BTC? Let’s delve into the details!</p>

<h2><strong><a href="https://vcspectra.io/">BUY SPECTRA TOKENS NOW</a></h2></strong>

<h3>Chainlink Bulls Break The $6 Barrier, Yet Things Don’t Seem Too Bullish</h3>

<p>After seeing a long haul from the sub $6 range in the previous weeks, <strong>Chainlink (LINK) has finally broken through the $6 barrier</strong>. LINK followed in as BTC plummeted 16% and hit its monthly high of $31,233. However, LINK immediately faced its first resistance point of $6.36, which it couldn’t break.</p>

<p>Consequently, <strong>a slightly bearish trend closed the Chainlink token trade at $5.91</strong>. Regardless of the settling bear trend, the bulls finally rose, and the Chainlink token gained 5.49% and <strong>rose above the resistance line of $6.36 momentarily before dropping to $6.1-ish levels on 25th June</strong>.</p>

<p>Getting to the overall trend, the 4H and weekly Chainlink charts clearly show <strong>a growing bear market for LINK</strong>. The token is being oversold, which might result in a further drop in its value. This situation resembles April’s bear market for the Chainlink (LINK) token.</p>

<p>With the recent up trend, we finally see some action from the Chainlink bulls resulting in a slightly bullish trend. However, the $6.36 resistance line might be too much for the bulls after two failed attempts to break through.</p>

<p>Whether Chainlink’s LINK token can break the resistance and turn strongly bullish as the SPCT token entirely depends on its market cap and overall volume, which, as of the time of this writing, is not looking bullish.</p>

<h3>VC Spectra (SPCT) Overtakes the Market with An Upward Trajectory</h3>

<p>VC Spectra (SPCT), the parent chain of the SPCT token, has already raised more than $2.3 million in presales. This ultimately promises its investors a <strong>900% surge</strong> and <strong>10x</strong> their investment as the VC Spectra token price draws nearer to the launch target of <strong>$0.08</strong> from the current price of <strong>$0.008</strong>.</p>

<p>Additionally, VC Spectra (SPCT) is well on its way to maintaining its upward trajectory. With multiple investment portfolios and the strong backing of a hedge fund, VC Spectra (SPCT) is looking to top the charts in green. Especially since there are <strong>no intermediaries involved</strong>, users have <strong>full authority over their funds</strong> and can move them around at will.</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/chainlink-bulls-break-barrier-continue/">Chainlink Bulls Break The $6 Barrier – Can LINK Copy SPCT and Continue Its Upward Trajectory?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/chainlink-bulls-break-barrier-continue/">Chainlink Bulls Break The $6 Barrier – Can LINK Copy SPCT and Continue Its Upward Trajectory?</a> was first posted on June 29, 2023 at 11:38 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is the Minimum RSP Amount in Singapore?</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/what-is-the-minimum-rsp-amount-in-singapore/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[KryptoMoney]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 23:41:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65286</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Retirement Sum Scheme (RSS) is designed to help Singaporeans save for retirement. It is crucial in providing financial security and stability, especially during old age. However, the RSS also has its limitations. One of them is the minimum Retirement Sum (RSP) amount that Singaporeans need to commit to enjoying the benefits provided by this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/what-is-the-minimum-rsp-amount-in-singapore/">What is the Minimum RSP Amount in Singapore?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/what-is-the-minimum-rsp-amount-in-singapore/">What is the Minimum RSP Amount in Singapore?</a> was first posted on June 23, 2023 at 7:41 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The Retirement Sum Scheme (RSS) is designed to help Singaporeans save for retirement. It is crucial in providing financial security and stability, especially during old age. However, the RSS also has its limitations. One of them is the minimum Retirement Sum (RSP) amount that Singaporeans need to commit to enjoying the benefits provided by this scheme.</p>
<p>Under the current Central Provident Fund (CPF) Board rules, Singaporean citizens below 55 must set aside a minimum sum of S$85,500 in their CPF accounts as part of their RSP commitment. This amount is known as the Basic Retirement Sum (BRS). Those aged 55 and above must meet a higher RSP amount, the Full Retirement Sum (FRS). This amount is set at S$171,000.</p>
<p>The CPF Board periodically reviews and adjusts the FRS and BRS amounts to reflect changes in life expectancy and inflation levels. The last review for both sets of figures occurred two years ago when they were reviewed upwards by 4%.</p>
<p>In its review report, the CPF Board further stated that &#8220;the Basic Retirement Sum and Full Retirement Sum will be reviewed every five years so that members can enjoy retirement adequacy&#8221;. Singaporeans below 55 can expect their RSP amounts to grow over time.</p>
<p>Additionally, those needing more retirement funds can commit additional amounts beyond the minimum RSP requirement. It can be done in two ways. The first is through the Flexible Retirement Sum (FRS), which allows members to set aside additional funds for a higher monthly payout upon reaching 55.</p>
<p>The second way of topping up one&#8217;s RSP amount is through the Special Retirement Sum (SRS). This scheme incentivises Singaporeans to top up their CPF accounts with extra funds, and it offers them a higher monthly payout after they reach the age of 65.</p>
<h2>Other ways Singaporeans are saving for their retirement</h2>
<p>Many Singaporeans are finding other innovative ways of saving for their retirement. One popular option is the Voluntary Retirement Scheme (VRS). This scheme encourages Singaporeans to top up their CPF accounts with extra funds while still working, and it offers them a higher monthly payout once they reach the age of 65.</p>
<p>Another option is to take out an annuity plan from an insurance company. Annuities provide a steady income stream throughout one&#8217;s retirement, which helps ensure financial security in old age. However, this can be expensive and may only be ideal for some.</p>
<p>Some Singaporeans also invest in property as part of their retirement savings strategy. Property prices in Singapore have been rising steadily over the years, which means that investing in property now can result in huge returns when one reaches retirement age. But it&#8217;s crucial to remember that real estate investments can come with risks, so you should research before deciding.</p>
<p>A more recent development in Singapore is using robo-advisors for retirement planning. Robo-advisors use advanced algorithms and data analytics to offer low-cost personalised investment advice. These services allow users to track their progress towards reaching their goals and make adjustments accordingly.</p>
<p>Many Singaporeans are turning to social media to save for retirement. Using platforms such as Facebook and Instagram, users can connect with people with similar financial and social interests and goals, which can help them find new investment opportunities or ideas for saving money over the long term.</p>
<p>For those looking for more traditional options, endowment plans are available through banks or insurance companies that offer guaranteed returns over a certain period, offering peace of mind and financial security during one&#8217;s golden years.</p>
<p>A <a href="https://www.home.saxo/en-sg/products/regular-savings-plan" target="_blank">regular savings plan</a> is also essential for retirement planning. It involves setting aside a small amount of money monthly and investing it in long-term instruments such as stocks and mutual funds. Regular saving helps to accumulate a substantial sum over time, which can be used during retirement.</p>
<h3>Conclusion</h3>
<p>Singaporeans must assess their financial well-being and understand how much they need to save to fully enjoy a comfortable retirement. It includes familiarising themselves with the minimum RSP amounts to make informed decisions when setting up their respective CPF accounts. In addition, those who need more funds can also consider topping up their accounts through the FRS and SRS schemes for extra financial security in their later years.</p>timed sell orders for BNB tokens, capitalizing on the situation. Data from TradingView reveals that around 125,000 BNB, equivalent to $37 million, were sold in a surge of aggregated sell orders on the BNB/USDT order book on Binance.</p>
<p>These sell orders occurred at 11:45 p.m. UTC on June 4 and 1:45 a.m. UTC on June 5, just before the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) announced its lawsuit against Binance.</p>
<p>Furthermore, <a href="https://coinalyze.net/binance-coin/open-interest/">Coinalyze</a> data indicates that BNB&#8217;s open interest, which represents the total number of outstanding derivative contracts held by investors, increased by approximately $30 million in the first nine hours of June 5.</p>
<p>This rise in open interest occurred before the news of the SEC&#8217;s allegations, revealed at 11:15 a.m., which accused Binance of commingling customer funds and operating an unregistered securities exchange. An increase in open interest suggests that new traders are entering the market and initiating new positions rather than closing existing ones.</p>
<p>Following the SEC&#8217;s crackdown, the price of BNB, which the SEC considers a security, experienced a drop of over 9%, falling from $300 to $272 within an hour.</p>
<p>Traders who speculated that the price of BNB would decrease before 11:15 a.m. on June 5 profited significantly from the subsequent price action following the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Binance, the largest cryptocurrency exchange by trading volume.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/what-is-the-minimum-rsp-amount-in-singapore/">What is the Minimum RSP Amount in Singapore?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/what-is-the-minimum-rsp-amount-in-singapore/">What is the Minimum RSP Amount in Singapore?</a> was first posted on June 23, 2023 at 7:41 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Users Sold BNB Token in Millions Ahead of SEC Lawsuits</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/binance-users-sold-bnb-token-in-millions-ahead-of-sec-lawsuits/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 23:41:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance (BNB)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65275</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ahead of the significant SEC crackdown on Binance, it appears that some traders executed well-timed sell orders for BNB tokens, capitalizing on the situation. Data from TradingView reveals that around 125,000 BNB, equivalent to $37 million, were sold in a surge of aggregated sell orders on the BNB/USDT order book on Binance. These sell orders [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-users-sold-bnb-token-in-millions-ahead-of-sec-lawsuits/">Binance Users Sold BNB Token in Millions Ahead of SEC Lawsuits</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-users-sold-bnb-token-in-millions-ahead-of-sec-lawsuits/">Binance Users Sold BNB Token in Millions Ahead of SEC Lawsuits</a> was first posted on June 11, 2023 at 7:41 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Ahead of the significant <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/sec-hits-coinbase-with-lawsuit-a-day-after-binance/">SEC crackdown</a> on Binance, it appears that some traders executed well-timed sell orders for BNB tokens, capitalizing on the situation. Data from TradingView reveals that around 125,000 BNB, equivalent to $37 million, were sold in a surge of aggregated sell orders on the BNB/USDT order book on Binance.</p>
<p>These sell orders occurred at 11:45 p.m. UTC on June 4 and 1:45 a.m. UTC on June 5, just before the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) announced its lawsuit against Binance.</p>
<p>Furthermore, <a href="https://coinalyze.net/binance-coin/open-interest/">Coinalyze</a> data indicates that BNB&#8217;s open interest, which represents the total number of outstanding derivative contracts held by investors, increased by approximately $30 million in the first nine hours of June 5.</p>
<p>This rise in open interest occurred before the news of the SEC&#8217;s allegations, revealed at 11:15 a.m., which accused Binance of commingling customer funds and operating an unregistered securities exchange. An increase in open interest suggests that new traders are entering the market and initiating new positions rather than closing existing ones.</p>
<p>Following the SEC&#8217;s crackdown, the price of BNB, which the SEC considers a security, experienced a drop of over 9%, falling from $300 to $272 within an hour.</p>
<p>Traders who speculated that the price of BNB would decrease before 11:15 a.m. on June 5 profited significantly from the subsequent price action following the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Binance, the largest cryptocurrency exchange by trading volume.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-users-sold-bnb-token-in-millions-ahead-of-sec-lawsuits/">Binance Users Sold BNB Token in Millions Ahead of SEC Lawsuits</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/binance-users-sold-bnb-token-in-millions-ahead-of-sec-lawsuits/">Binance Users Sold BNB Token in Millions Ahead of SEC Lawsuits</a> was first posted on June 11, 2023 at 7:41 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Circle Continues Public Listing Plans, Unfazed by SEC’s Recent Actions</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/circle-continues-public-listing-plans-unfazed-by-secs-recent-actions/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 23:27:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[circle]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65271</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Despite the recent SEC action against Coinbase, crypto payments technology company Circle, along with others in the industry, remains determined to pursue its goal of going public. However, industry executives acknowledge that the current environment poses challenges for most companies considering a public listing. In 2021, Circle announced its intention to become a public company [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/circle-continues-public-listing-plans-unfazed-by-secs-recent-actions/">Circle Continues Public Listing Plans, Unfazed by SEC’s Recent Actions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/circle-continues-public-listing-plans-unfazed-by-secs-recent-actions/">Circle Continues Public Listing Plans, Unfazed by SEC’s Recent Actions</a> was first posted on June 9, 2023 at 7:27 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Despite the recent <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/sec-hits-coinbase-with-lawsuit-a-day-after-binance/">SEC action against Coinbase,</a> crypto payments technology company Circle, along with others in the industry, remains determined to pursue its goal of going public. However, industry executives acknowledge that the current environment poses challenges for most companies considering a public listing.</p>
<p>In 2021, <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/circle-breaks-boundaries-with-new-cross-chain-usdc-protocol/">Circle</a> announced its intention to become a public company through a merger with a special purpose acquisition company (SPAC).</p>
<p>However, CEO Jeremy Allaire mentioned in a December 2022 tweet that his company had not completed SEC qualification in time.</p>
<p>Earlier this year, Circle reiterated that going public is still a fundamental part of its strategy, which was confirmed by a company spokesperson and a recent job posting. While no specific deadline has been set, Circle is actively taking steps to progress toward becoming a public company as soon as feasible.</p>
<p>A recent job listing for corporate counsel at Circle also indicated the company&#8217;s intentions. The role would involve assisting with the potential SEC process related to going public and supporting the development of policies, practices, and processes for the public company.</p>
<p>Circle&#8217;s determination to go public remains intact, despite the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Coinbase. Coinbase has been a public company for over two years, having completed its initial public offering in April 2021 after the SEC approved its registration on Form S-1. However, the SEC has accused Coinbase of operating as an unregistered exchange, allegations that Coinbase has denied.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/circle-continues-public-listing-plans-unfazed-by-secs-recent-actions/">Circle Continues Public Listing Plans, Unfazed by SEC’s Recent Actions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/circle-continues-public-listing-plans-unfazed-by-secs-recent-actions/">Circle Continues Public Listing Plans, Unfazed by SEC’s Recent Actions</a> was first posted on June 9, 2023 at 7:27 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Google Provides $1M Protection Against Crypto Mining Attacks</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/google-provides-1m-protection-against-crypto-mining-attacks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 23:05:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin hacks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google cloud]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65267</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Google Cloud has introduced a new initiative to safeguard certain customers against the costs incurred during undetected crypto mining attacks, offering them up to $1 million in protection. This program is specifically available to subscribers of Google&#8217;s Security Command Center Premium, a cyber threat detection service. Philip Bues, a cloud security expert at market research [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/google-provides-1m-protection-against-crypto-mining-attacks/">Google Provides $1M Protection Against Crypto Mining Attacks</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/google-provides-1m-protection-against-crypto-mining-attacks/">Google Provides $1M Protection Against Crypto Mining Attacks</a> was first posted on June 8, 2023 at 7:05 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/google-cloud-users-can-now-pay-via-coinbase-with-bitcoin-ethereum-and-dogecoin/">Google Cloud</a> has introduced a new initiative to safeguard certain customers against the costs incurred during undetected crypto mining attacks, offering them up to $1 million in protection. This program is specifically available to subscribers of Google&#8217;s Security Command Center Premium, a cyber threat detection service.<br /><br />Philip Bues, a cloud security expert at market research firm IDC, praised Google Cloud&#8217;s proactive step in addressing the issue. Bues emphasized that crypto mining attacks pose significant security and financial risks for organizations lacking adequate preventative controls and threat detection capabilities in their cloud environments.<br /><br />The decision to provide coverage for these types of breaches stems from a<a href="https://services.google.com/fh/files/blogs/gcat_threathorizons_full_sept2022.pdf"> report</a> published by Google&#8217;s Cybersecurity Action Team in September 2022. The report revealed that 65% of cases involving compromised cloud accounts were linked to hackers engaging in cryptocurrency mining.<br /><br />The report also highlighted that these attacks are often carried out through partially or fully automated means, making them swift and easily executed.<br /><br />If a hacker successfully evades Google&#8217;s detection mechanisms and proceeds to run crypto mining software on a user&#8217;s cloud account, Google Cloud will assume responsibility for the associated expenses. They will provide coverage of up to $1 million towards the customer&#8217;s bill.<br /><br />It is worth noting that this protection program is not related to Bitcoin mining. Instead, it exclusively applies to individuals using mining software, with one of the popular cryptocurrencies mined in this manner being Monero (XMR).</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/google-provides-1m-protection-against-crypto-mining-attacks/">Google Provides $1M Protection Against Crypto Mining Attacks</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/google-provides-1m-protection-against-crypto-mining-attacks/">Google Provides $1M Protection Against Crypto Mining Attacks</a> was first posted on June 8, 2023 at 7:05 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vitalik Buterin Donates Millions To Support Research on COVID-19, Future Pandemics</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/vitalik-buterin-donates-millions-to-support-research-on-covid-19-future-pandemics/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 22:44:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[COVID-19]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Decentralized finance (DeFi)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65263</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin and Polygon co-founder Sandeep Nailwal have announced their renewed commitment to supporting research on pandemic relief efforts. In a recent Twitter post, Buterin stated that last year, Crypto Relief, led by Sandeep Nailwal, allocated $100 million towards COVID research projects. After discussing and evaluating the impact of these initiatives, they concluded [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/vitalik-buterin-donates-millions-to-support-research-on-covid-19-future-pandemics/">Vitalik Buterin Donates Millions To Support Research on COVID-19, Future Pandemics</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/vitalik-buterin-donates-millions-to-support-research-on-covid-19-future-pandemics/">Vitalik Buterin Donates Millions To Support Research on COVID-19, Future Pandemics</a> was first posted on June 8, 2023 at 6:44 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Ethereum co-founder <a href="https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin/status/1666860069273710606">Vitalik Buterin</a> and Polygon co-founder Sandeep Nailwal have announced their renewed commitment to supporting research on pandemic relief efforts. In a recent Twitter post, Buterin stated that last year, Crypto Relief, led by Sandeep Nailwal, allocated $100 million towards <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/vet-price-analysis-vet-usd-pauses-uptrend-at-0-0346-high-vechain-use-case-extends-to-covid-19-vaccination-records/">COVID</a> research projects. <br /><br />After discussing and evaluating the impact of these initiatives, they concluded that continued support is crucial. Consequently, they have decided to contribute an additional $100 million to these projects.<br /><br />Buterin emphasized that COVID and potential future pandemics are global challenges that demand a global solution involving cutting-edge scientific innovation and widespread implementation worldwide. <br /><br />He stressed the importance of finding public health solutions that uphold individuals&#8217; rights and freedoms while remaining accessible to all. The goal is not only to ensure survival and good health but also to promote enjoyable and fulfilling lives.<br /><br />Out of the newly pledged funds, Buterin personally committed $10 million. Nailwal, who established the emergency relief fund COVID Relief in April 2021, has already disbursed more than $58 million in pandemic relief grants. As per the organization&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptorelief.in/transparency">website</a>, COVID Relief currently holds over $20 million in its bank account.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/vitalik-buterin-donates-millions-to-support-research-on-covid-19-future-pandemics/">Vitalik Buterin Donates Millions To Support Research on COVID-19, Future Pandemics</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/vitalik-buterin-donates-millions-to-support-research-on-covid-19-future-pandemics/">Vitalik Buterin Donates Millions To Support Research on COVID-19, Future Pandemics</a> was first posted on June 8, 2023 at 6:44 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Whale Moves $40M After 10 Years of Dormancy</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-whale-moves-40m-after-10-years-of-dormancy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 08:19:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65259</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a significant event, a dormant wallet holding a substantial sum of Bitcoin recently initiated a transfer of 1,432.93 bitcoins, valued at approximately $37.8 million, to a new address. This move comes after more than a decade of inactivity, adding to a series of similar transfers witnessed in recent months. On April 9, 2013, when [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-whale-moves-40m-after-10-years-of-dormancy/">Bitcoin Whale Moves $40M After 10 Years of Dormancy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-whale-moves-40m-after-10-years-of-dormancy/">Bitcoin Whale Moves $40M After 10 Years of Dormancy</a> was first posted on June 8, 2023 at 4:19 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In a significant event, a <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/activity-finally-observed-in-bitcoin-whale-wallet-following-several-years-of-dormancy/">dormant wallet</a> holding a substantial sum of Bitcoin recently initiated a<a href="https://bitinfocharts.com/bitcoin/address/1E6nViR5Xv1wyNXg87SamvtLJ5TyXuksLC"> transfer</a> of 1,432.93 bitcoins, valued at approximately $37.8 million, to a new address. This move comes after more than a decade of inactivity, adding to a series of similar transfers witnessed in recent months.<br /><br />On April 9, 2013, when the price of Bitcoin was a mere $195.40 per coin, the address received the Bitcoin in question, as highlighted by on-chain analyst <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1666679589421338626?s=46&amp;t=yoL7WJcO9vZ3TjSE2j6FRQ">Lookonchain</a>. The fact that the wallet remained dormant for over ten years has drawn attention and sparked speculation regarding the motives and identity of the owner.<br /><br />This transfer is not an isolated incident. In April, there were several notable movements of dormant whale addresses. On April 24, an address that had been inactive for 12 years transferred nearly $11 million worth of Bitcoin to another address. Just days before that, a separate whale address, dormant for nine years, transferred approximately $61 million worth of Bitcoin. Another wallet that had remained dormant for a decade made a transfer of 279 bitcoins.<br /><br />Interestingly, the activity is not limited to Bitcoin alone. On the same day, April 24, an Ethereum address that had been inactive for 7.7 years, since the project&#8217;s initial coin offering, suddenly woke up and transferred a single ether. While the transfer amount may not be significant, it serves as another intriguing event in the realm of dormant addresses coming to life.<br /><br />These movements of long-dormant wallets have prompted speculation among cryptocurrency enthusiasts and analysts. Questions arise regarding the motives behind these transfers after such prolonged periods of inactivity. <br /><br />The identity of the wallet owners, their intentions, and the potential implications for the cryptocurrency market as a whole remain topics of discussion.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-whale-moves-40m-after-10-years-of-dormancy/">Bitcoin Whale Moves $40M After 10 Years of Dormancy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/bitcoin-whale-moves-40m-after-10-years-of-dormancy/">Bitcoin Whale Moves $40M After 10 Years of Dormancy</a> was first posted on June 8, 2023 at 4:19 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Robinhood Reevaluates Crypto offering as SEC Intensifies Scrutiny</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/robinhood-reevaluates-crypto-offering-as-sec-intensifies-scrutiny/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 08:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robinhood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65255</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Robinhood Markets, the popular trading platform, is reassessing its cryptocurrency offerings in light of the intensified regulatory crackdown on the industry. According to Dan Gallagher, the firm&#8217;s legal chief and a former SEC commissioner, Robinhood is actively reviewing the US Securities and Exchange Commission&#8217;s (SEC) analysis to determine the necessary actions. The SEC recently filed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/robinhood-reevaluates-crypto-offering-as-sec-intensifies-scrutiny/">Robinhood Reevaluates Crypto offering as SEC Intensifies Scrutiny</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/robinhood-reevaluates-crypto-offering-as-sec-intensifies-scrutiny/">Robinhood Reevaluates Crypto offering as SEC Intensifies Scrutiny</a> was first posted on June 8, 2023 at 4:02 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/robinhood-to-pay-10-2-million-in-outage-settlement/">Robinhood</a> Markets, the popular trading platform, is reassessing its cryptocurrency offerings in light of the intensified regulatory crackdown on the industry. <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-06/robinhood-reviews-crypto-offerings-after-regulatory-crackdown">According t</a>o Dan Gallagher, the firm&#8217;s legal chief and a former SEC commissioner, Robinhood is actively reviewing the US Securities and Exchange Commission&#8217;s (SEC) analysis to determine the necessary actions.<br /><br />The SEC recently filed lawsuits against two major players in the digital asset market, <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/sec-hits-coinbase-with-lawsuit-a-day-after-binance/">Binance and Coinbase</a>, which collectively account for half of global cryptocurrency trading. This regulatory action has prompted Robinhood to tread carefully and avoid drawing unwanted attention from the SEC.<br /><br />While Robinhood provides users with access to 18 different digital assets, including Solana (SOL), Cardano (ADA), and Polygon (MATIC), the SEC&#8217;s lawsuits this week have classified these tokens as unregistered securities. Although Robinhood&#8217;s crypto offerings are relatively limited compared to Binance and Coinbase, the company aims to ensure compliance and avoid regulatory issues.<br /><br />Robinhood has already faced regulatory challenges in the past. Earlier this year, the company was fined over $10 million by US-based regulators due to operational deficiencies that negatively impacted investors during the COVID-19 crisis. Additionally, the New York State Department of Financial Services (NYDFS) imposed a $30 million penalty on Robinhood last summer for violations related to anti-money laundering and cybersecurity laws. The NYDFS also discovered significant failures in the company&#8217;s compliance program, citing policies that did not align with virtual currency and cybersecurity regulations.<br /><br />As the regulatory landscape evolves, Robinhood finds itself carefully considering its crypto offerings and striving to navigate the complex regulatory environment to ensure compliance and address potential concerns raised by regulators.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/robinhood-reevaluates-crypto-offering-as-sec-intensifies-scrutiny/">Robinhood Reevaluates Crypto offering as SEC Intensifies Scrutiny</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/robinhood-reevaluates-crypto-offering-as-sec-intensifies-scrutiny/">Robinhood Reevaluates Crypto offering as SEC Intensifies Scrutiny</a> was first posted on June 8, 2023 at 4:02 am.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Regulation Might Face Long Delays, CFTC Chair Tells Lawmakers</title>
		<link>https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-regulation-might-face-long-delays-cftc-chair-tells-lawmakers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomiwabold Olajide]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 23:06:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US CFTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://kryptomoney.com/?p=65251</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Even if Congress passes legislation to establish a clearer framework for digital assets transitioning from security to commodity status, the process of implementing new crypto rules in the United States is expected to be far from immediate. Rostin Behnam, Chair of the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), informed the House Agriculture Committee that the introduction [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-regulation-might-face-long-delays-cftc-chair-tells-lawmakers/">Crypto Regulation Might Face Long Delays, CFTC Chair Tells Lawmakers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-regulation-might-face-long-delays-cftc-chair-tells-lawmakers/">Crypto Regulation Might Face Long Delays, CFTC Chair Tells Lawmakers</a> was first posted on June 6, 2023 at 7:06 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Even if Congress passes legislation to establish a clearer framework for digital assets transitioning from security to commodity status, the process of implementing new crypto rules in the United States is expected to be far from immediate. Rostin Behnam, Chair of the <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/cftc-chairman-confirms-commodity-status-of-bitcoin-and-ether-says-xrp-is-uncertain/">Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC)</a>, informed the House Agriculture Committee that the introduction of regulations for digital assets would require a significant amount of time, even if the agency receives additional funding for crypto-related resources.<br /><br />Behnam explained that with added funding, it would take at least one to two years to establish the rules, while without the extra resources, the process could extend to three to four years. Currently, the CFTC&#8217;s authority is limited to regulating derivatives of digital assets like bitcoin and ether, but Behnam stressed the necessity for expanded oversight, particularly in the spot markets of digital tokens that do not fall under the securities category.<br /><br />Representative David Scott, the top Democrat on the committee, emphasized the importance of providing sufficient funding to the CFTC for this crucial task. The Agriculture Committees in the House and Senate hold jurisdiction over the CFTC due to their oversight of commodities futures, primarily crop-related.<br /><br />To address the urgency surrounding digital asset regulations, House Agriculture Committee Chair Glenn &#8216;GT&#8217; Thompson and House Financial Services Committee Chair Patrick McHenry introduced new legislation that, if passed, would grant greater authority to the CFTC. It would also direct both the CFTC and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to establish a more defined pathway for digital assets to be classified as commodities.<br /><br />Behnam underscored the need for proactive policing authority to address potential risks in digital asset markets, especially if they experience significant growth after a period of market correction. He emphasized that unchecked expansion could pose financial stability risks and other concerns for the broader financial markets. <br /><br />The collapses of <a href="https://kryptomoney.com/ftx-set-to-make-a-comeback-after-recovering-7-3-billion/">FTX</a>, Celsius, Voyager, and Terra-Luna in the previous year have further fueled regulators&#8217; and policymakers&#8217; push to enhance safeguards around digital assets, should their market size begin to impact the US and global financial sectors.</p>
<p>Image Credit: Shutterstock</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-regulation-might-face-long-delays-cftc-chair-tells-lawmakers/">Crypto Regulation Might Face Long Delays, CFTC Chair Tells Lawmakers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>.</p>
<hr style="border-top: black solid 1px" /><a href="https://kryptomoney.com/crypto-regulation-might-face-long-delays-cftc-chair-tells-lawmakers/">Crypto Regulation Might Face Long Delays, CFTC Chair Tells Lawmakers</a> was first posted on June 6, 2023 at 7:06 pm.<br />&copy;2021 &quot;<a href="https://kryptomoney.com">Latest Crypto News</a>&quot;. Use of this feed is for personal non-commercial use only. If you are not reading this article in your feed reader, then the site is guilty of copyright infringement. Please contact me at <!--email_off-->info@kryptomoney.com<!--/email_off--><br />]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>