<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 02:26:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Continue to Struggle Near $92</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-continue-to-struggle-near-92/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-continue-to-struggle-near-92/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 02:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78709</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin started a steady increase above $85 against the US Dollar. LTC price is now trading below $92 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $91.65 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could gain bullish<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-continue-to-struggle-near-92/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-continue-to-struggle-near-92/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Continue to Struggle Near $92</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Litecoin started a steady increase above $85 against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>LTC price is now trading below $92 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $91.65 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $91.50 and $92 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Litecoin price is showing positive signs above $85 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-soon-revisit-28500/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. LTC price could climb further if there is a clear move above $92.</em></p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few sessions, there were mostly bullish moves in Bitcoin, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-turns-red-below-1850/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Ethereum</a>, Ripple, and Litecoin against the US Dollar. Earlier, LTC formed a base above the $83.60 level and started a fresh increase.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above the $85 and $86 resistance levels. The price even climbed above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $97.53 swing high to the $83.66 low. However, the bears were active near the $91 resistance zone.</p>
<p>It is now consolidating below $92 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $90.60 level. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $97.53 swing high to the $83.66 low.</p>
<p>There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $91.65 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair. A clear move above the $91.65 level could push the price toward the $92.00 level.</p>
<p>The next major resistance sits near the $95 level. Any more gains might send the price toward the $100 level. On the downside, initial support is near the $85.80 level. The next major support is near the $83.60 level. If there is a downside break below the $83.60 support, the price could accelerate lower toward the $80 level in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_78710" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Litecoin-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78710" class="size-full wp-image-78710" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Litecoin-1.png" alt="Litecoin (LTC) Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78710" class="wp-caption-text">Litecoin (LTC) Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Litecoin’s price is trading below $92 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $91.65 and $92 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LTC/USD is now losing pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $85.80 and $83.60</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $91.65 and $92.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-continue-to-struggle-near-92/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Continue to Struggle Near $92</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-continue-to-struggle-near-92/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Musician Troy Sivan Sees Twitter Account Overtaken by Crypto Hackers</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/musician-troy-sivan-sees-twitter-account-overtaken-by-crypto-hackers/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/musician-troy-sivan-sees-twitter-account-overtaken-by-crypto-hackers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 17:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto hack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Troy Sivan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78092</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Musician and artist Troy Sivan recently became the victim of an online Twitter scam in which he was inherently associated with a new digital asset called $TROYE. Troy Sivan Has Twitter Account Hacked The artist’s Twitter profile was overtaken by hackers who not only touted his new album, but also discussed a new digital currency<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/musician-troy-sivan-sees-twitter-account-overtaken-by-crypto-hackers/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/musician-troy-sivan-sees-twitter-account-overtaken-by-crypto-hackers/">Musician Troy Sivan Sees Twitter Account Overtaken by Crypto Hackers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Musician and artist Troy Sivan recently <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/hackers-siege-troye-sivans-twitter-promising-album-and-hocking-cryptocurrency/ar-AA1ao6sF" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">became the victim of an online</a> Twitter scam in which he was inherently associated with a new digital asset called $TROYE.</p>
<h2>Troy Sivan Has Twitter Account Hacked</h2>
<p>The artist’s Twitter profile was overtaken by hackers who not only touted his new album, but also discussed a new digital currency that had allegedly been created in his name. Known as $TROYE, the asset is apparently not real according to Sivan, who went online publicly to denounce the asset and say that he had nothing to do with its promotion.</p>
<p>He has since gone on to delete his Twitter account and says that any further promotions of the asset will not come from him or those associated with him. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I deleted my Twitter, so whoever has the account now is not me. They are scammers. We’re going to get it deleted hopefully, but Twitter is a hell scape&#8230; This is not the rise of crypto Troye.</p></blockquote>
<p>Twitter has long been the focus of crypto hackers looking to either make off with assets or get unsuspecting victims to fall for scams. One of the biggest crypto-based Twitter hacks in history occurred over the summer of 2020 (roughly three years ago).</p>
<p>The accounts of many high-profile individuals – including Tesla and SpaceX CEO Elon Musk, Microsoft king Bill Gates, and former president Barack Obama – had <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/twitter-hack-leads-to-120000-in-stolen-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">their accounts overtaken</a> by a scammer who promised that those who sent in bitcoin would see their funds doubled.</p>
<p>In truth, the person instigating the “giveaways” had no intention of ensuring people got additional funds, nor did he seek to stay true to his alleged promises, and those who gave their money to the included addresses did not see their money doubled. Rather, the funds disappeared, and the scammer made off with more than $100K in BTC before getting caught.</p>
<p>When he was finally brought to justice, people were shocked to see that the culprit was a young, 17-year-old kid. He was later sentenced (via plea bargain) to time in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/twitter-btc-scammer-graham-clark-sentenced-to-jail/" data-wpel-link="internal">a juvenile detention center</a> and was ordered to give all the money back to those he took it from.</p>
<p>Figures like Elon Musk have, many times, been <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-and-his-likeness-were-at-the-center-of-another-twitter-btc-scam/" data-wpel-link="internal">unwillingly involved</a> in crypto scams, and have had their likenesses utilized to either promote phony giveaways or fake coins. It’s an ongoing issue that even now, despite Musk having purchased Twitter not too long ago and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-fan-elon-musk-now-fully-controls-twitter/" data-wpel-link="internal">serving as the company’s</a> new chief, doesn’t seem to be disappearing anytime soon.</p>
<h2>This Happens Too Much</h2>
<p>Discussing his new album before deleting his Twitter account, Sivan said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think what I feel comfortable saying is that it’s full of hope, which I didn’t know it was going to be when I first started making it.</p></blockquote>
<p>Not long ago, crypto firm Gate.io had <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/twitter-account-of-crypto-firm-gate-io-overtaken-by-hackers/" data-wpel-link="internal">its Twitter account overtaken</a> by hackers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/musician-troy-sivan-sees-twitter-account-overtaken-by-crypto-hackers/">Musician Troy Sivan Sees Twitter Account Overtaken by Crypto Hackers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/musician-troy-sivan-sees-twitter-account-overtaken-by-crypto-hackers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Last Year&#8217;s Crypto Winter Over? Analysts Say, &#8220;Yup!&#8221;</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-last-years-crypto-winter-over-analysts-say-yup/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-last-years-crypto-winter-over-analysts-say-yup/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 15:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto winter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Standard Chartered]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78089</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is the crypto winter of 2022 officially over? According to various analysts, the answer is “yes.” The Crypto Winter Is Done For The crypto winter of the previous year was one of the worst events on record for bitcoin and the digital currency arena. Prices of several assets fell like comets, and the industry appeared<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-last-years-crypto-winter-over-analysts-say-yup/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-last-years-crypto-winter-over-analysts-say-yup/">Is Last Year&#8217;s Crypto Winter Over? Analysts Say, &#8220;Yup!&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is the crypto winter of 2022 officially over? <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/04/26/crypto-winter-finally-over-bank-crisis-a-catalyst-for-huge-2-trillion-bitcoin-prediction-as-ethereum-price-suddenly-storms-back/?sh=6238f6d046e3" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">According to various analysts</a>, the answer is “yes.”</p>
<h2>The Crypto Winter Is Done For</h2>
<p>The crypto winter of the previous year was one of the worst events on record for bitcoin and the digital currency arena. Prices of several assets fell like comets, and the industry appeared to be on the verge of fully collapsing into a heaping pile of nothingness.</p>
<p>Bitcoin, for example, is the world’s number one digital currency by market cap. The asset reached a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit in November of 2021, and at that time, many traders and investors were convinced that the digital currency world could never be brought down, but boy… Were they wrong!</p>
<p>Just a few months later, bitcoin began crashing, and then it crashed some more, and by the time we reached the end of 2022, the asset had lost more than 70 percent of its value and was trading in the mid-$16K range. It was a sad and ugly sight to see, and it would have been bad enough had it stood on its own, but crypto has a habit of moving in tandem with other assets and coins, so when one major asset falls, it’s likely others will follow suit.</p>
<p>This time was no exception. Other cryptocurrencies like Ethereum traveled the same path that bitcoin was on. This ultimately contributed to the digital currency space losing more than $2 trillion in overall valuation over the course of just ten or so months.</p>
<p>Now that we’ve entered 2023, there are many analysts that have noted the digital currency arena turning itself around. They say the crypto winter has reached its end, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/standard-chartered-btc-will-hit-a-six-figure-price-soon/" data-wpel-link="internal">and companies like</a> Standard Chartered believe that the bitcoin price has the capacity to reach a whopping six-figure price by the end of next year. In a recent report, the analysis firm said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We see potential for bitcoin to reach the $100,000 level by end 2024, as we believe the much-touted ‘crypto winter’ is finally over.</p></blockquote>
<p>The company’s head of digital assets research, Goeff Kendrick, further explained that there are many things contributing to its end, one big one being <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-spikes-following-more-banking-troubles/" data-wpel-link="internal">the ongoing banking crisis</a>. He says that many people are beginning to see bitcoin and other assets as “safe havens” yet again, and bank deposits are losing some of their appeal.</p>
<h2>Many Things Pushing BTC Up</h2>
<p>He also said the upcoming halving of next year is building BTC up further:</p>
<blockquote><p>The current stress in the traditional banking sector is highly conducive to bitcoin outperformance and validates the original premise for bitcoin as a decentralized, trustless, and scarce digital asset. Against this backdrop, bitcoin has benefited from its status as a branded safe haven, a perceived relative store of value, and a means of remittance.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-last-years-crypto-winter-over-analysts-say-yup/">Is Last Year&#8217;s Crypto Winter Over? Analysts Say, &#8220;Yup!&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-last-years-crypto-winter-over-analysts-say-yup/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coin Flip Introduces Olliv, a Crypto Platform for Beginners</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coin-flip-introduces-olliv-a-crypto-platform-for-beginners/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coin-flip-introduces-olliv-a-crypto-platform-for-beginners/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 13:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coin Flip]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Olliv]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trading]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78086</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coin Flip – a leading crypto and fintech company famous for its wide branches of crypto-based ATMs – is launching a new platform called Olliv. The product is designed to be safe, inclusive, and self-custody-powered, ensuring everyone who invests or trades in crypto gains access to simple financial services like they would in any other<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coin-flip-introduces-olliv-a-crypto-platform-for-beginners/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coin-flip-introduces-olliv-a-crypto-platform-for-beginners/">Coin Flip Introduces Olliv, a Crypto Platform for Beginners</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coin Flip – a leading crypto and fintech company famous for its wide branches of crypto-based ATMs – is launching a new platform called Olliv. The product is <a href="https://www.tmcnet.com/usubmit/2023/04/26/9802560.htm" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">designed to be safe</a>, inclusive, and self-custody-powered, ensuring everyone who invests or trades in crypto gains access to simple financial services like they would in any other market.</p>
<h2>Coin Flip Opens the Door to Easy Trading with Olliv</h2>
<p>Olliv gives everyone a chance to buy, sell, trade, and receive digital currencies through self-custodial wallets, thus omitting all middlemen, third parties, and prying eyes from the picture. Users can maintain control over not only their assets, but over the data they present and their identities, thus adhering to all the initial goals of blockchain and crypto.</p>
<p>Ben Weiss – CEO and co-founder of Coin Flip – explained in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>With the launch of Olliv, our goal is to demystify cryptocurrency and create an inviting community for everyone. We aim to welcome customers with open arms into this next step toward financial revolution, regardless of their financial knowledge or background. We&#8217;re always looking for ways to invest in our customers that will contribute to the future of DeFi. We are confident our self-custodial model, a key value of Coin Flip&#8217;s business since inception, will pave the path for a significant and much-needed shift in the industry. We look forward to continued growth and innovation in the coming year as we get one step closer to on-ramping the next generation of crypto investors.</p></blockquote>
<p>Rory Herriman – chief technology, digital, and strategy officer at <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/coin-flip/" data-wpel-link="internal">Coin Flip</a> – also threw his two cents into the mix, commenting:</p>
<blockquote><p>We envision a future where everyone can participate in the digital economy and utilize their holdings to make everyday purchases and gain access to previously hard-to-buy assets such as precious metals, real estate, and energy without the need for frustrating third-party intermediaries. Our vision for Olliv is to innovate and break down barriers around safety, security, and sovereignty, to empower people to invest and give them individual ownership of their assets thanks to the accessibility cryptocurrency provides.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Getting a New Generation of Traders</h2>
<p>One of the big goals behind Olliv is to give more people a chance to enter the crypto arena. It realizes that for this space to grow and become more mainstream and legitimate, other players need to enter the fray and become established, regular traders. By making it easy to not only trade but onboard oneself, the path has been paved for people to take those first, early steps towards whatever crypto goals they might seek to achieve in the coming future.</p>
<p>Olliv provides all users with state-of-the-art encryption, ensuring their data always remains protected. The platform also boasts low fees and top-notch customer service, which is available to traders 24 hours a day, seven days a week.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coin-flip-introduces-olliv-a-crypto-platform-for-beginners/">Coin Flip Introduces Olliv, a Crypto Platform for Beginners</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coin-flip-introduces-olliv-a-crypto-platform-for-beginners/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Key Uptrend Support Intact</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-key-uptrend-support-intact/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-key-uptrend-support-intact/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 04:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78699</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tron price started a fresh downside correction from the $0.0855 zone against the US Dollar. TRX price is now trading above $0.0770 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.0777 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could continue to<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-key-uptrend-support-intact/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-key-uptrend-support-intact/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Key Uptrend Support Intact</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Tron price started a fresh downside correction from the $0.0855 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>TRX price is now trading above $0.0770 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.0777 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it breaks the $0.0768 support zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>TRON price started a fresh decline below the $0.0820 zone against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-soon-revisit-28500/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. TRX price could accelerate lower if there is a move below $0.0768.</em></p>
<h2>Tron Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, Tron price started a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-dips-supported-near-0-075/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">steady increase</a> above the $0.0750 resistance level against the US Dollar. TRX price struggled to gain pace for more gains and formed a top near $0.0855.</p>
<p>The price started a fresh decline below the $0.0820 level. There was a move below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.0741 swing low to the $0.0856 high. However, the bulls were active near the $0.0770 level.</p>
<p>There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.0777 on the 4-hour chart. The price is now trading above $0.0770 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, TRX is facing resistance near the $0.0800 level.</p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $0.082 level. A close above $0.082 is a must for a fresh increase. In the stated case, the price could rise toward the $0.0855 resistance in the near term.</p>
<p>On the downside, initial support is near the $0.0777 level and the trend line. The next major support is now forming near $0.0768. It is near the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.0741 swing low to the $0.0856 high.</p>
<p>If there is a downside break below the $0.0768 support, the price might revisit the $0.0720 support. Any more losses might call for a move toward the $0.0700 zone in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_78700" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/TRON-TRX.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78700" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78700" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/TRON-TRX.png" alt="Tron (TRX) Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78700" class="wp-caption-text">Tron (TRX) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/TRXUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that TRX price is now trading above $0.0770 and near the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it breaks the $0.0768 support zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for TRX/USD is slowly losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for TRX/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.0768 and $0.0720.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.080, $0.082, and $0.0855.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-key-uptrend-support-intact/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Key Uptrend Support Intact</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-key-uptrend-support-intact/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Could Soon Revisit 28,500</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-soon-revisit-28500/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-soon-revisit-28500/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 02:38:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78696</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price is attempting a fresh increase from the $25,500 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading near $27,000 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $26,900 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-soon-revisit-28500/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-soon-revisit-28500/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Could Soon Revisit 28,500</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin price is attempting a fresh increase from the $25,500 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading near $27,000 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $26,900 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could start a fresh increase if it clears the $27,350 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin price is rising from $25,500 against the US Dollar. BTC might eye another increase if the bulls remain active above the $26,550 zone.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price remained well-bid above the $25,500 level. A base was formed and the price was able to settle above the $26,000 resistance zone. The bulls remained active above $26,000 and initiated a decent increase.</p>
<p>There was a move above the 50% Fib retracement level of the key decline from the $28,431 swing high to the $25,351 low. Besides, there was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $26,900 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is now trading near $27,000 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-another-increase-to-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. Immediate resistance on the upside is near the $27,350 level.</p>
<p>The next major resistance might be near the $27,700 zone or the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the key decline from the $28,431 swing high to the $25,351 low. A clear move above the $27,350 and $27,700 resistance levels might send the price toward <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-key-resistance-near-28-5k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">$28,500</a>.</p>
<p>Any more gains might push the price toward the $29,500 zone. If there is no upside break, the price might start a fresh decline below the $26,800 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>The first major support is near $26,550. The next key support is near the $26,000 level, below which the price might accelerate lower. In the stated case, the price could decline toward the $25,500 level in the coming sessions.</p>
<div id="attachment_78697" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Bitcoin.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78697" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78697" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Bitcoin.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78697" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XBTUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Bitcoin’s price is trading near $27,000 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start a fresh increase if it clears the $27,350 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD is now losing momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $26,550 and $26,000.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $27,350, $27,700, and $28,500.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-soon-revisit-28500/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Could Soon Revisit 28,500</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-soon-revisit-28500/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Piers Ridyard on Radix, One of Crypto&#8217;s Oldest Companies</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/piers-ridyard-on-radix-one-of-cryptos-oldest-companies/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/piers-ridyard-on-radix-one-of-cryptos-oldest-companies/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 17:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Piers Ridyard]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Radix]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78083</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Piers Ridyard is the CEO of Radix, one of the world’s oldest digital currency companies. The project is on the verge of turning ten, and he believes many new opportunities and challenges are coming not only for his enterprise, but for the crypto industry in general. Piers Ridyard Discusses His Crypto Journey Discussing his early<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/piers-ridyard-on-radix-one-of-cryptos-oldest-companies/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/piers-ridyard-on-radix-one-of-cryptos-oldest-companies/">Piers Ridyard on Radix, One of Crypto&#8217;s Oldest Companies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Piers Ridyard is the CEO of Radix, one of the <a href="https://techbullion.com/pierce-ridyard-ceo-of-radix-layer-1-blockchain-we-can-compare-radix-to-when-the-iphone-was-launched-in-2007/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">world’s oldest digital currency</a> companies. The project is on the verge of turning ten, and he believes many new opportunities and challenges are coming not only for his enterprise, but for the crypto industry in general.</p>
<h2>Piers Ridyard Discusses His Crypto Journey</h2>
<p>Discussing his early crypto days, he said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I started in crypto when I started mining on the genesis block of Ethereum in early 2015, investing in ‘the DAO’ and going deep on everything from game theory to prediction markets. This eventually led me to build and exit Surematics, a Y combinator company that built decentralized deal room software for insurance companies in 2017… I became CEO of RDX Works… joining the founder, Dan Hughes, and building the team to over 75 people around the world. My background includes finance, law, electronics, and mathematics. I also have two degrees, one in Chinese and business and a second in law, as well as having achieved level 1 chartered financial analyst designation.</p></blockquote>
<p>He was also quick to comment that Radix has brought a lot of unique <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/blockchain/" data-wpel-link="internal">blockchain</a> solutions to the market. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Like Ethereum, Radix is a layer 1 smart contract platform, although Radix is as different to Ethereum as a jumbo jet is to a biplane. In a nutshell, Radix is the base layer upon which any developer can build dApps (decentralized applications) on top of. End users can use those dApps for services such as payments, borrowing, trading, or lending for any form of a digital asset such as tokens or NFTs. You can also use Radix for password-less login to any app or website that supports it without relying on any centralized service to hold your data. The Radix project is one of the origins of the crypto industry. It’ll be ten years next month. The reason it’s taken this long is that we had an end goal in mind and worked backwards from that objective. That objective is to build a decentralized ledger capable of supporting mainstream-ready experiences for users, developers, and capital at the scale of the global financial system.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Connecting Everyone to the Blockchain</h2>
<p>Discussing how his company connects both products and developers to the blockchain industry, Ridyard mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Radix is just software that anyone can run on their computer. When a computer runs that software and connects to others running that software, it forms a network, and we call those computers nodes. Those nodes, in turn, then agree with one another on the state of the Radix Ledger, which is an immutable record of transactions. The Radix Ledger can hold any kind of data, whether it’s who won a sports game for a decentralized prediction application, a record of who owns a token, or the smart contract logic that forms the basis of a dApp.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/piers-ridyard-on-radix-one-of-cryptos-oldest-companies/">Piers Ridyard on Radix, One of Crypto&#8217;s Oldest Companies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/piers-ridyard-on-radix-one-of-cryptos-oldest-companies/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Me We Social Network Integrates Blockchain to Ensure User Control</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/me-we-social-network-integrates-blockchain-to-ensure-user-control/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/me-we-social-network-integrates-blockchain-to-ensure-user-control/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 15:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Frequency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Me We]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78080</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Me We – an up-and-coming social media platform – has adopted the Frequency blockchain as a means of connecting more users and bringing about new internet revolutions. Me We and Blockchain&#8230; A Perfect Match? The goal of integrating blockchain into its system is to give users unique social identities that are fully owned by the<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/me-we-social-network-integrates-blockchain-to-ensure-user-control/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/me-we-social-network-integrates-blockchain-to-ensure-user-control/">Me We Social Network Integrates Blockchain to Ensure User Control</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Me We – an up-and-coming social media platform – has adopted the Frequency blockchain as a means of connecting more <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/frequency-blockchain-deliver-decentralized-social-160000803.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">users and bringing about</a> new internet revolutions.</p>
<h2>Me We and Blockchain&#8230; A Perfect Match?</h2>
<p>The goal of integrating blockchain into its system is to give users unique social identities that are fully owned by the individuals they’re issued to. The move is a big step away from how social media platforms are usually handled. Often, a platform is centralized, and a small group of individuals at the top of the executive ladder have control over a users’ information and whatever they divulge or post.</p>
<p>However, following problems surrounding things like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/facebook-coin-is-garnering-mixed-reactions/" data-wpel-link="internal">Cambridge Analytica and Facebook</a> from five years ago, Me We wants to do things differently and give all its users a little more control over what they do and what happens to their data. The social identities they’re given will also allow them access to a wide array of new Web3-based protocols and services the company plans on introducing.</p>
<p>Braxton Woodham – president of Amplica Labs, the team that helped bring the Frequency blockchain to fruition – stated in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Frequency breaks the price barrier so blockchain technology can be used to decentralize social at massive scale. This breakthrough enables a bridge for Web 2.0 apps to connect their existing user bases to Web3 value and opens blockchain for use cases that go far beyond DeFi.</p></blockquote>
<p>Jeffrey Edell – CEO and chairman of Me We – also threw his two cents into the mix, claiming:</p>
<blockquote><p>Since our founding, Me We has surpassed industry norms to protect individuals&#8217; digital rights. We are furthering this commitment by literally handing control of data over to our users. By pioneering the migration to the social web, we seek to be a leader in bringing into existence a world in which people, not corporations, control the way digital spaces work.</p></blockquote>
<p>The goals of the social organization flow directly with those of blockchain, which was initially designed to give users more independence and autonomy. The idea is that through blockchain, middlemen, third parties, and prying eyes would be completely cut out of the picture for transactors.</p>
<h2>Keeping Things Safe for Users</h2>
<p>Frank McCourt – founder and executive chairman of Project Liberty and McCourt Global – said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Today&#8217;s prevailing tech architecture, one that profits from exploiting and dividing people, has caused widespread harm and led to a breakdown in our social fabric, and with the emergence of AI, the damage being done will only accelerate. With this significant milestone, we are witnessing firsthand the creation of a new and exciting model for technology. By utilizing DSNP to catalyze systemic change and by empowering people to take control of their digital lives, we can replace today&#8217;s broken tech model with a better version, enabling a much brighter future for us all.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/me-we-social-network-integrates-blockchain-to-ensure-user-control/">Me We Social Network Integrates Blockchain to Ensure User Control</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/me-we-social-network-integrates-blockchain-to-ensure-user-control/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Spikes Following More Banking Troubles</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-spikes-following-more-banking-troubles/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-spikes-following-more-banking-troubles/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 13:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[First Republic bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mike McGlone]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78078</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin rose eight percent in late April after First Republic Bank fell under a negative light, and many analysts believed it would be next to collapse. Bitcoin Spikes Following More Issues with Banks Bitcoin had fallen into the high $20,000 range prior, a near $3,000 dip from the $30K, ten-month high it had previously hit.<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-spikes-following-more-banking-troubles/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-spikes-following-more-banking-troubles/">Bitcoin Spikes Following More Banking Troubles</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin rose eight percent in late April after First Republic Bank fell <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/04/26/bitcoin-jumps-as-first-republic-pulls-banking-sector-concerns-back-into-focus.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">under a negative light</a>, and many analysts believed it would be next to collapse.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Spikes Following More Issues with Banks</h2>
<p>Bitcoin had fallen into <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-falls-to-28k-analysts-are-wondering-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">the high $20,000 range</a> prior, a near $3,000 dip from the $30K, ten-month high it had previously hit. However, now it looks like bank fears are once again on the horizon, and when banks aren’t doing well, that’s usually a cue for bitcoin to step in and save the day once again. At the time of this writing, BTC is back to trading for around $29,800.</p>
<p>Matt Hougan – chief investment officer at Bitwise Asset Management – said in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>Crypto rallies during banking crises, and it looks like the banking crisis may not be over.</p></blockquote>
<p>Shares in First Republic fell nearly 50 percent over the course of a single day. The company has endured a major slip in deposits ever <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/did-crypto-cause-banks-to-fall-experts-weigh-in/" data-wpel-link="internal">since Silicon Valley Bank</a> went under. During that initial collapse, the price of bitcoin shot up by more than 20 percent. James Lavish, managing partner at Bitcoin Opportunity Fund, said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin continues to straddle between being the ultimate lifeboat from the current banking system and the leading risk-on asset. As First Republic is now on the verge of collapse, bitcoin represents a ‘safe haven’ versus uncertain bank deposits.</p></blockquote>
<p>Still, while the news is positive for BTC, many analysts say traders shouldn’t be breaking open the champagne just yet. The Federal Reserve, for example, has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/federal-reserve-hikes-rates-again-what-will-happen-to-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">hinted that it plans</a> to continue hiking rates in 2023, and that so long as inflation remains a problem, the organization will do all it can to curb its effects. Yuya Hasegawa – crypto market analyst at Japanese crypto exchange Bit Bank – said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The crypto market learned last month that [the] banking crisis works favorably for bitcoin’s price, but we need to approach it from multiple angles. The Fed Funds futures market is pricing in the beginning of rate cuts later this year, and it could be a source of disappointment if the Fed continues to refrain from commenting on or even denies the possibility of rate cuts this year.</p></blockquote>
<h2>We Need to Remain Careful</h2>
<p>Mike McGlone – a senior macro strategist at Bloomberg Intelligence – <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/04/26/crypto-winter-finally-over-bank-crisis-a-catalyst-for-huge-2-trillion-bitcoin-prediction-as-ethereum-price-suddenly-storms-back/?sh=2cff2c0646e3" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">also threw his two cents</a> into the mix, claiming:</p>
<blockquote><p>The up-and-coming 24/7 traded leading indicators, revolutionary technologies and assets – bitcoin and Ethereum – may be running into a wall of resistance at the key round number levels of $30,000 and $2,000. Our bias is bullish in the long term for the top cryptos, but an overwhelming force of the stock market going down with the Fed tightening into a recession has the potential to lower the tide for all risk assets, and bitcoin and Ethereum are among the riskiest.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-spikes-following-more-banking-troubles/">Bitcoin Spikes Following More Banking Troubles</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-spikes-following-more-banking-troubles/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=3859 metric#misses=6 metric#hit-ratio=99.8 metric#bytes=6631795 metric#prefetches=398 metric#store-reads=16 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=402 metric#store-misses=1 metric#sql-queries=14 metric#ms-total=245.96 metric#ms-cache=18.38 metric#ms-cache-avg=1.0810 metric#ms-cache-ratio=7.5 -->
