<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 12:25:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Nirmala Sitharaman Thinks Crypto Will Dominate India&#8217;s Future</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nirmala-sitharaman-thinks-crypto-will-dominate-indias-future/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nirmala-sitharaman-thinks-crypto-will-dominate-indias-future/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 17:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nirmala Sitharaman]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77873</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>India’s Minister of Finance Nirmala Sitharaman says cryptocurrencies will take up most of the chat time during this year’s upcoming G20 presidency event in India. Nirmala Sitharaman on Crypto in India Not long ago, Sitharaman visited Washington and explained in a statement: Given so many collapses and shocks in cryptocurrencies, we seek to develop a<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nirmala-sitharaman-thinks-crypto-will-dominate-indias-future/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nirmala-sitharaman-thinks-crypto-will-dominate-indias-future/">Nirmala Sitharaman Thinks Crypto Will Dominate India&#8217;s Future</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>India’s Minister of Finance Nirmala Sitharaman says <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-in/news/other/finance-minister-nirmala-sitharaman-seeks-common-framework-for-cryptocurrency-says-important-part-of-discussion-under-india-s-g20-presidency/ar-AA19HD9V" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">cryptocurrencies will take</a> up most of the chat time during this year’s upcoming G20 presidency event in India.</p>
<h2>Nirmala Sitharaman on Crypto in India</h2>
<p>Not long ago, Sitharaman visited Washington and explained in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>Given so many collapses and shocks in cryptocurrencies, we seek to develop a common framework for all countries to deal with this matter.</p></blockquote>
<p>She was referring to the fateful <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">fall of FTX</a>, once one of the top digital currency exchanges in the world. The company came crashing down in November of last year in a very unexpected fashion, and there are many governments and regulators out there doing all they can to try and avoid another (similar) situation like that happening. They are allegedly concerned about investors’ funds, and they don’t want to see crypto executives commingling them with business assets the way Sam Bankman-Fried did.</p>
<p>Sitharaman was participating in a roundtable discussion in Washington in which she discussed India’s future regarding crypto and upcoming business opportunities pertaining to the digital currency arena.</p>
<p>A few months ago, Shaktikanta Das – the governor of the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) – said he doesn’t think crypto assets have any place in India and he would prefer to do away with all of them, no matter how big or important they might seem. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>RBI&#8217;s position is very clear. It should be banned, all of them. The technology of blockchain needs to be supported.</p></blockquote>
<p>Sitharaman further commented during the roundtable meeting:</p>
<blockquote><p>Free trade agreements are being signed in a much faster way, nowadays. We&#8217;ve just concluded one with Australia. Earlier, we concluded with UAE, Mauritius, and with ASEAN. We have extended the quota-free and tariff-free regime to least developed countries.</p></blockquote>
<p>India has long had a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/regulators-in-india-are-still-at-war-with-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">very up-and-down relationship</a> with bitcoin and crypto. Back in 2018, the nation announced that traditional financial institutions would not be allowed to do any work or business with crypto firms. While many outlets reported that crypto was receiving a full-on ban, this wasn’t quite true, and it was just that banks and other standard financial platforms were no longer allowed to provide tools or services to blockchain and crypto-based enterprises.</p>
<h2>Turning Things Around</h2>
<p>About two years later, the nation’s Supreme Court decided that such action was unconstitutional, and a reversal was initiated. From there, many analysts thought India would become the next big crypto haven of the world, and for a while, it looked like this was going to be the path the nation took, though eventually, the country’s parliament began discussing a full crypto ban in which trading or being involved in assets would be punishable by fines and even prison sentences.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, no official decisions regarding the potential ban have been made yet.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nirmala-sitharaman-thinks-crypto-will-dominate-indias-future/">Nirmala Sitharaman Thinks Crypto Will Dominate India&#8217;s Future</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nirmala-sitharaman-thinks-crypto-will-dominate-indias-future/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Next BTC Halving Is a Year Away; What&#8217;s Going to Happen?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-next-btc-halving-is-a-year-away-whats-going-to-happen/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-next-btc-halving-is-a-year-away-whats-going-to-happen/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 15:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jamie Sly]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77871</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>2024 is set to be a big year for several reasons. A big one is that Americans can finally vote Joe Biden out of office and spare their nation more incompetency, but a different reason is because the next bitcoin halving is set to occur. The Halving Is on Its Way Bitcoin halving events take<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-next-btc-halving-is-a-year-away-whats-going-to-happen/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-next-btc-halving-is-a-year-away-whats-going-to-happen/">The Next BTC Halving Is a Year Away; What&#8217;s Going to Happen?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>2024 is set to be a big year for several reasons. A big one is that Americans can finally vote Joe Biden out of office and spare their nation more incompetency, but a different <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-is-one-year-away-from-a-major-technical-event-history-suggests-the-start-of-another-bull-run/ar-AA19KSBy" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reason is because the</a> next bitcoin halving is set to occur.</p>
<h2>The Halving Is on Its Way</h2>
<p>Bitcoin halving events take place every four years or so. It’s when the world’s number one digital currency by market cap undergoes a technical change that causes its rarity to grow via the slashing of digital rewards that go to miners.</p>
<p>Basically, for every new block that gets mined and extracted from the blockchain to be added to circulation, the miners receive crypto-based rewards for their activities, though with each halving, the rewards they get are ultimately reduced by 50 percent.</p>
<p>2024 will be no different, and while the specific date is not yet known, the halving is slated to occur in either April or May of that year. In anticipation of the halving, the bitcoin price has been spiking over the last several weeks, and the currency recently hit an 11-month high <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">of about $30K</a>. This marks the first time the currency has struck such a chord since June of last year.</p>
<p>Vijay Ayyar – vice president of corporate development and international at crypto exchange Luno – commented in an interview that the “cyclical” bottom for BTC has formed largely due to the banking <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-the-silvergate-collapse-shouldnt-predict-cryptos-future/" data-wpel-link="internal">crisis that occurred</a> earlier in the year. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>This tends to happen a year or so prior to the bitcoin&#8217;s halving event, which is slated next for around April 2024.</p></blockquote>
<p>One of the cool things about all past halving events is that they usually precede major rallies, and there are many analysts that don’t think 2024 will be an exception to the rule. They predict that the price of bitcoin is going to spike even higher and thus push it to a new record price. Jamie Sly – analyst at Crypto Compare – said in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>Analyzing historical bitcoin halving patterns, it appears that investors often accumulate bitcoin in the run-up to the halving event, although the exact timing and extent of returns post-halving can differ. The accumulation period from the market bottom after the breakout to the halving date has historically spanned at least 500 days… This would mean, if we were to assume that the market bottom for this cycle was in November [of] last year (when bitcoin hit a yearly low of $15,760), then we are only 142 days into the current cycle. This would correlate with the next expected bitcoin halving date, which is another 378 days ahead.</p></blockquote>
<h2>BTC Has Been Doing Quite Well</h2>
<p>Bitcoin is presently more than 70 percent higher than where it was at the end of 2022.</p>
<p>By that time, it had fallen into the mid-$16K range.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-next-btc-halving-is-a-year-away-whats-going-to-happen/">The Next BTC Halving Is a Year Away; What&#8217;s Going to Happen?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-next-btc-halving-is-a-year-away-whats-going-to-happen/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Warren Buffett Continues to Hate on Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/warren-buffett-continues-to-hate-on-bitcoin/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/warren-buffett-continues-to-hate-on-bitcoin/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 13:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin streaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warren Buffett]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77868</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has been doing quite well as of late. The currency recently hit a price of $30K for the first time in about 11 months and the asset has shot up steadily since the beginning of the year. Sadly, this has not been enough to convince Warren Buffett – a long-time crypto critic – of<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/warren-buffett-continues-to-hate-on-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/warren-buffett-continues-to-hate-on-bitcoin/">Warren Buffett Continues to Hate on Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has been doing quite well as of late. The currency recently hit a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">price of $30K for</a> the first time in about 11 months and the asset has shot up steadily since the beginning of the year. Sadly, this has not been enough to convince Warren Buffett – a long-time crypto critic – of its worth, and he’s doubling down <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/savingandinvesting/i-ve-seen-people-do-stupid-things-all-my-life-warren-buffett-doubles-down-on-his-long-held-views-on-bitcoin-and-crypto/ar-AA19Mfw7" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">on his hatred and skepticism</a> of the world’s number one digital currency by market cap.</p>
<h2>Warren Buffett Still Doesn&#8217;t Care About BTC</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, he compared buying bitcoin to gambling or playing the lottery. Buffett said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I didn’t like chain letters when I was a kid. I thought, ‘Why in the world should I send along a chain letter?’ […] I’ve seen people do stupid things all my life, and I really, I empathize with that. I mean, people like to play the lottery […] People love the idea that they’re going to make more money tomorrow.</p></blockquote>
<p>He has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/warren-buffett-explains-his-hate-for-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">stated in the past</a> that bitcoin will not amount to a darn thing. He has gone so far as to refer to it as “rat poison squared,” and he doesn’t think the currency has any real value to it, at one point even comparing selling bitcoin to trying to sell a button of one’s own shirt. Buffett continued with:</p>
<blockquote><p>I looked at all these people, who had flown thousands of miles to do something that [was] unintelligent as fast as they could. They thought the dice were hot or something like that, and I thought, ‘I’m going to get rich in this country.’ I mean if that’s what people do. I can be smarter than that.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also says the only real reason anybody gets involved in bitcoin or other forms of crypto is because they see their neighbors are making money and they begin to experience FOMO (fear of missing out). At the end of the day, however, he believes this is never a reason to get involved in a potential investment, and people aren’t doing their research or due diligence enough. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>It really drives them crazy if their next-door neighbor is making more money not knowing what they’re doing and they’re just sitting there, and their spouse is saying, ‘Why is that guy getting a second car, and why are we missing this whole thing?’ The gambling instinct is so strong.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Avoid Investing in Film Ventures</h2>
<p>When it comes to <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/savingandinvesting/warren-buffett-tears-into-banks-trashes-bitcoin-and-warns-inflation-and-recession-can-lead-to-big-problems/ar-AA19Lqa3" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">other negative investments</a>, he said that the movie and entertainment industries sit in this category in that while moviemakers and everyone involved in the working elements tend to do well, the shareholders don’t. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Streaming is not really a very good business. The people in entertainment have made lots of money. The shareholders really haven&#8217;t done that great over time.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/warren-buffett-continues-to-hate-on-bitcoin/">Warren Buffett Continues to Hate on Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/warren-buffett-continues-to-hate-on-bitcoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Texas Paid Crypto Mining Firm a Lot of Money to Shut Its Machines Off</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-paid-crypto-mining-firm-bit-deer-a-lot-of-money-to-shut-its-machines-off/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-paid-crypto-mining-firm-bit-deer-a-lot-of-money-to-shut-its-machines-off/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 17:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bit Deer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Texas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77859</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In early 2021, the state of Texas paid a bitcoin mining company called Bit Deer approximately $175,000 per hour. Texas Doled Out Cash for No Work For what purpose, you ask? Well, it wasn’t because the Lone Star State wanted to gain access to mined BTC units. It wasn’t to create jobs, and it wasn’t<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-paid-crypto-mining-firm-bit-deer-a-lot-of-money-to-shut-its-machines-off/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-paid-crypto-mining-firm-bit-deer-a-lot-of-money-to-shut-its-machines-off/">Texas Paid Crypto Mining Firm a Lot of Money to Shut Its Machines Off</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In early 2021, the state of Texas paid a <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/texas-paid-bitcoin-company-175k-205910042.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">bitcoin mining company</a> called Bit Deer approximately $175,000 per hour.</p>
<h2>Texas Doled Out Cash for No Work</h2>
<p>For what purpose, you ask? Well, it wasn’t because the Lone Star State wanted to gain access to mined BTC units. It wasn’t to create jobs, and it wasn’t to help build the region’s economy. It was because the state was suffering from devastating winter storms, and the money was so that the company would shut off its mining rigs and not put the power grid in trouble.</p>
<p>The early 2021 winter storms suffered by Texas ultimately led to several deaths and a wide array of other problems. There were simply too many people blasting their heaters all day and night, and this led to serious issues with the state’s power sources. It also prevented many other individuals from gaining access to the power they needed to heat their homes and stay warm.</p>
<p>Over the past several years, Texas has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-is-still-a-major-crypto-mining-hub/" data-wpel-link="internal">become home to a wide</a> array of crypto mining companies, many of which hail from China given their home country ended bitcoin <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-crypto-mining-clampdown-in-china-is-not-over/" data-wpel-link="internal">mining in the summer</a> of 2021 and dubbed the practice illegal. Texas – known for its vast open spaces and low-cost energy – seemed like a good place to set up shop and keep things going, but this has led to some unexpected barricades, as with so many digital currency mining enterprises now making their way to the rural south, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nasty-heatwave-causes-texas-btc-miners-to-slow-down/" data-wpel-link="internal">power has become</a> limited and at times, more expensive for common people.</p>
<p>February of 2021 saw Texas suffering from winter storms Uri and Viola. The events led to several blackouts and freezing temperatures for residents. Mining computers and other machinery used by companies like Bit Deer were allegedly utilizing as much electricity as was required to power 6,500 homes. The money the state paid to Bit Deer was doled out over a four-day period of no activity, meaning the firm garnered as much as $18 million for NO WORK. As much as we all love mining, in many ways, that just doesn’t sound morally or ethically right.</p>
<h2>Is Mining Really That Bad?</h2>
<p>Crypto mining has garnered something of a negative reputation over the years amongst eco-friendly individuals. They say the practice should be outlawed fully given it is allegedly leading Mother Earth towards a dismal path that there’s no return from. In addition, there have been several reports published in the past suggesting crypto <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-bitcoin-mining-may-require-more-energy-than-180-countries/" data-wpel-link="internal">mining utilizes more energy</a> than most developing nations.</p>
<p>Even industry heads like Elon Musk have expressed concerns about the mining process. In early 2021, Musk was all set to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-permits-bitcoin-payments-for-tesla-vehicles/" data-wpel-link="internal">let crypto holders</a> buy Tesla vehicles with BTC, but the decision was later rescinded as Musk <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-has-taken-a-nasty-stumble-many-are-blaming-elon-musk/" data-wpel-link="internal">demanded answers regarding</a> the cleanliness of miners’ energy sources.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-paid-crypto-mining-firm-bit-deer-a-lot-of-money-to-shut-its-machines-off/">Texas Paid Crypto Mining Firm a Lot of Money to Shut Its Machines Off</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-paid-crypto-mining-firm-bit-deer-a-lot-of-money-to-shut-its-machines-off/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Survey Suggests Americans Aren&#8217;t Crazy About Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-survey-suggests-americans-arent-crazy-about-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-survey-suggests-americans-arent-crazy-about-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 15:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[survey]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77857</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A survey conducted by the Pew Research Center suggests most Americans don’t feel confident about, nor do they feel safe using, crypto. Survey: American&#8217;s Aren&#8217;t Confident Around Crypto Between March 13 and 19 of this year, the Research Center asked a group of people about their feelings towards crypto, and roughly three quarters of the<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-survey-suggests-americans-arent-crazy-about-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-survey-suggests-americans-arent-crazy-about-crypto/">New Survey Suggests Americans Aren&#8217;t Crazy About Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A survey conducted by the Pew Research Center suggests <a href="https://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2023/04/10/majority-of-americans-arent-confident-in-the-safety-and-reliability-of-cryptocurrency/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">most Americans don’t</a> feel confident about, nor do they feel safe using, crypto.</p>
<h2>Survey: American&#8217;s Aren&#8217;t Confident Around Crypto</h2>
<p>Between March 13 and 19 of this year, the Research Center asked a group of people about their feelings towards crypto, and roughly three quarters of the respondents (about 75 percent) suggested that their confidence in the space was lacking or nonexistent. For example, just under 40 percent of those taking part in the study said that they had zero confidence in the industry and didn’t feel comfortable in any way, shape, or form trading or using digital assets in any capacity.</p>
<p>Another 36 percent of the respondents, while their negative feelings weren’t nearly as large as the first group, said that their confidence was not particularly strong, and that it would take a lot to convince them otherwise. The most depressing part of the survey? Only two to four percent of those taking part said they feel extremely confident in crypto, while 18 percent said they only feel “somewhat” confident.</p>
<p>These kinds of numbers are a shame because despite all that’s been accomplished in the digital currency arena over the last ten years, there are still far too many people marred by recent incidents involving <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX</a> and other faulty companies. Like we’ve mentioned in several articles in the past, the FTX debacle is likely to leave a long-lasting – if not permanent – stain on the face of crypto.</p>
<p>With so much fraud taking place throughout the departments of FTX, and many other forms of crypto-related heists and crime occurring, one can’t really blame people for not feeling as strongly about crypto as they should.</p>
<p>FTX, for example, saw more <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-the-damage-caused-by-ftx-was-worse-than-initially-thought/" data-wpel-link="internal">than $200 billion in crypto</a> wiped from the digital slate, and it’s been alleged that customer funds were used by Sam Bankman-Fried and his fellow executive inappropriately (to either purchase luxury Bahamian real estate or to pay off loans for another company). This kind of fusing of both customer and company funds is illegal, and it casts a serious pall over the arena.</p>
<h2>There&#8217;s So Much Fraudulent Activity</h2>
<p>In addition, we’re constantly hearing about crypto cyberattacks and scams, the most common now being <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/romance-scams/" data-wpel-link="internal">romance scams</a>. There are so many people out there looking for love or significant others. In the digital age, they’re turning to the internet to find their perfect matches, but things are getting thwarted as many of those with online love profiles could potentially be crypto thieves that tell their victims to invest in criminal-controlled digital platforms.</p>
<p>Once they begin investing and trust that things are going well, they’re likely to encounter issues if they try to extract money from the platforms, and it’s not long before they realize they’ve been played.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-survey-suggests-americans-arent-crazy-about-crypto/">New Survey Suggests Americans Aren&#8217;t Crazy About Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-survey-suggests-americans-arent-crazy-about-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is the Gemini Exchange Suffering Financially?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-gemini-exchange-suffering-financially/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-gemini-exchange-suffering-financially/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 13:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genesis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Winklevoss]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77854</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The effects of the 2022 bear market haven’t fully disappeared, it seems. There are many companies out there still dealing with the repercussions of those bearish ripples, the Gemini exchange in New York being a big one. Gemini Gets $100 Million from Its Founders Not long ago, it was announced that Gemini founders Tyler and<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-gemini-exchange-suffering-financially/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-gemini-exchange-suffering-financially/">Is the Gemini Exchange Suffering Financially?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The effects of the 2022 bear market haven’t fully disappeared, it seems. There are many companies out there still dealing with the repercussions of those bearish ripples, the Gemini exchange in New York <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/the-winklevoss-twins-have-lent-100-million-of-their-own-money-to-keep-their-gemini-exchange-afloat-as-venture-funding-slows/ar-AA19IGfp" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">being a big one</a>.</p>
<h2>Gemini Gets $100 Million from Its Founders</h2>
<p>Not long ago, it was announced that Gemini founders Tyler and Cameron Winklevoss issued a loan of approximately $100 million of their own funds to aid in the company’s continued operations. This suggests one of many things, a major one being that the exchange is now on pins and needles and could be walking the same cold and ugly path that so many other crypto platforms (from <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX</a> to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/celsius-network-is-next-crypto-company-to-file-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">Celsius</a>) have trodden over the past 12 months.</p>
<p>To be fair, those companies arguably engaged in fraudulent and criminal activity, which is why they likely experienced troubles (both financial and otherwise) towards the end. At the time of writing, Gemini hasn’t been accused of any wrongdoing, nor is there any evidence suggesting the company took part in scam-like behavior, so it’s likely Gemini is still reeling from the ongoing bear conditions that made themselves so prominent last year.</p>
<p>On the one hand, it’s good news that the Winklevoss Twins are endowed with so much money given their company likely wouldn’t be surviving right about now without it. The fact that they’re able to shell out the necessary funds to keep the firm going suggests Gemini has a fighting chance, and its customers still have time to receive what’s theirs and enjoy a certain degree of stability.</p>
<p>However, it’s disappointing to know that while individual assets are doing relatively well (BTC, for example, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">recently hit $30K</a> for the first time in about ten months), the respective exchanges that sell or hold them are another story. It’s as though the fall of FTX is still ringing bells (and rather negative ones at that) approximately half a year after the exchange came crashing to the ground, and it’s likely that trust for crypto exchanges has fallen in recent weeks and months due to the fraudulent behavior that has clearly taken place within its departments.</p>
<p>While neither Cameron nor Tyler Winklevoss have issued individual statements regarding Gemini’s fate, they have mentioned that the money they’ve issued will be utilized strictly for operational purposes.</p>
<h2>A Lot of Previous Problems</h2>
<p>Gemini has been hit hard over the past 12 months. The company engaged in not one, but two separate <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gemini-exchange-engages-in-more-layoffs/" data-wpel-link="internal">layoff orders</a> that saw more than ten percent of its overall staff suddenly hitting the bread lines. In addition, the company’s lending arena Genesis Global Capital is now being scrutinized by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<p>The agency recently hit <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/investors-are-suing-the-gemini-exchange-over-alleged-fraud/" data-wpel-link="internal">Genesis with charges</a> that it sold unregistered securities through a lending program called Gemini Earn.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-gemini-exchange-suffering-financially/">Is the Gemini Exchange Suffering Financially?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-gemini-exchange-suffering-financially/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Woman in South Korea Murdered for Her Crypto Holdings</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/woman-in-south-korea-murdered-for-her-crypto-holdings/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/woman-in-south-korea-murdered-for-her-crypto-holdings/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 17:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Do Kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Murder]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77852</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The recent kidnapping and murder of a woman in Seoul, South Korea (the nation’s capital city) has turned up some new evidence. Police investigating the matter believe the woman may have been involved in various crypto-related disputes, and that her attacker was associated and hired by the opposing party. Why Is There So Much Crypto<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/woman-in-south-korea-murdered-for-her-crypto-holdings/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/woman-in-south-korea-murdered-for-her-crypto-holdings/">Woman in South Korea Murdered for Her Crypto Holdings</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The recent kidnapping and murder of a woman in Seoul, South Korea (the nation’s capital city) has turned up <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/2nd-ld-key-suspect-in-kidnapping-murder-first-proposed-killing-over-cryptocurrency-disputes-police/ar-AA19DSnQ" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">some new evidence</a>. Police investigating the matter believe the woman may have been involved in various crypto-related disputes, and that her attacker was associated and hired by the opposing party.</p>
<h2>Why Is There So Much Crypto Crime in South Korea?</h2>
<p>The pair perpetrating the crime was a husband-and-wife duo named Yoo and Hwang, and they are believed to have paid more than $53,000 to the key suspect in the murder to carry things out. This stems from an official statement from Seoul’s Suseo Police Station. Arrest warrants were later issued for the suspect (who goes by the name Lee) and for Hwang, who is wanted for questioning.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, Lee has confessed to all the charges that are against him, while the married couple say they have nothing to do with what’s going on. Lee has been arrested along with two other accomplices for allegedly carrying out the murder of the 48-year-old woman from the Gangnam district in Seoul, South Korea. The killing is believed to have occurred on March 29 of this year. Lee and his associates then later (crudely) disposed of her remains.</p>
<p>Lee has issued an apology to the victim and her family, saying in recent statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>I&#8217;d like to offer my sincere apology to the victim in this case, and I pray for the repose of her soul. I am also really sorry to her family for the irreparable scars this has caused.</p></blockquote>
<p>South Korea appears to be at the center of heavy digital currency-centered crime as of late. Not long ago, it was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-executive-do-kwon-arrested-in-montenegro/" data-wpel-link="internal">announced that Do Kwon</a> – the creator of Terra Labs – had been arrested in the European nation of Montenegro after he was discovered to be holding phony passports at an airport terminal. Do Kwon was wanted by authorities in connection with the collapse of Terra USD, an algorithmic stable currency that fell apart in the summer of last year, causing investors to lose billions.</p>
<h2>Kwon Making Off with Investments?</h2>
<p>Kwon is believed to have transferred all his Terra <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-case-against-crypto-exec-do-kwon-just-got-a-lot-hairier/" data-wpel-link="internal">holdings into BTC just</a> weeks before the coin’s collapse, suggesting to authorities that Kwon was planning to kill the currency and make off with any remaining profits in a rug pull. For months, Kwon was a fugitive hiding from the law, though he continued to deny this claim on social media, instead mentioning that he <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-exec-do-kwon-says-hes-willing-to-cooperate-following-arrest-warrant/" data-wpel-link="internal">was willing to cooperate</a> with police and that he was busy writing code in his living room.</p>
<p>The victim in this present case was part of a crypto investment scheme that the married couple also took part in. They ultimately discussed stealing her digital currency stash after the murder was to take place.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/woman-in-south-korea-murdered-for-her-crypto-holdings/">Woman in South Korea Murdered for Her Crypto Holdings</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/woman-in-south-korea-murdered-for-her-crypto-holdings/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How strong is the AI quantitative trading bot? speak with data</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-strong-is-the-ai-quantitative-trading-bot-speak-with-data/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-strong-is-the-ai-quantitative-trading-bot-speak-with-data/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 15:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78402</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The picture above is a return test chart of a quantitative strategy. Before the back test week is 2021 to 2023, 25 months, the rate of return is as high as 7869%, which is equivalent to an annualized rate of return of 3779%, which is the annualized rate of return. The rate is close to<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-strong-is-the-ai-quantitative-trading-bot-speak-with-data/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-strong-is-the-ai-quantitative-trading-bot-speak-with-data/">How strong is the AI quantitative trading bot? speak with data</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The picture above is a return test chart of a quantitative strategy. Before the back test week is 2021 to 2023, 25 months, the rate of return is as high as 7869%, which is equivalent to an annualized rate of return of 3779%, which is the annualized rate of return. The rate is close to 40 times. It&#8217;s time to embrace the future with <a href="https://www.atpbot.com?utm_source=livebitcoinnews&amp;utm_medium=sp&amp;utm_campaign=20230512" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>AI trading bots</strong></a>.</p>
<h4>What is Quantitative Trading?</h4>
<p>The quantitative strategy platform is a trading platform based on big data and artificial intelligence technology that develops a series of automated trading strategies by studying historical data and market trends. Through the quantitative strategy platform, you can choose a strategy that suits you, and automatically trade to obtain stable returns. According to incomplete statistics, the proportion of quantitative transactions used by investment banking institutions has exceeded 90%, and it has already determined the future of the speculative world.</p>
<h4>What are the advantages of automated quantitative trading over manual trading?</h4>
<p>Faster speed: Automated trading systems can analyze market data and execute trading operations more quickly, so that transactions can respond faster and capture market opportunities faster.</p>
<p>Better discipline: automated trading systems can adhere to strict trading rules and strategies, and avoid bad trading decisions caused by emotions and subjective judgments. Therefore, automated trading systems are better able to maintain trading discipline and stability.</p>
<p>More Precise: Automated trading systems are able to use sophisticated algorithms and models to analyze market data to more precisely identify and exploit trading opportunities and better manage risk.</p>
<p>Automated execution: The automated trading system can automatically execute trading strategies 24 hours a day, reducing the manpower and time costs required for manual trading, and can also keep trading while sleeping or leaving the computer.</p>
<p>Backtesting and optimization: Automated trading systems can use historical data for backtesting and optimization to improve trading strategies and improve trading performance.</p>
<h4>Why are quantitative trading bots suitable for the crypto market?</h4>
<p>The cryptocurrency market is highly volatile, and market trends are difficult to predict, and many investors have suffered losses as a result. However, trading platforms based on quantitative strategies can use data analysis and machine learning technology to find the laws and trends in the market, improve the success rate of investment, and reduce risks.</p>
<p>How should we carry out quantitative trading? First of all, you have to have a quantitative strategy. If you don&#8217;t have one, then ATPBot is a good choice.</p>
<h4>What is ATPBot?</h4>
<p><a href="https://www.atpbot.com?utm_source=livebitcoinnews&amp;utm_medium=sp&amp;utm_campaign=20230512" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>ATPBot</strong></a> is a platform that focuses on the development and service of quantitative trading strategies, and is committed to providing efficient and stable trading strategies for cryptocurrency investors. Using supercomputers and AI algorithms, combined with data analysis, social network sentiment analysis, fundamental analysis and other methods, a variety of scientific and effective quantitative trading strategies have been developed. All released strategies are back-tested with millisecond-level data, and many of them Quantitative strategies with an annual return of more than 1000% help you easily obtain returns in the market. ATPBot adheres to the consistent concept of integrity, transparency and security, and strives to make quantitative transactions easier, more efficient and more reliable.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-78404 aligncenter" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Picture107-600x424.png" alt="" width="600" height="424" /></p>
<h4>How is ATPBot different from traditional trading bots?</h4>
<p>Compared with other trading bots on the market, ATPBot has unique advantages. Unlike many other trading bot platforms that rely entirely on predetermined parameters set by the trader, ATPBot employs extensively tested and proven trading strategies. By conducting rigorous historical data analysis and market analysis, ATPBot has fine-tuned its strategies to minimize risks and losses while maximizing profits. This is different from other trading bots that cannot control the trading process and often cause traders to lose money.</p>
<p>Additionally, ATPBot eliminates the need for users to spend countless hours manually testing different parameters or gaining expertise in chart and indicator manipulation. With ATPBot, users can rely on a reliable and proven trading bot to professionally manage their investments for an efficient and effective trading experience.</p>
<p>In conclusion, choose ATPBot for an unparalleled trading experience, delivering results through proven trading strategies and professional investment management.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-78405 aligncenter" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Picture108-600x336.png" alt="" width="600" height="336" /></p>
<h4>Why choose ATPBot?</h4>
<p><strong>Technology leadership</strong>: Using the most advanced technology, combining multiple factors, looking for profit methods through complex data types.</p>
<p><strong>Convenient and easy to use</strong>: The platform is easy to use, one-click start strategy, provide professional guidance, suitable for inexperienced traders.</p>
<p><strong>Professional customization</strong>: Personally customize strategies for each customer, and strive to provide each customer with the most suitable quantitative strategy for them.</p>
<p>S<strong>ecurity and transparency</strong>: Customer funds cannot be accessed, all operations are transparent and visible, and we are committed to providing maximum protection for customer transactions.</p>
<p><strong>Monitoring and service</strong>: Provide 24-hour monitoring and one-on-one service to quickly solve customer problems.</p>
<p><strong>Ultra-low management fee</strong>: Provide a one-time payment and permanent operation mode, so that the investment income is greater.</p>
<p>In addition to the functions of the platform itself, ATPBot also has a professional <a href="https://discord.gg/JQnY3pNtkk" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>discord community</strong></a>, which gathers a large number of quantitative trading researchers and practitioners. In the community, you can interact with quantitative trading enthusiasts from all over the world, sharing experiences and ideas. Not only will this improve your trading knowledge and skills, but you can also learn and get inspired by other people&#8217;s trading strategies. At the same time, our community also provides professional guidance, including guidance on market trends, market analysis and trading skills, to help you go further on the road of quantitative trading.</p>
<p>Just <a href="https://www.atpbot.com/signup?utm_source=livebitcoinnews&amp;utm_medium=sp&amp;utm_campaign=20230512" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>register an account</strong></a> at ATPBot, you can open the door of automatic quantitative trading and share the results brought by big data.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-strong-is-the-ai-quantitative-trading-bot-speak-with-data/">How strong is the AI quantitative trading bot? speak with data</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-strong-is-the-ai-quantitative-trading-bot-speak-with-data/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Report Details What Really Led to the FTX Collapse</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-report-details-what-really-led-to-the-ftx-collapse/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-report-details-what-really-led-to-the-ftx-collapse/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 15:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hubris]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77849</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new report has emerged talking about what it was that really led to the destruction and collapse of the FTX digital currency exchange. Why Did FTX Really Fall? Everyone would like to think it was heavy corruption or something similar, but per the words of the report, it was merely “hubris and greed.” Hubris<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-report-details-what-really-led-to-the-ftx-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-report-details-what-really-led-to-the-ftx-collapse/">New Report Details What Really Led to the FTX Collapse</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new report has emerged talking about what it was that <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/hubris-incompetence-and-greed-plagued-failed-cryptocurrency-exchange-ftx/ar-AA19HgzF" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">really led to the destruction</a> and collapse of the FTX digital currency exchange.</p>
<h2>Why Did FTX <em>Really</em> Fall?</h2>
<p>Everyone would like to think it was heavy corruption or something similar, but per the words of the report, it was merely “hubris and greed.” Hubris is described as “arrogance before the gods” (according to games like <em>Far Cry 5</em>). Mere mortals like us should take that like everyone at FTX had tremendous egos. They all thought they were too smart and too capable and thus didn’t take necessary precautions.</p>
<p>In terms of greed, it’s clear that many people involved with the company sought to get their hands on money they didn’t necessarily need. Money that belonged to other people. This is among the many charges that the former head executive of FTX – Sam Bankman-Fried – is now facing. It is said that SBF utilized customer funds to purchase luxury real estate in the Bahamas, where the company was stationed. Naughty, naughty, naughty…</p>
<p>In addition, the debtors’ report also suggests that an incredible lack of competence underlined the many mishaps that occurred behind the FTX walls. For example, the company failed to create key executive roles to ensure specific duties were tackled in due time. Thus, you had an environment where everyone was clearly multi-tasking… Something they weren’t equipped to do. There was also no cybersecurity department to keep customer funds safe should mishaps have occurred (which they obviously did).</p>
<p>Lastly, the company is believed to have lied to third parties about its funds and business dealings, and there were many jokes amongst employees about how quick the company was to lose track of millions of dollars at a time. There was also no controlled framework or oversight of business dealings. In the end, this helped the firm to “collapse as quickly as it had grown,” the report comments.</p>
<p>The fall of FTX is likely to go down as one of the most embarrassing occurrences within the digital currency space. Founded in 2019 (merely four years ago), the company quickly rose through the ranks to become the third largest crypto exchange in the world by the summer of 2021. Everyone thought the company was on top of the world and incapable of collapsing, but they were wrong…</p>
<h2>A History of Bad Behavior</h2>
<p>In November of 2022, Sam Bankman-Fried complained online <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">that his company needed</a> cash fast to continue operating. He <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">approached his competitor</a> Binance about being bought out, but the latter firm took one look at FTX’s issues and quickly said “no.” FTX then had no choice but to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">file bankruptcy</a>.</p>
<p>It wasn’t long before this led to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftxs-disgraced-founder-has-been-arrested/" data-wpel-link="internal">the arrest</a> of Sam Bankman-Fried, who is <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-to-await-trial-at-his-parents-house/" data-wpel-link="internal">now awaiting trial</a> at his parents’ home in Northern California.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-report-details-what-really-led-to-the-ftx-collapse/">New Report Details What Really Led to the FTX Collapse</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-report-details-what-really-led-to-the-ftx-collapse/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
