<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 04:29:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Mike Novogratz Is Predicting a Major BTC Bull Run Soon</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-novogratz-is-predicting-a-major-btc-bull-run-soon/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-novogratz-is-predicting-a-major-btc-bull-run-soon/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 17:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mike Novogratz]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77892</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has been on a roll since the beginning of the year. The world’s number one digital currency has recently reached a price of about $30K per unit (for the first time in about ten or 11 months), and it seems like 2023 is set to be a year of healing for the asset. Now,<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-novogratz-is-predicting-a-major-btc-bull-run-soon/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-novogratz-is-predicting-a-major-btc-bull-run-soon/">Mike Novogratz Is Predicting a Major BTC Bull Run Soon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has been on a roll since the beginning of the year. The world’s number one digital currency has recently reached a price <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">of about $30K per</a> unit (for the first time in about ten or 11 months), and it seems like 2023 is set to be a year of healing for the asset. Now, Mike Novogratz – a bitcoin bull and billionaire hedge fund manager – <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/04/13/fed-sweet-spot-could-be-about-to-trigger-a-200-billion-bitcoin-price-boom/?sh=29b30bbf138d" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">believes the currency</a> is going to see a major price boom in the final months of the year.</p>
<h2>Mike Novogratz Predicts Big Things for BTC</h2>
<p>2023 is shaping up to be the exact opposite of 2022. The latter year was one of the worst on record for BTC. The currency lost more than 70 percent of its value after hitting a new all-time high in November of 2021. During that time, the currency was trading at a whopping $68,000 per unit, though by the time the end of 2022 came around, the currency had fallen into the mid-$16K range. It was a sad and ugly sight.</p>
<p>In his recent discussion, Novogratz said he’s confident the Federal Reserve is going to initiate maneuvers that ultimately help bitcoin. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>The clearest trades have been and will continue to be long gold, long euro, long bitcoin, [and] long Ethereum. These assets should do well with the Fed stopping hiking and then cutting.</p></blockquote>
<p>Not long ago, the Federal Reserve hinted that 2023 could be a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/federal-reserve-hikes-rates-again-what-will-happen-to-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">year of continued</a> rate hikes, though they don’t expect them to be as aggressive as they were in 2022. In addition, the federal agency said there’s a likelihood of a “mild recession” towards the end of the year.</p>
<p>In 2022, the Fed initiated so many rate hikes as a means of fighting inflation (which continues to be a problem in America having recently hit a 40-year high), that it ultimately caused problems for bitcoin and other assets, though Novogratz doesn’t think that’ll be the case this time around. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin had a huge run. We can consolidate here before moving towards $40,000 so long as the Fed plays out the way I think it’s going to play out.</p></blockquote>
<h2>$30K was a Big Turning Point for the World&#8217;s Leader in Digital Assets</h2>
<p>He believes that in the final months of 2023,  bitcoin will reach a price of about $40K, which will ultimately add about $200 billion to the crypto space. Alex Kuptsikevich – a senior market analyst at FX Pro – also stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>The $30,000 mark was significant for bitcoin in 2021 and the first half of 2022, acting as a market mode switch. Last year, bitcoin consolidated around this price for about five weeks before plunging sharply. There is a greater chance of a mirror dynamic, with the bulls taking a long time to gather their strength before making a decisive move higher.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-novogratz-is-predicting-a-major-btc-bull-run-soon/">Mike Novogratz Is Predicting a Major BTC Bull Run Soon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-novogratz-is-predicting-a-major-btc-bull-run-soon/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Ethereum Shapella Upgrade Occurred; Now What?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-ethereum-shapella-upgrade-occurred-now-what/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-ethereum-shapella-upgrade-occurred-now-what/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 15:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[merge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shapella]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77890</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>April saw the next big Ethereum update take place, and analysts are weighing in on what it can do for the world’s second largest digital currency by market cap (and the primary competitor to bitcoin) in the long run. Ethereum Endures Its Second Major Upgrade in 7 Months This is the second major upgrade to<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-ethereum-shapella-upgrade-occurred-now-what/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-ethereum-shapella-upgrade-occurred-now-what/">The Ethereum Shapella Upgrade Occurred; Now What?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>April saw the next big Ethereum update take place, and <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/ethereums-highly-anticipated-network-upgrade-is-here-heres-how-the-change-will-impact-the-worlds-2nd-biggest-cryptocurrency/ar-AA19OTBz" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">analysts are weighing</a> in on what it can do for the world’s second largest digital currency by market cap (and the primary competitor to bitcoin) in the long run.</p>
<h2>Ethereum Endures Its Second Major Upgrade in 7 Months</h2>
<p>This is the second major upgrade to Ethereum in about seven months. The first took place in September and was known as <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/merge/" data-wpel-link="internal">the Merge</a>. That upgrade moved Ethereum from a proof of work (PoW) to a proof of stake (PoS) module, thus allowing it to become greener and less energy intensive.</p>
<p>This new upgrade, called Shapella, will allow the withdrawals of staked ETH. Brian Fakhoury – a junior partner of venture firm Mechanism Capital – explained in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>It&#8217;s hard to tell [the impact] in the short term as there will be a lot of reshuffling in the [ether] staked. These flows could be bearish or bullish for the [decentralized finance] ecosystem and the Ethereum network itself. In the long run, the Shanghai upgrade brings native [ether] yield to a truly free market, which I believe is a requirement for real growth. As the withdrawal queue clears out, liquid staking protocols will be able to compete on more even terms as outflows from worse to better opportunities can be acted upon by market participants.</p></blockquote>
<p>While the Shapella upgrade is slated to assist the Ethereum network in the long term, there are likely to be short-term problems in that such a vast amount of staked ETH suddenly becoming available could lead to people selling their units as a means of making quick profits. This could ultimately affect the network for a little while and result in Ethereum price dips, though it’s not expected that this will last terribly long.</p>
<p>Constantin Guggi – CEO and co-founder of blockchain solutions provider Swisstronik – threw his two cents into the mix by saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>The staked tokens unlock is significant, and it may cause temporary volatility on the market. Due to the ever-changing nature of the industry, including its regulatory aspect, some validators had legal and financial difficulties during the lockup period. Now that they [have] gained access to their tokens, they will urge to sell them.</p></blockquote>
<h2>The Price May Be Affected Short Term</h2>
<p>Ben Caselin – vice president at crypto exchange Mask EX – said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Shapella is beneficial to the Ethereum project and should be regarded as a bullish event. Overall, we could expect some volatility around the event as is often the case when Ethereum goes through another upgrade, mostly because crypto markets are still primarily sentiment driven… Nonetheless, macro-conditions are more important at this stage, and we cannot isolate changes on the Ethereum chain from the wider economic context within which investors determine their risk appetite.</p></blockquote>
<p>Not long after the upgrade occurred, Ethereum shot up to the $1,900 range.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-ethereum-shapella-upgrade-occurred-now-what/">The Ethereum Shapella Upgrade Occurred; Now What?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-ethereum-shapella-upgrade-occurred-now-what/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lebanon Police Track Down and Take Back Stolen Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lebanon-police-track-down-and-take-back-stolen-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lebanon-police-track-down-and-take-back-stolen-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 13:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scam]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lebanon Police]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[romance scams]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77887</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Lebanon Police Department has been successful in tracking down a customer’s crypto funds that ultimately fell into the hands of a scammer. Lebanon Police Know What They&#8217;re Doing Richard Norris – supervisor of the Cyber Crimes Unit at the Lebanon Department – explained in an interview: Our unit handles everything from forensic extractions of<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lebanon-police-track-down-and-take-back-stolen-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lebanon-police-track-down-and-take-back-stolen-crypto/">Lebanon Police Track Down and Take Back Stolen Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Lebanon Police Department has been <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/lebanon-police-department-cybercrimes-unit-recovers-victim-s-money-in-cryptocurrency-scam/ar-AA19Nbln" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">successful in tracking down</a> a customer’s crypto funds that ultimately fell into the hands of a scammer.</p>
<h2>Lebanon Police Know What They&#8217;re Doing</h2>
<p>Richard Norris – supervisor of the Cyber Crimes Unit at the Lebanon Department – explained in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Our unit handles everything from forensic extractions of mobile devices and computers. We’re a member of the Internet Crimes Against Children Task Force, where we investigate people who try and use the internet to sexually exploit children, and we investigate almost every kind of electronic crime for the Lebanon Police Department.</p></blockquote>
<p>The cyber crime division of the Lebanon police authority is widely considered one of the best in the country as the agents have access to software that is rare or unavailable in many instances. Chief Phillip Roberts of the Lebanon Police Department said in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>It’s all in an effort to combat the ever-changing times of the internet and computer crimes that we’re seeing.</p></blockquote>
<p>Not long ago, the police gave a big presentation at a local nursing home warning the individuals living there that they were the most vulnerable to fraud. Roberts said:</p>
<blockquote><p>At the conclusion of the presentation, they had a chance to speak with a resident there that ultimately reported that she fell victim to a fraud.</p></blockquote>
<p>Describing how the police were able to find the stolen crypto units in the case, Roberts mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>They were able to execute the legal process to freeze that wallet and then subsequently forfeit the contents of the wallet to the Lebanon police’s government crypto account.</p></blockquote>
<p>In all, more than $5,000 in crypto was returned to the victim. Norris expressed his enthusiasm regarding the results of the department’s involvement, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>I’m very proud of the Cyber Crimes Unit. As their supervisor, people who work in this unit are incredibly dedicated, and the citizens in Lebanon should be proud that they have a unit like the LPD Cyber Crimes Unit. There are very few in existence that can do what we do.</p></blockquote>
<p>The department is continuing to perform outreach to let people know how they can avoid becoming victims of crypto scams. A big tactic is avoiding answering calls you don’t recognize or speaking to people that aren’t familiar to you. If any of them request payments, the time has come to hang up.</p>
<h2>Time to Take Action!</h2>
<p>In addition, if people feel they’ve been the victims of crypto scams, they should call their local district attorneys and tell them what happened.</p>
<p>Among the most common crypto scams today are <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/romance-scams/" data-wpel-link="internal">romance scams</a>, in which people allegedly looking for love online narrow in on victims and get them to invest in criminal-controlled crypto platforms that ultimately bar them from making withdrawals or taking advantage of their (albeit false) gains.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lebanon-police-track-down-and-take-back-stolen-crypto/">Lebanon Police Track Down and Take Back Stolen Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lebanon-police-track-down-and-take-back-stolen-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Could Nosedive Below $0.087</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-nosedive-below-0-087/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-nosedive-below-0-087/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 06:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar Lumens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78437</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stellar lumen price is struggling below the $0.0920 resistance zone against the US Dollar. XLM price is now trading below $0.0900 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0900 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could start a recovery<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-nosedive-below-0-087/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-nosedive-below-0-087/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Could Nosedive Below $0.087</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Stellar lumen price is struggling below the $0.0920 resistance zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>XLM price is now trading below $0.0900 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0900 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a recovery wave if it clears the $0.090 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Stellar lumen price is trading below $0.0900 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-27250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. XLM price could extend losses if it trades below the $0.0870 support.</em></p>
<h2>Stellar Lumen Price Analysis (XLM to USD)</h2>
<p>After a sharp decline below $0.090, Stellar Lumen price struggled to gain bullish momentum against the US Dollar. The XLM/USD pair traded below the $0.0880 level to move further into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>A low was formed near $0.0827 before the price started an upside correction. There was a move above the $0.0865 and $0.0870 levels. The price climbed above the 50% Fib retracement level of the key drop from the $0.0948 swing high to the $0.0827 low.</p>
<p>The price is now facing resistance near the $0.090 level. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0900 on the 4-hour chart.</p>
<p>XLM is now trading below $0.0890 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-turns-sell-on-rallies-near-0-092/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. Initial support on the downside is near the $0.0870 level. The next major support is near the $0.0855 zone. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.0820 level in the near term, below which the price might even retest $0.0800.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $0.0885 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). The next major resistance is near the $0.0900 zone and the trend line.</p>
<p>A clear upside break above the $0.090 zone might send the price toward $0.0920. Any more gains could lead the price toward the $0.0955 level or even $0.100.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78438" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-3.png" alt="•	Stellar lumen price is struggling below the $0.0920 resistance zone against the US Dollar. •	XLM price is now trading below $0.0900 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). •	There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0900 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken). •	The pair could start a recovery wave if it clears the $0.090 resistance. Stellar lumen price is trading below $0.0900 against the US Dollar, similar to Bitcoin. XLM price could extend losses if it trades below the $0.0870 support. Stellar Lumen Price Analysis (XLM to USD) After a sharp decline below $0.090, Stellar Lumen price struggled to gain bullish momentum against the US Dollar. The XLM/USD pair traded below the $0.0880 level to move further into a bearish zone. A low was formed near $0.0827 before the price started an upside correction. There was a move above the $0.0865 and $0.0870 levels. The price climbed above the 50% Fib retracement level of the key drop from the $0.0948 swing high to the $0.0827 low. The price is now facing resistance near the $0.090 level. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0900 on the 4-hour chart.  XLM is now trading below $0.0890 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Initial support on the downside is near the $0.0870 level. The next major support is near the $0.0855 zone. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.0820 level in the near term, below which the price might even retest $0.0800.  On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $0.0885 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). The next major resistance is near the $0.0900 zone and the trend line.  A clear upside break above the $0.090 zone might send the price toward $0.0920. Any more gains could lead the price toward the $0.0955 level or even $0.100.  The chart indicates that XLM price is now trading below $0.0900 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start a recovery wave if it clears the $0.090 resistance. Technical Indicators 4 hours MACD – The MACD for XLM/USD is gaining momentum in the bearish zone. 4 hours RSI - The RSI for XLM/USD is now below the 50 level. Key Support Levels – $0.0870 and $0.0855. Key Resistance Levels – $0.090, $0.0920, and $0.0950." width="1834" height="845" /></a></p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XLMUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that XLM price is now trading below $0.0900 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start a recovery wave if it clears the $0.090 resistance.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XLM/USD is gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for XLM/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.0870 and $0.0855.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.090, $0.0920, and $0.0950.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-nosedive-below-0-087/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Could Nosedive Below $0.087</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-nosedive-below-0-087/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Price Analysis: More Gains Possible Above $0.47</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-more-gains-possible-above-0-47/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-more-gains-possible-above-0-47/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 04:28:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78434</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple price started a downside correction from the $0.4700 zone against the US dollar. The price is now trading above $0.44 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break above a key contracting triangle with resistance near $0.430 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Kraken). The<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-more-gains-possible-above-0-47/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-more-gains-possible-above-0-47/">Ripple Price Analysis: More Gains Possible Above $0.47</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ripple price started a downside correction from the $0.4700 zone against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $0.44 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a key contracting triangle with resistance near $0.430 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a fresh increase above the $0.4700 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ripple price is consolidating near $0.452 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-27250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. XRP price must stay above the $0.440 support to remain in a bullish zone.</em></p>
<h2>Ripple Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, Ripple price saw a decent increase above the $0.4250 resistance against the US Dollar. The XRP/USD pair climbed above the $0.432 resistance to move into a positive zone.</p>
<p>There was a break above a key contracting triangle with resistance near $0.430 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair. The bulls even pumped the price above the $0.45 resistance. A high was formed near $0.4750 and the price recently corrected lower.</p>
<p>There was a move below the $0.470 and $0.465 levels. The bears pushed the price below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.4187 swing low to the $0.4750 high.</p>
<p>The price is now trading above $0.44 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-could-face-hurdles-near-0-45/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. It is trading above the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.4187 swing low to the $0.4750 high. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near $0.470.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $0.4750 level. A close above the $0.4750 resistance zone might start a strong increase. In the stated case, the price could even surpass the $0.5000 resistance. Any more gains might send the price toward the $0.525 resistance.</p>
<p>Initial support on the downside is near the $0.451 level. The next major support is near the $0.4400 level. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.42 level, below which the price might even test $0.400.</p>
<div id="attachment_78435" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Ripple-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78435" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78435" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Ripple-3.png" alt="Ripple Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78435" class="wp-caption-text">Ripple Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">chart</a>, Ripple’s price is now trading above the $0.44zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start a fresh increase above the $0.4700 resistance.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XRP/USD is now gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for XRP/USD is near the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.4510, $0.4400, and $0.4200.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.4700 and $0.4750.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-more-gains-possible-above-0-47/">Ripple Price Analysis: More Gains Possible Above $0.47</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-more-gains-possible-above-0-47/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nirmala Sitharaman Thinks Crypto Will Dominate India&#8217;s Future</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nirmala-sitharaman-thinks-crypto-will-dominate-indias-future/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nirmala-sitharaman-thinks-crypto-will-dominate-indias-future/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 17:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nirmala Sitharaman]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77873</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>India’s Minister of Finance Nirmala Sitharaman says cryptocurrencies will take up most of the chat time during this year’s upcoming G20 presidency event in India. Nirmala Sitharaman on Crypto in India Not long ago, Sitharaman visited Washington and explained in a statement: Given so many collapses and shocks in cryptocurrencies, we seek to develop a<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nirmala-sitharaman-thinks-crypto-will-dominate-indias-future/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nirmala-sitharaman-thinks-crypto-will-dominate-indias-future/">Nirmala Sitharaman Thinks Crypto Will Dominate India&#8217;s Future</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>India’s Minister of Finance Nirmala Sitharaman says <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-in/news/other/finance-minister-nirmala-sitharaman-seeks-common-framework-for-cryptocurrency-says-important-part-of-discussion-under-india-s-g20-presidency/ar-AA19HD9V" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">cryptocurrencies will take</a> up most of the chat time during this year’s upcoming G20 presidency event in India.</p>
<h2>Nirmala Sitharaman on Crypto in India</h2>
<p>Not long ago, Sitharaman visited Washington and explained in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>Given so many collapses and shocks in cryptocurrencies, we seek to develop a common framework for all countries to deal with this matter.</p></blockquote>
<p>She was referring to the fateful <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">fall of FTX</a>, once one of the top digital currency exchanges in the world. The company came crashing down in November of last year in a very unexpected fashion, and there are many governments and regulators out there doing all they can to try and avoid another (similar) situation like that happening. They are allegedly concerned about investors’ funds, and they don’t want to see crypto executives commingling them with business assets the way Sam Bankman-Fried did.</p>
<p>Sitharaman was participating in a roundtable discussion in Washington in which she discussed India’s future regarding crypto and upcoming business opportunities pertaining to the digital currency arena.</p>
<p>A few months ago, Shaktikanta Das – the governor of the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) – said he doesn’t think crypto assets have any place in India and he would prefer to do away with all of them, no matter how big or important they might seem. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>RBI&#8217;s position is very clear. It should be banned, all of them. The technology of blockchain needs to be supported.</p></blockquote>
<p>Sitharaman further commented during the roundtable meeting:</p>
<blockquote><p>Free trade agreements are being signed in a much faster way, nowadays. We&#8217;ve just concluded one with Australia. Earlier, we concluded with UAE, Mauritius, and with ASEAN. We have extended the quota-free and tariff-free regime to least developed countries.</p></blockquote>
<p>India has long had a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/regulators-in-india-are-still-at-war-with-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">very up-and-down relationship</a> with bitcoin and crypto. Back in 2018, the nation announced that traditional financial institutions would not be allowed to do any work or business with crypto firms. While many outlets reported that crypto was receiving a full-on ban, this wasn’t quite true, and it was just that banks and other standard financial platforms were no longer allowed to provide tools or services to blockchain and crypto-based enterprises.</p>
<h2>Turning Things Around</h2>
<p>About two years later, the nation’s Supreme Court decided that such action was unconstitutional, and a reversal was initiated. From there, many analysts thought India would become the next big crypto haven of the world, and for a while, it looked like this was going to be the path the nation took, though eventually, the country’s parliament began discussing a full crypto ban in which trading or being involved in assets would be punishable by fines and even prison sentences.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, no official decisions regarding the potential ban have been made yet.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nirmala-sitharaman-thinks-crypto-will-dominate-indias-future/">Nirmala Sitharaman Thinks Crypto Will Dominate India&#8217;s Future</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nirmala-sitharaman-thinks-crypto-will-dominate-indias-future/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Next BTC Halving Is a Year Away; What&#8217;s Going to Happen?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-next-btc-halving-is-a-year-away-whats-going-to-happen/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-next-btc-halving-is-a-year-away-whats-going-to-happen/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 15:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jamie Sly]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77871</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>2024 is set to be a big year for several reasons. A big one is that Americans can finally vote Joe Biden out of office and spare their nation more incompetency, but a different reason is because the next bitcoin halving is set to occur. The Halving Is on Its Way Bitcoin halving events take<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-next-btc-halving-is-a-year-away-whats-going-to-happen/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-next-btc-halving-is-a-year-away-whats-going-to-happen/">The Next BTC Halving Is a Year Away; What&#8217;s Going to Happen?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>2024 is set to be a big year for several reasons. A big one is that Americans can finally vote Joe Biden out of office and spare their nation more incompetency, but a different <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-is-one-year-away-from-a-major-technical-event-history-suggests-the-start-of-another-bull-run/ar-AA19KSBy" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reason is because the</a> next bitcoin halving is set to occur.</p>
<h2>The Halving Is on Its Way</h2>
<p>Bitcoin halving events take place every four years or so. It’s when the world’s number one digital currency by market cap undergoes a technical change that causes its rarity to grow via the slashing of digital rewards that go to miners.</p>
<p>Basically, for every new block that gets mined and extracted from the blockchain to be added to circulation, the miners receive crypto-based rewards for their activities, though with each halving, the rewards they get are ultimately reduced by 50 percent.</p>
<p>2024 will be no different, and while the specific date is not yet known, the halving is slated to occur in either April or May of that year. In anticipation of the halving, the bitcoin price has been spiking over the last several weeks, and the currency recently hit an 11-month high <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">of about $30K</a>. This marks the first time the currency has struck such a chord since June of last year.</p>
<p>Vijay Ayyar – vice president of corporate development and international at crypto exchange Luno – commented in an interview that the “cyclical” bottom for BTC has formed largely due to the banking <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-the-silvergate-collapse-shouldnt-predict-cryptos-future/" data-wpel-link="internal">crisis that occurred</a> earlier in the year. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>This tends to happen a year or so prior to the bitcoin&#8217;s halving event, which is slated next for around April 2024.</p></blockquote>
<p>One of the cool things about all past halving events is that they usually precede major rallies, and there are many analysts that don’t think 2024 will be an exception to the rule. They predict that the price of bitcoin is going to spike even higher and thus push it to a new record price. Jamie Sly – analyst at Crypto Compare – said in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>Analyzing historical bitcoin halving patterns, it appears that investors often accumulate bitcoin in the run-up to the halving event, although the exact timing and extent of returns post-halving can differ. The accumulation period from the market bottom after the breakout to the halving date has historically spanned at least 500 days… This would mean, if we were to assume that the market bottom for this cycle was in November [of] last year (when bitcoin hit a yearly low of $15,760), then we are only 142 days into the current cycle. This would correlate with the next expected bitcoin halving date, which is another 378 days ahead.</p></blockquote>
<h2>BTC Has Been Doing Quite Well</h2>
<p>Bitcoin is presently more than 70 percent higher than where it was at the end of 2022.</p>
<p>By that time, it had fallen into the mid-$16K range.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-next-btc-halving-is-a-year-away-whats-going-to-happen/">The Next BTC Halving Is a Year Away; What&#8217;s Going to Happen?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-next-btc-halving-is-a-year-away-whats-going-to-happen/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Warren Buffett Continues to Hate on Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/warren-buffett-continues-to-hate-on-bitcoin/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/warren-buffett-continues-to-hate-on-bitcoin/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 13:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin streaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warren Buffett]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77868</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has been doing quite well as of late. The currency recently hit a price of $30K for the first time in about 11 months and the asset has shot up steadily since the beginning of the year. Sadly, this has not been enough to convince Warren Buffett – a long-time crypto critic – of<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/warren-buffett-continues-to-hate-on-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/warren-buffett-continues-to-hate-on-bitcoin/">Warren Buffett Continues to Hate on Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has been doing quite well as of late. The currency recently hit a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">price of $30K for</a> the first time in about 11 months and the asset has shot up steadily since the beginning of the year. Sadly, this has not been enough to convince Warren Buffett – a long-time crypto critic – of its worth, and he’s doubling down <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/savingandinvesting/i-ve-seen-people-do-stupid-things-all-my-life-warren-buffett-doubles-down-on-his-long-held-views-on-bitcoin-and-crypto/ar-AA19Mfw7" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">on his hatred and skepticism</a> of the world’s number one digital currency by market cap.</p>
<h2>Warren Buffett Still Doesn&#8217;t Care About BTC</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, he compared buying bitcoin to gambling or playing the lottery. Buffett said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I didn’t like chain letters when I was a kid. I thought, ‘Why in the world should I send along a chain letter?’ […] I’ve seen people do stupid things all my life, and I really, I empathize with that. I mean, people like to play the lottery […] People love the idea that they’re going to make more money tomorrow.</p></blockquote>
<p>He has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/warren-buffett-explains-his-hate-for-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">stated in the past</a> that bitcoin will not amount to a darn thing. He has gone so far as to refer to it as “rat poison squared,” and he doesn’t think the currency has any real value to it, at one point even comparing selling bitcoin to trying to sell a button of one’s own shirt. Buffett continued with:</p>
<blockquote><p>I looked at all these people, who had flown thousands of miles to do something that [was] unintelligent as fast as they could. They thought the dice were hot or something like that, and I thought, ‘I’m going to get rich in this country.’ I mean if that’s what people do. I can be smarter than that.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also says the only real reason anybody gets involved in bitcoin or other forms of crypto is because they see their neighbors are making money and they begin to experience FOMO (fear of missing out). At the end of the day, however, he believes this is never a reason to get involved in a potential investment, and people aren’t doing their research or due diligence enough. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>It really drives them crazy if their next-door neighbor is making more money not knowing what they’re doing and they’re just sitting there, and their spouse is saying, ‘Why is that guy getting a second car, and why are we missing this whole thing?’ The gambling instinct is so strong.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Avoid Investing in Film Ventures</h2>
<p>When it comes to <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/savingandinvesting/warren-buffett-tears-into-banks-trashes-bitcoin-and-warns-inflation-and-recession-can-lead-to-big-problems/ar-AA19Lqa3" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">other negative investments</a>, he said that the movie and entertainment industries sit in this category in that while moviemakers and everyone involved in the working elements tend to do well, the shareholders don’t. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Streaming is not really a very good business. The people in entertainment have made lots of money. The shareholders really haven&#8217;t done that great over time.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/warren-buffett-continues-to-hate-on-bitcoin/">Warren Buffett Continues to Hate on Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/warren-buffett-continues-to-hate-on-bitcoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Texas Paid Crypto Mining Firm a Lot of Money to Shut Its Machines Off</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-paid-crypto-mining-firm-bit-deer-a-lot-of-money-to-shut-its-machines-off/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-paid-crypto-mining-firm-bit-deer-a-lot-of-money-to-shut-its-machines-off/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 17:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bit Deer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Texas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77859</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In early 2021, the state of Texas paid a bitcoin mining company called Bit Deer approximately $175,000 per hour. Texas Doled Out Cash for No Work For what purpose, you ask? Well, it wasn’t because the Lone Star State wanted to gain access to mined BTC units. It wasn’t to create jobs, and it wasn’t<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-paid-crypto-mining-firm-bit-deer-a-lot-of-money-to-shut-its-machines-off/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-paid-crypto-mining-firm-bit-deer-a-lot-of-money-to-shut-its-machines-off/">Texas Paid Crypto Mining Firm a Lot of Money to Shut Its Machines Off</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In early 2021, the state of Texas paid a <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/texas-paid-bitcoin-company-175k-205910042.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">bitcoin mining company</a> called Bit Deer approximately $175,000 per hour.</p>
<h2>Texas Doled Out Cash for No Work</h2>
<p>For what purpose, you ask? Well, it wasn’t because the Lone Star State wanted to gain access to mined BTC units. It wasn’t to create jobs, and it wasn’t to help build the region’s economy. It was because the state was suffering from devastating winter storms, and the money was so that the company would shut off its mining rigs and not put the power grid in trouble.</p>
<p>The early 2021 winter storms suffered by Texas ultimately led to several deaths and a wide array of other problems. There were simply too many people blasting their heaters all day and night, and this led to serious issues with the state’s power sources. It also prevented many other individuals from gaining access to the power they needed to heat their homes and stay warm.</p>
<p>Over the past several years, Texas has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-is-still-a-major-crypto-mining-hub/" data-wpel-link="internal">become home to a wide</a> array of crypto mining companies, many of which hail from China given their home country ended bitcoin <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-crypto-mining-clampdown-in-china-is-not-over/" data-wpel-link="internal">mining in the summer</a> of 2021 and dubbed the practice illegal. Texas – known for its vast open spaces and low-cost energy – seemed like a good place to set up shop and keep things going, but this has led to some unexpected barricades, as with so many digital currency mining enterprises now making their way to the rural south, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nasty-heatwave-causes-texas-btc-miners-to-slow-down/" data-wpel-link="internal">power has become</a> limited and at times, more expensive for common people.</p>
<p>February of 2021 saw Texas suffering from winter storms Uri and Viola. The events led to several blackouts and freezing temperatures for residents. Mining computers and other machinery used by companies like Bit Deer were allegedly utilizing as much electricity as was required to power 6,500 homes. The money the state paid to Bit Deer was doled out over a four-day period of no activity, meaning the firm garnered as much as $18 million for NO WORK. As much as we all love mining, in many ways, that just doesn’t sound morally or ethically right.</p>
<h2>Is Mining Really That Bad?</h2>
<p>Crypto mining has garnered something of a negative reputation over the years amongst eco-friendly individuals. They say the practice should be outlawed fully given it is allegedly leading Mother Earth towards a dismal path that there’s no return from. In addition, there have been several reports published in the past suggesting crypto <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-bitcoin-mining-may-require-more-energy-than-180-countries/" data-wpel-link="internal">mining utilizes more energy</a> than most developing nations.</p>
<p>Even industry heads like Elon Musk have expressed concerns about the mining process. In early 2021, Musk was all set to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-permits-bitcoin-payments-for-tesla-vehicles/" data-wpel-link="internal">let crypto holders</a> buy Tesla vehicles with BTC, but the decision was later rescinded as Musk <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-has-taken-a-nasty-stumble-many-are-blaming-elon-musk/" data-wpel-link="internal">demanded answers regarding</a> the cleanliness of miners’ energy sources.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-paid-crypto-mining-firm-bit-deer-a-lot-of-money-to-shut-its-machines-off/">Texas Paid Crypto Mining Firm a Lot of Money to Shut Its Machines Off</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-paid-crypto-mining-firm-bit-deer-a-lot-of-money-to-shut-its-machines-off/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
