<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 12:33:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The FTX Arena Is Changing Its Name Following the Exchange&#8217;s Fall</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-ftx-arena-is-changing-its-name-following-exchange-collapse/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-ftx-arena-is-changing-its-name-following-exchange-collapse/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 17:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tom Brady]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75460</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The FTX collapse has been all everyone’s talked about over the last month or so, and it appears that many people and businesses that were once tied to the now failed exchange are looking to distance themselves from it and quickly. The Miami Heat Is Ending Its Relationship with FTX One of them is the<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-ftx-arena-is-changing-its-name-following-exchange-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-ftx-arena-is-changing-its-name-following-exchange-collapse/">The FTX Arena Is Changing Its Name Following the Exchange&#8217;s Fall</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The FTX collapse has been all everyone’s talked about over the last month or so, and it appears that many people and businesses that were once tied to the now failed exchange are looking to distance themselves from it and quickly.</p>
<h2>The Miami Heat Is Ending Its Relationship with FTX</h2>
<p>One of them is the FTX Arena, which hosts home games for the Miami Heat. It’s now looking to end its relationship with the <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/miami-heat-will-rename-ftx-arena-after-cryptocurrency-exchange-collapses/ar-AA140KAR" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">disgraced trading platform</a> and change its name fast. In a statement, the team said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Miami-Dade County and the Miami Heat are immediately taking action to terminate our business relationships with FTX, and we will be working together to find a new naming rights partner for the arena.</p></blockquote>
<p>The Miami Heat is famous for having basketball players such as Shaquille O’Neal on its roster at one point. Spokespeople for the Miami Heat have stated that the situation surrounding FTX is “extremely disappointing.&#8221;</p>
<p>FTX gained a lot of fame in the industry for its use of traditional television commercials and sponsorships. The company has also formed heavy relationships with sports stars, many of which were featured in their small-screen ads. One such figure was Tom Brady, the legendary quarterback for the New England Patriots. He was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tom-brady-featured-in-new-ftx-crypto-commercial/" data-wpel-link="internal">seen in a commercial</a> for the firm a few months back that poked fun at the digital currency mining process.</p>
<p>Prominently armed with a flamethrower, Brady fired a hot blaze at a nearby block of ice. Once the ice had melted, a bitcoin was visible to the audience. Brady has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sports-stars-stephen-curry-and-tom-brady-join-the-ftx-exchange-family-as-ambassadors/" data-wpel-link="internal">also agreed to serve</a> as a brand ambassador in the past to the company.</p>
<p>But was once all money, fun, and games for FTX has quickly turned into embarrassment as the company has collapsed rather suddenly, taking many players’ money with it. The firm first began experiencing issues in mid-November and went to Binance for help, claiming it <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">was experiencing a liquidity</a> crunch. This meant it didn’t have enough funds on hand to stay afloat, and it asked the larger enterprise to engage in a buyout.</p>
<p>From there, it looked <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">like a major acquisition</a> was about to happen, though it never did as Changpeng Zhao, the man behind Binance, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">eventually backed away from</a> the deal, claiming FTX’s problems were simply too big to manage. From there, the company <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">has fallen into bankruptcy</a> and the head executive of the company, Sam Bankman-Fried, has resigned.</p>
<h2>So Much Controversy</h2>
<p>It’s a sad and ugly sight as what was considered one of the top crypto exchanges in the industry has now fallen into the same ranks as enterprises like the Celsius Network and Three Arrows Capital.</p>
<p>At this time, FTX-based controversy continues as many are <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/half-a-billion-dollars-goes-missing-from-ftx-exchange/" data-wpel-link="internal">wondering how half a billion</a> in crypto funds could have gone missing from the exchange.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-ftx-arena-is-changing-its-name-following-exchange-collapse/">The FTX Arena Is Changing Its Name Following the Exchange&#8217;s Fall</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-ftx-arena-is-changing-its-name-following-exchange-collapse/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vitalik Buterin Wants All Crypto Exchanges to Be Transparent About Their Financials</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vitalik-buterin-wants-all-crypto-exchanges-to-be-transparent-about-their-financials/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vitalik-buterin-wants-all-crypto-exchanges-to-be-transparent-about-their-financials/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 15:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vitalik buterin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75458</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Following the collapse of famed crypto exchange FTX, Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin is planning a new set of protocols that would help exchanges show their customers what reserves they have in place. Vitalik Buterin Says Exchanges Need to Be Clear One of the big things that allegedly led to the fall of FTX was the<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vitalik-buterin-wants-all-crypto-exchanges-to-be-transparent-about-their-financials/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vitalik-buterin-wants-all-crypto-exchanges-to-be-transparent-about-their-financials/">Vitalik Buterin Wants All Crypto Exchanges to Be Transparent About Their Financials</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Following the collapse of famed crypto exchange FTX, Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin is planning a new set of protocols that <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/ethereums-vitalik-buterin-is-planning-this-cryptocurrency-safeguard-changpeng-zhao-tells-benzinga-in-twitter-space/ar-AA146m0o" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">would help exchanges</a> show their customers what reserves they have in place.</p>
<h2>Vitalik Buterin Says Exchanges Need to Be Clear</h2>
<p>One of the big things that allegedly led to the fall of FTX was the sudden and unexpected “liquidity crunch” the company seemed to endure last-minute. It was stated in a series of messages online that Sam Bankman-Fried, the man tasked with running the firm, had <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">reached out to his bigger</a> counterpart Binance to claim that the company was experiencing a sudden lack of funds, and that Binance stood to benefit by buying the smaller company out.</p>
<p>For a while, it looked <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">like this was going</a> to happen, though Binance later sent out an announcement saying that it <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">would not be moving</a> forward with the acquisition given FTX was dealing with far too many issues, and there was nothing its staff could do. As such, FTX later fell into disarray.</p>
<p>To ensure that this never happens again, Buterin thinks it’s important for all crypto exchanges to be able to show from the get-go that they have money in place to support themselves even in the direst circumstances. He says this will help build customer trust and allow them to see what they’re dealing with in terms of finding companies to trade through.</p>
<p>Right now, Buterin wants to use Binance as a guinea pig of sorts, in which the exchange is used to test out the new series of protocols. Changpeng Zhao – the man behind the trading platform – said in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>And I think there are no suspicious activities related to us. For other players, I have not seen their books, so [I] cannot comment, but it is not a very good thing to do. They may or may not have a valid reason to do so, but I really don’t know… We expect it (the Merkle tree) in a couple of weeks and therefore, we have published all our cold wallet addresses. It is not as good as a Merkle tree, but at least users know how [many] funds we have.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Zhao Doesn&#8217;t Want to Play God</h2>
<p>Zhao has faced some criticism for previously selling his FTT tokens, FTT being the native cryptocurrency of the FTX exchange. He has defended his actions, claiming to have only sold a small portion. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>So, I think we acted in very ethical ways&#8230; We will try to help FTX users, but it was the users who chose to use FTX, right? We don’t want to create a situation where if anything goes down in the industry, we [need] to pay for it. That is not right for our users.</p></blockquote>
<p>He is adamant that Binance cannot step in and solve every problem in the industry.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vitalik-buterin-wants-all-crypto-exchanges-to-be-transparent-about-their-financials/">Vitalik Buterin Wants All Crypto Exchanges to Be Transparent About Their Financials</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vitalik-buterin-wants-all-crypto-exchanges-to-be-transparent-about-their-financials/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Where Did Sam Bankman-Fried Go? Many Crypto Analysts Are Curious</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/where-is-sam-bankman-fried-many-crypto-analysts-want-to-know/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/where-is-sam-bankman-fried-many-crypto-analysts-want-to-know/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 13:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mark Cuban]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75455</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Many are wondering where Sam Bankman-Fried of FTX fame (or rather notoriety, at this point) has gone. The executive resigned from his company in mid-November following its collapse and he hasn’t been seen or heard from since. Has Sam Bankman-Fried Gone Missing? So, where is he? There seems to be a wide array of speculation<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/where-is-sam-bankman-fried-many-crypto-analysts-want-to-know/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/where-is-sam-bankman-fried-many-crypto-analysts-want-to-know/">Where Did Sam Bankman-Fried Go? Many Crypto Analysts Are Curious</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Many <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/disgraced-ftx-founder-knocks-down-191830684.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">are wondering where</a> Sam Bankman-Fried of FTX fame (or rather notoriety, at this point) has gone. The executive resigned from his company in mid-November following its collapse and he hasn’t been seen or heard from since.</p>
<h2>Has Sam Bankman-Fried Gone Missing?</h2>
<p>So, where is he? There seems to be a wide array of speculation online about what has become of the executive, with some claiming he has taken a private jet and fled to Argentina. Allegedly, one news source sent him a text asking this question only to receive a text message saying, “Nope.”</p>
<p>Others say he fled to the Bahamas where FTX is based, though this isn’t likely given he is presently under investigation in that country. The man has been very standoffish in recent weeks after the fall of his company and becoming a national embarrassment.</p>
<p>One journalist – Caitlin Ostroff, who works for the <em>Wall Street Journal</em> – says that this is very unlike him. She says that often, he’s very friendly and outgoing and is quick to respond to inquiries or requests for interviews and information. She commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>You would send emails to the press team at FTX, and Sam Bankman-Fried himself would email you back. He was very approachable, very easily accessed.</p></blockquote>
<p>Not long ago, however, that attitude appeared to change, with one reporter claiming that he was very fidgety in a Zoom call and that he appeared very nervous about answering specific questions such as where he was based. The reporter claimed that this was the answer given by Bankman-Fried during the online meeting about his location:</p>
<blockquote><p>I, uh, so, sorry, I, I’m hesitating because I mostly sleep on a bag… I live, I don’t know. Technically I live alone, but don’t sleep there. I mostly sleep on couches and beanbags.</p></blockquote>
<p>Mark Cuban – a billionaire investor and a major bitcoin and crypto bull – describes Sam Bankman-Fried as running FTX in a “dumb” way. In a statement, he commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>So, what does Sam Bankman do? He just, give me more, give me more, give me more, so I’m going to borrow money, loan it to my affiliated company, and hope and pretend to myself that the FTT tokens that are in there on my balance sheet are going to sustain their value.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Huge and Ugly Situation</h2>
<p>FTX and its subsequent collapse will likely go down in history as some of the biggest crypto debacles to ever occur. At only three years old, FTX rose to prominence not long after it opened its doors for business in 2019. Just a few weeks ago, the company <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">reached out to Binance</a> for help, claiming it was enduring a “liquidity crunch” and not likely to survive unless the larger firm was willing to buy it out.</p>
<p>Sadly, the deal was not to be, and the company has since crashed.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/where-is-sam-bankman-fried-many-crypto-analysts-want-to-know/">Where Did Sam Bankman-Fried Go? Many Crypto Analysts Are Curious</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/where-is-sam-bankman-fried-many-crypto-analysts-want-to-know/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Earn 175% APR Through ApeCoin (APE) Staking on LBank Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/earn-175-apr-through-apecoin-ape-staking-on-lbank-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/earn-175-apr-through-apecoin-ape-staking-on-lbank-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 12:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76040</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec 14, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has recently launched ApeCoin (APE) staking in its &#8220;Earn” – “Flexible” section, users will be able to earn APE token with an annual return of 175% (floating adjustment), and withdraw anytime without locking. APE Staking Is the New Trend Recently,<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/earn-175-apr-through-apecoin-ape-staking-on-lbank-exchange/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/earn-175-apr-through-apecoin-ape-staking-on-lbank-exchange/">Earn 175% APR Through ApeCoin (APE) Staking on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec 14, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has recently launched ApeCoin (APE) staking in its &#8220;Earn” – “Flexible” section, users will be able to earn APE token with an annual return of 175% (floating adjustment), and withdraw anytime without locking.</p>
<p><strong>APE Staking Is the New Trend</strong></p>
<p>Recently, ApeCoin DAO (ApeDAO) has established an official staking protocol for ApeCoin (APE), which was created as a way for APE, BAYC, MAYC, and BAKC holders to earn rewards through staking. APE can be staked by itself or in conjunction with a BAYC, MAYC, or BAKC in one of the four staking pools, with each pool offering different levels of rewards.</p>
<p>The protocol was proposed in AIPs 21 and 22 and subsequently approved by the community on May 4, 2022. Following approval, the Ape Foundation enlisted Horizen Labs to provide a platform for the staking protocol according to the specifications set forth in the AIPs.</p>
<p>Staking is a common way to earn passive income in crypto space. This protocol basically allows holders of APE to put their idle tokens to work by staking them within various pools and earning additional rewards in the form of more APE. Being more than just a simple staking pool, the protocol has the distinction of offering layers of rewards for holders of certain NFTs. These NFTs grant holders access to exclusive staking pools, operating like a safe-deposit box key.</p>
<p>According to the recent data on dune.com, the protocol’s APE-Only Pool has reached an astonishing 175% APR. Apparently, staking APE has become a new trend. However, in order to join these staking pools, one must meet some requirements that may not be easy to meet. For instance, some pools require users to own Yuga Labs’ official NFTs to join, and these NFTs cannot be sold while it is committed in a BAYC or MAYC pool, otherwise users may lose all of their staked APEs.</p>
<p><strong>Earn APE on LBank Exchange</strong></p>
<p>To provide an alternative solution, LBank Exchange recently launched its own APE Staking in its “Earn” – “Flexible” section. Users will be able to earn 175% APR (floating adjustment) and enjoy daily rewards settlement by simply joining. And since it’s “Flexible”, there’s no locking required, users can withdraw their staked APE tokens whenever they want.</p>
<p>To join the APE Staking on LBank Exchange, just click <a href="https://www.lbank.com/locking-list.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Earn</a> and find the APE on the list, then click “Join Now”. The minimum interest-bearing amount requires that users’ account assets are not less than 6 APE tokens, and there’s no limit on the maximum interest-bearing amount. The settlement process includes interest calculation on T+1 and interest payment on T+2.</p>
<p>Follow the new trend in crypto and seize the opportunity to earn 175% APR through APE Staking on LBank Exchange right now!</p>
<p><strong>Click [</strong><a href="https://www.lbank.com/locking-list.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>Earn</strong></a><strong>] to Participate</strong></p>
<p>* Assets registered in &#8220;APE Staking&#8221; do not affect trading or withdrawal. However, after registration, the assets that have been traded or withdrawn will not enter the interest calculation of the day. The amount gap will be released at 2:00 pm the next day.</p>
<p>* The freezing assets due to orders and participation in activities does not affect the interest calculation of assets.</p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media: </strong></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Facebook</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong></p>
<p>LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
LBank Exchange<br />
<a href="mailto:marketing@lbank.info">marketing@lbank.info</a><br />
<a href="mailto:business@lbank.info">business@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/earn-175-apr-through-apecoin-ape-staking-on-lbank-exchange/">Earn 175% APR Through ApeCoin (APE) Staking on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/earn-175-apr-through-apecoin-ape-staking-on-lbank-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LBank Exchange Will List LynKey (LYNK) on December 19, 2022</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-lynkey-lynk-on-december-19-2022/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-lynkey-lynk-on-december-19-2022/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 12:29:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76037</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec. 16, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list LynKey (LYNK) on December 19, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the LYNK/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading at 8:00 (UTC) on December 19, 2022. Powered by blockchain and NFTs, LynKey (LYNK) creates an<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-lynkey-lynk-on-december-19-2022/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-lynkey-lynk-on-december-19-2022/">LBank Exchange Will List LynKey (LYNK) on December 19, 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec. 16, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list LynKey (LYNK) on December 19, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the LYNK/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading at 8:00 (UTC) on December 19, 2022.</p>
<p>Powered by blockchain and NFTs, <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/lynkey/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LynKey</a> (LYNK) creates an ecosystem for smart luxury resort, tourism and property investment. Its native token LYNK will be listed on LBank Exchange at 8:00 (UTC) on December 19, 2022, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision.</p>
<p><strong>Introducing </strong><strong>LynKey</strong></p>
<p>LynKey is a blockchain-enabled ecosystem that provides timeshare and NFT solutions for luxurious holiday experiences for the global audience via smart contracts. The tourists, business travelers, travel agencies, tourism operators, hospitality chains, and property clients from all over the world are increasingly accepting this revolutionary scheme. The premium vacation property &#8211; resorts, hotels, marinas, and many more are sliced to smaller fractions as digital assets.</p>
<p>These digital assets or NFTs could be staked or lent over the marketplace to earn profits. Users are able to combat the associated risks that arise due to jurisdiction matters. Moreover, the security provided by digital contracts is a benefit that is welcomed by property investors all over the world. Furthermore, blockchain with guaranteed transparency and decentralized system can democratize it entirely for the members of the LynKey community. Its overall system architecture links the enthusiasts with attractions in an increasingly reliable way.</p>
<p>Besides DeFi protocols, the LynKey project has been designed with a framework of products like digital wallet, NFT marketplace, and a crypto exchange. Not only that, the reward and loyalty credit system make the entire vacation experience consensually efficient and liquid.</p>
<p>LynKey’s smart “All in one” ecosystem is valued at $8B+, and identifies the key sites in Vietnam and Southeast Asia, and more prospective properties globally. It aims to create a seamless community that is exemplary in its existence for the 4IR smart city concept. LynKey intends to fraternise the global enthusiasts who pledge to evolve with the technology, and find real-time solutions to tech conventional operational challenges.</p>
<p><strong>About LYNK Token</strong></p>
<p>LYNK is the native token of LynKey ecosystem. The benefit of holding a LYNK token is that the token value is based on the utility value of resort tourism, purchase services within the ecosystem also affords the user the opportunity to take advantage of discounts that are made available to token holders, and the opportunity to exchange tokens for NFTs representing a real value experiences, timeshare, and license for resort properties.</p>
<p>Based on ERC-20, LYNK has a total supply of 1 billion (i.e. 1,000,000,000) tokens, of which 5% is provided for angle sale, 2% is provided for IDO, 8% is provided for private sale, 10% is provided for pre-sale, another 10% is provided for farming and staking, another 10% is allocated to advisors and partners, 12% is allocated to the team, 20% is provided for the ecosystem, and the rest 23% is reserved and allocated for liquidity.</p>
<p>The LYNK token will be listed on LBank Exchange at 8:00 (UTC) on December 19, 2022, investors who are interested in the LynKey investment can easily buy and sell LYNK token on LBank Exchange by then. The listing of LYNK token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p>
<p><strong>Learn More about</strong><strong> LYNK Token:</strong></p>
<p>Official Website: <a href="https://lynkey.com" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://lynkey.com</a><br />
Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/LynKeychat" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://t.me/LynKeychat</a><br />
Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/LynKey_" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/LynKey_</a><br />
Instagram: <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lynkey__/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.instagram.com/lynkey__/</a><br />
Facebook: <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LynKey-103648988780161" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://www.facebook.com/LynKey-103648988780161</a></p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.info/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.info</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media: </strong></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Facebook</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong><br />
LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
LBank Exchange<br />
<a href="mailto:marketing@lbank.info">marketing@lbank.info</a><br />
<a href="mailto:business@lbank.info">business@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-lynkey-lynk-on-december-19-2022/">LBank Exchange Will List LynKey (LYNK) on December 19, 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-lynkey-lynk-on-december-19-2022/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gearing Up for the Next Big Leap, The HyperNation Announced in the Year-end Global Virtual Gala</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gearing-up-for-the-next-big-leap-the-hypernation-announced-in-the-year-end-global-virtual-gala/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gearing-up-for-the-next-big-leap-the-hypernation-announced-in-the-year-end-global-virtual-gala/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 06:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76035</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This festive season has just gotten merrier with The HyperNation revealing more exciting development in the December grand event, ‘Whimsical Gaming Kingdom’. The year-end event, set to be the largest ever held by the first virtual nation, has received encouraging responses from the massive crowd who turned up at the virtual gala on 17 December<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gearing-up-for-the-next-big-leap-the-hypernation-announced-in-the-year-end-global-virtual-gala/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gearing-up-for-the-next-big-leap-the-hypernation-announced-in-the-year-end-global-virtual-gala/">Gearing Up for the Next Big Leap, The HyperNation Announced in the Year-end Global Virtual Gala</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This festive season has just gotten merrier with The HyperNation revealing more exciting development in the December grand event, ‘Whimsical Gaming Kingdom’. The year-end event, set to be the largest ever held by the first virtual nation, has received encouraging responses from the massive crowd who turned up at the virtual gala on 17 December 2022 08:00 EST. All attendants were amazed by the next big leap coming forth as the New Year 2023 approaches.</p>
<p>The year 2022 has been an exhilarating journey for The HyperNation with numerous milestones achieved, including the successful launch of Hitchhiker of Star, Citizen Welfare, HyperNation Dollar (HND) and HyperNation Token (HNT), Liquidity Mining and the HyperWallet Token (HWT), Booster Marketplace, to name a few. To serenade these achievements as all things planned in the roadmap have come to fruition, The HyperNation has officiated an anthem, entitled ‘Rise to the Glory’ during the gala.</p>
<p><strong>Bureau of Forefront, the First-line of The HyperNation’s Security Protection</strong></p>
<p>Yes, it was an eventful year, and The HyperNation has pulled through every obstacle. Hence, this grand gala marked a new adventure ahead. As citizens’ welfare in all aspects is the top priority, The HyperNation is set to establish the Bureau of Forefront, a team of security personnel that will keep all threats at bay. It is a rewarding initiative launched to safeguard all citizens in the fore-coming virtual realm.</p>
<p>With a goal set to preserve the nation’s reputation and integrity while protecting the constitutional rights of the citizens, the Bureau of Forefront has the highest duty and responsibility to defend The HyperNation, which prides itself as a new constitution that will soon open up in the Metaverse. Yes, you hear it right. That is a hint about the next phase of The HyperNation, which will be the long-awaited GameFi platform in the Metaverse.</p>
<p><strong>A Whimsical Event That Rewards Every Citizen</strong></p>
<p>Now, to end the year 2022 on a high note, it is with great honor and heartfelt pleasure to unveil some of the highly-anticipated new initiatives of The HyperNation. The next in the line would be the Limited-time Special Welfare Bonanza, in which The HyperNation is knocking off 10% of the usual selling price for fellow citizens to enjoy welfare and receive a Whimsical Edition Christmas H.O.S. NFT worth USD $1,000.</p>
<p>There will be two types of welfare available, including Whimsical Welfare, which is equivalent to Social Welfare, and Christmas Welfare, which is identical to Financial Welfare, minus the lower price tag during this festive season.</p>
<p>This Limited-time Special Welfare Bonanza comes in two phases: 17~20 December 2022 and 20~25 December 2022. During the first phase, special welfares are available at a 10% off promo price. In contrast, the second phase will allow citizens to subscribe to welfare with HyperBond (HB) pairing, which is a 20% selling price payable in HB, apart from the 10% less.</p>
<p>Subscribing any of the welfare consecutively in both phases will entitle the subscriber to a Whimsical Edition Christmas H.O.S. NFT. The HyperNation leaves no one behind. All subscribers of the Christmas Sensation bundles earlier on will also receive this Whimsical Edition Christmas H.O.S. NFT by making a subscription in Phase 1 of the Limited-edition Special Welfare Bonanza. These NFTs will be credited to the user’s account by 5 January 2023. As the total supply is limited, Whimsical Welfare and Christmas Welfare are available on a first-come-first-serve basis. So, hurry up and get yours now!</p>
<p><strong>Looking Forward to Welcoming a Glistening Year Ahead</strong></p>
<p>Ushering citizens into the year 2023 is the highly-anticipated GameFi virtual realm in the Metaverse. The Whimsical Gaming Kingdom global virtual conference also disclosed a spectacular sneak-peek preview of how the GameFi platform will look like.</p>
<p>Styled as the ‘HyperPlanet’, this will be the first virtual game accessible in the Metaverse brought to you by The HyperNation. Currently in the midst of a diligent beta test, the GameFi platform is slated to open up to the public in Q1 of 2023.</p>
<p>So, stay tuned as The HyperNation has so much to unfold for a fabulous year ahead!</p>
<p><strong>To find out more, follow us on:</strong></p>
<p>Twitter <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f449.png" alt="👉" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://twitter.com/HyperNation8" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/HyperNation8</a><br />
Discord <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f449.png" alt="👉" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://discord.gg/hypernation" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://discord.gg/hypernation</a><br />
YouTube <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f449.png" alt="👉" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/HyperNation8" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/c/HyperNation8</a><br />
Telegram <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f449.png" alt="👉" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.me/TheHyperNationCitizenship" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://t.me/TheHyperNationCitizenship</a><br />
Hyperxnews <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f449.png" alt="👉" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><a href="https://www.hyperxnews.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.hyperxnews.com/</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gearing-up-for-the-next-big-leap-the-hypernation-announced-in-the-year-end-global-virtual-gala/">Gearing Up for the Next Big Leap, The HyperNation Announced in the Year-end Global Virtual Gala</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gearing-up-for-the-next-big-leap-the-hypernation-announced-in-the-year-end-global-virtual-gala/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Half a Billion in Crypto Goes Missing from FTX Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/half-a-billion-dollars-goes-missing-from-ftx-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/half-a-billion-dollars-goes-missing-from-ftx-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 17:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75452</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nearly half a billion dollars has been taken out of the now failed FTX exchange, and nobody really seems to know where the money went. Money Is Missing from FTX Spokespeople for the crypto exchange claim that “unauthorized transactions” are what caused the money to disappear, and it is being said that the company might<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/half-a-billion-dollars-goes-missing-from-ftx-exchange/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/half-a-billion-dollars-goes-missing-from-ftx-exchange/">Half a Billion in Crypto Goes Missing from FTX Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nearly half a billion dollars has been <a href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/half-billion-dollars-mysteriously-disappears-111248374.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">taken out of the now</a> failed FTX exchange, and nobody really seems to know where the money went.</p>
<h2>Money Is Missing from FTX</h2>
<p>Spokespeople for the crypto exchange claim that “unauthorized transactions” are what caused the money to disappear, and it is being said that the company might have been hacked and the money stolen. The question is, “By who?”</p>
<p>At the time of writing, the company has moved whatever funds it still had into cold storage to ensure no further illicit transactions could occur. FTX is also working with law enforcement agents and regulators to figure out what might have happened.</p>
<p>Frances Coppola – an independent financial and economic commentator – explained in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>We’ll have to wait and see what the fallout is, but I think we are going to see more dominoes falling and an awful lot of people stand to lose their money and their savings, and that is just tragic, really.</p></blockquote>
<p>FTX is likely to go down in history as one of the biggest embarrassments to ever occur within the digital currency space. Founded in 2019, the company was relatively new still at the time of its collapse. By some miracle, the firm rose to prominence rather easily during the three years that it was fully alive, and many credited its founder Sam Bankman-Fried as something of a genius.</p>
<p>They wondered how he could make a company get so big in so little time, but clearly, things weren’t done well enough to ensure the firm could remain afloat.</p>
<p>Trouble for the firm began in mid-November when it was announced that FTX was experiencing <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">something of</a> a “liquidity crunch.” Apparently, the firm didn’t have enough money on hand due to mismanaged financial accounts and the FTT token, which is the native cryptocurrency of the exchange, saw massive dips in its price.</p>
<p>The company went to Binance for <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">help and for a while</a>, it was being reported that the larger firm was potentially going to buy the smaller one, but within 24 hours or so, Binance announced on social media that it was dropping out of the deal, saying that FTX’s problems were simply too big to handle.</p>
<p>From there, the enterprise became the latest big name in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">crypto to undergo bankruptcy</a> proceedings, and Sam Bankman-Fried has since resigned from the company, claiming in a recent message that he had “f*cked up.”</p>
<h2>Many Want Regulation</h2>
<p>The incident is causing <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/congress-wants-to-really-regulate-crypto-after-ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">many members of Congress</a> to (unsurprisingly) revoice their desires for hardcore crypto regulation.</p>
<p>Not long ago, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brad-sherman-billionaires-have-prevented-crypto-regulation-from-forming/" data-wpel-link="internal">Congressman Brad Sherman</a> – a known crypto skeptic – cited FTX as the reason as to why he was now looking to establish serious regulation as a means of preventing something like this from ever happening again.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/half-a-billion-dollars-goes-missing-from-ftx-exchange/">Half a Billion in Crypto Goes Missing from FTX Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/half-a-billion-dollars-goes-missing-from-ftx-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brad Sherman: Billionaires Have Prevented Crypto Regulation from Forming</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brad-sherman-billionaires-have-prevented-crypto-regulation-from-forming/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brad-sherman-billionaires-have-prevented-crypto-regulation-from-forming/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 15:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brad Sherman]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto-regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75450</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Brad Sherman – a cryptocurrency skeptic and congressman – says crypto billionaires are largely responsible for the fact that digital asset regulation has taken so long to arrive. Brad Sherman Wants Regulation NOW In a recent interview, Sherman said that the collapse of the leading exchange FTX in mid-November is reason enough to get the<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brad-sherman-billionaires-have-prevented-crypto-regulation-from-forming/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brad-sherman-billionaires-have-prevented-crypto-regulation-from-forming/">Brad Sherman: Billionaires Have Prevented Crypto Regulation from Forming</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Brad Sherman – a cryptocurrency skeptic and congressman – says <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-in/news/other/us-congressman-brad-sherman-holds-billionaire-crypto-bros-responsible-for-delayed-cryptocurrency-legislation/ar-AA145hay" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">crypto billionaires are</a> largely responsible for the fact that digital asset regulation has taken so long to arrive.</p>
<h2>Brad Sherman Wants Regulation NOW</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, Sherman said that the collapse of the leading exchange FTX in mid-November is reason enough to get the ball rolling on digital currency regulation. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>The collapse this week of one of the largest cryptocurrency firms in the world has been a dramatic demonstration of both the inherent risks of digital assets and the critical weaknesses in the industry that have grown up around them. For years, I have advocated for Congress and federal regulators to take an aggressive approach in confronting the many threats to our society posed by cryptocurrencies.</p></blockquote>
<p>To be fair, Congress has been pushing for hardcore crypto <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/regulation/" data-wpel-link="internal">regulation</a> for some time. It appears lawmakers either don’t trust the space, or they’re trying hard to impose on our freedoms even further. In any case, there are those that argue for crypto regulation, and those that argue against it, and there hasn’t been much headway in the space over the last few years.</p>
<p>Those that say crypto regulation is a negative feel so because it allegedly goes against everything the digital currency space stands for. They say the point of crypto is to give traders full financial autonomy and independence, and thus they shouldn’t be prone to the same third parties, prying eyes, and middlemen that one often sees in the traditional financial sector. Thus, the regulatory aspects of this world should be left out of the equation.</p>
<p>Others, however, feel that crypto regulation is necessary precisely because it has given way to a lot of malicious behavior from individuals who feel they can get away with everything they do because of a lagging legal presence. Many feel that what happened with FTX occurred simply because the space is unregulated, and that this may not have happened if the right laws were in place.</p>
<p>Sherman clearly falls into the latter category. He continued his interview with:</p>
<blockquote><p>[Regulators] are reacting to an industry that is evolving constantly, but overregulation could stifle that innovation… poorly thought-out regulation could create a two-fold issue. First, it could limit US consumers’ ability to participate in the cryptocurrency ecosystem, and it could also drive these businesses to less regulated jurisdictions. This creates more risk for customers as it puts them in a position of dealing with less regulated institutions to participate in the ecosystem.</p></blockquote>
<h2>He&#8217;s Working on the Issues at Hand</h2>
<p>Sherman announced he is now planning to work with his associates to establish full, long-term financial regulation for the crypto space.</p>
<p>He believes it will be executed with the aid and cooperation of executives working in the crypto arena.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brad-sherman-billionaires-have-prevented-crypto-regulation-from-forming/">Brad Sherman: Billionaires Have Prevented Crypto Regulation from Forming</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brad-sherman-billionaires-have-prevented-crypto-regulation-from-forming/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lauren Duncan Nearly Fell Victim to a Crypto Scam</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lauren-duncan-nearly-fell-victim-to-a-crypto-scam/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lauren-duncan-nearly-fell-victim-to-a-crypto-scam/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 13:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lauren Duncan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Matteo Thomas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[romance scam]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75448</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Romance scams are a growing trend in the digital currency arena, and one woman – Lauren Duncan – is sharing her story hoping that people can be saved from the same scenario that almost plagued her. Lauren Duncan Nearly Became Another Crypto Victim Duncan, like many people in America, was looking for love online one day and went<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lauren-duncan-nearly-fell-victim-to-a-crypto-scam/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lauren-duncan-nearly-fell-victim-to-a-crypto-scam/">Lauren Duncan Nearly Fell Victim to a Crypto Scam</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/romance-scam/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/romance-scam/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668540092927000&amp;usg=AOvVaw1CY4UsYAMbniDmndnTU6hE" data-wpel-link="internal">Romance scams</a> are a growing trend in the digital currency arena, and one woman – Lauren Duncan – is sharing her story <a href="https://www.clickorlando.com/news/investigators/2022/11/04/go-with-your-gut-feeling-florida-woman-warns-dating-app-users-of-cryptocurrency-scam/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.clickorlando.com/news/investigators/2022/11/04/go-with-your-gut-feeling-florida-woman-warns-dating-app-users-of-cryptocurrency-scam/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668540092927000&amp;usg=AOvVaw3BKEqawJeFvMB01-NJ4Axa" data-wpel-link="external">hoping that people</a> can be saved from the same scenario that almost plagued her.</p>
<h2>Lauren Duncan Nearly Became Another Crypto Victim</h2>
<p>Duncan, like many people in America, was looking for love online one day and went so far as to join Hinge, a dating app that’s designed to be deleted once a person has found their special someone. Duncan indeed found someone special, but for all the wrong reasons.</p>
<p>The 60-year-old former airline worker divorced her husband roughly ten years ago and admits to not having dated anyone since (it’s likely she’ll never date anyone else again after this event). She decided, at least temporarily, to jump back into the dating mix and created her profile on Hinge, thus prompting several messages to come in from potential suitors.</p>
<p>One – a man known as Matteo Thomas – hailed from Jacksonville, Florida, and seemed to be everything she wanted at first. She looked deeper into Thomas’ profile to see if he was real or just a figment of her overactive (and romance-themed) imagination. She said in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>He sent me a rose (emoji), which caught my attention. You can send a rose, and that’s like they are really interested in you.</p></blockquote>
<p>One of the texts Duncan received from him read as follows:</p>
<blockquote><p>I am lovely, caring, and romantic.</p></blockquote>
<p>He then forwarded her several pictures of himself. Later digging led to these same photos being discovered on several websites that track imposters, meaning Thomas was never who he claimed to be, though Duncan was late in realizing this. The pictures sent were later tracked to a medical technician that lives in Hamburg, Germany. He is nowhere near Jacksonville, and all the photos Duncan received were not of her actual suitor.</p>
<p>It didn’t take long before he began pressuring her to invest in a new crypto opportunity. Interestingly, Duncan says she began to sense something was wrong during this conversation, and she immediately went back to him and explained that she wasn’t interested in investing at that time. She went with her gut and when she was told to invest approximately $3K, she immediately alerted Hinge as to what she felt was going on.</p>
<h2>You Need to Have a Careful Eye Out</h2>
<p>Brian Watson – a veteran with the Orlando-based Secret Service – says these scams often result in people seeing returns on their investments, though they are never able to withdraw them as the platforms are controlled by malicious actors. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>You’re not going to get these returns anywhere. Some people are re-mortgaging their homes because they think the money is real and they can make a killing on it. The bad guys are taking it to the bank and cashing out.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lauren-duncan-nearly-fell-victim-to-a-crypto-scam/">Lauren Duncan Nearly Fell Victim to a Crypto Scam</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lauren-duncan-nearly-fell-victim-to-a-crypto-scam/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
