<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 12:16:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Crypto Mining Firm Greenidge Generation Hints at Potential Bankruptcy</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-mining-firm-greenidge-generation-hints-at-potential-bankruptcy/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-mining-firm-greenidge-generation-hints-at-potential-bankruptcy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 17:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bankruptcy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Greenidge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76159</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Another crypto mining firm is in trouble. This time, the alleged victim is Greenidge Generation (GREE), which has hinted that it could file bankruptcy in the coming weeks if its present deal with NYDIG doesn’t work out. Greenidge Generation Could Be the Next to Go The company is struggling to restructure its nearly $75 million<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-mining-firm-greenidge-generation-hints-at-potential-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-mining-firm-greenidge-generation-hints-at-potential-bankruptcy/">Crypto Mining Firm Greenidge Generation Hints at Potential Bankruptcy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Another crypto mining firm is in trouble. This time, the alleged victim is Greenidge Generation (GREE), <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/bitcoin-miner-greenidge-reaches-debt-124316270.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">which has hinted that</a> it could file bankruptcy in the coming weeks if its present deal with NYDIG doesn’t work out.</p>
<h2>Greenidge Generation Could Be the Next to Go</h2>
<p>The company is struggling to restructure its nearly $75 million debt. By doing this, the company could avoid a long bankruptcy line that initially began last summer with firms like Celsius, though Greenidge is not out of the woods yet. Even if the plan goes through, the company is still required to garner at least $20 million in new funding before the end of 2023. This could prove challenging if the crypto space does not heal by then.</p>
<p>To say 2022 was a bad year for crypto would be a terrible understatement. The world’s biggest digital currency – bitcoin – fell by more than 70 percent from the all-time high of $68,000 per unit it achieved in November of 2021. By the time the year ended, the currency was trading in the high $16K range.</p>
<p>Several other leading tokens followed in the asset’s footsteps. The crypto space ultimately lost more than $2 trillion of its overall value and there were several companies that went under or were forced to file bankruptcy due to the weak sentiment surrounding the space.</p>
<p>Celsius is arguably the firm that started the trend. The company <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/another-mega-bitcoin-crash-is-in-the-books/" data-wpel-link="internal">halted all withdrawals</a> in the summer of 2022 and caused everyone to raise eyebrows when they suddenly couldn’t access their funds. From there, the company engaged in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/celsius-network-is-next-crypto-company-to-file-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">bankruptcy proceedings</a> to protect itself against angry creditors and customers, all the while dealing with a very unstable market.</p>
<p>Other enterprises followed suit, including <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-hedge-fund-three-arrows-capital-is-now-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">Three Arrows Capital</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-lender-voyager-digital-files-chapter-11-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">Voyager Digital</a>, and then <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX</a>, which appears to have engaged in various criminal acts including using traders’ assets to fund personal ventures such as buying luxury condominiums in the Bahamas for Sam Bankman-Fried – the head executive of the exchange – and other employees.</p>
<p>The company is now at the center of a huge scandal and Sam Bankman-Fried <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-to-await-trial-at-his-parents-house/" data-wpel-link="internal">is out on bail while</a> he awaits trial in California after spending time in a Bahamian jail cell.</p>
<h2>You Can&#8217;t Just Make Money Mining</h2>
<p>To try and survive for the next 12 months, Greenidge will no longer be hosting its own digital currency mining machines. Instead, it will play host to the machines of NYDIG. The company must also run completely on natural gas as a means of reducing its costs, and it must also sell energy produced in a natural gas plant and not just rely on crypto mining to make ends meet.</p>
<p>This is a huge change for a company that just last October and November, was driving through more than $8 million each month. Of that money, $5.5 million went to NYDIG payments.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-mining-firm-greenidge-generation-hints-at-potential-bankruptcy/">Crypto Mining Firm Greenidge Generation Hints at Potential Bankruptcy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-mining-firm-greenidge-generation-hints-at-potential-bankruptcy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sam Bankman-Fried to Await Trial at His Parents&#8217; House</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-to-await-trial-at-his-parents-house/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-to-await-trial-at-his-parents-house/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 15:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bahamas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76157</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sam Bankman-Fried – the disgraced head executive of the now defunct crypto exchange FTX – is out of prison on a $250 million bond. While awaiting trial, he will live at his parents’ house in California. Sam Bankman-Fried Is Temporarily Out of Jail Bankman-Fried made his way back to the United States from a Bahamian<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-to-await-trial-at-his-parents-house/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-to-await-trial-at-his-parents-house/">Sam Bankman-Fried to Await Trial at His Parents&#8217; House</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sam Bankman-Fried – the disgraced head executive of the now defunct crypto exchange FTX – is out of <a href="https://www.thestreet.com/investing/cryptocurrency/sam-bankman-fried-gets-out-250-million-bail" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">prison on a $250 million</a> bond. While awaiting trial, he will live at his parents’ house in California.</p>
<h2>Sam Bankman-Fried Is Temporarily Out of Jail</h2>
<p>Bankman-Fried made his way back to the United States from a Bahamian jail in late December of last year. He also made a court appearance on January 3. The bond in question is different from bail. What it means is that if Bankman-Fried attempts to flee the country while awaiting trial or if he engages in any activity that authorities find suspicious, those closest to him can expect to be charged $250 million.</p>
<p>Right now, his parents have offered their home and other personal items as collateral should their son try to tuck tail and run from the U.S. court system. Other friends and family members also have various items on the line if Bankman-Fried tries to flee.</p>
<p>The FTX case is already significantly underway. Several former executives of the now collapsed trading platform have pled guilty to assorted crimes including former FTX co-founder and chief technology officer Zixiao Wang (age 29) and Caroline Ellison, the 280-year-old former CEO of Alameda Research, which was also founded by Bankman-Fried.</p>
<p>U.S. attorney Damian Williams, who is overseeing the case, explained in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>As I said last week, this investigation is very much ongoing. Let me reiterate a call I made last week. If you participated in misconduct at FTX or Alameda, now is the time to get ahead of it. We are moving quickly, and our patience is not eternal.</p></blockquote>
<p>The FTX debacle will likely go down in crypto history as one of the most embarrassing events to occur within the space’s borders. The collapse happened back in mid-November. Bankman-Fried complained of a “<a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">liquidity crunch</a>” on social media and said he was now turning to his biggest rival, Binance, to buy his company out and save it from financial disaster.</p>
<h2>Things Fell Very Quickly</h2>
<p>While things were looking good for the company in this department for a while, Binance later went back on its <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">deal to buy out the company</a>, claiming the problems FTX was facing were simply too big for it to handle. From there, the company had no choice <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">but to engage in bankruptcy</a> proceedings, and Bankman-Fried resigned from his post.</p>
<p>Things didn’t end there, however. It turned out that Bankman-Fried had allegedly used traders’ funds stored on the exchange to purchase luxury condominiums for himself and other members of the FTX team in the Bahamas. The situation has been labeled one of the biggest crypto Ponzi schemes to ever occur, and Bankman-Fried was later arrested and spent time behind bars for his role in the firm’s crash.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-to-await-trial-at-his-parents-house/">Sam Bankman-Fried to Await Trial at His Parents&#8217; House</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-to-await-trial-at-his-parents-house/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Australian Authorities Say Crypto Is Too Often Used for Money Laundering</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/australian-authorities-say-crypto-is-too-often-used-for-money-laundering/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/australian-authorities-say-crypto-is-too-often-used-for-money-laundering/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 13:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Australian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[John Moss]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Tink]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76154</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Australian law enforcement agents are claiming that crypto has become the number one go-to tool for those looking to commit money laundering or financial fraud. Australian Authorities Issue Crypto Warning Senior executives of the Australian Transaction Reports and Analysis Center (AUSTRAC) claim crypto has become part of the “money laundering tool kit,” and that using<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/australian-authorities-say-crypto-is-too-often-used-for-money-laundering/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/australian-authorities-say-crypto-is-too-often-used-for-money-laundering/">Australian Authorities Say Crypto Is Too Often Used for Money Laundering</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Australian law enforcement agents are claiming that <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/australia-news/2022/dec/23/cryptocurrency-becomes-mainstream-option-for-money-laundering-and-funding-of-terrorism-austrac-says" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">crypto has become the number</a> one go-to tool for those looking to commit money laundering or financial fraud.</p>
<h2>Australian Authorities Issue Crypto Warning</h2>
<p>Senior executives of the Australian Transaction Reports and Analysis Center (AUSTRAC) claim <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">crypto</a> has become part of the “money laundering tool kit,” and that using digital currency technology to sneak and hide funds from prying eyes has become standard behavior in the world of criminality. John Moss – head of the Australian agency – claimed in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>We are now seeing more traditional money laundering being displaced into cryptocurrency, particularly to send money offshore.</p></blockquote>
<p>Not long ago, Chainalysis – a blockchain analysis firm – said that approximately $2.2 million in crypto has been sent over this year alone to Russian paramilitary groups, and that the money is being used to purchase weapons and other items to fund and boost Russia’s side of the war. Moss explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>This shows how easy it is to use crypto as a fundraising source, and when you mix it with social media, you get a big reach. You’ve got a technology that’s easy to use, and if you’re flexible in the type of cryptos you take, you can do quite well out of it.</p></blockquote>
<p>Michael Tink – the national manager of intelligence operations at AUSTRAC – also threw his two cents into the mix, commenting:</p>
<blockquote><p>We have seen evidence of Australians sending money to offshore cryptocurrency accounts linked to al-Qaida [and] ISIL, and this is largely organizational support for travel, training, the salaries of fighters, and uniforms. It doesn’t take a lot of money to have an impact on a terrorist organization in a conflict zone, and small amounts of money can buy weapons and result in attacks, so it’s still a significant risk.</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition, it’s being said that many of these criminals and potential warmongers are using digital currency ATMs to get their hands on funds. Moss is concerned that these machines could eventually give way to a crime web that spreads across the globe. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>These machines are not seen in places like the UK. When you look at the reporting, you see lots of fraud victims. Very vulnerable people put large amounts of cash into these ATMs, which is essentially immediately gone offshore.</p></blockquote>
<h2>ATMs Are Often Looked To</h2>
<p>Tink also said that ATMs are often the first method of converting crypto into cash so that illicit purchases and deals can be made. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>One of the key vulnerabilities for a crime group laundering money is the placement stage of the money-laundering cycle, so that’s trying to get cash into cryptocurrency. [These ATMs] are a good way to do that. There is a perception that if you are putting money through a hole in the wall, or a box in a shopping center, that it will be more anonymous.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/australian-authorities-say-crypto-is-too-often-used-for-money-laundering/">Australian Authorities Say Crypto Is Too Often Used for Money Laundering</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/australian-authorities-say-crypto-is-too-often-used-for-money-laundering/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Warren Buffett: Forget Gold and BTC, Invest in Stocks!</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/warren-buffett-forget-gold-and-btc-invest-in-stocks/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/warren-buffett-forget-gold-and-btc-invest-in-stocks/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 17:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warren Buffett]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76132</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Warren Buffett is telling all his followers that buying bitcoin or gold during times of war is a terrible mistake. He is telling them all to avoid these assets and to avoid hoarding cash and to put all their money into stocks, as these are the only safe assets that can assuredly build wealth in<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/warren-buffett-forget-gold-and-btc-invest-in-stocks/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/warren-buffett-forget-gold-and-btc-invest-in-stocks/">Warren Buffett: Forget Gold and BTC, Invest in Stocks!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Warren Buffett is telling all his followers that <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/warren-buffett-cautioned-against-stockpiling-113345846.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">buying bitcoin or gold during</a> times of war is a terrible mistake. He is telling them all to avoid these assets and to avoid hoarding cash and to put all their money into stocks, as these are the only safe assets that can assuredly build wealth in the long-term.</p>
<h2>Warren Buffett: Stocks Are the Only Answer</h2>
<p>Buffett has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/warren-buffett-explains-his-hate-for-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">never been a big bitcoin</a> fan. He has often referred to it as “rat poison squared” and applied other derogatory terms to the world’s number one digital currency by market cap, but ever since Russia reportedly invaded Ukraine in March of last year, the idea is that bitcoin cannot be trusted along with other assets, and stocks are the only real answer towards staying financially put.</p>
<p>He said that when Russia first invaded Ukraine, he wasn’t prompted to sell his stocks like other people even though the market was taking several drastic hits. He stated in an interview during that time:</p>
<blockquote><p>If stocks are cheaper, I&#8217;ll be more likely to be buying them.</p></blockquote>
<p>He further commented that even if World War III were to potentially break out, he still wouldn’t sell his stocks and he would stay completely still unless prices dropped further. If that were the case, he would simply buy up more units. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Well, if you tell me all of that is going to happen, I will still be buying the stock. You’re going to invest your money in something over time. The one thing you could be quite sure of is if we went into some very major war, the value of money would go down. I mean, that&#8217;s happened in virtually every war that I&#8217;m aware of, so the last thing you&#8217;d want to do is hold money during a war.</p></blockquote>
<p>He further mentioned that stocks in American businesses ultimately went up drastically during World War II and they’ve done nothing but become stronger and bigger with time. Buffett said:</p>
<blockquote><p>American businesses are going to be worth more money. Dollars are going to be worth less, so that money won&#8217;t buy you quite as much, but you&#8217;re going to be a lot better off owning productive assets  over the next 50 years than you will be owning pieces of paper, or I might throw in bitcoins.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Staying On an 80-Year Course</h2>
<p>Buffett was 11 years old in 1942 when he bought his first stock shares, and he hasn’t looked back since. At an annual shareholder meeting in 2018, he stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>All you had to do was figure that America was going to do well over time [and] that we would overcome the current difficulties. You didn&#8217;t have to pick out winning stocks. You didn&#8217;t have to pick out a winning time or anything of the sort.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/warren-buffett-forget-gold-and-btc-invest-in-stocks/">Warren Buffett: Forget Gold and BTC, Invest in Stocks!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/warren-buffett-forget-gold-and-btc-invest-in-stocks/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>India&#8217;s Shaktikanta Das: Crypto Should Be &#8220;Prohibited&#8221;</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/indias-shaktikanta-das-crypto-should-be-prohibited/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/indias-shaktikanta-das-crypto-should-be-prohibited/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 15:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Millennials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shaktikanta Das]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76130</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shaktikanta Das – the governor of India’s central bank – says that the 2008 financial crisis could happen all over again if people don’t start cracking down on the world’s leading digital currencies. He says another financial disaster is right around the corner, and a lot of it will likely be attributed to bitcoin and<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/indias-shaktikanta-das-crypto-should-be-prohibited/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/indias-shaktikanta-das-crypto-should-be-prohibited/">India&#8217;s Shaktikanta Das: Crypto Should Be &#8220;Prohibited&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shaktikanta Das – the governor of India’s central bank – says <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/billybambrough/2022/12/21/mark-my-words-surprise-crisis-prediction-sends-shockwaves-through-crypto-markets-as-the-price-of-bitcoin-and-ethereum-swing-wildly/?sh=547117e45e57" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">that the 2008 financial crisis</a> could happen all over again if people don’t start cracking down on the world’s leading digital currencies. He says another financial disaster is right around the corner, and a lot of it will likely be attributed to bitcoin and its altcoin cousins.</p>
<h2>Shaktikanta Das Is Not a Crypto Fan</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, Das said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Our view is that it should be prohibited because if you try to regulate it and allow it to grow, please mark my words the next financial crisis will come from private cryptocurrencies.</p></blockquote>
<p>The Great Recession – as the financial crisis of roughly 15 years ago is called – is responsible for the birth of bitcoin and the digital market space. It was during this time that the whitepaper for bitcoin was unveiled to the public, and just a few months later, bitcoin was mined for the first time.</p>
<p>It has also widely been said that young people – such as millennials and Generation Z – are big fans of bitcoin and related cryptocurrencies because they <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/millenials-are-investing-more-in-grayscale/" data-wpel-link="internal">grew up during the time</a> of the recession. They saw firsthand what centralized money and financial institutions did to their parents and adult friends. They saw how many banks and businesses went under and they saw how quick the government was to bailout the firms that directly benefited its members while letting others die out.</p>
<p>As a result, many of these young people have come to distrust things like stocks and standard financial investing tools, and they’ve since turned to bitcoin and cryptocurrencies to establish their wealth and bring themselves up the monetary ladder. What a horrible stroke of irony it would be if another financial recession is caused by the asset its predecessor birthed.</p>
<p>Das says bitcoin and many other forms of crypto don’t have any real, actual value to them. By contrast, he believes that all they do is expose investors to unnecessary risks and give people the impression that they own something that could be taken from them at any moment. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>[Bitcoin, Ethereum and other cryptocurrencies] have no underlying value. They have huge inherent risks for our macroeconomic and financial stability. I [have] yet to hear any credible argument about what public good or what public purpose [they] serve.</p></blockquote>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>By contrast, Das is confident that CBDCs – central bank digital currencies – could pave the way for a new future in the world of finance, and he thinks more banks will come to embrace the technology behind digital assets for their own well-being. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>You will see in days to come more and more central banks will embrace digital currencies, and India has been in the forefront of the digital revolution in the current century.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/indias-shaktikanta-das-crypto-should-be-prohibited/">India&#8217;s Shaktikanta Das: Crypto Should Be &#8220;Prohibited&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/indias-shaktikanta-das-crypto-should-be-prohibited/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Core Scientific Is Next Crypto Firm to Go Bankrupt</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/core-scientific-is-next-crypto-firm-to-go-bankrupt/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/core-scientific-is-next-crypto-firm-to-go-bankrupt/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 13:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celsius Network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Core Scientific]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76112</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Core Scientific – one of the largest digital currency mining firms in the world – has announced it’s filing for chapter 11 bankruptcy protection. The proceedings took place in a federal bankruptcy court in southern Texas. Core Scientific Is Filing Bankruptcy Core Scientific has been hinting at potential bankruptcy for some time. It stated in<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/core-scientific-is-next-crypto-firm-to-go-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/core-scientific-is-next-crypto-firm-to-go-bankrupt/">Core Scientific Is Next Crypto Firm to Go Bankrupt</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Core Scientific – one of the largest digital currency mining firms in the world – has announced it’s filing <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-miner-core-scientific-files-for-bankruptcy/ar-AA15wSpC" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">for chapter 11 bankruptcy</a> protection. The proceedings took place in a federal bankruptcy court in southern Texas.</p>
<h2>Core Scientific Is Filing Bankruptcy</h2>
<p>Core Scientific has been hinting <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-firm-core-scientific-says-its-considering-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">at potential bankruptcy</a> for some time. It stated in its official court documents that the declining price of bitcoin, as well as rising electricity prices to run its mining centers have become too difficult and heavy to contend with. At the time of writing, shares in the publicly traded company are down roughly 25 percent.</p>
<p>2023 was supposed to be the year in which bitcoin and crypto got the time they needed to heal and recover from the ravaging trends of 2022. During the latter year, bitcoin – the world’s largest and most popular digital currency – dropped more than 70 percent in value from its most recent all-time high of $68,000 per unit. This number was achieved in November of 2021, though about one year later, the currency had fallen into the mid-$16,000 range, and 2022 has been nothing but an embarrassment of sorts for all digital assets.</p>
<p>In addition, Core Scientific is neither the first, nor the only crypto-centered firm to file bankruptcy over the last six months. Others have come along in the form of the Celsius Network, for example, which last summer, caused many eyebrows to raise when the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/another-mega-bitcoin-crash-is-in-the-books/" data-wpel-link="internal">company announced it</a> was going to be halting all withdrawals and preventing customers from gaining access to their money.</p>
<p>From there, the problem got even worse when it was said that the firm <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/celsius-network-is-next-crypto-company-to-file-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">would be entering bankruptcy</a> proceedings to prevent vulnerability to angry customers and/or lenders that wanted to be paid back. Other firms – from <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-hedge-fund-three-arrows-capital-is-now-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">Three Arrows Capital</a> to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-lender-voyager-digital-files-chapter-11-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">Voyager Digital</a> – later followed suit.</p>
<p>Matthew Sigel – head of digital assets research at Van Eck – commented in a recent interview that he thinks things will get a lot worse with bitcoin before they get better. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We think it&#8217;s possible, and possibly likely that bitcoin will test the $10,000 to $12,000 level amidst a wave of [bitcoin] miner bankruptcies.</p></blockquote>
<h2>FTX Is Still the Biggest Bankruptcy Story</h2>
<p>The biggest bankruptcy story of 2022 arguably came about with FTX, a once respected digital currency exchange that has since fallen into oblivion and may go down in history as a nothing but a criminal haven. First coming to fruition in 2019, the exchange was run by Sam Bankman-Fried and rose through the ranks over the next three years to become one of the biggest digital currency trading platforms in the world.</p>
<p>However, after experiencing <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">a liquidity crunch</a> in November of last year, the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">company sought</a> aid from Binance and a possible bailout, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">though this never happened</a>. From there, the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">company filed bankruptcy</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftxs-disgraced-founder-has-been-arrested/" data-wpel-link="internal">SBF was arrested</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/core-scientific-is-next-crypto-firm-to-go-bankrupt/">Core Scientific Is Next Crypto Firm to Go Bankrupt</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/core-scientific-is-next-crypto-firm-to-go-bankrupt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The History of the Change in the Price of the CRV Token</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-history-of-the-change-in-the-price-of-the-crv-token/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-history-of-the-change-in-the-price-of-the-crv-token/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 12:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sponsored]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76504</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Curve platform was founded in 2020 as an automated market making exchange for traders with the focus on stablecoins &#8211; crypto backed by fiat currencies like US dollar. This approach helps Curve traders generate income from lending protocols avoiding high-volatile assets. The platform is aimed at providing stability while avoiding speculation and highly volatile<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-history-of-the-change-in-the-price-of-the-crv-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-history-of-the-change-in-the-price-of-the-crv-token/">The History of the Change in the Price of the CRV Token</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Curve platform was founded in 2020 as an automated market making exchange for traders with the focus on stablecoins &#8211; crypto backed by fiat currencies like US dollar. This approach helps Curve traders generate income from lending protocols avoiding high-volatile assets. The platform is aimed at providing stability while avoiding speculation and highly volatile coins.</p>
<p>The main advantages of Curve:</p>
<ul>
<li>low commissions;</li>
<li>loe slippage;</li>
<li>smart contracts.</li>
</ul>
<p>Liquidity providers receive rewards in the form of <a href="https://blog.whitebit.com/en/crv/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">CRV crypto</a>. You can buy this token on any crypto exchange or earn it via yield farming. For that purpose, you need to put some tokens into the liquidity pool and receive more tokens in return as a reward. It encourages liquidity providers to add more liquidity to pools and provides them ownership of a DeFi protocol.</p>
<p>CRV coin holders can offer changes in the Curve ecosystem, which may connect commissions, allocation of fees, new pools, yield farming, etc.</p>
<p>The longer you lock CRV, the more weight your vote has.</p>
<h4><strong>History of CRV Price</strong></h4>
<p>The token reached $11,54 in August 2022. That was an all-time high. In January 2022, the price reached the mark of $6,5. As of mid-December 2022, the rate is $0.52. So we can see a considerable drop in CRV price. However, 2022 was the year of bearish sentiment in the market. Experts predict the CRV token can reach $2.82 in 2023. So it is worth buying it in the long term.</p>
<p>You can buy CRV crypto on the WhiteBIT exchange using a convenient crypto converter. There is an opportunity to buy coins with fiat money by adding your bank card to the account.</p>
<p>WhiteBIT offers reliable storage for crypto assets and provides a wide range of trading tools such as futures, leverage, spot, p2p, etc.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-history-of-the-change-in-the-price-of-the-crv-token/">The History of the Change in the Price of the CRV Token</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-history-of-the-change-in-the-price-of-the-crv-token/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Trade Forex Beginners in Thai</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-to-trade-forex-beginners-in-thai/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-to-trade-forex-beginners-in-thai/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 12:06:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sponsored]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76500</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>All Forex trading for beginners in Thai comes down to finding answers to questions such as: “When will the price start to rise or fall?” “When is it more profitable to buy or sell a currency?” and the like. This part of the work is considered the most difficult. Typically, one or more methods are<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-to-trade-forex-beginners-in-thai/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-to-trade-forex-beginners-in-thai/">How to Trade Forex Beginners in Thai</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>All Forex trading for beginners in Thai comes down to finding answers to questions such as: “When will the price start to rise or fall?” “When is it more profitable to buy or sell a currency?” and the like. This part of the work is considered the most difficult. Typically, one or more methods are used to find solutions. All of them are combined into a whole science — this is &#8220;Technical Analysis.&#8221;</p>
<p>The developed methods are reduced to the analysis of the quotes chart by calculating the values of individual indicators. To get the most accurate forecast results, technical analysis is combined with Fundamental analysis (macroeconomic indicators). If a trader correctly uses these tools, they can easily make profitable transactions with <a href="https://fbs.co.th/trading/specs/audjpy" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">AUDJPY</a>, NZDJPY, and other currency pairs.</p>
<h4><strong>Forex: How to start making money in Thai</strong></h4>
<p>How to start earning on Forex if you have not dealt with currency before? Very simple. The main thing is to understand the essence of what is happening so that new knowledge is superimposed on the right basis. Imagine that you have a box of chocolates. Now, it costs $10. There are two ways to make money on this product.</p>
<ul>
<li>Option one is to wait until the price rises to 12 and sell the chocolate. The difference between the buy and sell price ($2) is the trader&#8217;s profit.</li>
<li>The second option is to sell a box of chocolates for $10. In this case, you must be sure that the goods will fall in price, say, to 8. If the forecast comes true, you will be able to buy back the box at a lower price. Profit is also formed due to the difference in the price of sale and purchase.</li>
</ul>
<h4><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-76501 aligncenter" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Picture277-600x394.png" alt="" width="600" height="394" /></h4>
<h4><strong>The Psychology of Forex Trading in Thai</strong></h4>
<p>The psychology of Forex trading helps the trader fight the main enemies. All of them live in our heads. Greed is danger #1. Here, everything is good in moderation. If a trader is greedy too little, they miss a lot of opportunities to earn. Profitable transactions remain, but their number and volumes are gradually decreasing.</p>
<p>When greed takes over, the number of unreasonably risky transactions increases dramatically. The result of uncontrolled behavior is a partial drain of the deposit or complete ruin. The best way to conquer greed and other emotions is to learn to control and suppress them. Do not rush to earn a million or open more positions. It is better to make one deal a day but understand the true reasons for what is happening.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-to-trade-forex-beginners-in-thai/">How to Trade Forex Beginners in Thai</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-to-trade-forex-beginners-in-thai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bytekode Onboarding Alpha Users to Make the Blockchain Easy as ABC</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bytekode-onboarding-alpha-users-to-make-the-blockchain-easy-as-abc/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bytekode-onboarding-alpha-users-to-make-the-blockchain-easy-as-abc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 10:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76497</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bytekode is on a mission to make the blockchain understandable to everyone. Web3 is poised to onboard trillions of dollars of value and be the next explosive growth sector in our modern information age. However, it has a core problem &#8211; it’s hard to understand. Experts are still figuring out the details, and retail users<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bytekode-onboarding-alpha-users-to-make-the-blockchain-easy-as-abc/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bytekode-onboarding-alpha-users-to-make-the-blockchain-easy-as-abc/">Bytekode Onboarding Alpha Users to Make the Blockchain Easy as ABC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bytekode is on a mission to make the blockchain understandable to everyone. Web3 is poised to onboard trillions of dollars of value and be the next explosive growth sector in our modern information age. However, it has a core problem &#8211; it’s hard to understand. Experts are still figuring out the details, and retail users often just accept what they’re told and hope for the best. That’s not what blockchain is about. Web3 is about transparency, communication, security, and everyone being in-the-know through recordable, public, distributed ledgers.</p>
<h4>What is Bytekode?</h4>
<p>Bytekode turns smart contract code into easy to read bitesize chunks, and tells everyone exactly what’s written there. It makes those ledgers easy to understand. It opens up the world of web3 to the everyman and everywoman. The translation is hard-coded, and is not editable by dapp developers, smart contract coders, validators, or Bytekode itself. It provides a secure, direct translation of what the blockchain is doing.</p>
<p>Now Bytekode is onboarding its first wave of dapp developers who want to take advantage of this to implant an immediate UI representation of what their smart contracts are doing for their users, with no need for graphical updates or any other changes, interference or control of their existing codebase. Dapp developers don’t have to worry about explaining what their smart contract does, their users can simply see it for themselves.</p>
<h4>Boosting Adoption Through Understanding</h4>
<p>It promises to contribute to a huge boost in the adoption of more fledgling apps who have great fundamentals but haven’t yet figured out how to present their offering to users. Bytekode does the basics for them. It also allows education for the end-user, as they can, over time, absorb what different smart contracts do as they tinker with new web3 applications. It holds the users hands and gives them a basic underpinning to fall back on. Yes, a developer can build their own GUI and explain what the contracts do in their own terms, but a user will always have Bytekode to fall back on.</p>
<p>Bytekode also helps with security too. Dapp developers can’t use Bytekode to misrepresent what’s in their smart contracts. Bytekode reads the smart contract directly and outputs the results in plaintext script that anyone can read. Bytekode will act as assurance that what will happen is exactly what the smart contract is already programmed to do.</p>
<h4>The Benefits for Retail and Mass Adoption</h4>
<p>The benefits for end users are legion. Long transaction hashes are not the way forward to drive wide scale adoption. End users want simple, readable messages for everything they do. They do not want to use clunky block explorers and panic over every digit in a transaction id or hash when they use the blockchain.</p>
<p>What is done should be output clearly and sent to the user in a simple fashion where they can make judgments for themselves. We don’t ask the bank to just send us the swift/iban code of every transaction we make and the account numbers and let us figure it out for ourselves.</p>
<p>This is, of course, obvious. Every app in the whole world does this in some way or another, converting complex behind the scenes system operations into easy-to-read notifications that’s easy for us to read. With blockchain, however, work still needs to be done. This is because you can’t just trust a centralised company or service to write blockchain descriptions for you.</p>
<p>You need what is output in plaintext to the end user to be a result of the immutable, open-source code that everyone checks and secures so that nothing can be in doubt. That is the dream of the blockchain, and that is the dream of Bytekode &#8211; to make it so everyone can understand what is happening on-chain, and create a transparent, fertile environment of open-source innovation in the spirit of shared achievement and honest community.</p>
<p>To join that dream, you can join the Bytekode alpha over at their website. If you’re a dapp developer or just passionate about Bytekode’s mission and watch to help playtest the and read through the plaintext they’ve created for the blockchain and help refine it, <a href="https://www.bytekode.xyz/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">you can sign up for the Alpha now.</a></p>
<p>Bytekode has huge future expansion plans that centre around the core idea of reading the blockchain for everyone. Crypto is fantastic because it is &#8211; despite what naysayers will have you believe &#8211; completely transparent. The issue is it takes an expert eye to sort through reams of data on block explorers, compile and track it usefully, then get any findings from it. It’s because block explorers are far too arcane for the general public, and even people who know what they’re doing find it laborious</p>
<h4>Building a Block Explorer for Novices</h4>
<p>Bytekode will build a block explorer network through its partner dapps that allows for simple, naturalistic web2-esque exploration of different blockchains, as well as launching their own block explorer that utilises the technology they are building.</p>
<p>The goal would be to give every member of the general public the same ability and skill to go through blockchain transactions and ‘follow the money’ as if they were an expert, and increase education and learning about crypto as a whole. This will drive adoption in crypto as Bytekode breaks down the key problem: it’s currently too hard to understand.</p>
<h4>Join the ByteKode Alpha</h4>
<p>Bytekode has already built <a href="https://twitter.com/shlokm289/status/1575827598348718082" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">plenty of partnerships</a> and is now ready to get the first users in. <a href="https://www.bytekode.xyz/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">The Bytekode website</a> has all the details about the Alpha. You’ve read this far in (mostly) plain English, now are you ready to read the blockchain with Bytekode?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bytekode-onboarding-alpha-users-to-make-the-blockchain-easy-as-abc/">Bytekode Onboarding Alpha Users to Make the Blockchain Easy as ABC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bytekode-onboarding-alpha-users-to-make-the-blockchain-easy-as-abc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
