<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 03:19:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/cropped-fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Could Restart Rally Above This Resistance</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-restart-rally-above-this-resistance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 03:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79242</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price is attempting a fresh increase from the $29,800 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above $30,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,800 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-restart-rally-above-this-resistance/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Could Restart Rally Above This Resistance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin price is attempting a fresh increase from the $29,800 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $30,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,800 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could start a fresh increase if it clears the $31,500 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin price is rising from $29,800 against the US Dollar. BTC might eye another increase if the bulls remain active above the $30,000 zone.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price remained in a range after it failed to clear the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-more-upsides-above-31250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$31,500 resistance</a>. BTC was rejected a couple of times but the bulls were active above near the $30,000 zone.</p>
<p>The recent swing low was formed near $29,715 before the price moved higher. The bulls were able to push the price above the $30,200 and $30,250 levels. There was a move above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $31,525 swing high to the $29,715 low.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is now trading above $30,500 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-bulls-in-control-above-29500/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. Immediate resistance on the upside is near the $30,750 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,800 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>The trend line is just below the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $31,525 swing high to the $29,715 low. The next major resistance might be near the $31,500 zone.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $31,450 and $31,500 resistance levels might send the price toward $32,500. Any more gains might push the price toward the $34,000 zone. If there is no upside break, the price might start a fresh decline below the $30,450 level.</p>
<p>The first major support is near $30,000. The next key support is near the $29,750 level, below which the price might accelerate lower. In the stated case, the price could decline toward the $28,200 level.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79244" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79244" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-2.png"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-79244" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-2.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-2.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-2-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-2-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-2-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-2-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-2-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-2-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79244" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XBTUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, Bitcoin’s price is trading above $30,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start a fresh increase if it clears the $31,500 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD is now losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $30,000 and $29,750.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $30,800, $31,500, and $32,500.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-restart-rally-above-this-resistance/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Could Restart Rally Above This Resistance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vietnam&#8217;s Crypto Boom: Attracting Top Blockchain Projects</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vietnams-crypto-boom-attracting-top-blockchain-projects/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Gautham]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 17:35:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry and Adoption]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79210</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Vietnam&#8217;s economy is undergoing a digital revolution, with a projected compound annual growth rate of 8.9% in the digital economy from 2022 to 2026. This growth rate surpasses that of 51 other countries worldwide, including economic powerhouses like China, the US, the UAE, and all European countries, according to the FT-Omdia Digital Economy Index. Experts [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vietnams-crypto-boom-attracting-top-blockchain-projects/">Vietnam&#8217;s Crypto Boom: Attracting Top Blockchain Projects</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Vietnam&#8217;s economy is undergoing a digital revolution, with a projected compound annual growth rate of 8.9% in the digital economy from 2022 to 2026. This growth rate surpasses that of 51 other countries worldwide, including economic powerhouses like China, the US, the UAE, and all European countries, according to the FT-Omdia Digital Economy Index. Experts attribute this projected success to several factors, including Vietnam&#8217;s youthful population, government policies fostering an enabling environment for innovation, and a substantial influx of foreign investment and investors that are driving the country&#8217;s digital landscape.</p>
<p>The flourishing ecosystem of tech start-ups with a focus on innovation and entrepreneurship has extended its reach to the world of cryptocurrencies, leading to a proliferation of blockchain projects and initiatives in Vietnam. Chainalysis, a blockchain analytics firm, revealed that Vietnam secured the top spot in the 2022 Cryptocurrency Adoption Ranking.</p>
<p>The Vietnamese population&#8217;s interest lies in blockchain services that address the gaps prevalent in the country&#8217;s financial system. Payment solutions, investment opportunities for retail investors, and convenient acquiring products for small and medium-sized businesses are particularly popular. Despite rapid technological advancements, Vietnam&#8217;s population remains underbanked, with only about 60% of Vietnamese adults having a bank account, according to a report by the National Payments Corporation of Vietnam (Napas).</p>
<p>The demand for blockchain services that work with cryptocurrencies and offer a user-friendly interface is evident from the growing number of active users on the <a href="https://mineplex.finance/en">CrossFi</a> blockchain. This blockchain serves as the foundation for various decentralized financial and payment services. Within a year, the user base of CrossFi products attracted 5,000 active participants from Vietnam, and this number is projected to grow three to six times over the next couple of years.</p>
<p>The CrossFi blockchain offers a range of payment solutions, including fast transfer services for swift cross-border transactions. It also enables the issuance and acquisition of tokens at private, corporate, and government levels, covering cryptocurrencies, stablecoins, and digital twins. Additionally, CrossFi facilitates the tokenization of banking services and loyalty programs. Their crypto-acquiring platform provides ready-made solutions for enterprises and businesses, utilizing payment cards, POS-terminals, and self-service terminals.</p>
<p>The remarkable growth in the number of users utilizing CrossFi blockchain solutions can be attributed to several key factors:</p>
<p><strong>Wide range of products</strong>: CrossFi offers an extensive selection of solutions, encompassing both traditional banking services with fiat currencies and services related to cryptocurrencies. Exchange transactions and money transfers can be completed swiftly and effortlessly, even without deep technical expertise. This comprehensive approach appeals to a broader audience, attracting individuals already familiar with traditional banking and those keen to explore the world of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Focus on Entrepreneurship</strong>: CrossFi-based products cater to the specific needs of the business community by providing a diverse range of business-specific offerings. Entrepreneurs, who often seek efficient and flexible financial solutions to support their ventures, find that CrossFi-based services grant them access to payment gateways for both fiat and crypto transactions. Moreover, these services enable the implementation of tokenized loyalty programs with NFTs, aligning well with the interests of a young and entrepreneurial audience.</p>
<p><strong>Simplicity and convenience</strong>: All services boast a user-friendly interface and seamless integration of various financial services. This ensures a convenient and accessible experience for users. The simplicity of these services plays a critical role in attracting and retaining customers, especially in the highly competitive fintech industry.</p>
<p><strong>Affordability</strong>: CrossFi-based solutions actively promote financial inclusion in Vietnam, addressing the fact that a significant portion of the population remains unbanked or underbanked. By offering a diverse range of financial options, these solutions empower individuals and businesses that have previously been excluded from traditional banking systems.</p>
<p><strong>Innovation</strong>: The distinctive features of CrossFi-based products, such as payment solutions and acquiring capabilities for both fiat and cryptocurrencies, as well as tokenized loyalty programs with NFTs and the seamless transition to traditional banking services, set them apart from conventional financial platforms. These innovations captivate users who are intrigued by the potential of blockchain and NFT technology.</p>
<p><strong>Benefit</strong>: Users of the CrossFi blockchain are rewarded for staking native MPX coins, with an average monthly return of approximately 8% in XFI coins. MPX coins function as a unit of computing power within the CrossFi blockchain, possessing a stable and fixed value. During MPX staking, other native coins of the CrossFi blockchain, namely <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/mineplex-2/">XFI</a>, are generated. XFI serves as a volatile settlement unit that is utilized across all CrossFi services and can be traded on crypto exchanges. MPX stakers receive rewards in XFI tokens, which can be utilized within CrossFi services or exchanged for other cryptocurrencies on crypto exchanges.</p>
<p><strong>Strategic Partnerships</strong>: The CrossFi team actively collaborates with other businesses and financial institutions to expand the capabilities of CrossFi-based solutions, enabling them to reach new customer segments and enhance their offerings.</p>
<p>In the coming months, all CrossFi-based products will be consolidated into a single Finance mobile banking application, streamlining interaction with cryptocurrencies and providing access to financial services for a wide range of users in Vietnam. The application has already obtained a PCI DSS compliance certificate, signifying the high reliability of its software security systems.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-79211 aligncenter" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture122-565x600.png" alt="" width="565" height="600" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture122-565x600.png 565w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture122.png 624w" sizes="(max-width: 565px) 100vw, 565px" /></p>
<p>Vietnam&#8217;s emergence as a digital hub in Southeast Asia stems from the country&#8217;s appeal to blockchain initiatives, providing an opportunity to showcase their full potential. By offering users, including entrepreneurs, a combination of traditional and cryptocurrency financial services with high accessibility and a focus on innovation, Vietnam has positioned itself as an attractive destination in the world of blockchain.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vietnams-crypto-boom-attracting-top-blockchain-projects/">Vietnam&#8217;s Crypto Boom: Attracting Top Blockchain Projects</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blockchain Capital Plunks Money into Eyeball-Scanning Technology</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-capital-plunks-money-into-eyeball-scanning-technology/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 17:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain capital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eyeball scanning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World Coin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78531</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain Capital – a funding company that’s made a name for itself giving several new blockchain startups life – is betting big on a new eyeball-scanning orb. Blockchain Capital Invests in Some Questionable Tech The firm has funded all kinds of crypto companies from Coinbase and Kraken to NFT marketplace Open Sea. In an interview, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-capital-plunks-money-into-eyeball-scanning-technology/">Blockchain Capital Plunks Money into Eyeball-Scanning Technology</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain Capital – a funding company that’s made a name for itself giving several new blockchain startups life – is betting big on a <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/05/26/explaining-blockchain-capitals-big-bet-on-an-eyeball-scanning-orb/">new eyeball-scanning orb</a>.</p>
<h2>Blockchain Capital Invests in Some Questionable Tech</h2>
<p>The firm has funded all kinds of crypto companies from <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/coinbase/">Coinbase</a> and Kraken to NFT marketplace Open Sea. In an interview, general partner Spencer Bogart talked about how much of the company investors currently own. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>It’s not a figure I have in front of me, right now. Generally, companies sell 20 percent of the [equity] in each financing. Granted, things can move down or up from there significantly. I think in this case, the number is going to be meaningfully lower than that across the series A, the series B, and series C.</p></blockquote>
<p>Not long ago, the enterprise invested in a new venture called World Coin. Discussing what led them to take part in this, Bogart explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>The original genesis was… What if I could create a cryptocurrency that I could distribute to everyone in the world, and everyone got an equal share of it? For me, from a venture perspective, that’s certainly interesting, [though] I don’t know that it’s something that we would be super excited to go and underwrite based on the things that our team is typically interested in. [Meanwhile] this requires basically making sure that no one person can accumulate a disproportionate share of [the currency], which requires the ability to identify unique humans. This gets into the part that we’re really excited about, which is World ID. It’s this ability to easily distinguish between machines and humans on the internet [which is crucial as] most of the internet is supported by ad revenue and it costs just as much to serve bot traffic as it does to service human traffic. It’s why various applications and service providers have used CAPTCHAs to distinguish between bots and humans, but that’s no longer viable in a world of advanced automated systems and particularly things powered by AI. It also doesn’t differentiate between unique humans, so I don’t know if the same person is coming to consume a resource excessively.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Lot of People Looking the Same</h2>
<p>Regarding the company’s funding of the eye scanner, he said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The root of what defines humans is biometrics, and my first thought was, ‘Why create this custom hardware to go scan eyeballs?’ Like, billions of people are already walking around with an iPhone. Why don’t we use Face ID, right? The problem is that human facial structures do not have sufficient randomness or entropy to distinguish between unique humans at the scale of tens of millions or hundreds of millions of people… I didn’t think about the fact that once you get past one hundred million people, there are going to be a lot of people that look like Spencer Bogart.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-capital-plunks-money-into-eyeball-scanning-technology/">Blockchain Capital Plunks Money into Eyeball-Scanning Technology</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Where Will Bitcoin Be at the End of 2023? Analysts Weigh In</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/where-will-bitcoin-be-at-the-end-of-2023-analysts-weigh-in/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 15:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tim Shan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78528</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has been on something of a roll in 2023. While things aren’t quite where they could be, many analysts are excited about the fact that this has virtually been the exact opposite of 2022, a year in which bitcoin and its many crypto cousins fell into oblivion, and they’re all wondering where the world’s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/where-will-bitcoin-be-at-the-end-of-2023-analysts-weigh-in/">Where Will Bitcoin Be at the End of 2023? Analysts Weigh In</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has been on something of a roll in 2023. While things aren’t quite where they could be, many analysts are excited about the fact that this has virtually been the exact opposite of 2022, a year in which bitcoin and its many crypto cousins fell into oblivion, and they’re all wondering where the world’s leading digital <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-is-on-a-tear-in-2023-heres-where-4-crypto-pros-see-the-coin-headed-by-the-end-of-the-year/ar-AA1bNtIV">asset will end the year</a>.</p>
<h2>Where Will Bitcoin Be in 6 Months?</h2>
<p>Charmyn Ho – head of crypto insights at digital asset exchange By Bit – said in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>A possible headwind is the potential recession forecast to hit the US, Europe, and other major economies due to a stubbornly inverted yield curve. Couple this with a bunch of other unsavory macro factors, such as inflation, [and] many investors would rather remain on the sidelines. This is contributing to the mostly sideways price action we&#8217;ve been experiencing.</p></blockquote>
<p>Ho also weighed in on next year’s <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/halving/">halving</a>. It’s alleged that this event, as it’s done in the past, will bear a lot of weight on the price of bitcoin in the coming months. Ho said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin halvings are significant because they slash the production of new bitcoins on the network by half. This curtails the supply of freshly minted coins, thus leading to a price increase if the demand persists. Litecoin, which is due [to halve] this year, is up around 90 percent since its lows in Q3, 2022. Therefore, if we take that as a guide, it is possible that we could see a similar 90 percent move from bitcoin&#8217;s Q3, 2023 price, which would give a rough target of about $60,000.</p></blockquote>
<p>Jagdeep Sidhu – president of the Syscoin Foundation – was also quick to comment and said:</p>
<blockquote><p>While we&#8217;ve weathered some storms recently, the resilience of the crypto ecosystem remains evident. From the ashes of FTX, the market has rebounded, demonstrating its inherent capacity to absorb shocks and evolve. As we approach the next bitcoin halving and crypto dominance looks set to peak, we&#8217;re on the cusp of exciting developments in the crypto world.</p></blockquote>
<p>Tim Shan – COO at decentralized exchange Dexalot – mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>My base case is bitcoin will trade in a range between $25,000 and $32,000 for the remainder of 2023, but if we see inflation remain high, I think bitcoin could trade back down to lows of the year. The short to medium term driver is still inflation, and specifically US inflation. I think core inflation has been sticky, but [it] will continue to decline in the US, leading the Fed to pause for the rest of the year.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Investors Remaining Sidelined?</h2>
<p>Last came David Uhryniak, an employee of Tron. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Right now, smart traders are waiting for greater validation as to which way bitcoin and the rest of the market will move next before committing serious money.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/where-will-bitcoin-be-at-the-end-of-2023-analysts-weigh-in/">Where Will Bitcoin Be at the End of 2023? Analysts Weigh In</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinswapz Travel Says &#8220;Yes&#8221; to Crypto Payments</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinswapz-travel-says-yes-to-crypto-payments/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 13:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinswapz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto payments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dubai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[travel]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78524</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinswapz Travel – a new kind of travel company based in the United Arab Emirates – is making headlines after it announced that travel hounds and general customers can utilize digital currencies to book their trips and take care of other vacation-related expenses. Coinswapz Will Accept Crypto Payments The move is pushing the goals of bitcoin [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinswapz-travel-says-yes-to-crypto-payments/">Coinswapz Travel Says &#8220;Yes&#8221; to Crypto Payments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coinswapz Travel – a new kind of travel company based in the United Arab Emirates – is making headlines after it announced that travel hounds and general customers <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coinswapz-travel-introduces-cryptocurrency-transactions-195000116.html">can utilize digital currencies</a> to book their trips and take care of other vacation-related expenses.</p>
<h2>Coinswapz Will Accept Crypto Payments</h2>
<p>The move is pushing the goals of bitcoin and its digital counterparts closer to being achieved. What many people likely forget is that while bitcoin and many of its crypto cousins have taken on either speculative or even hedge-like statuses in recent years, many of them were initially designed to serve as payment tools. They were built to push checks, credit cards, and fiat currencies to the side, but this has been a relatively slow journey given the volatility that continues to drag them down.</p>
<p>It is extremely hard to understand when bitcoin and its crypto family will go up or down when it comes to their prices. Many stores and companies have been reluctant to say “yes” when it comes to accepting crypto payments for this reason, and to a degree, we can’t blame them.</p>
<p>Consider the following scenario: someone walks into a store and buys $50 worth of merchandise with bitcoin. For one reason or another, the store doesn’t trade the BTC into fiat right away and about 24 hours go by. From there, the price of BTC goes down and that $50 becomes $40. The customer gets to keep everything he or she bought, but the store loses money in the end. Is this a fair situation? Not everyone thinks so.</p>
<p>That’s what makes enterprises like Coinswapz so important. They understand the initial purposes of bitcoin and digital currencies and are trying to transform them into usable tools that everyday people can benefit from.</p>
<p>While right now, customers are primarily limited to using the company’s native digital token, Coinswapz has hinted that it may be open to accepting other cryptocurrencies as payment methods in the future. The enterprise assures customers that using digital assets to pay for trips is not only hassle-free and easier to do when compared with using credit cards of fiat currencies, but that it’s also safer.</p>
<h2>What Can You Buy?</h2>
<p>Among the things people can pay for via crypto are hotel stays, flights, visa fees, and transportation costs. In addition, they can also pay for gift cards for both hotels and Airbnb locations with crypto.</p>
<p>The company is in the heart of Dubai, which over the past several years, has proven to be a leading hub for all things digital currency and blockchain-related. Last December, the city <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dubai-is-creating-a-new-crypto-regulatory-agenda/">became one of the</a> first to introduce the world to a new set of crypto regulations as a means of making the industry more legitimate and mainstream and attracting further businesses.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinswapz-travel-says-yes-to-crypto-payments/">Coinswapz Travel Says &#8220;Yes&#8221; to Crypto Payments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Is the Recovery Just Getting Started?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-is-the-recovery-just-getting-started/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 05:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79207</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ADA price is struggling to climb above the $0.2920 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading near $0.288 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a connecting bullish trend line forming with support near $0.2850 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Coinbase). The price could gain bullish momentum [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-is-the-recovery-just-getting-started/">Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Is the Recovery Just Getting Started?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>ADA price is struggling to climb above the $0.2920 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading near $0.288 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a connecting bullish trend line forming with support near $0.2850 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Coinbase).</li>
<li>The price could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $0.292 and $0.302 levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Cardano price is holding the $0.276 support against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-more-upsides-above-31250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. ADA price could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $0.302 resistance.</em></p>
<h2>Cardano Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, Cardano price saw a decent upward move from the $0.276 support against the US Dollar. The ADA/USD pair was able to climb above the $0.285 and $0.292 resistance levels.</p>
<p>However, the bears were active near the $0.302 zone. A high is formed near $0.3018 before there was a fresh decline. A low is formed near $0.2768 and the price is now rising. It broke the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3018 swing high to the $0.2768 low.</p>
<p>ADA is now trading near $0.288 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-more-gains-seems-likely-above-0-30/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. There is also a connecting bullish trend line forming with support near $0.285 on the 4-hour chart.</p>
<p>On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $0.292 zone. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3018 swing high to the $0.2768 low. The next major resistance is near the $0.302 level.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $0.302 resistance might start a steady increase. In the stated case, the price may perhaps rise toward the $0.325 resistance or even $0.332.</p>
<p>On the downside, immediate support is near the $0.285 level. The next major support is near the $0.276 level. A clear move below the $0.276 level might send the price toward the $0.265 level. Any more losses might send the price toward the $0.242 support, below which the bears could aim for a test of $0.225.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79208" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79208" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Cardano-Price-1.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-79208" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Cardano-Price-1.png" alt="Cardano (ADA) Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Cardano-Price-1.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Cardano-Price-1-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Cardano-Price-1-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Cardano-Price-1-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Cardano-Price-1-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Cardano-Price-1-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Cardano-Price-1-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79208" class="wp-caption-text">Cardano (ADA) Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ADAUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a> indicates that ADA price is now trading near $0.288 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $0.292 and $0.302 levels.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ADA/USD is now losing pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for ADA/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.285 and $0.276.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.292 and $0.302.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-is-the-recovery-just-getting-started/">Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Is the Recovery Just Getting Started?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Aims Fresh Run To $2,000</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-aims-fresh-run-to-2000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 03:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79204</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum price is eyeing an upside break above the $1,900 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH price is now trading below $1,890 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,900 on the 4-hour chart (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could climb further [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-aims-fresh-run-to-2000/">Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Aims Fresh Run To $2,000</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ethereum price is eyeing an upside break above the $1,900 resistance against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>ETH price is now trading below $1,890 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,900 on the 4-hour chart (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could climb further if it stays above the $1,825 support zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ethereum price is rising above the $1,850 level against the US Dollar. ETH/USD could rise further if it clears the $1,900 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Ethereum Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, Ethereum saw a bearish wave from the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-rally-above-2000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$2,000 zone</a> against the US Dollar. ETH price declined below the $1,900 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>The bears even pushed the price below the $1,850 level. A low was formed near $1,825 and the price is now attempting a fresh increase. There was a move above the $1,850 resistance level. The price broke the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $1,976 swing high to the $1,825 low.</p>
<p>It is now trading below $1,890 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-eyes-more-gains-above-1920/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. Immediate resistance on the upside is near the $1,900 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,900 on the 4-hour chart.</p>
<p>The trend line is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $1,976 swing high to the $1,825 low. The next major resistance is near the $1,940 zone. A clear move above the $1,940 level could send the price toward $1,980.</p>
<p>Any more gains could even send the price toward the $2,000 resistance zone or $2,050 in the near term. On the downside, initial support is near the $1,860 level. The next major support is now near the $1,825 level.</p>
<p>A break below the $1,825 support could push the price to $1,760. Any more losses could lead the price toward $1,720 or even $1,700 in the coming days.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79205" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79205" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum-1.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-79205" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum-1.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum-1.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum-1-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum-1-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum-1-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum-1-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum-1-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum-1-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79205" class="wp-caption-text">Ethereum Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/">chart</a>, Ethereum price is clearly trading below the $1,890 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, Ether price could climb further if it stays above the $1,825 support zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now losing momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $1,860, followed by the $1,825 zone.</p>
<p>Key Resistance$ Levels – $1,900 and $1,940.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-aims-fresh-run-to-2000/">Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Aims Fresh Run To $2,000</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Opinion: Is Trump Crypto&#8217;s Best Hope for Survival in America?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-is-trump-cryptos-best-hope-for-survival-in-america/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 17:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OpEd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[America]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trump]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78519</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Several people have thrown their hats into the 2024 presidential ring, and while many of them are talking about their alleged plans involving crypto and America, it’s interesting that the one man who’s stayed relatively silent on the subject – Donald Trump – could still be the best hope for the country’s digital currency arena. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-is-trump-cryptos-best-hope-for-survival-in-america/">Opinion: Is Trump Crypto&#8217;s Best Hope for Survival in America?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Several people have thrown their hats into the 2024 presidential ring, and while many of them are talking about their alleged plans involving crypto and America, it’s interesting that the one man who’s stayed relatively silent on the subject – Donald Trump – could still be the best hope for the country’s digital currency arena.</p>
<h2>Why Trump Remains the #1 Choice</h2>
<p>Let’s look at the most known presidential candidates to see which one stands higher than the rest:</p>
<h2>Joe Biden</h2>
<p>Everyone knows that another term for Joe Biden would mean the death of crypto. As the leading face of the democrat party, Biden has worked hard to make traders’ lives miserable. Between an Obama-era policy designed to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-biden-using-an-obama-era-program-to-ban-btc/">shut out the crypto</a> arena from traditional financial tools, a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-amendment-for-infrastructure-bill-leads-to-more-problems-and-infighting/">phony infrastructure bill</a> aimed at traders, and now a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/biden-wants-to-tax-crypto-mining-companies-at-30/">30 percent tax</a> on all crypto mining, it’s clear Biden seeks a future for America where crypto doesn’t exist.</p>
<p>Unless Americans want more persecution and financial repression, they should do all they can to get Biden out of office.</p>
<h2>Robert Kennedy Jr.</h2>
<p>Arguably Biden’s biggest threat when it comes to this year’s democratic nomination, Kennedy has said, in passing, he’s against Biden on all things when it comes to crypto. Making an appearance at this year’s Miami Bitcoin Conference, he <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-candidate-robert-kennedy-jr-has-big-plans-for-the-crypto-space/">mentioned he’s not only</a> accepting crypto donations for his campaign, but he’ll ensure no government interference ever occurs when it comes to bitcoin trading.</p>
<p>While this sounds dandy, the fact remains that Kennedy is still an active member of the democrat party, which one could argue is the main enemy of all crypto fans in the U.S. Figures like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elizabeth-warren-is-building-an-anti-crypto-rhetoric-as-part-of-her-reelection-campaign/">Elizabeth Warren</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-attorney-generals-office-now-suing-ku-coin-exchange/">Leticia James</a> in New York, and others have made it clear they seek to end the reign of crypto in this country for good.</p>
<p>They’ve also made a habit of sticking together no matter what. This raises several questions, a big one being whether Kennedy, down the line, will have the guts to always stand up against those he calls his colleagues, and if he does, will he have the strength to maintain such fortitude for four years? Getting the answers to these questions <em>after</em> he’s entered the White House may prove too late.</p>
<h2>Vivek Ramaswamy</h2>
<p>Republican candidate Ramaswamy has stated that he <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vivek-ramaswamy-is-making-crypto-a-big-part-of-his-white-house-campaign/">seeks to limit all taxes</a> on crypto mining. He’s also very much against the damaging tactics Biden has instilled and wants America to ring in a whole new wave of crypto innovation.</p>
<p>While this sounds promising, however, what else is he planning? Ramaswamy, for the most part, has remained relatively silent when it comes to other policy aspects. What will he do, for example, about the economy should he win next year? Bitcoin and crypto can only go so far, and it’s unlikely they’ll solve all the damage done to America’s financial system… at least not quickly, so what else does he have in store?</p>
<p>Unfortunately, we don’t quite know, and until we do, we cannot assume that his candidacy is strong or legitimate enough simply because he’s willing to discuss crypto and blockchain when others won’t.</p>
<h2>Ron DeSantis</h2>
<p>At first glance, DeSantis – the republican governor of Florida who announced <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ron-desantis-is-running-for-president-appears-to-be-very-pro-crypto/">his candidacy in late</a> May – seems like the perfect candidate. He’s commented, in the past, that everyone has a right to bitcoin trading, and he’s worked to prevent CBDCs from <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ron-desantis-signs-anti-cbdc-crypto-bill-into-law/">being established in Florida</a>, as he believes they’ll be tools for government spying. This is all good… Right?</p>
<p>Unfortunately, DeSantis’ background and network appear rather shady when one looks deep enough. There are several allegations, for example, that DeSantis is a neocon secretly <a href="https://truenewsamerica.com/2023/02/25/ron-desantis-accepts-endorsement-and-donations-from-george-soros/">being funded by</a> George Soros, a known enemy of the U.S. Soros is <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-fans-see-joe-biden-for-the-destructive-force-he-is/">also funding Alvin Bragg</a>, the corrupt DA in Manhattan who lets violent criminals get off with warnings while going after President Trump for an NDA case from roughly seven years ago that both the federal government and the Federal Election Commission (FEC) looked at and passed on after feeling there was nothing worthy of prosecution.</p>
<p>If such statements regarding DeSantis are true, that’s scary, and it’s something Americans likely don’t want to find out after he’s already been elected to the White House. If DeSantis indeed has connections to Soros, one can bet that all his talk about crypto will probably go out the door if he’s pressed to police Americans and their financial liberties.</p>
<h2>Donald Trump</h2>
<p>When it comes to crypto’s future in America, Trump (who&#8217;s currently <a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/meet-the-press/meetthepressblog/new-polls-show-trump-commanding-lead-2024-gop-race-rcna86232">leading in all the polls</a>) may seem like the least likely candidate given he’s said some <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/donald-trump-is-no-fan-of-bitcoin/">negative things about digital</a> assets in the past. However, when one puts these comments aside, they can’t help but realize that he’s the one, true choice if crypto is going to survive within this nation’s borders.</p>
<p>The fact is that Trump already has a proven track record, meaning he can potentially get the current financial state of America back on track in the shortest period. During his first term as president, <a href="https://www.newsweek.com/face-it-economy-under-trump-great-opinion-1484645">the economy was in</a> its best shape in a long while. Bitcoin reached its first all-time high of <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/gmnovp/what_caused_bitcoin_to_rise_to_20k_in_2017/">nearly $20K during</a> 2017, and the arena endured a remarkable <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/bitcoin-and-cryptocurrencys-2020-turnaround-5094080">turnaround in 2020 during</a> the COVID pandemic, a time when it likely should have gone to pieces.</p>
<p>In addition, <a href="https://www.gobankingrates.com/investing/stocks/stocks-soared-under-trumps-presidency/">stocks</a> and <a href="https://www.mining.com/gold-price-rockets-on-trump-victory/">gold</a> were also high, and this is <em>exactly</em> what crypto fans should be eager for. An arena where all three primary asset classes – stocks, precious metals, and digital currencies – are strong and on the same level. This is the only way to achieve economic balance. This doesn’t happen when one is performing miles above another or when one endures shakiness while another is steady. Trump, in many ways, leveled the playing field for America’s economy like no other president has, and for this reason alone, he’s likely the top candidate when it comes to crypto’s safety.</p>
<p>Lastly, Trump has pledged freedom for all American citizens, suggesting that while he may not partake in crypto trading, investors can rest assured their plans will not be hindered while he’s in office.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-is-trump-cryptos-best-hope-for-survival-in-america/">Opinion: Is Trump Crypto&#8217;s Best Hope for Survival in America?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Report: Bitcoin Volatility Lowest in Nearly Three Years</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-bitcoin-volatility-lowest-in-three-years/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 15:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Noelle Acheson]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[volatility]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78516</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Despite what has still felt like a relatively up-and-down period for bitcoin, the world’s number one digital currency by market cap, a new study suggests that the volatility of the asset is at its lowest since 2020. Bitcoin Volatility is Slowing Down Big Time The last time bitcoin was this calm was in October three [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-bitcoin-volatility-lowest-in-three-years/">Report: Bitcoin Volatility Lowest in Nearly Three Years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite what has still felt like a relatively up-and-down period for bitcoin, the world’s number one digital currency by market cap, a new <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-volatility-drops-lowest-since-161846391.html">study suggests that the</a> volatility of the asset is at its lowest since 2020.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Volatility is Slowing Down Big Time</h2>
<p>The last time bitcoin was this calm was in October three years ago. During that period, bitcoin either didn’t move at all or endured very small maneuvers over 70 separate sessions, and it looks like those patterns are repeating. Strahinja Savic – head of data and analytics at FRNT Financial – commented on the situation and said:</p>
<blockquote><p>There are a few macro catalysts playing out right now. Whether debt-ceiling negotiations or the Fed rate policy, traders are waiting for more clarity. It’s just a wait-and-see-type of moment.</p></blockquote>
<p>The news is odd given that in May, for example, bitcoin endured a near $4,000 slide <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/">from the $30K price</a> it hit just a month earlier. In April, bitcoin struck a ten-month high, and many felt that the days of 2022 – arguably the worst period on record for the currency – were finally coming to an end.</p>
<p>However, the following month, it was clear that present resistance was still proving to be too harsh an enemy for the world’s leading digital asset. The currency fell into the mid-$26,000 range and only hit $27K briefly after it was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-prices-rise-following-positive-sentiment-from-hong-kong/">announced that Hong Kong</a> would allow certain forms of retail crypto trading through specific (licensed) platforms.</p>
<p>When one looks at data like this, it’s easy to assume that volatility is still relatively constant in the digital currency arena, though it could also be argued that bitcoin has remained almost completely still compared with where it was last year. In her newsletter “Crypto Is Macro Now,” Noelle Acheson explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>There could be some downside, but conviction in this is not strong enough to offset the possibility of missing out on any rally. Obviously, there is some buying and selling going on, but it is not enough to boost volatility despite the low volumes and liquidity.</p></blockquote>
<h2>2022: The Worst Year on Record!</h2>
<p>The good news is that 2023 has offered a degree of healing that many crypto fans and traders likely needed to see before they jumped back into the trading game. The fact is nothing has ever been as damaging as the trends witnessed in 2022, which will probably go down as one of the worst years for bitcoin and crypto.</p>
<p>During that period, the leading digital asset lost more than 70 percent of its value, dropping from $68,000 (an all-time high) in November 2021 to about $16,600 just a year later. Sadly, the trouble didn’t stop there, as several assets chose to follow in BTC’s footsteps and bring the overall valuation of the crypto arena down by more than $2 trillion.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-bitcoin-volatility-lowest-in-three-years/">Report: Bitcoin Volatility Lowest in Nearly Three Years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
