<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 14:56:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/cropped-fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>New Japan Laws Will Put Limits on Crypto Taxation</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-japan-laws-will-put-limits-on-crypto-taxation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 17:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Japan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78940</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Japan just established a whole new level of clarity to its crypto tax agenda. Up to this point, all unrealized gains from crypto assets were subjected to the country’s present 30 percent corporate tax rate, though now, it appears this is coming to an end. Japan is Putting an End to Some Crypto Taxation The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-japan-laws-will-put-limits-on-crypto-taxation/">New Japan Laws Will Put Limits on Crypto Taxation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Japan just established a whole new level of <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cryptocurrency-issuers-japan-crucial-tax-114456001.html">clarity to its crypto tax agenda</a>. Up to this point, all unrealized gains from crypto assets were subjected to the country’s present 30 percent corporate tax rate, though now, it appears this is coming to an end.</p>
<h2>Japan is Putting an End to Some Crypto Taxation</h2>
<p>The news came from Japan’s National Tax Agency (NTA). The agency explained in a statement that crypto assets will be excluded from any company’s asset valuation based on market value if certain conditions are met. For example, a company is required to hold crypto assets for certain periods after they’re obtained if tax exemptions are to occur. Also, it’s been stated that all crypto transfers are subject to specific restrictions.</p>
<p>Soto Watanabe – CEO of web3 development firm Stake Technologies Pte. – believes the new taxation laws will open all kinds of doors for innovation in Japan, and he thinks this will do wonders in preventing Japanese crypto companies from leaving. At the same time, he also says the rules can be extended somewhat to ensure crypto firms in other regions also benefit. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>For the time being, people who want to do something… can now do it without leaving the country. I would like to continue constructive discussions with politicians and authorities. Next, I would like to do something about the end-of-term taxation of holding tokens issued by other companies as a corporation, as it is a hindrance to the domestic expansion of projects and domestic projects.</p></blockquote>
<p>While crypto taxation hasn’t become null and void in Japan, the present rules are considered far less strict and a solid move forward for the Asian country, which up to this stage, was considered one of the harshest with its digital currency laws given it was home to both the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/mt-gox/">Mt. Gox</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/coincheck/">Coincheck</a> debacles. Both are considered among the biggest crypto exchange hacks in history.</p>
<p>The first, which occurred in 2014, saw more than $400 million in BTC disappear overnight, while the second (which occurred four years later) saw more than half a billion in assorted crypto funds vanish. The situation surrounding Japan and crypto taxation begs the question, “If a country that’s home to not just one, but two of the biggest crypto mishaps can take it easy on the industry, why can’t the U.S.?&#8221;</p>
<p>America is currently utilizing an attitude of regulation through enforcement when it comes to crypto. Agencies like the SEC are coming after the industry with everything it has, and lawsuits are being initiated against some of the biggest crypto firms out there including <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-hit-with-sec-lawsuit-says-it-operated-as-an-exchange-broker/">Coinbase</a>.</p>
<h2>The U.S. is in a Bad Place</h2>
<p>Noriyuki Hirosue – CEO of crypto exchange Bit Bank – said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The U.S. regulators are increasingly tightening controls, but that doesn’t mean the same things will happen in Japan.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-japan-laws-will-put-limits-on-crypto-taxation/">New Japan Laws Will Put Limits on Crypto Taxation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase: Multiple Companies Are Now Exploring Blockchain Options</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-multiple-companies-are-now-exploring-blockchain-options/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 15:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78938</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new report produced by leading digital currency exchange Coinbase suggests over 52 percent of Fortune 500 companies are exploring blockchain technology. They’re also looking at crypto and web3. Coinbase Believes Blockchain Innovation is Growing The blockchain industry has walked a long route in a particularly short period. For example, the bitcoin blockchain – which [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-multiple-companies-are-now-exploring-blockchain-options/">Coinbase: Multiple Companies Are Now Exploring Blockchain Options</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new report <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/over-half-of-fortune-100-firms-are-betting-on-blockchain-coinbase-finds/ar-AA1cZeGt">produced by leading digital</a> currency exchange Coinbase suggests over 52 percent of Fortune 500 companies are exploring blockchain technology. They’re also looking at crypto and web3.</p>
<h2>Coinbase Believes Blockchain Innovation is Growing</h2>
<p>The blockchain industry has walked a long route in a particularly short period. For example, the bitcoin blockchain – which was first introduced in a whitepaper on Halloween of 2008 – didn’t see mining action until early 2009, meaning it’s only been around for 14 years. Still, blockchain remains an intriguing new point for financial companies to at least look at.</p>
<p>At the same time, it appears much of the blockchain traction we’ve grown so privy to has occurred just in the past few weeks, with large financial firms like BlackRock announcing new plans for bitcoin-based exchange-traded funds (EFTs) and related projects. Most of the time, traditional finance and crypto don’t always mix, and if they do, it’s simply because a crypto company needs a bank account or similar tool.</p>
<p>This time around, however, it appears one of the biggest financial firms in BlackRock is <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blackrock-etf-application-causes-btc-eth-to-surge/">looking to create</a> a revolutionary new crypto-based product that everyone in the industry has been anticipating for several years. Many companies, from <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/vaneck/">Van Eck</a> to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitwise/">Bitwise</a>, have tried to submit bitcoin-based ETF applications to the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) as a means of opening trading doors for customers, and none have been successful thus far.</p>
<p>There are many, however, that believe BlackRock’s case will be different. The company has garnered more than 500 application approvals from the SEC in the past, and it only has one rejection to its name. Also, the firm has named Coinbase as its custody provider when the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-hit-with-sec-lawsuit-says-it-operated-as-an-exchange-broker/">exchange is presently engaged</a> in a lawsuit with the financial agency. It’s accusing the exchange of operating as an unlicensed broker-dealer.</p>
<p>Regarding its recent report findings, Coinbase said:</p>
<blockquote><p>These companies are innovating and investing in these technologies because they know that the century-old global financial system needs updating, that blockchain can be a foundational solution, and that not keeping pace will mean losing ground in this global economy to competitors around the world, among other possible reasons.</p></blockquote>
<h2>The U.S. Needs to Stop Its Present Action</h2>
<p>The document also said that the U.S.’s current streak of regulation enforcement has been very damaging to the crypto industry and is ultimately preventing innovation from happening. It said if America continues this route, things are not going to go well for it financially or economically. The report states:</p>
<blockquote><p>The U.S. is at risk of losing out on one million web3 developer jobs and three million related non-technical jobs to other countries between now and 2030 if it continues on its current path of regulation by enforcement.</p></blockquote>
<p>Among the firms exploring blockchain are Bank of America, Nike, and PayPal.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-multiple-companies-are-now-exploring-blockchain-options/">Coinbase: Multiple Companies Are Now Exploring Blockchain Options</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Redefine Blockchain Mixes with Safe to Enhance Transaction Security</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/redefine-blockchain-mixes-with-safe-to-enhance-transaction-security/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 13:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Redefine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Safe]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78936</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain security firm Redefine has joined hands with digital currency management platform Safe. The goal is to integrate the former’s platform De Fire Wall software into Safe’s infrastructure to ensure Safe can properly check each transaction and prevent any sort of illicit activity or fraud. Redefine and Safe: A Perfect Match? Safe has been garnering [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/redefine-blockchain-mixes-with-safe-to-enhance-transaction-security/">Redefine Blockchain Mixes with Safe to Enhance Transaction Security</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain security firm Redefine has <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/enhanced-blockchain-security-redefine-partners-130400720.html">joined hands with digital</a> currency management platform Safe. The goal is to integrate the former’s platform De Fire Wall software into Safe’s infrastructure to ensure Safe can properly check each transaction and prevent any sort of illicit activity or fraud.</p>
<h2>Redefine and Safe: A Perfect Match?</h2>
<p>Safe has been garnering a lot of traction lately amongst web3 startups. The company has become the official asset holder for several of these new enterprises, as it’s presently the custody head for more than $50 billion in digital assets. The main intent for Safe is to begin bringing web2 users over to the web3 spectrum and set new standards for security and accessibility. Among Safe’s current big-name users include Vitalik Buterin, the co-founder of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ethereum/">Ethereum</a>, and AAVE.</p>
<p>Richard Meissner – co-founder and technical lead at Safe – said in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Improving the user interfaces of web3 platforms is one of the greatest tools we have in order to combat bad actors and exploits in this industry. The issue of blind signing, where users may sign off on transactions they are not fully informed about, is an area of concern as we look to make self-custody accessible to a wider range of users and organizations. By partnering with Redefine and integrating De Fire wall, Safe is offering greater transparency and assurance in their everyday transactions, enabling sustainable growth on the platform.</p></blockquote>
<p>While crypto has come a long way in the last few years, the industry has suffered heavily from the lack of safety it’s still clearly suffering from. Scams, wallet hacks, and exchange attacks continue to plague the digital currency arena, and it’s become clear there are no easy answers when it comes to crypto’s ongoing safety problems.</p>
<p>De Fire Wall at least serves as a step forward. The platform works to check every transaction that occurs on Safe’s blockchain. Risk reports are created based on these transactions which are then followed by actionable insights. Security is strengthened for the company, while unauthorized fund use becomes significantly limited. Shira Brezis – CEO and co-founder of Redefine – mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Safe is an unrivaled and trusted platform that financial institutions and other users depend on for managing their digital assets securely. This integration combines two crucial elements for users: enhanced risk visibility and trusted security. We look forward to ushering in a new era of security with this collaboration between Safe and Redefine.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Keeping Web3 Safe</h2>
<p>Redefine seeks to ensure the web3 industry is a responsible one. The company aims to mix cybersecurity solutions with blockchain analytics to engage in appropriate decision making and prevent any kind of loss or fraud.</p>
<p>As a leading self-custody company, Safe seeks a world centered on crypto in which security, usability, data, and identity are all thrown together.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/redefine-blockchain-mixes-with-safe-to-enhance-transaction-security/">Redefine Blockchain Mixes with Safe to Enhance Transaction Security</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New String of Bomb Threats Are Followed By BTC Demands</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-string-of-bomb-threats-are-followed-by-btc-demands/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 17:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bomb threats]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kroger]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78925</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A series of fake bomb threats aimed at some of America’s largest retailers has law enforcement baffled. The threats involved perpetrators asking for gift cards and bitcoin in exchange for not setting off explosives or doing lots of damage. Bomb Threats and Bitcoin&#8230; A Deadly Match? Among the big-name stores being targeted by the bomb [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-string-of-bomb-threats-are-followed-by-btc-demands/">New String of Bomb Threats Are Followed By BTC Demands</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A series of fake bomb threats aimed at some of America’s largest retailers <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/hoax-bomb-threats-target-major-164837472.html?ref=upstract.com">has law enforcement baffled</a>. The threats involved perpetrators asking for gift cards and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitcoin/">bitcoin</a> in exchange for not setting off explosives or doing lots of damage.</p>
<h2>Bomb Threats and Bitcoin&#8230; A Deadly Match?</h2>
<p>Among the big-name stores being targeted by the bomb threats are Kroger, Meijer, Walmart, and Whole Foods. The threats also took place in several states rather than isolated regions. Several individuals have allegedly called in and threatened to detonate bombs if bitcoin, cash, or gift cards were not provided in a timely manner. Thus far, an investigation has turned up little to no evidence regarding who could have been involved.</p>
<p>Per police statements, the callers have repeatedly used blocked numbers as a means of preventing their identities from being discovered. One call, for example, was made to a Chicago-based Whole Foods store. The caller said that if $5,000 in BTC wasn’t delivered to a specific address within a set period, a pipe bomb would be detonated within its walls.</p>
<p>A separate call placed to a Kroger grocery outlet in New Mexico demanded over $5,000 in Apple gift cards. Failure to comply, per the perpetrator, meant a bomb would go off and people would be hurt.</p>
<p>A spokesperson for the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) has issued the following statement regarding the matter and its subsequent investigation:</p>
<blockquote><p>The FBI remains vigilant and continues to work closely with our law enforcement partners on a state and local level. The FBI asks members of the public to maintain awareness of their surroundings and to report any suspicious activity to law enforcement.</p></blockquote>
<p>Crypto-related crime is nothing new, but this is arguably the first time it’s taken on such a devastating tone. Robbing individual wallets or even an exchange is one thing, but this time around, lives are being threatened, property is in danger of being damaged, and many more harmful effects could be set to take place. The only good news, at the time of writing, is that these calls appear to be fake, though that doesn’t offer any excuses.</p>
<h2>May Not Be Real</h2>
<p>Still, the FBI and other law enforcement agencies don’t want to take any chances that there could be elements of reality to the calls. Thus, should stores receive similar messages in the future, they’re advised to get in touch with the FBI or local police forces and tell them about the occurrence(s) so more research and investigating can be done.</p>
<p>Lisa Bruno – a senior executive vice president of retail operations at the Retail Industry Leaders Association – commented in a recent interview that this is just another “evolving scam” for U.S. retailers, and that while still scary, incidents like these have occurred many times in the past.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-string-of-bomb-threats-are-followed-by-btc-demands/">New String of Bomb Threats Are Followed By BTC Demands</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chen Zhuling: Blockchain Will Be Bigger Than Ever</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/chen-zhuling-blockchain-will-be-bigger-than-ever/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chen Zhuling]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78923</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chen Zhuling – founder and CEO of Rock X – is confident blockchain is going to reach new levels of usage and popularity in the coming months. Chen Zhuling on Blockchain&#8217;s Future In a recent interview, he stated: The attraction of leading technology developers to the blockchain industry represents a broadening recognition of blockchain as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/chen-zhuling-blockchain-will-be-bigger-than-ever/">Chen Zhuling: Blockchain Will Be Bigger Than Ever</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chen Zhuling – founder and CEO of Rock X – is confident <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/crypto-veteran-chen-zhuling-says-blockchain-innovations-set-to-skyrocket/ar-AA1d0OWD">blockchain is going</a> to reach new levels of usage and popularity in the coming months.</p>
<h2>Chen Zhuling on Blockchain&#8217;s Future</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, he stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>The attraction of leading technology developers to the blockchain industry represents a broadening recognition of blockchain as more than just a financial instrument. It is a foundation for the new digital frontier. Blockchain is akin to a new-age internet, being increasingly utilized as a robust, decentralized platform for innovation. This evolution is still nascent, predominantly scrutinized through a financial lens by regulators. As the industry matures and regulations broaden to embrace the technological potential of blockchain, we will see a global surge in blockchain-enabled innovations.</p></blockquote>
<p>Regarding current market sentiments and the overall trends being witnessed in the web3 arena, Zhuling further mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Like any other, the cryptocurrency market is subject to fluctuations and periods of downturn. However, those who see the long-term potential of these digital assets and the technology underpinning them may find it worthwhile to weather these volatile periods. The future of web3, the decentralized internet, is ripe with promise. Though we can&#8217;t predict the exact timing of a market rebound, we can expect continued growth and development in this sphere, driving new applications and opportunities.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also said that the full adoption of crypto is critical if the finance industry is to stand strong in the coming future. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>The institutional adoption of cryptocurrencies is a critical indicator of their viability and future potential. Assets like bitcoin and Ethereum have been embraced by increasing financial institutions, which indicates a strong confidence in their value as investment instruments. As the industry matures, we are likely to see more sophisticated products emerge, from passive staking yields to hedging mechanisms, all aimed at optimizing the potential returns of these crypto assets.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also discussed the future developments and upgrades involving <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ethereum/">Ethereum</a>, the world’s second largest digital asset by market cap:</p>
<blockquote><p>The recent transition of Ethereum from a mining-centric, proof of work model to a more energy-efficient, proof of stake mechanism marks a significant leap forward for the platform. This change has boosted participation in the Ethereum network and attracted institutional attention. The Shapella upgrade, successfully implemented in April, has further bolstered Ethereum&#8217;s appeal, leading to a surge in ETH being staked. While current staking yields of four to six percent may appear modest, they represent a sustainable method of earning crypto returns without the inherent risks associated with trading or lending.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Who Could Beat ETH?</h2>
<p>Regarding ETH’s biggest rivals Cosmos and Polkadot, he said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Emerging blockchains like Cosmos and Polkadot, while still younger than Ethereum, are rapidly carving out their niches. Cosmos is recognized for its innovative scalability solutions, while Polkadot stands out for its interoperability.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/chen-zhuling-blockchain-will-be-bigger-than-ever/">Chen Zhuling: Blockchain Will Be Bigger Than Ever</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zachery Ty Bryan: From Child Star to Alleged Crypto Fraudster</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/zachery-ty-bryan-from-child-star-to-potential-crypto-fraudster/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 13:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Producers Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zachery Ty Bryan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78920</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Zachery Ty Bryan is a former child star famous for his role on the television program “Home Improvement,” starring comedian Tim Allen. He went from acting as a child, to garnering a fortune in bitcoin, to earning a reputation as a potential fraudster. Zachery Ty Bryan Went from Child Acting to BTC Bryan referred to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/zachery-ty-bryan-from-child-star-to-potential-crypto-fraudster/">Zachery Ty Bryan: From Child Star to Alleged Crypto Fraudster</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Zachery Ty Bryan is a former child star famous for his role on the television program “Home Improvement,” starring comedian Tim Allen. He went <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/tv/celebrity/zachery-ty-bryan-discusses-substance-abuse-issues-says-he-started-drinking-at-14-while-on-home-improvement/ar-AA1cU9tn?OCID=ansmsnnews11">from acting as a child</a>, to garnering a fortune in bitcoin, to earning a reputation as a potential fraudster.</p>
<h2>Zachery Ty Bryan Went from Child Acting to BTC</h2>
<p>Bryan referred to his times on the show as some of the best of his life, but eventually, things spiraled out of control thanks to alcohol habits that brought him into the doldrums. He commented in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Dude, I started drinking when I was 14. Back then, I was going to nightclubs, and they would just let me in because I was the kid from ‘Home Improvement.’</p></blockquote>
<p>After his time on the show, Bryan continued to act, doing a few movies here and there, though he eventually became a reporter for <em>The Daily Wire</em> and <em>Fox News</em>. He was also able to switch from acting to producing television and film productions like “The Kindergarten Teacher” and “Skin,” and he was able to fund all his productions through the fortune he made in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitcoin/">bitcoin</a> as an early investor.</p>
<p>His attachment to crypto garnered him a partnership with an ag-tech startup called Producers Market. It was here that things really started to fall apart, as he would often name drop people as a means of attracting investors. He would tell people that he knew Luke Bryan, Tom Brady, and others as a means of impressing investors and garnering funds. Travis Aaron Wade – an actor and friend of Bryan – mentioned in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>He would be dating someone, a random girl that he met on Bumble or Tinder, and he would save their name as someone famous so that when his phone would ring, it would pop up as Angelina Jolie or whatever. The guy has two sides. His dark is dark, but his light is [really] light. It&#8217;s sad because you really do fall in love with him. He&#8217;s a great guy, but I see it as my responsibility to not let other people get taken advantage of.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Ending the Partnership</h2>
<p>Eventually, Bryan disappeared from the Producers Market’s website, and investors grew restless. It’s alleged that Bryan stole as much as $50K worth of digital tokens by selling them when the company had initially decided they were <em>not</em> to be sold or given away. This eventually caught the ugly eye of the company, who ended his advisory role and issued a cease-and-desist order to him. They company said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Mr. Bryan misrepresented our company without our knowledge, participation, or permission. When we found out, we immediately issued a cease-and-desist demand to him. This activity is unacceptable and not a reflection of our mission to support the well-being of farmers and our food systems.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/zachery-ty-bryan-from-child-star-to-potential-crypto-fraudster/">Zachery Ty Bryan: From Child Star to Alleged Crypto Fraudster</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PayPal Steps Away from Palestine; Is Bitcoin the Answer?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paypal-steps-away-from-palestine-is-bitcoin-the-answer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 17:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Palestine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78918</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin is getting very popular in Palestine and particularly in the Gaza Strip, the big reason being that PayPal has decided not to offer its services in this corner of the world. Palestine and BTC Get Close as PayPal Drives Away The reason PayPal isn’t setting foot in Palestine is because of the alleged dangers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paypal-steps-away-from-palestine-is-bitcoin-the-answer/">PayPal Steps Away from Palestine; Is Bitcoin the Answer?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin is getting very popular in Palestine and <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/06/23/why-bitcoin-cant-replace-paypal-in-palestine/?sh=79ef60c9db4c">particularly in the Gaza Strip</a>, the big reason being that PayPal has decided not to offer its services in this corner of the world.</p>
<h2>Palestine and BTC Get Close as PayPal Drives Away</h2>
<p>The reason <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/paypal/">PayPal</a> isn’t setting foot in Palestine is because of the alleged dangers that stem from endless conflict with its geographic neighbor Israel. At least 12 congressmen, at the time of writing, have signed a proposal supporting the financial company’s decision, which is now being enforced by its CEO Dan Schulman. The proposal they’ve signed reads as follows:</p>
<blockquote><p>PayPal has a responsibility to ensure its services and operations are provided in a non-discriminatory manner and in accordance with the United Nations Guiding Principles on Business and Human Rights.</p></blockquote>
<p>Without PayPal, the people of Palestine have had to find other ways of getting the items they need to survive… The goods and services necessary for everyday life. As a result, many have turned to bitcoin.</p>
<p>One of those people – Fadi Elsalameen – is a Palestinian activist and adjunct senior fellow at the Bitcoin Policy Institute. In an interview, Elsalameen commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>I stopped sending wires to Palestine and now only make payments with bitcoin. Bitcoin solves issues of high banking or transfer fees, or extreme and invasive government overreach and unfair treatment of Palestinians by international monetary organizations as in the case of PayPal.</p></blockquote>
<p>Eric Sype of 7amleh – a digital rights group in Palestine – shares this ideology. He believes PayPal has become extremely frustrating over the years, and that bitcoin’s popularity is growing thanks to the simplicity and levels of trust that surround it. He commented that while there are several individuals who are still skeptical of using bitcoin as a method of payment, tensions are easing slowly. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The vast majority of online freelance service providers exclusively use PayPal, so that cuts off many freelance opportunities for Palestinians.</p></blockquote>
<p>This is just another example of bitcoin’s original usage intent coming into play. Initially, when first created, bitcoin was designed as a payment tool. Something that could potentially replace all fiat currencies, checks, and credit cards down the line. However, its volatility has gotten in the way.</p>
<p>Thus, there are several companies out there that refuse to accept BTC as a payment method because they could wind up losing money, and there are still many people who don’t think to use it considering its lack of mainstream appeal.</p>
<h2>Making Things Easier</h2>
<p>Elsalameen, however, has hope that all this is going to change, and he says the opportunities that arise through bitcoin payment options are endless. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>I reach the account of those I need to send bitcoin to without anyone weaponizing my transactions against me. Today, I can even buy art in Palestine with bitcoin.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paypal-steps-away-from-palestine-is-bitcoin-the-answer/">PayPal Steps Away from Palestine; Is Bitcoin the Answer?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cameron Winklevoss: Buy BTC Now Before It Explodes</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cameron-winklevoss-buy-btc-now-before-it-explodes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 15:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cameron Winklevoss]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETF]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78916</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cameron Winklevoss – one half of the Winklevoss Twins who run the Gemini crypto exchange in New York – is confident bitcoin is about to burst out of its shell and reach a new bullish peak nobody is prepared for. Cameron Winklevoss on the Future of BTC&#8217;s Price At the end of June, the price [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cameron-winklevoss-buy-btc-now-before-it-explodes/">Cameron Winklevoss: Buy BTC Now Before It Explodes</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cameron Winklevoss – one half of the Winklevoss Twins who run the Gemini crypto exchange in New York – is confident bitcoin is <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/06/23/open-the-floodgates-crypto-billionaire-warns-the-window-is-closing-fast-amid-100-billion-bitcoin-and-ethereum-price-boom/?sh=650f482f1eef">about to burst out of</a> its shell and reach a new bullish peak nobody is prepared for.</p>
<h2>Cameron Winklevoss on the Future of BTC&#8217;s Price</h2>
<p>At the end of June, the price of bitcoin rose beyond $31,000. This is the highest bitcoin’s been all year, and certainly higher than where it was for most of 2022, arguably the most bearish period on record for the world’s number one digital currency by market cap. Cameron Winklevoss believes that if people are going to take advantage of bitcoin still being somewhat low, they need to get involved now. Otherwise, they’re going to be paying a lot more for units. In an interview, he commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>The great accumulation of bitcoin has begun. Anyone watching the flurry of ETF filings understands the window to purchase pre-IPO bitcoin before ETFs go live and open the floodgates is closing fast.</p></blockquote>
<p>The warning comes after BlackRock – one of the biggest financial investment companies in the world – announced it was planning to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blackrock-etf-application-causes-btc-eth-to-surge/">submit a bitcoin-based</a> exchange-traded fund (ETF) application to the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The news came as a surprise to many people for several reasons, a big one being that in the long run, BlackRock is considered a traditional finance company, and many of these institutions won’t go anywhere near crypto.</p>
<p>Another big reason is that the SEC is going after several crypto companies right now, huge ones like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sues-binance-alleges-selling-of-illegal-securities/">Binance</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-hit-with-sec-lawsuit-says-it-operated-as-an-exchange-broker/">Coinbase</a>. It’s become clear that the SEC doesn’t care who gets victimized so long as it can follow through on its agenda of eliminating crypto from America and having complete control.</p>
<p>However, many believe that BlackRock may pave the way for a bitcoin-based ETF (<a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-delays-its-decisions-on-several-btc-etfs/">something the SEC has</a> long rejected) thanks to its high-ranking record with the financial agency. Thus far, BlackRock has enjoyed over 500 accepted proposals with the SEC and only one rejection.</p>
<h2>This New ETF Could Really Pave the Way</h2>
<p>Markus Thielen – head of research at Matrix Port – was quick to agree with Cameron Winklevoss and believes the bulls may return sooner than investors think. Discussing the new ETF, he commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>While crypto still needs more than favorable macroeconomic tailwinds and institutional inflows into bitcoin, this is a welcoming development that reminds investors that crypto is here to stay. We can imagine that this BlackRock iShares &#8216;commodity&#8217; bitcoin ETF will attract an allocation in the range of around $20 billion to $50 billion over time as ETFs that are focusing on gold alone hold around $100 billion. This BlackRock announcement has a high probability of being approved by the SEC and will drive continuous adoption from institutional investors for bitcoin.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cameron-winklevoss-buy-btc-now-before-it-explodes/">Cameron Winklevoss: Buy BTC Now Before It Explodes</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>El Salvador Continues to Make Big Bitcoin Waves</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-continues-to-make-big-bitcoin-waves/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 13:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[El Salvador]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fold]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78909</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>El Salvador is really gaining traction as a leading bitcoin haven. El Salvador was Smart to Implement Bitcoin Not long ago, professional surfer Kelly Slater commented on social media: The government has really put an emphasis on surfing (and bitcoin). A crypto winter and bear market were both responsible for bitcoin shedding quite a bit [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-continues-to-make-big-bitcoin-waves/">El Salvador Continues to Make Big Bitcoin Waves</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>El Salvador is really gaining traction as a leading bitcoin haven.</p>
<h2>El Salvador was Smart to Implement Bitcoin</h2>
<p>Not long ago, professional surfer Kelly Slater commented on social media:</p>
<blockquote><p>The government has really put an emphasis on surfing (and bitcoin).</p></blockquote>
<p>A crypto winter and bear market were both responsible for bitcoin shedding quite a bit of value in 2022, and while we’re not entirely out of the woods yet, El Salvador continues to <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/06/21/emphasis-on-surf-and-bitcoin-attracts-investments-to-el-salvador/?sh=2c37c76671dc">gain a lot of talent</a> and business in terms of bitcoin companies that want to make the Central American nation the land of their homes.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/el-salvador/">El Salvador</a> has made a partner out of Fold, for example, a bitcoin rewards app. That company is now working hand in hand with Visa to help boost crypto payment options throughout Central and South America. Will Reeves, the CEO of Fold, explained in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>El Salvador really was the shining option for us there. There was no second-best option. Bukele has announced and implemented some very serious benefits to entities operating out of El Salvador. Not only protections, but incentives that are almost unmatched and especially unmatched in North America, Central America, and South America.</p></blockquote>
<p>U.S. ambassador to El Salvador Milena Mayorga also threw her two cents into the mix, claiming that the notions of bitcoin have attracted huge investments into the country thanks to the fact that crypto is now getting integrated into the nation’s politics.</p>
<p>For example, in April of this year, a new law was developed for crypto and tech companies. These businesses become exempt from both income and capital gains taxes for 15 years granted they invest funds into the nation’s infrastructure. Mayorga said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Every day, companies are calling us here at the embassy to ask us how they can transfer their operations. We try to get rid of the bureaucracy. We try to accompany them in different meetings, according to the needs of each company.</p></blockquote>
<p>Stacy Herbert – an advisor with Bitcoin Office – further mentioned that forming crypto companies in nations like El Salvador is quite easy, and the group is considering setting up shop there as a means of avoiding all the red tape and other troubles that come with the current U.S. landscape. She stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Company formation is also a lot easier now, as is the process of returning or moving to El Salvador with the removal of red tape and taxes.</p></blockquote>
<h2>So Many People Want to Move There</h2>
<p>According to Mayorga, several Americans are also looking to make their homes in the nation she represents. She says the country can offer them a lot of benefits and mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Many North Americans are asking for Salvadoran citizenship, and it&#8217;s one of the greatest interests worldwide. How can they obtain a residence or citizenship; how can they become Salvadoran.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-continues-to-make-big-bitcoin-waves/">El Salvador Continues to Make Big Bitcoin Waves</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
