<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 03:32:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ripple Price Analysis: Risk of A Drop Below $0.30</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-risk-of-a-drop-below-0-30/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-risk-of-a-drop-below-0-30/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 03:48:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76272</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple price started a fresh decline below the $0.3800 zone against the US dollar. The price is now trading below $0.3550 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.3400 on the 4-hours chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Bittrex). The pair could<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-risk-of-a-drop-below-0-30/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-risk-of-a-drop-below-0-30/">Ripple Price Analysis: Risk of A Drop Below $0.30</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ripple price started a fresh decline below the $0.3800 zone against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $0.3550 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.3400 on the 4-hours chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Bittrex).</li>
<li>The pair could extend losses if it stays below the $0.3500 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ripple price is struggling below $0.3550 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-drop-to-new-2022-lows/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. XRP price must stay above $0.3000 to avoid more downsides in the near term.</em></p>
<h2>Ripple Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, ripple price saw a bearish reaction below the $0.3800 zone against the US Dollar. The XRP/USD pair declined below the $0.3720 support zone to move into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>The price even traded below the $0.3550 level. Finally, there was a move below the $0.3200 level. The price traded as low as $0.3159 and is currently attempting an upside correction. The price is now trading below $0.3550 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-struggle-below-0-36/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near $0.3300. It is near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3800 swing high to $0.3159 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $0.3400 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.3400 on the 4-hours chart of the XRP/USD pair. The main resistance is near the $0.3500 zone. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3800 swing high to $0.3159 low.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $0.3480 and $0.3500 resistance zones might start a fresh increase. In the stated case, the price could even surpass the $0.3740 resistance. Any more gains might send the price towards the $0.400 resistance.</p>
<p>An initial support on the downside is near the $0.3200 level. The next major support is near the $0.3150 level, below which the price could even test the $0.300 support. Any more losses could lead the price towards the $0.2800 level, below which the price might even test $0.2650.</p>
<div id="attachment_76273" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Ripple.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76273" class="size-full wp-image-76273" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Ripple.png" alt="Ripple Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76273" class="wp-caption-text">Ripple Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, ripple price is now trading below the $0.355 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could extend losses if it stays below the $0.3000 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XRP/USD is now gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for XRP/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.3200, $0.3150 and $0.300.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.3400 and $0.3500.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-risk-of-a-drop-below-0-30/">Ripple Price Analysis: Risk of A Drop Below $0.30</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-risk-of-a-drop-below-0-30/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cathie Wood: FTX Has Done Harsh Damage to the Crypto Space</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-ftx-has-done-harsh-damage-to-the-crypto-space/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-ftx-has-done-harsh-damage-to-the-crypto-space/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cathie Wood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75714</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin bull and crypto investor Cathie Wood thinks the FTX debacle may have done irreparable damage to the crypto space, and she says the incident will likely make many institutional investors stay away for a long time. Cathie Wood Thinks the Damage Done by FTX Is Severe The FTX fiasco will go down as one<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-ftx-has-done-harsh-damage-to-the-crypto-space/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-ftx-has-done-harsh-damage-to-the-crypto-space/">Cathie Wood: FTX Has Done Harsh Damage to the Crypto Space</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin bull and crypto investor Cathie Wood <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/savingandinvesting/ark-invest-says-ftx-collapse-could-delay-institutional-crypto-adoption-by-years/ar-AA146Ma1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">thinks the</a> FTX debacle may have done irreparable damage to the crypto space, and she says the incident will likely make many institutional investors stay away for a long time.</p>
<h2>Cathie Wood Thinks the Damage Done by FTX Is Severe</h2>
<p>The FTX fiasco will go down as one of the biggest embarrassments of the arena. Long considered one of the greatest players in crypto, the company first came to fruition in 2019. It rose through the ranks and was one of the top digital currency trading platforms in the world. Its founder, Sam Bankman-Fried, was labeled a genius by many, though that reputation faded quickly in mid-November of last year.</p>
<p>FTX began <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">experiencing what it referred</a> to as a “liquidity crunch” during that time. It approached Binance as a means of staying afloat and tried to work out a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">deal where the larger</a> company purchased the smaller one. Sadly, things didn’t quite work out that way, and before long, FTX was filing bankruptcy <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">and its head executive</a> was resigning from his post. It was an ugly sight to watch.</p>
<p>Cathie Wood believes what’s happening with FTX will be the final nail in the coffin. She thinks this event will make several institutional traders turn away for good. She is also confident that this is going to pave the way for hardcore regulation that will make the crypto industry almost unrecognizable.</p>
<p>Wood stated in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>In our view, FTX’s insolvency is one of the most damaging events in crypto history. It could delay institutional crypto adoption by years and perhaps give regulators license to take draconian measures… ARK’s conviction in the long-term promise of public blockchains across money, finance, and the internet is not wavering. While the crypto asset market could labor under selling pressure and liquidity crunches in the short term, we believe this crisis is purging bad actors and will enhance the health of the crypto ecosystem with more transparency and decentralization in the longer term.</p></blockquote>
<p>There already appears to be some truth to what Wood is suggesting. Indeed, there have been huge and newfound calls for <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/biden-voices-support-for-crypto-regulation/" data-wpel-link="internal">crypto regulation following</a> what occurred with FTX. Many politicians and lawmakers claim that what happened with the exchange cannot happen again, and the only way to ensure this is by putting certain laws in place to keep users protected.</p>
<p>One of the people who is unsurprisingly calling for more regulation is democrat Massachusetts senator Elizabeth Warren. She’s <a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/senators-press-fidelity-to-reconsider-allowing-bitcoin-access-in-401k-plans-2022-11-21" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">even asking Fidelity to</a> go back on its 401K and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fidelity-is-still-taking-flak-for-its-crypto-offerings/" data-wpel-link="internal">crypto retirement propositions</a> following the exchange’s collapse.</p>
<h2>Congress Needs to Get Its Act Together</h2>
<p>She mentioned in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>The implosion of FTX must be a wake-up call for Congress and financial regulators to hold this industry and its executives accountable. Too much of the crypto industry is smoke and mirrors.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-ftx-has-done-harsh-damage-to-the-crypto-space/">Cathie Wood: FTX Has Done Harsh Damage to the Crypto Space</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-ftx-has-done-harsh-damage-to-the-crypto-space/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Customers May Say Bye to Their Money for Good</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-customers-may-be-saying-bye-to-their-money-forever/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-customers-may-be-saying-bye-to-their-money-forever/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 15:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bankruptcy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mt Gox]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75710</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FTX caused a lot of nasty spillage and other problems in late 2022. Here we are in 2023, and unfortunately, the final remnants of what will likely be labeled a huge bad actor and very poor player in the crypto economy continues to wreak havoc on the space and on customers. FTX Customers May Not<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-customers-may-be-saying-bye-to-their-money-forever/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-customers-may-be-saying-bye-to-their-money-forever/">FTX Customers May Say Bye to Their Money for Good</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FTX caused a lot of nasty spillage and other problems in late 2022. Here we are in 2023, and unfortunately, the final remnants of what will likely be labeled a huge bad actor and very poor player in the crypto economy continues to <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/customers-of-bankrupt-ftx-may-never-get-their-crypto-back/ar-AA145SEK" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wreak havoc on the space</a> and on customers.</p>
<h2>FTX Customers May Not Get Their Funds Back</h2>
<p>It has been suggested by many analysts and traders that the company’s users will not get their money back. That’s right… Whatever funds they lost due to the firm’s mismanagement of their funds are potentially gone forever.</p>
<p>While this isn’t necessarily set in stone yet, it’s being suggested based on information from the infamous <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/mt-gox/" data-wpel-link="internal">Mt. Gox</a> fiasco that took place in 2014. At nearly nine years old (the incident occurred in February of 2014), Mt. Gox filed bankruptcy after allegedly losing more than $400 million in BTC funds, and those bankruptcy proceedings are still ongoing today.</p>
<p>This suggests that filing bankruptcy in the crypto space is a complicated matter. Thus, many industry heads believe that it will be a long time before FTX players ever see a dime of their money, and that’s assuming they ever see anything at all.</p>
<p>St. Johns University law professor Anthony Sabino is confident that while these customers will get some of their money back, they will never see their full stashes again. He also said that many of the assets they stored on the platform are likely to experience further price dips as the FTX drama continues to take hold of the space. In an interview, he commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>People are going to be waiting on the sidelines for a very long time, and only heaven knows what it&#8217;s going to be worth. It does not look good at all.</p></blockquote>
<p>One of the more unique aspects of FTX is that while its bankruptcy proceedings are occurring, the company is being investigated by agencies like the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Joshua Peck – an alleged expert on crypto risk – says that while these investigations won’t delay the bankruptcy, the judge overseeing the cases is going to pay very close attention to what’s uncovered.</p>
<p>He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I expect the FTX bankruptcy to take a decade or more for the process to sort out what assets remain and who owns them.</p></blockquote>
<p>Referring to the Mt. Gox debacle to support his argument, Peck stated that that company exists all over again in something like FTX. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>The Mt. Gox bankruptcy is the precedent here. That bankruptcy started in 2014 and is still ongoing.</p></blockquote>
<h2>The Trouble Began Two Months Ago</h2>
<p>FTX first began encountering difficulties in mid-November. This caused the company to seek aid from Binance, who <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">appeared to be on the verge</a> of buying the enterprise.</p>
<p>This <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">didn’t happen however</a>, and FTX has since fallen into oblivion.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-customers-may-be-saying-bye-to-their-money-forever/">FTX Customers May Say Bye to Their Money for Good</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-customers-may-be-saying-bye-to-their-money-forever/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>2023 Has Arrived. Will It Be a Good Year for Bitcoin?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/2023-has-arrived-will-it-be-a-good-year-for-bitcoin/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/2023-has-arrived-will-it-be-a-good-year-for-bitcoin/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 13:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75707</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>2023 has finally arrived. Happy New Year to all digital currency enthusiasts out there! Here’s to hoping that all bitcoin players are greeted with kinder, gentler, and more loving maneuvers to their crypto stashes than what was doled out in 2022. Could Bitcoin Recover Soon? To say 2022 was a bad year for crypto would<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/2023-has-arrived-will-it-be-a-good-year-for-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/2023-has-arrived-will-it-be-a-good-year-for-bitcoin/">2023 Has Arrived. Will It Be a Good Year for Bitcoin?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>2023 has finally arrived. Happy New Year to all digital currency enthusiasts out there! Here’s to hoping that all bitcoin players are greeted with kinder, gentler, and more loving maneuvers to their crypto stashes than what was doled out in 2022.</p>
<h2>Could Bitcoin Recover Soon?</h2>
<p>To say 2022 was a bad year for crypto would be a huge understatement. It was by far one of the most bearish periods ever to strike the space, and many argued that assets <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paul-krugman-btc-is-on-the-verge-of-disappearing/" data-wpel-link="internal">like BTC were on the verge</a> of collapsing for good. While it doesn’t look like we’re quite there yet, the asset no doubt experienced one of its harshest beatings, and it’s going to take a while for the world’s number one digital currency by market cap – and the space in general – to heal up.</p>
<p><a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Bitcoin</a>, back in November of 2021, was trading at a whopping $68,000 per unit. This was a new all-time high for the cryptocurrency, and many believed it was in a place that could never be brought down. Boy were they wrong!</p>
<p>The crypto asset began a series of falls as soon as 2022 rang in. From there, the currency fell into the $40K range, then $30K, and before long, $20K was knocking at its door. Within just a few months, the world’s primary form of crypto had lost more than 70 percent of its value, and things didn’t end there.</p>
<p>2022 was marred by many bad actors, one of which was FTX, which caused the price of bitcoin and many of its altcoin cousins to fall even further. FTX will probably go down as one of the biggest blunders to ever occur within the confines of the space, and it’s likely turned a lot of high-scale investors off to crypto investing for good.</p>
<p>Widely labeled as one of the big golden players in the industry, the FTX exchange was only three years old, yet rose to prominence as one of the biggest digital currency trading platforms in the world. Its founder and head executive, Sam Bankman-Fried, was considered a genius by many, and his net worth stood beyond the $16 billion mark prior to the company’s collapse.</p>
<h2>Let&#8217;s Hope Things Change</h2>
<p>Sadly, this reputation faded quickly as the company experienced a liquidity crunch in mid-November of last year, which caused it <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">to seek aid from larger</a> competitor Binance. While it looked like the bigger firm was going to buy out the smaller one, things didn’t work out that way. Before long, FTX had joined a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">long list of bankrupt crypto</a> players and its founder was resigning from his post in shame.</p>
<p>With a new year comes new trends, however, so let’s join hands in hoping that 2023 proves to be a year of recovery and good fortune for all crypto fans.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/2023-has-arrived-will-it-be-a-good-year-for-bitcoin/">2023 Has Arrived. Will It Be a Good Year for Bitcoin?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/2023-has-arrived-will-it-be-a-good-year-for-bitcoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Can Bitcoin Look Forward to in 2023?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-can-bitcoin-look-forward-to-in-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-can-bitcoin-look-forward-to-in-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 17:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2023]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75577</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin had a very harsh year in 2022. Can we expect 2023 to be any better now that it’s about to enter the fray? The Bitcoin Price Had It Really Hard This Year We are literally hours away from greeting 2023, and we can’t help but reflect on what a year 2022 has been for<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-can-bitcoin-look-forward-to-in-2023/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-can-bitcoin-look-forward-to-in-2023/">What Can Bitcoin Look Forward to in 2023?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin had a very harsh year in 2022. Can we expect 2023 to be any better now that it’s about to enter the fray?</p>
<h2>The Bitcoin Price Had It Really Hard This Year</h2>
<p>We are literally hours away from greeting 2023, and we can’t help but reflect on what a year 2022 has been for the world’s number one digital currency by market cap. The crypto space has had extreme difficulty staying at the top of its game these last 12 months, and many of us are surprised that bitcoin and its crypto cousins are still around, ready and willing to play.</p>
<p>In this sense, we can be grateful that bitcoin has matured enough that it’s able to withstand the harsh conditions it’s endured. At the same time, we can’t help but reflect on how bearish this period has been, and we truly hope things improve now that the new year has arrived.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a> price has taken its biggest beating since it first rose to prominence 14 years ago. The world’s number one digital currency rose to a whopping $68,000 per unit, for example, in November of last year. The currency hit a new peak and it looked like it suddenly had newfound power that was never going to fade, but we couldn’t have been more wrong.</p>
<p>Sadly, 2022 started on a weak note in that the currency fell into the $40K range, nearly $20,000 less than where it had been just two months prior. From there, the currency endured a long string of losses that ultimately brought it down to its present price, which lies in the $16K arena. It’s a sad and ugly sight to see, and one that has permeated the entire crypto space, causing it to lose more than $2 trillion in valuation in just the last few months.</p>
<p>In many ways, 2022 is comparable to 2018, though the damage has been far greater than what occurred four years ago. This is primarily because bitcoin has grown so much since that bear year, but there is also some good news in that 2019 brought a strong level of recovery from 2018, and with so many 2018 patterns showing themselves in 2022, perhaps we can expect 2019’s recovery to appear again in 2023.</p>
<h2>So Many Companies Fell</h2>
<p>Many companies have fallen victim to the crypto crash that endured. Earlier today, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-top-bitcoin-and-crypto-stories-of-2022/" data-wpel-link="internal">we published a piece</a> talking about all the companies that filed bankruptcy thanks to the ongoing speculation and volatility. We’ve also seen several firms – <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-just-bought-more-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">like MicroStrategy</a> – fall heavily into debt due to their love of BTC.</p>
<p>There is a lot of healing that now needs to happen, and we’re confident that 2023 can at least bring us a small taste of that healing. Let’s keep our fingers crossed and hope for the absolute best over the next 12 months.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-can-bitcoin-look-forward-to-in-2023/">What Can Bitcoin Look Forward to in 2023?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-can-bitcoin-look-forward-to-in-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Top Bitcoin and Crypto Stories of 2022</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-top-bitcoin-and-crypto-stories-of-2022/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-top-bitcoin-and-crypto-stories-of-2022/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 15:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celsius]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75574</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>2022 is on the verge of disappearing forever, and Live Bitcoin News is looking back one last time on the biggest digital currency stories of the year. The Bitcoin Price The biggest story of 2022 revolved around how poorly bitcoin did. What was once one of the largest and most worthwhile assets around sank to<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-top-bitcoin-and-crypto-stories-of-2022/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-top-bitcoin-and-crypto-stories-of-2022/">The Top Bitcoin and Crypto Stories of 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>2022 is on the verge of disappearing forever, and <em>Live Bitcoin News</em> is looking back one last time on the biggest digital currency stories of the year.</p>
<h2>The Bitcoin Price</h2>
<p>The biggest story of 2022 revolved around how poorly bitcoin did. What was once one of the largest and most worthwhile assets around sank to the bottom of a deep financial pit, and the currency has refused to get up. In November of last year, for example, the world’s number one digital currency by market cap rose to a whopping $68,000 per unit, the largest it’s ever been.</p>
<p>From there, however, the currency began to endure a series of dips that have taken it to its current price. At the time of writing, one unit of bitcoin has fallen into the mid-$16K range. That’s a loss of more than 70 percent. In addition, the entire crypto space has followed suit, and the arena has lost more than $2 trillion in overall valuation.</p>
<h2>Bankruptcies Galore</h2>
<p>Due to the crash of bitcoin and ongoing volatility and speculation, many <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-in-the-age-of-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">crypto and blockchain-based</a> companies endured horrific circumstances that caused them to engage in behaviors which made several traders raise their eyebrows in shock and disgust. Many investors didn’t know that these initial maneuvers were the beginning of something worse, and that many of these enterprises were either on their way out or were on the verge of entering bankruptcy.</p>
<p>Perhaps the biggest name to come to mind in this category is lending network Celsius, which in the summer, stirred fear in the hearts of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/another-mega-bitcoin-crash-is-in-the-books/" data-wpel-link="internal">traders after it halted</a> all withdrawals as a means of dealing with the ongoing crypto price swirls. From there, however, the company was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/celsius-network-is-next-crypto-company-to-file-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">quick to file bankruptcy</a> so that it could explore other options of staying in business and satisfying customers while avoiding the angry faces of lenders.</p>
<p>Many other digital currency companies took the same path. Among the other firms to crash and burn this year were <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-lender-voyager-digital-files-chapter-11-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">Voyager Digital</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-mining-firm-compute-north-files-for-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">Compute North</a>, and hedge fund <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-hedge-fund-three-arrows-capital-is-now-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">Three Arrows Capital</a>.</p>
<h2>FTX – The Fall of an Empire</h2>
<p>In mid-November, the crypto world was dealt a harsh blow when FTX – one of the largest and most powerful digital currency trading platforms around – <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">entered bankruptcy</a>. The company was widely considered the golden boy of the crypto arena, and its founder – Sam Bankman-Fried – was lauded as a genius by many, but an investigation into the firm following its bankruptcy filings and the resignation of its head executive shows a company that has long been mismanaged.</p>
<p>Investor funds were played with and used to buy luxury homes in the Bahamas for company employees, while virtually no <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/john-ray-iii-ftx-is-the-most-mismanaged-company-ive-ever-seen/" data-wpel-link="internal">business structure could</a> be uncovered by John Ray III, the lawyer called in to clean up FTX’s mess.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-top-bitcoin-and-crypto-stories-of-2022/">The Top Bitcoin and Crypto Stories of 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-top-bitcoin-and-crypto-stories-of-2022/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Evan Luthra, a Victim of Crypto Exchange FTX, Shares His Story</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/evan-luthra-a-victim-of-crypto-exchange-ftx-shares-his-story/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/evan-luthra-a-victim-of-crypto-exchange-ftx-shares-his-story/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 13:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evan Luthra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75579</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The FTX disaster was something nobody saw coming, and now one investor – a young man named Evan Luthra – has described the debacle he’s endured after losing nearly $2 million in crypto funds following the collapse of one of the biggest and most powerful crypto trading platforms in the world. Evan Luthra Has Lost<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/evan-luthra-a-victim-of-crypto-exchange-ftx-shares-his-story/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/evan-luthra-a-victim-of-crypto-exchange-ftx-shares-his-story/">Evan Luthra, a Victim of Crypto Exchange FTX, Shares His Story</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The FTX disaster was something nobody saw coming, and <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/ftx-investor-calls-crypto-exchange-decline-big-lesson-says-lawmakers-should-return-funds-to-victims/ar-AA14jkd7" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">now one investor</a> – a young man named Evan Luthra – has described the debacle he’s endured after losing nearly $2 million in crypto funds following the collapse of one of the biggest and most powerful crypto trading platforms in the world.</p>
<h2>Evan Luthra Has Lost a Lot of Money</h2>
<p>UBS Americas CEO Robert Wolf recently labeled FTX as a “Ponzi scheme.” Millions of investors have seen their money completely vanish after it’s been shown that FTX <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/john-ray-iii-ftx-is-the-most-mismanaged-company-ive-ever-seen/" data-wpel-link="internal">used customer funds</a> to purchase items like luxury condominiums in the Bahamas. Luthra himself lost quite a bit, and now he’s sharing his story to help others learn from what’s happened. In a recent discussion with <em>FOX News</em>, he said:</p>
<blockquote><p>This is a big lesson for everybody in the crypto community. It&#8217;s a big, strong lesson [of] not your keys, not your crypto. If you don&#8217;t hold the keys to crypto, it&#8217;s not really your money.</p></blockquote>
<p>Sam Bankman-Fried – the man behind the exchange – is believed to have pocketed as much as $300 million from investors. In his interview, Luthra slammed the former CEO, claiming that he’s nothing but a criminal and that everything that occurred with FTX did so because he and his fellow executives wanted it to happen. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>This was all intentionally done. This was a very calculated plan, or I should say a crime that has taken place… You could have a car manufacturer who cut some corners and then defrauded the industry. Doesn&#8217;t mean electric vehicles are bad. So, it&#8217;s like bitcoin by itself. The fundamentals are still very strong and if you have bitcoin in your hard wallet, in your hand, you have not lost any money today… From all this, I&#8217;ve already come to realize that Sam Bankman-Fried is a bad actor, here. We already know that this is a bad actor, this is a fraud, [and] this is a criminal.</p></blockquote>
<p>Many are calling for a fund to be established to help the victims of the fallen company. Also, several <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-gave-a-lot-of-money-to-democrats-what-will-they-do-with-it/" data-wpel-link="internal">democrat politicians accepted</a> money from FTX, and they’re now being pressured to give it back.</p>
<h2>This was a Criminal Act</h2>
<p>Luthra doesn’t blame the politicians for taking the money as he’s convinced that they weren’t aware of the company’s dirty dealings or criminal behavior. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>You can&#8217;t blame the government for accepting donations without knowing that this was going to be criminal. You can&#8217;t really blame anybody in this case except Sam Bankman-Fried who is cruel, who intentionally planned and executed a fraud against the whole community, but the right thing would be for them to give the funds back. Whoever got the donations, and it should go back to the victims whose funds it really is. This was never his money to give away. This was our money.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/evan-luthra-a-victim-of-crypto-exchange-ftx-shares-his-story/">Evan Luthra, a Victim of Crypto Exchange FTX, Shares His Story</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/evan-luthra-a-victim-of-crypto-exchange-ftx-shares-his-story/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Does Edward Snowden Have a Big BTC Stash?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/does-edward-snowden-have-a-big-btc-stash/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/does-edward-snowden-have-a-big-btc-stash/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 17:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[edward snowden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[russia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75705</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Edward Snowden – the U.S. intelligence leaker now living in Moscow – hinted he has quite a few bitcoins to his name, and that he’s got enough to live on “until the f*cking sun dies.&#8221; How Much BTC Does Edward Snowden Own? Since he left the country, many entrepreneurs in Silicon Valley have been sending<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/does-edward-snowden-have-a-big-btc-stash/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/does-edward-snowden-have-a-big-btc-stash/">Does Edward Snowden Have a Big BTC Stash?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Edward Snowden – the U.S. intelligence leaker now living in Moscow – hinted he has <a href="https://money.yahoo.com/snowden-bitcoin-holdings-151914599.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">quite a few bitcoins</a> to his name, and that he’s got enough to live on “until the f*cking sun dies.&#8221;</p>
<h2>How Much BTC Does Edward Snowden Own?</h2>
<p>Since he left the country, many entrepreneurs in Silicon Valley have been sending him bitcoin and crypto units so he could stay afloat. This has turned into a vast and considerable sum over the years, and Snowden appears to be living well thanks to the amount of crypto he’s accumulated.</p>
<p>In October, Snowden made a special panel appearance via satellite and was asked if he was “bitcoin rich.” He laughed this off, claiming that what everyone has read about his alleged bitcoin stash might not be true. While he didn’t give a straight answer, he hinted that his ties to crypto could have been forged and were initially based on a comment that was never meant to go public. This puts things in a weird loop and doesn’t allow crypto fans to fully understand what’s going on.</p>
<p>In the interview, he said:</p>
<blockquote><p>So, one thing I would say [is] don’t trust everything you read in the press. Secondly, that [bitcoin comment] was a private comment that wasn’t meant to be published, but look, my advice is as a privacy advocate. If anybody asks you what crypto you have, what you hold, the answer is, ‘What is crypto?’ but I’m not at risk of going hungry, certainly not this year. Let’s put it that way.</p></blockquote>
<p><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/edward-snowden/" data-wpel-link="internal">Snowden</a> stirred controversy roughly ten years ago when allegations from the U.S. government came about that he had removed more than one million classified documents from various U.S. systems in 2012 and 2013. At the time, Snowden was working as an NSA contractor in Hawaii. He’s believed to have provided over 200,000 of those documents to foreign entities and journalists before fleeing to Russia.</p>
<p>Not long after he fled the U.S., Kremlin-linked lawyer Anatoly Kucherena explained that Snowden was on the verge of building a “new life in Russia.” The attorney also commented that Snowden would hold an IT job with an unnamed enterprise in the country, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>Edward Snowden will begin working in one of the biggest Russian companies. His job will be to provide support and develop one of Russia’s biggest websites.</p></blockquote>
<h2>He&#8217;s Pretty Active</h2>
<p>One would think a man like Snowden would do everything to maintain a low profile, but this isn’t quite the case. In fact, he’s quite active on Twitter, and boasts a following of more than five million people. Following <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">the fall of FTX</a> he mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>There&#8217;s still a lot of trouble ahead, but for the first time in a while, I&#8217;m starting to feel the itch to scale back in.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/does-edward-snowden-have-a-big-btc-stash/">Does Edward Snowden Have a Big BTC Stash?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/does-edward-snowden-have-a-big-btc-stash/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>VISION OF BLOCKCHAIN (VOB) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vision-of-blockchain-vob-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vision-of-blockchain-vob-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 16:53:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76256</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec 30, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed VISION OF BLOCKCHAIN (VOB) on December 30, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the VOB/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading. By providing a stable token economy and opportunities to generate profits worldwide, ONE BIT<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vision-of-blockchain-vob-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vision-of-blockchain-vob-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">VISION OF BLOCKCHAIN (VOB) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec 30, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed VISION OF BLOCKCHAIN (VOB) on December 30, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the VOB/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading.</p>
<p>By providing a stable token economy and opportunities to generate profits worldwide, ONE BIT TEN creates a more advanced platform with its customized AI for trading solutions based on accurate information. Its native token <a href="https://bscscan.com/token/0xdb83921D152f362b8Ae79a1C2ddC33a5588924f7" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">VISION OF BLOCKCHAIN</a> (VOB) has been listed on LBank Exchange at 6:00 UTC on December 30, 2022, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision.</p>
<p><strong>Introducing </strong><strong>ONE BIT TEN</strong></p>
<p>ONE BIT TEN is a startup-sized company whose goal is to globally expand the trading platform through accurate information by combining and processing data based on the trading volume of CEX, DEX, and OTC markets in distributed supercomputers.</p>
<p>One of the major projects of ONE BIT TEN is ONEBOT. It’s an automated computer program designed to execute specific tasks with minimal human intervention. In the world of cryptocurrency, cryptocurrency transaction bots aim to provide AI Trading Indicators and automated transaction bots that automatically trade one or more cryptocurrencies on one or more platforms on behalf of the owner or user to minimize risk and help achieve maximum individual goals.</p>
<p>In the exchange, Tokens&#8217; transaction volume, ask and bid volumes, wallet movement, and numerous past data are combined to discard dummy data and process practical data only. A well performing leading index and trading bot are profitable. It is proven how well ONEBOT has combined automatic and manual trading strategies with monitoring system, which suggests the most efficient leading index and trading bot for trends supported by the user growth.</p>
<p>In short, ONEBOT can import, analyze, and use customized or other exchanges&#8217; trading strategy data to automate trading executions. ONEBOT is classified as a margin trading bot, a leverage bot, and a spot trading bot by using automated and smart technologies such as AI and machine learning, helping investors to maximize profits by efficiently acting as an auxiliary indicator.</p>
<p>ONEBOT is increasing the number of users by delivering constantly efficient data. In that process, ONT BIT TEN provides a more advanced platform by building an ecosystem with technological advancement and ONE BIT TEN&#8217;s Token. Furthermore, the project will provide stable Token Economy and revenue generation opportunities through the activation of NFT.</p>
<p>With all technological approaches to machine learning and deep learning, ONE BIT TEN will continue to develop aggressive development and marketing for global top-tier products in areas related to trading investments. In addition, ONE BIT TEN will further develop and strategically cooperate with developers who are globally distributed, participating in voluntary development, and even supercomputer projects that can handle a lot of data in higher speed.</p>
<p><strong>About VOB Token</strong></p>
<p>VISION OF BLOCKCHAIN (VOB) is the native token of ONE BIT TEN ecosystem. As VOB Token is used as a payment method, users will be able to gain greater flexibility in the application of usage. In addition, ONEBOT will increase flexibility and brand awareness by issuing VOB Token and using it as a payment. This will increase the adoption rate of platform for new members by securing abundant liquidity and enhancing security.</p>
<p>Based on BEP-20, VOB has a total supply of 300 million (i.e., 300,000,000) tokens, of which 1% is provided for presale ,10% is allocated to the management team, 14% is provided for the community, 20% is allocated for the ecosystem, 18% will be used for marketing, 6% is allocated to partners, 7% is allocated to the team and advisors, 9% will be used for development, 5% will be auto-burned, and the remaining 10% is reserved.</p>
<p>VOB token has been listed on LBank Exchange at 6:00 UTC on December 30, 2022, investors who are interested in the ONE BIT TEN investment can easily buy and sell VOB token on LBank Exchange right now. The listing of VOB token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p>
<p><strong>Learn More about</strong><strong> VOB Token:</strong></p>
<p>Official Website: <a href="http://www.vobc.io" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.vobc.io</a><br />
Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/onebittenglobal" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://t.me/onebittenglobal</a><br />
Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/1BIT_10" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/1BIT_10</a><br />
Instagram: <a href="https://www.instagram.com/onebitten_kr/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.instagram.com/onebitten_kr/</a><br />
Facebook: <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ONE-BIT-TEN-105686928470145" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://www.facebook.com/ONE-BIT-TEN-105686928470145</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vision-of-blockchain-vob-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">VISION OF BLOCKCHAIN (VOB) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vision-of-blockchain-vob-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
