<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 13:16:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Stable Coin Tether Buys Over $200 Million Worth of BTC</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stable-coin-tether-buys-over-200-million-worth-of-btc/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stable-coin-tether-buys-over-200-million-worth-of-btc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paolo Ardoino]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tether]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78372</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Executives behind the stable currency Tether – which is not only popular, but also somewhat controversial – have announced they just bought more than $200 million worth of bitcoin as a means of backing their digital currency. Tether and Bitcoin&#8230; Together Again A stable currency is a digital currency that’s not subjected to the same<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stable-coin-tether-buys-over-200-million-worth-of-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stable-coin-tether-buys-over-200-million-worth-of-btc/">Stable Coin Tether Buys Over $200 Million Worth of BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Executives behind the stable currency Tether – which is not only popular, but also somewhat controversial – have <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/tether-buys-222-million-worth-of-bitcoin-to-back-its-usdt-stablecoin/ar-AA1bj6a1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced they just bought</a> more than $200 million worth of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a> as a means of backing their digital currency.</p>
<h2>Tether and Bitcoin&#8230; Together Again</h2>
<p>A stable currency is a digital currency that’s not subjected to the same volatility and speculative nature that one often sees with more mainstream cryptos, such as bitcoin and Ethereum. What makes them stable is that they are often supported by various forms of collateral, whether they be gold (or other precious metals) or fiat currencies like USD, the yen, or the yuan. Thus, they tend to retain their dollar pegs and don’t go crashing into oblivion like so many other assets have done in the past. One unit of a stable currency is often worth $1.</p>
<p>There are many kinds of stable coins out there, and Tether is arguably one of the biggest and most well-known. The goal amongst company members is to “diversify” reserves backing the token. The currency has been on a serious bull run since the early portion of the year, accumulating a net profit of close to $1.5 billion last March. It is also said that Tether reserves are near $2.5 billion.</p>
<p>Tether CTO Paolo Ardoino explained in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>The decision to invest in bitcoin, the world&#8217;s first and largest cryptocurrency, is underpinned by its strength and potential as an investment asset. Bitcoin has continually proven its resilience and has emerged as a long-term store of value with substantial growth potential. Its limited supply, decentralized nature, and widespread adoption have positioned bitcoin as a favored choice among institutional and retail investors alike.</p></blockquote>
<p>This would all be fine and dandy except back in 2019, Texas professor John Griffin <a href="https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=3195066" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">unveiled a report that</a> explained the full bull run of 2017 and the subsequent bear run in 2018 that occurred for the crypto industry. The report alleges that many Tether holders used their units to purchase BTC, thus tying the stable currency to the asset and keeping it afloat. This is what ultimately helped BTC reach $20K (it’s then all-time high) in the year 2017, though it also contributed greatly to the crash that followed the next year.</p>
<h2>Could This Be Problematic?</h2>
<p>While the circumstances are somewhat different this time around, the situation is virtually the same in that Tether and bitcoin are being tied together. Last time, Tether was supporting bitcoin. This time, bitcoin is supporting Tether. Could the reversal of the roles inherently cause bitcoin to fall again like it did five years ago? It’s a scary thought for many.</p>
<p>Previously, Tether held many of its reserves in commercial paper, which wasn’t considered safe, though it wound down its holdings to zero last February.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stable-coin-tether-buys-over-200-million-worth-of-btc/">Stable Coin Tether Buys Over $200 Million Worth of BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stable-coin-tether-buys-over-200-million-worth-of-btc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Scammer Mona Montrage Arrested in the U.K.</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-scammer-mona-montrage-arrested-in-the-u-k/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-scammer-mona-montrage-arrested-in-the-u-k/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 15:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scam]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mona Montrage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[romance scam]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78370</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mona Faiz Montrage – an influencer on Instagram that’s originally from Ghana, but now lives in New Jersey – has been arrested for allegedly taking part in a romance scam that saw several old men send her lavish gifts including prepaid cards and cryptocurrency. Mona Montrage Sent to Court According to her Instagram page, Montrage<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-scammer-mona-montrage-arrested-in-the-u-k/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-scammer-mona-montrage-arrested-in-the-u-k/">Crypto Scammer Mona Montrage Arrested in the U.K.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mona Faiz Montrage – an influencer on Instagram that’s originally from Ghana, but now lives in New Jersey – <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/05/16/us/mona-montrage-alleged-romance-scammer-cec/index.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">has been arrested for</a> allegedly taking part in a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/romance-scam/" data-wpel-link="internal">romance scam</a> that saw several old men send her lavish gifts including prepaid cards and cryptocurrency.</p>
<h2>Mona Montrage Sent to Court</h2>
<p>According to her Instagram page, Montrage is an influencer who’s part of the African music scene. Many of her 4.2 million fans are under the impression that she often spends time in London and Accra, the capital of her native country of Ghana.</p>
<p>However, court documents reveal this may not be the case, and that she is in fact part of a large cybercrime ring in West Africa that thus far, has seen more than $2 million stolen from older (and vulnerable) American citizens, many of whom are in their 80s. Not long ago, Montrage was arrested in the United Kingdom and extradited to New York, where she made her first court appearance.</p>
<p>Thus far, she has pleaded not guilty to all the charges laid against her including conspiracy to commit wire fraud, conspiracy to receive stolen money, and money laundering. She’s 30 years of age and has allegedly been engaging in this scam-like behavior since 2013. She and her cronies would often reach out to the victims via dating apps and after earning their trust, would get them to believe that there was romance in the future. Papers detailing the indictment read:</p>
<blockquote><p>Once members of the enterprise had successfully convinced victims that they were in a romantic relationship and had gained their trust, they convinced the victims, under false pretenses, to transfer money to bank accounts the victims believed were controlled by their romantic interests, when, in fact, the bank accounts were controlled by members of the enterprise.</p></blockquote>
<p>In one instance, she took the scam so far that she sent her victim a tribal marriage certificate from Ghana, getting him to believe that they were officially and legally bound. The documents continue with:</p>
<blockquote><p>Montrage sent the victim a tribal marriage certificate purporting to show that Montrage and the victim had been married in Ghana.</p></blockquote>
<p>She got this victim to send close to $90,000 to her through a collection of payments. In another instance, she received close to $200K from a separate victim. Michael J. Driscoll – the FBI assistant director in charge – commented on how common romance scams have become. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Romance scams – especially those that target older individuals – are of major concern.</p></blockquote>
<h2>This Is Too Common</h2>
<p>The Federal Trade Commission (FTC) also threw its two cents in, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>These scammers pay close attention to the information you share, and don’t miss a beat becoming your perfect match. You like a thing, so that’s their thing, too. You’re looking to settle down.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-scammer-mona-montrage-arrested-in-the-u-k/">Crypto Scammer Mona Montrage Arrested in the U.K.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-scammer-mona-montrage-arrested-in-the-u-k/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Popular Strategies For Playing Crypto Slots</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/popular-strategies-for-playing-crypto-slots/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/popular-strategies-for-playing-crypto-slots/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Guest]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 13:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Guest Article]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78983</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Today, cryptocurrency slot machines are a captivating online gambling type gaining popularity. These crypto slots operate similarly to conventional slot machines. Instead of relying on traditional money, they employ digital currencies like Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Litecoin to wager and engage in slot machine gameplay. Their decentralized nature sets them apart, eliminating the need for a<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/popular-strategies-for-playing-crypto-slots/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/popular-strategies-for-playing-crypto-slots/">Popular Strategies For Playing Crypto Slots</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Today, cryptocurrency slot machines are a captivating online gambling type gaining popularity. These crypto slots operate similarly to conventional slot machines. Instead of relying on traditional money, they employ digital currencies like Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Litecoin to wager and engage in slot machine gameplay.</p>
<p>Their decentralized nature sets them apart, eliminating the need for a central authority. Despite this distinction, these games offer enhanced security, transparency, and global accessibility to players.</p>
<p>Additionally, they incorporate various innovative technologies into their systems and present promising prospects. Hence, this article delves into practical techniques to enhance your winning possibilities in cryptocurrency-based slot games, enabling you to <a href="https://www.ccn.com/crypto-slots/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">play slots with crypto using similar strategy</a>.</p>
<h4>Strategies For Winning Crypto Slot Games</h4>
<p>Achieving success in crypto casinos&#8217; slot games is a relatively simple process. Nevertheless, enhancing your earnings in these casinos requires careful consideration and implementing specific methods. Let&#8217;s explore practical strategies to improve your winning odds when participating in Bitcoin casino games.</p>
<h4>Gain Insight into the Game</h4>
<p>A comprehensive understanding of the game you are engaging in is <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/why-use-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">essential to succeeding in Bitcoin</a> slots. Familiarizing oneself with the rules, payout charts, and relevant information before placing any bets is vital.</p>
<p>Additionally, certain games may encompass concealed conditions and agreements that necessitate exploration before achieving victory on the platform.</p>
<p>By grasping the intricacies of a game, players can make well-informed decisions and avoid costly blunders. It is unwise to rely on assumptions when partaking in these games; instead, conduct thorough research to ascertain effective strategies for gameplay.</p>
<p>To enhance your gaming journey, exploring blogs and seeking guidance from experienced players who can provide valuable insights and knowledge is beneficial.</p>
<h4>Make Use of Free Play</h4>
<p>Numerous online casinos provide a free-play alternative, enabling you to try out games without wagering real money. Regrettably, individuals accustomed to other Bitcoin games perceive the free trial session as unnecessary. As a result, these players often choose to bypass this section whenever it appears on their screen.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, the free trial presents an excellent opportunity to familiarize yourself with the game mechanics, features, and bonuses. You can play with actual currency once you become comfortable with the game. Fully explore the game options in their accessible trial mode before committing to any Bitcoin slot game.</p>
<h4>Developing a financial strategy and adhering to it</h4>
<p>By establishing a well-defined financial plan and sticking to predetermined boundaries, one can steer clear of the potentially habit-forming allure of gambling. Begin by determining the maximum amount you are willing and able to lose and committing not to exceed that sum.</p>
<p>This financial plan will serve as a means to regulate the flow of your cryptocurrency and effectively manage your emotions. Dedicated gamblers who wish to employ this approach can utilize various tools, like Microsoft Excel spreadsheets, to itemize their expenditures.</p>
<p>Additionally, there are other applications available that can assist in calculating monthly expenses and provide guidance on spending. By making optimal use of these applications, you will be able to handle your gambling funds effectively.</p>
<h4>Seek out Bitcoin slot machines with a High RTP</h4>
<p>The RTP percentage indicates the money a Bitcoin slot machine returns to players over time. It is advisable to prioritize slots with a higher RTP, as they are more inclined to provide frequent payouts than those with a lower RTP. Reputable online casinos prioritizing customer satisfaction offer an RTP of 97% or above.</p>
<h4>Consider Progressive Jackpot Bitcoin Slots for Enhanced Winnings</h4>
<p>When selecting casino games, progressive jackpot Bitcoin slots present an enticing opportunity. These games feature a jackpot that grows progressively with each bet, offering the potential for massive winnings.</p>
<p>Progressive jackpots can accumulate into millions of dollars or cryptocurrency and are typically won by a single fortunate player. Although the likelihood of achieving a <a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-england-stoke-staffordshire-34495287" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">progressive jackpot</a> is minimal, the potential rewards can dramatically transform one&#8217;s life.</p>
<p>The potential for significantly higher earnings than traditional games sets progressive Bitcoin games apart. Many gamblers who delve into progressive slots are amassing far greater profits than those who stick to conventional options.</p>
<p>A victory in an advanced game can surpass all previous losses and catapult players into millionaire status. Moreover, these gamblers strongly believe in their ability to outsmart the house and achieve success consistently.</p>
<h4>Utilize Bonuses and Promotional Offers</h4>
<p>Online casinos frequently provide bonuses and promotions to entice and keep players engaged. Make sure to seize these opportunities, as they can enhance your funds and increase your winning prospects.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, it&#8217;s crucial to thoroughly review the terms and conditions to be aware of any wagering requirements or limitations that may be in place.</p>
<h4>Engage with Multiple Paylines</h4>
<p>In numerous Bitcoin games, you&#8217;ll come across multiple pay lines, specific lines where identical symbols need to appear to activate a payout. Playing in various pay lines can enhance your likelihood of winning, granting you additional possibilities to achieve winning combinations.</p>
<h4>Implementing effective bankroll management</h4>
<p>Implementing <a href="https://www.thetimes.co.uk/money-mentor/article/ways-to-save-money/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">effective bankroll management</a> is crucial for achieving sustained success in crypto slots. Players should allocate their bankroll into smaller portions and wager only a modest percentage on each spin. By adhering to this approach, you can minimize the risk of depleting your entire bankroll within a single gaming session.</p>
<h4>Take Breaks</h4>
<p>It is crucial to give yourself regular rest intervals while engaging in gambling activities. The mental and emotional demands of gambling can be overwhelming, so taking breaks becomes necessary to rejuvenate your mind and body.</p>
<p>Taking frequent breaks and utilizing this time to stretch your body and engage in other activities can help you maintain focus and prevent exhaustion. Walking or engaging in stress-relieving conversations can be beneficial during these breaks.</p>
<h4>Maintain Concentration and Perseverance</h4>
<p>In crypto casinos, retaining your focus and exercising patience is crucial. Achieving success in any Bitcoin casino necessitates the virtues of patience, self-control, and a touch of good fortune. Nonetheless, players must avoid getting distracted by other players or unimportant events and instead focus on the chosen strategy.</p>
<h4>Conclusion</h4>
<p>Achieving success in slot games on crypto gambling platforms requires skill, strategy, and luck. Players should become familiar with the game to increase their chances of winning. They should establish a budget and select high RTP slots. Engaging in multi-payline play is another strategy to consider. Additionally, practicing effective bankroll management, taking periodic breaks, and maintaining focus can improve the odds of winning and enhance the overall enjoyment of the gambling experience.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/popular-strategies-for-playing-crypto-slots/">Popular Strategies For Playing Crypto Slots</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/popular-strategies-for-playing-crypto-slots/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Opinion: America Really DOESN&#8217;T NEED a CBDC Right Now</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-america-really-doesnt-need-a-cbdc-right-now/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-america-really-doesnt-need-a-cbdc-right-now/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 13:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kristi Noem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ron DeSantis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78361</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The topic of a central bank digital currency (CBDC) continues to permeate the digital currency arena. The question is, “Does a CBDC warrant anything special, and should we really be paying attention to such a concept?” A CBDC May Not Be the Best Thing for America A CBDC is a digital asset issued not by<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-america-really-doesnt-need-a-cbdc-right-now/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-america-really-doesnt-need-a-cbdc-right-now/">Opinion: America Really DOESN&#8217;T NEED a CBDC Right Now</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The topic of a central bank digital currency (CBDC) continues to permeate the digital currency arena. The question is, “Does a CBDC warrant anything special, and should we really be paying attention to such a concept?”</p>
<h2>A CBDC May Not Be the Best Thing for America</h2>
<p>A <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/cbdc/" data-wpel-link="internal">CBDC</a> is a digital asset issued not by any specific blockchain or token company. Rather, it stems from a centralized bank (i.e., Wells Fargo, Chase Bank, Bank of America, etc.). It’s handed out like paper money, and it’s dealt with in a similar manner.</p>
<p>There are some that believe the issuance of a CBDC would ultimately bring the crypto arena to its highest level. This would mean the digital currency space would become legitimate; it would reach a degree of mainstream appeal that would be undeniable to even the most hardcore deniers.</p>
<p>At the same time, one cannot ignore the issues that come with a CBDC, a big one being that it’s coming from entities that were never designed to take part in the crypto arena to begin with, nor were they invited to step in when assets like bitcoin first arrived on the scene well over ten years ago.</p>
<p>A few years back, a version of a CBDC was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/56412-2/" data-wpel-link="internal">unveiled in China</a>. Many analysts took issue with the structure of the token in that it allowed Chinese regulators to spy on users and see what they were utlizing the coin to buy.</p>
<p>This goes against the very notions of crypto. Digital currencies were built to give their users full independence and autonomy. If it’s going to be treated like a normal form of fiat – an asset that’s doled out by a standard bank – then why’d we ever bother setting up these rules and ideals for independence in the first place? The entire situation is very incongruous.</p>
<p>There’s another major problem in that with the current U.S. administration being so tied to and influenced by China (Joe Biden has literally <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-family-received-millions-from-foreign-nationals-tried-to-conceal-source-of-funds-house-oversight/ar-AA1b06gG" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">garnered millions from</a> the Chinese government and lied about it), one can easily assume that those in charge, should they build a CBDC, will model theirs exactly like the currency introduced in the east. It will have the same structure, and it will probably be used to spy on traders.</p>
<h2>Underlying Problems</h2>
<p>Over the past several months, many governors and regional leaders – like Kristi Noem of South Dakota and Ron DeSantis of Florida – have recognized the underlying evil that can easily strike via the issuance of a CBDC. They have thus either <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/governor-kristi-noem-vetoes-central-bank-digital-currency-bill/" data-wpel-link="internal">vetoed bills permitting</a> the creation of such assets, or initiated laws <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ron-desantis-signs-anti-cbdc-crypto-bill-into-law/" data-wpel-link="internal">preventing their establishment</a> outright.</p>
<p>Examining all this, crypto fans throughout America need to realize that a CBDC, at least right now, would be a tool that could ultimately hurt them rather than aid them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-america-really-doesnt-need-a-cbdc-right-now/">Opinion: America Really DOESN&#8217;T NEED a CBDC Right Now</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-america-really-doesnt-need-a-cbdc-right-now/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SOL Price Analysis: Solana Could Recover Further If It Holds This Support</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sol-price-analysis-solana-could-recover-further-if-it-holds-this-support/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sol-price-analysis-solana-could-recover-further-if-it-holds-this-support/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 04:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78980</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Solana price started a decent increase above the $16.00 resistance against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $16.50 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $16.20 on the 4-hour chart of the SOL/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sol-price-analysis-solana-could-recover-further-if-it-holds-this-support/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sol-price-analysis-solana-could-recover-further-if-it-holds-this-support/">SOL Price Analysis: Solana Could Recover Further If It Holds This Support</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Solana price started a decent increase above the $16.00 resistance against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $16.50 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $16.20 on the 4-hour chart of the SOL/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair must clear $17.00 and $17.78 to continue higher in the near term.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Solana price is trading above $16.00 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-bulls-in-control-above-29500/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. SOL could start a strong increase if it clears the $17.78 resistance.</em></p>
<h2>Solana (SOL) Price Analysis</h2>
<p>SOL price started a decent recovery wave above the $15 pivot level. The price formed a base and was able to climb above the $15.50 and $16.00 levels.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the key drop from the $22.32 swing high to the $13.20 low. The bulls were even able to pump the price above the $16.50 resistance zone. However, the bears were active near the $17.78 resistance.</p>
<p>The price struggled to surpass the 50% Fib retracement level of the key drop from the $22.32 swing high to the $13.20 low. SOL is now trading below $16.50 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/solana-sol-price-analysis-bulls-aim-recovery-to-18-50/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $17.00 level. The next major resistance is near the $17.78 zone. Any more gains might send SOL price towards the $18.50 resistance zone, above which the price could accelerate higher. The next major resistance sits near the $20.00 level.</p>
<p>On the downside, initial support is near the $16.20 level. There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support near $16.20 on the 4-hour chart of the SOL/USD pair.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $15.30 level. A downside break below the $15.30 support level might push the price toward the $14.20 support. Any more losses might open the doors for more losses toward the $13.20 low in the coming sessions.</p>
<div id="attachment_78981" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/SOL-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78981" class="size-full wp-image-78981" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/SOL-1.png" alt="Solana (SOL) Price" width="1835" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78981" class="wp-caption-text">Solana (SOL) Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/SOLUSD/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">chart</a>, Solana price is clearly trading just below $16.50 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price must clear $17.00 and $17.78 to continue higher in the near term.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD is now losing momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $16.20 and $15.30.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $17.00, $17.78, and $18.50.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sol-price-analysis-solana-could-recover-further-if-it-holds-this-support/">SOL Price Analysis: Solana Could Recover Further If It Holds This Support</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sol-price-analysis-solana-could-recover-further-if-it-holds-this-support/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Bulls In Control Above $29,500</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-bulls-in-control-above-29500/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-bulls-in-control-above-29500/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 02:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78977</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price started a fresh increase above the $28,500 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above $28,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $29,800 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-bulls-in-control-above-29500/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-bulls-in-control-above-29500/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Bulls In Control Above $29,500</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin price started a fresh increase above the $28,500 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $28,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $29,800 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to rise if it stays above the $29,500 support zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin price is showing positive signs above $29,000 against the US Dollar. BTC might correct lower but dips could be limited below the $29,500 zone.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price started a decent increase above the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-bulls-aim-fresh-uptrend/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">$27,000 resistance zone</a>. The price gained and cleared many hurdles near the $27,500 and $28,000 levels.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above the $28,500 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). The price even rallied above the $30,000 resistance zone. However, the bears were active near the $31,450 zone. A high was formed near $31,443 and the price is now consolidating gains.</p>
<p>The price traded below $30,500 but is still above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $24,751 swing low to the $31,443 high. The price is now trading well above $28,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>Immediate resistance on the upside is near the $31,000 level. The first major resistance is near the $31,450 level, above which the price could rise toward the $32,200 zone.</p>
<p>Any more gains might send the price toward the $33,200 zone. If there is no upside break, the price might start a downside correction below $30,000.</p>
<p>The next key support is near the $29,850 level. There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support near $29,800 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair. Any more losses might call for a move toward the $29,500 support zone or the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-rally-above-this-resistance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>The next major support is seen near the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $24,751 swing low to the $31,443 high.</p>
<div id="attachment_78978" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Bitcoin-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78978" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78978" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Bitcoin-3.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1835" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78978" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XBTUSD/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">chart</a>, Bitcoin price is trading above $28,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to rise if it stays above the $29,500 support zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD is now losing momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $29,850 and $29,500.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $31,000, $31,450, and $32,200.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-bulls-in-control-above-29500/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Bulls In Control Above $29,500</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-bulls-in-control-above-29500/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former Argo Blockchain CEO Peter Wall Joins Blockchain Firm SBP</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-argo-blockchain-ceo-peter-wall-joins-sbp-blockchain-firm/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-argo-blockchain-ceo-peter-wall-joins-sbp-blockchain-firm/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 17:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Argo Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peter Wall]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SBP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78353</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Peter Wall – the former CEO of bitcoin mining firm Argo Blockchain – has a new job. He’s stepped aboard the train of Sustainable Bitcoin Protocol (SBP) and will serve as the company’s new senior advisor. Peter Wall and SBP&#8230; The Perfect Match? The goal is to ensure SBP has the appeal necessary to enter<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-argo-blockchain-ceo-peter-wall-joins-sbp-blockchain-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-argo-blockchain-ceo-peter-wall-joins-sbp-blockchain-firm/">Former Argo Blockchain CEO Peter Wall Joins Blockchain Firm SBP</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Peter Wall – the former CEO of bitcoin mining firm Argo Blockchain – <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sustainable-bitcoin-protocol-welcomes-peter-135900027.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">has a new job</a>. He’s stepped aboard the train of Sustainable Bitcoin Protocol (SBP) and will serve as the company’s new senior advisor.</p>
<h2>Peter Wall and SBP&#8230; The Perfect Match?</h2>
<p>The goal is to ensure SBP has the appeal necessary to enter the hearts of institutional investors. It’s often been said in the digital currency arena that without institutions backing up crypto and blockchain, the industry is never going to reach the level of legitimacy so many traders and investors feel is necessary for it. Thus, it doesn’t matter how many retailers get involved. Without institutions, crypto won’t get far.</p>
<p>SBP CEO Brad van Voorhees expressed his enthusiasm about Wall coming onboard. In a recent interview, he stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>We are honored and excited to have Peter Wall join our team as a senior advisor. His expertise in the bitcoin mining sector, combined with his talent for storytelling, will be invaluable to our mission. We deeply respect Peter&#8217;s understanding of the pain points and challenges within the industry and believe that he will help us improve the way we articulate the mission of SBP and support miners.</p></blockquote>
<p>Wall was also very happy about being able to work with such a prominent company, explaining in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin has a unique opportunity to become one of the world&#8217;s most sustainable asset classes within the climate investing space, and I&#8217;m thrilled to join the SBP team in helping it reach that potential. Together, we will work to educate the global community on the environmental and social benefits of embracing bitcoin as a climate investing asset.</p></blockquote>
<p>Wall spent the first ten years of his career working as a journalist. From there, however, he became a prominent entrepreneur. Following this little stint, he joined the ranks of Argo Blockchain as the firm’s vice president of operations before eventually moving up the corporate ladder to serve as the enterprise’s CEO, a role he held for three years.</p>
<p>Wall is responsible for leading the company through a period of heavy growth. The company was listed on the Nasdaq (<a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-spikes-following-public-debut-of-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">clearly the predecessor to Coinbase</a>) and raised more than $200 million while also ensuring its tactics and protocols were appropriate for the environment.</p>
<h2>Making Sure BTC is Right for the Environment</h2>
<p>Wall will use his expertise to not only garner more institutional support, but to also push the idea that bitcoin is the preferred asset of impact investors. He clearly believes in bitcoin and everything it stands for, and he wants the values of SBP and bitcoin to always align.</p>
<p>Sustainable Bitcoin Protocol is also very interested in pushing investments in the renewable energy sector, which it believes will give the bitcoin scene more life and strength in the eyes of the public.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-argo-blockchain-ceo-peter-wall-joins-sbp-blockchain-firm/">Former Argo Blockchain CEO Peter Wall Joins Blockchain Firm SBP</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-argo-blockchain-ceo-peter-wall-joins-sbp-blockchain-firm/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Steve Hanke Really, Really Hates Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/steve-hanke-really-really-hates-bitcoin/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/steve-hanke-really-really-hates-bitcoin/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 15:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Steve Hanke]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78351</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Not everyone loves bitcoin. In fact, there are those out there – like Warren Buffett or his sidekick Charlie Munger – that hate it with passion, and now, it looks like top economist Steve Hanke is joining the ranks of BTC’s biggest opposers. Steve Hanke Isn&#8217;t a BTC Fan In a recent interview, Hanke stated<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/steve-hanke-really-really-hates-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/steve-hanke-really-really-hates-bitcoin/">Steve Hanke Really, Really Hates Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Not everyone loves bitcoin. In fact, there are those out there – like Warren Buffett or his <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/charlie-munger-is-still-one-of-btcs-biggest-haters/" data-wpel-link="internal">sidekick Charlie Munger</a> – that hate it with passion, and now, it looks like top economist Steve Hanke is joining the ranks of <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-is-a-bubble-with-no-inherent-value-and-is-terribly-overpriced-top-economist-steve-hanke-says/ar-AA1bdgaJ" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">BTC’s biggest opposers</a>.</p>
<h2>Steve Hanke Isn&#8217;t a BTC Fan</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, Hanke stated that bitcoin was a “bubble.” He said that it held no intrinsic value, that it was overpriced, and that it wasn’t likely to go anywhere in the future. In other words, those who buy it are stupid and are throwing their money into the trash can. Hanke commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin is a bubble. It has no inherent value and is terribly overpriced. Buying bitcoin is a fool’s game.</p></blockquote>
<p>While bitcoin indeed has a strong legion of fans, the world’s number one digital currency by market capitalization has had a hard time of things over the past year or so. In 2022, the asset lost more than 70 percent of its value and wound up taking a huge dip into the mid-$16K range by the end of the year. This was a big change from the new all-time high it achieved in November of 2021 (during that time, the currency hit a price of $68,000 per unit).</p>
<p>In any case, there was a lot of speculation of just how stable bitcoin truly was, as for the past several years, the asset had been touted as a hedge against inflation and all kinds of other things. These narratives were ultimately challenged in ways nobody thought possible given the currency fell so much during times of record inflation (it peaked last June and moved beyond nine percent).</p>
<p>With all this in mind, it seemed like bitcoin and many of its altcoin cousins were losing their mojos, but now that we’ve entered 2023, the currency and its brethren are experiencing rises here and there that have ultimately seen them enter phases of healing. Bitcoin recently hit a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">price of $30K</a>, and while the currency has dropped down again somewhat since then, the price was a walloping change from where it stood last year.</p>
<p>BTC has been subjected to some rather odd circumstances over the past few weeks given how much the financial space appears to be at war with itself. On the one hand, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-provide-their-thoughts-on-latest-bitcoin-rally/" data-wpel-link="internal">you have banks falling</a> left and right. Institutions like First Republic, Signature, and Silicon Valley Bank have crashed and burned, thus paving the way for bitcoin’s recovery.</p>
<h2>So Many Twists and Turns</h2>
<p>At the same time, organizations like the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) have done all they can to bring down major crypto players like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/" data-wpel-link="internal">Kraken</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">Coinbase</a>. This, naturally, has been weary for the asset.</p>
<p>Hanke is a former economic advisor to President Ronald Reagan, who served in the 1980s.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/steve-hanke-really-really-hates-bitcoin/">Steve Hanke Really, Really Hates Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/steve-hanke-really-really-hates-bitcoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Paul Tudor Jones: BTC&#8217;s Days as an Inflation Hedge Are Over</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paul-tudor-jones-btcs-days-as-an-inflation-hedge-are-over/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paul-tudor-jones-btcs-days-as-an-inflation-hedge-are-over/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 13:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Inflation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paul Tudor Jones]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78349</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The idea that bitcoin was always a hedge against inflation has been rather prominent amongst crypto fans for the past few years. Now, according to Paul Tudor Jones – a bitcoin bull and billionaire hedge fund manager – it sounds like this idea may have reached its peak and is coming to an end. Paul<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paul-tudor-jones-btcs-days-as-an-inflation-hedge-are-over/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paul-tudor-jones-btcs-days-as-an-inflation-hedge-are-over/">Paul Tudor Jones: BTC&#8217;s Days as an Inflation Hedge Are Over</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The idea that bitcoin was always a hedge against inflation has been rather prominent amongst crypto fans for the past few years. Now, according to Paul Tudor Jones – a bitcoin bull and billionaire hedge fund manager – it sounds like this idea <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/05/16/bitcoin-and-crypto-have-a-real-problem-paul-tudor-jones/?sh=2bd005494935" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">may have reached its peak</a> and is coming to an end.</p>
<h2>Paul Tudor Jones: BTC&#8217;s Inflationary Hedge Days Are Ending</h2>
<p>Many have long believed that buying bitcoin would somehow ensure their wealth and keep their portfolios steady should economic strife take hold. With assets like USD and other fiat currencies losing their value, the belief was that bitcoin could potentially work against inflation and other dollar-crushing maneuvers and keep one’s money pit nice and secure.</p>
<p>But Tudor Jones recently commented in an interview that he thinks the Fed is going to put a stop to the endless rate hikes we’ve seen the organization instill over the past year or so. With this on the horizon, one must assume that inflation will come to an end in the United States, and even if it doesn’t, it won’t be as harsh a problem as it has been over the past year. If this is the case, the days of buying bitcoin as an inflation hedge may be over. Jones commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>If inflation is truly done a bit, if that story’s been played, then you have to wonder… We were buying gold and bitcoin for the inflation hedges. That game may be over.</p></blockquote>
<p>Inflation has been striking the U.S. from all sides for well over a year. It hit a peak at more than nine percent in June last year. Thanks to weak leaders like Joe Biden, who has been in the habit of instilling poor economic policies and signing his name to a multitude of trillion-dollar spending bills, the country has been having to deal with rising food prices, gas prices, and just about everything else.</p>
<p>This has ultimately led the Fed to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-fed-bitcoins-worst-enemy-right-now/" data-wpel-link="internal">raise interest rates</a> as a means of fighting the ongoing inflation. However, this tactic hasn’t really done much except destroy crypto prices (remember 2022, anyone?) and prevent people from gaining access to the American dream. With rates being what they are, most people can no longer afford homes, cars, or other big items.</p>
<h2>I&#8217;m Still Holding Mine</h2>
<p>But while Jones is confident the initial goals of BTC holders will change, he’s still very much for keeping the asset as part of your portfolio. He stated that he’ll always allocate at least some small part of his wealth to BTC, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>From the beginning, I’ve always said I want to have a small allocation to it because it’s the only thing humans can’t adjust the supply in, so I’m sticking with it, and I’m going to always stick with it as a small diversification in my portfolio.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paul-tudor-jones-btcs-days-as-an-inflation-hedge-are-over/">Paul Tudor Jones: BTC&#8217;s Days as an Inflation Hedge Are Over</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paul-tudor-jones-btcs-days-as-an-inflation-hedge-are-over/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=3787 metric#misses=5 metric#hit-ratio=99.9 metric#bytes=6618648 metric#prefetches=319 metric#store-reads=68 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=401 metric#store-misses=0 metric#sql-queries=17 metric#ms-total=176.17 metric#ms-cache=24.06 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.3487 metric#ms-cache-ratio=13.7 -->
