<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 15:04:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Binance Halted Withdrawals in Mid-May; BTC Temporarily Fell</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-halted-withdrawals-in-mid-may-btc-temporarily-fell/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-halted-withdrawals-in-mid-may-btc-temporarily-fell/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 17:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Withdrawals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78237</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin endured a bit of a dip in mid-May when it was announced that Binance would briefly halt all withdrawals and deposits due to ongoing congestion and traffic. Binance Came to a Standstill (so Did BTC) Bitcoin had been trading in the $29,000 range prior, and there were many analysts out there who felt the<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-halted-withdrawals-in-mid-may-btc-temporarily-fell/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-halted-withdrawals-in-mid-may-btc-temporarily-fell/">Binance Halted Withdrawals in Mid-May; BTC Temporarily Fell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin endured a bit of a dip in mid-May when it <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-slides-after-network-congestion-leads-binance-to-briefly-halt-withdrawals/ar-AA1aTPjH" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">was announced that</a> Binance would briefly halt all withdrawals and deposits due to ongoing congestion and traffic.</p>
<h2>Binance Came to a Standstill (so Did BTC)</h2>
<p>Bitcoin had been trading in the $29,000 range prior, and there were many analysts out there who felt the world’s number one digital currency by market cap was on the verge of striking $30K again like it did in April. Sadly, it appears Binance got in the way of this and set BTC back a few steps.</p>
<p>While the halts were temporary and lasted only a short while, the damage was done to BTC, which had to fall back a few steps before it could proceed with its prior trek up the financial staircase. Binance issued the following tweet after the halts came to an end:</p>
<blockquote><p>To prevent a similar recurrence in the future, our fees have been adjusted. We will continue to monitor on-chain activity and adjust accordingly if needed. Our team has also been working on enabling BTC Lightning Network withdrawals, which will help in such situations.</p></blockquote>
<p>Joel Kruger – market strategist at LMAX Group – stated in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Reports of a large bitcoin outflow and withdrawals being paused at a major exchange could be factoring into some of the weakness we&#8217;re seeing. Ultimately, however, there haven&#8217;t been any major developments as far as price action goes, with bitcoin still very much confined to a multi-day bullish consolidation. Only a break back below $25,000 would give reason for concern. Until then, we suspect dips will continue to be very well supported.</p></blockquote>
<p>The news is unusual for a few reasons, a big one being Binance is the world’s largest and most popular digital trading platform. In terms of daily volume, no exchange can say it attracts the attention or activity Binance does. Given its size and prowess, you’d think such a firm would be ready for loads of traffic, though temporary halts and shutdowns of this nature are common for Binance.</p>
<p>Such an occurrence also took <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-scared-traders-in-late-march-when-it-temporarily-stopped-all-trading/" data-wpel-link="internal">place in late March</a>, though that time around, the problems were attributed – according to Ilya Volkov, CEO of You Hodler – to a technical glitch in the company’s network rather than heavy traffic. Volkov mentioned in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>These kinds of bugs could happen everywhere, and crypto exchanges are not unique.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Trying to Keep Up</h2>
<p>Oppenheimer analyst Owen Lau was also quick to throw his two cents in regarding the present issues. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>There is an increasing demand for BRC-20 tokens, which include transferring digital collectibles on [the] bitcoin network. The bitcoin network has gradually supported more different types of tokens like NFTs. This adoption should be a positive sign in the longer term, but it looks like it has slowed down the network.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-halted-withdrawals-in-mid-may-btc-temporarily-fell/">Binance Halted Withdrawals in Mid-May; BTC Temporarily Fell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-halted-withdrawals-in-mid-may-btc-temporarily-fell/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Liechtenstein Officials Say &#8220;Yes&#8221; to BTC Payments</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/liechtenstein-officials-say-yes-to-btc-payments/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/liechtenstein-officials-say-yes-to-btc-payments/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 15:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto payments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liechtenstein]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78234</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Liechtenstein – a small European nation that most people likely wouldn’t even be able to recognize on a map – is suddenly becoming very big in the crypto community. Government regulators have recently issued a statement claiming they’re looking into accepting bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies as payment methods for state services. Liechtenstein Loves Crypto, Apparently<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/liechtenstein-officials-say-yes-to-btc-payments/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/liechtenstein-officials-say-yes-to-btc-payments/">Liechtenstein Officials Say &#8220;Yes&#8221; to BTC Payments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Liechtenstein – a small European nation that most people likely wouldn’t even be able to recognize on a map – is suddenly <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/liechtenstein-government-plans-accept-bitcoin-094856431.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">becoming very big in the crypto</a> community. Government regulators have recently issued a statement claiming they’re looking into accepting bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies as payment methods for state services.</p>
<h2>Liechtenstein Loves Crypto, Apparently</h2>
<p>The news came from Prime Minister Daniel Risch. The new program would make it so that all crypto payments delivered for government and national services would immediately be converted into Swiss francs to avoid exchange-rate risks. Right now, the franc is the primary form of currency the country utilizes to stay afloat.</p>
<p>The move is pushing the goals of bitcoin and its digital counterparts closer to being achieved. What many people likely forget is that while bitcoin and many of its crypto cousins have taken on either speculative or even hedge-like statuses in recent years, many of them were initially designed to serve as payment tools. They were built to push checks, credit cards, and fiat currencies to the side, but this has been a relatively slow journey given the volatility that continues to drag them down.</p>
<p>It is extremely hard to understand when <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitcoin/" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitcoin/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1654270452656000&amp;usg=AOvVaw3bvGkqiDvhlSzR-S2K1YYe" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>bitcoin</strong></a> and its crypto family will go up or down when it comes to their prices. Many stores and companies have been reluctant to say “yes” when it comes to accepting crypto payments for this reason, and to a degree, we can’t blame them.</p>
<p>Consider the following scenario: someone walks into a store and buys $50 worth of merchandise with bitcoin. For one reason or another, the store doesn’t trade the BTC into fiat right away and about 24 hours go by. From there, the price of BTC goes down and that $50 becomes $40. The customer gets to keep everything he or she bought, but the store loses money in the end. Is this a fair situation? Not everyone thinks so.</p>
<p>That’s what makes countries like Liechtenstein so important. They understand the initial purposes of bitcoin and digital currencies and are trying to transform them into usable tools that everyday people can benefit from.</p>
<p>Risch says he and his fellow constituents involved in Liechtenstein matters have long been open to the ideas and principles presented by bitcoin and its altcoin cousins. He also stated that the nation is open to investing state reserves into crypto assets like bitcoin and Ethereum at some point in the future. Liechtenstein is unique in that it’s one of the few nations that has managed to remain fully debt free.</p>
<h2>Still Too Much Risk?</h2>
<p>Despite the forward steps, Risch was quick to acknowledge that crypto is still risk heavy. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Crypto assets like bitcoin are currently still too risky, but this assessment can change.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/liechtenstein-officials-say-yes-to-btc-payments/">Liechtenstein Officials Say &#8220;Yes&#8221; to BTC Payments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/liechtenstein-officials-say-yes-to-btc-payments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Presidential Hopeful Robert Kennedy Jr. Appeared at This Year&#8217;s Miami BTC Conference</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-hopeful-robert-kennedy-jr-appeared-at-this-years-miami-btc-conference/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-hopeful-robert-kennedy-jr-appeared-at-this-years-miami-btc-conference/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 13:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthony Scaramucci]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robert Kennedy Jr.]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78232</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Robert F. Kennedy Jr. – a democrat who’s thrown his hat into the presidential race against Joe Biden – made his first appearance as a candidate this month at the famed Miami Bitcoin Conference. Robert Kennedy and Bitcoin&#8230; A Solid Match? Kennedy is not your typical far-left leaning liberal. He’s a vaccine skeptic and he’s<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-hopeful-robert-kennedy-jr-appeared-at-this-years-miami-btc-conference/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-hopeful-robert-kennedy-jr-appeared-at-this-years-miami-btc-conference/">Presidential Hopeful Robert Kennedy Jr. Appeared at This Year&#8217;s Miami BTC Conference</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Robert F. Kennedy Jr. – a democrat who’s thrown his hat into the presidential race against Joe Biden – made his first <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/robert-kennedy-jr-to-make-campaign-debut-at-bitcoin-conference/ar-AA1aOW7z" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">appearance as a candidate</a> this month at the famed Miami Bitcoin Conference.</p>
<h2>Robert Kennedy and Bitcoin&#8230; A Solid Match?</h2>
<p>Kennedy is not your typical far-left leaning liberal. He’s a vaccine skeptic and he’s clearly standing with an industry that many of his constituents have deemed damaging to the environment. Elements like these are potentially going to get him a lot of followers in the coming weeks given there are likely to be several members of the democrat party that aren’t happy about the extreme stance their group has taken over the last five years.</p>
<p>Brandon Green – chief of staff to conference organizer BTC Media – commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>We asked him to speak after hearing his positive comments toward the bitcoin industry.</p></blockquote>
<p>Kennedy is not slated to be paid for making his appearance, nor is he going to earn any speaking fees for the campaign appearances he makes over the next year or so as he pursues the road to the White House, according to his spokesperson Stefanie Spear.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/anthony-scaramucci/" data-wpel-link="internal">Anthony Scaramucci</a> – a bitcoin fan and the former communications director for President Donald Trump – said Kennedy’s love for bitcoin will likely endear him to the growing array of digital currency fans that appear to be getting stronger each day. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>In my mind, there’s this shadow fandom or currently invisible lobbying group — and it’s probably currently about 77 million people — of bitcoin or other cryptocurrency holders in the United States. I think it’s going to be a topical issue in 2024, and I would imagine that one of these presidential nominees will embrace bitcoin, and if they do, that’ll give them an edge… These are people who are typically agnostic [to] party.</p></blockquote>
<p>In a recent discussion, Kennedy stated that monetary freedom is just as important as all the other rights and liberties given to naturalized Americans, thus suggesting crypto could indeed be a solid tool for remaining stable against oppressive regimes. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Monetary freedom is as important as freedom of speech. Without it, we are slaves. It’s not outlandish to imagine that even here in America, your bank account could one day be frozen because of your politics or comments you’ve made on social media.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Not Everyone&#8217;s Enthused</h2>
<p>Some, like Elizabeth Moran of the environmental non-profit Earth Justice, are skeptical of his alignment with the crypto space. They believe, given the industry’s knack for overusing energy, that this could wind up hurting Kennedy in the long run. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>This problem is really limited to bitcoin and maybe a couple of other smaller cryptocurrencies at this point. Energy consumption is so great in some places that utility bills are skyrocketing for consumers.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-hopeful-robert-kennedy-jr-appeared-at-this-years-miami-btc-conference/">Presidential Hopeful Robert Kennedy Jr. Appeared at This Year&#8217;s Miami BTC Conference</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-hopeful-robert-kennedy-jr-appeared-at-this-years-miami-btc-conference/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jack Dorsey Gives $10 Million to Bitcoin Non-Profit</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jack-dorsey-gives-10-million-to-bitcoin-non-profit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jack-dorsey-gives-10-million-to-bitcoin-non-profit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 17:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Open Sats]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78223</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Former Twitter head and current chief executive of Block Jack Dorsey has pledged a $10 million donation to a non-profit called Open Sats. The money is slated to be fully, 100 percent put towards a bitcoin-focused social media network. Jack Dorsey Gives a Lot of Money to Open Sats Dorsey has long been a bitcoin<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jack-dorsey-gives-10-million-to-bitcoin-non-profit/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jack-dorsey-gives-10-million-to-bitcoin-non-profit/">Jack Dorsey Gives $10 Million to Bitcoin Non-Profit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Former Twitter head and current chief executive of Block Jack Dorsey has <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/05/04/jack-dorsey-donates-10-million-to-fund-bitcoin-development/?sh=5e277cd2d640" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">pledged a $10 million</a> donation to a non-profit called Open Sats. The money is slated to be fully, 100 percent put towards a bitcoin-focused social media network.</p>
<h2>Jack Dorsey Gives a Lot of Money to Open Sats</h2>
<p>Dorsey has long been a bitcoin and crypto advocate. He <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/news/bitcoin-will-become-worlds-single-currency-dorsey/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">stated five years</a> ago that he was convinced bitcoin would become the sole currency of the world, and that all other fiat currencies – like the euro, the yen, the U.S. dollar, etc. – would be wiped out. He also (prior to the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/coronavirus/" data-wpel-link="internal">COVID pandemic</a>) pledged to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jack-dorsey-i-will-bring-btc-to-africa/" data-wpel-link="internal">spend three to six months</a> touring Africa to try and get its people to adopt the ways of bitcoin and blockchain so they could benefit financially and otherwise.</p>
<p>Open Sats is based in the city of Raleigh, North Carolina. The company received its non-profit status back in the year 2021 per data site Charity Navigator. Interestingly, the company started out with less than $200K to its name, though this sudden donation from Dorsey is likely to make a huge change for both the company and whatever projects it has on its roster.</p>
<p>In a recent statement, the company made it clear that bitcoin – and assets like it – are aligned with its primary values. The statement read as follows:</p>
<blockquote><p>We believe that free software and open protocols are necessary for a free and prosperous society. Without software that protects the individual user&#8217;s rights and freedoms, and without digital infrastructure that is open to all, modern society risks slipping further into digital totalitarianism.</p></blockquote>
<p>The company’s website says its primary objective is to “support and maintain a sustainable ecosystem of funding for free and open-source projects and contributors, especially bitcoin-related projects and projects which help bitcoin flourish.”</p>
<p>The company’s statement continued with:</p>
<blockquote><p>Open Sats will fund software developers, but also designers, reviewers, researchers, educators, and others who support these free and open-source tools.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Defending Bitcoin in the Long-Term</h2>
<p>Not long ago, Dorsey came to the aid of several <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jack-dorsey-is-defending-several-btc-developers-against-craig-wright/" data-wpel-link="internal">developers who had previously</a> worked for Australian computer scientist Craig Wright. The former social media executive created a defense fund for the developers after they were named as defendants in a lawsuit filed by their former boss, who over the course of several years, has stuck to the notion <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2021/apr/23/australian-man-craig-wrights-claim-he-invented-bitcoin-to-be-considered-by-uk-court" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">that he is Satoshi Nakamoto</a>, the legendary (and pseudonymous) creator of BTC, the world’s number one digital currency by market cap.</p>
<p>While the identity matter is still up for debate, Dorsey claimed that if Wright gets his way in the upcoming lawsuit, the open-source nature of bitcoin will be put on the line. His goal is to ensure that bitcoin always remains open source so developers can continue to learn from it and benefit from its technology.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jack-dorsey-gives-10-million-to-bitcoin-non-profit/">Jack Dorsey Gives $10 Million to Bitcoin Non-Profit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jack-dorsey-gives-10-million-to-bitcoin-non-profit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Charles Hoskinson on How the Banking Crisis Will Affect Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/charles-hoskinson-on-how-the-banking-crisis-will-affect-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/charles-hoskinson-on-how-the-banking-crisis-will-affect-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 15:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[banking crisis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charles Hoskinson]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78221</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the long run, the banking crisis that we’re presently seeing has helped assets like bitcoin and Ethereum really step into the limelight and do much better than they did in 2022. However, Charles Hoskinson – the co-founder of Ethereum and the creator of ETH rival Cardano – recently stated that he thinks the crisis<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/charles-hoskinson-on-how-the-banking-crisis-will-affect-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/charles-hoskinson-on-how-the-banking-crisis-will-affect-crypto/">Charles Hoskinson on How the Banking Crisis Will Affect Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the long run, the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-provide-their-thoughts-on-latest-bitcoin-rally/" data-wpel-link="internal">banking crisis</a> that we’re presently seeing has helped assets like bitcoin and Ethereum really step into the limelight and do much better than they did in 2022. However, Charles Hoskinson – the co-founder of Ethereum and the creator of ETH rival Cardano – <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/05/06/worse-than-2008-bitcoin-and-crypto-now-braced-for-540-billion-crisis-ethereum-cofounder-warns/?sh=2111d0cdf39f" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">recently stated that he</a> thinks the crisis will get a lot worse, and that in the end, it could have negative effects on crypto.</p>
<h2>Charles Hoskinson on Where Banks Will Go</h2>
<p>In an interview, Hoskinson said he thinks the crisis of 2008 and 2009 will be nothing like what’s coming. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>In 2008, we had $373 billion in tied-up assets. I think we’re over $540 billion now just in the 2023 crisis. We’re just getting started. That whole business model is falling apart when you give it a little bit of a push and then you lose these institutions like Silicon Valley Bank, and they get so politicized, and they get so globalized.</p></blockquote>
<p>Not long ago, the banking crisis was exacerbated when <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/first-republic-bank-is-gone-what-will-happen-to-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">First Republic Bank became</a> the latest financial institution to join the ranks of Silicon Valley Bank, Signature, and others. FRB went up in smoke and had all its assets sold off or provided to competing firms like JPMorgan Chase, which was glad to step in and offer a helping hand according to head executive Jamie Dimon. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Our government invited us and others to step up, and we did.</p></blockquote>
<p>It’s ironic that both Dimon and JPMorgan both played big parts in the 2008 Great Recession, and it looks like they’re being set up to play big roles again.</p>
<p>Hoskinson is convinced that the events of 15 years ago are not only going to repeat themselves, but they’re likely to be even larger, and he isn’t predicting good outcomes for any assets, whether they be bitcoin, Ethereum, gold, or obscure coins. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>What’s going to happen is ‘too big to fail’ is just going to lead to bigger institutions. We’ve seen this story in 2008, and this is the rerun. I don’t think anybody wants to watch it.</p></blockquote>
<h2>What Happens from Here?</h2>
<p>Bill Ackman – chief executive of New York hedge fund Pershing Square – agrees with Hoskinson that the present banking crisis could reach unprecedented levels. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Confidence in a financial institution is built over decades and destroyed in days. As each domino falls, the next weakest bank begins to wobble. We are running out of time to fix this problem. How many more unnecessary bank failures do we need to watch before the FDIC [Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation] and our government wake up? We need a systemwide deposit guarantee regime now.</p></blockquote>
<p>Thus far in 2023, the banking crisis has already (presumably) contributed to the Federal Reserve hiking rates not <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/federal-reserve-hikes-rates-again-what-will-happen-to-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">once</a>, but <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-fed-hikes-rates-again-but-analysts-think-bitcoin-will-surge-soon/" data-wpel-link="internal">twice</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/charles-hoskinson-on-how-the-banking-crisis-will-affect-crypto/">Charles Hoskinson on How the Banking Crisis Will Affect Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/charles-hoskinson-on-how-the-banking-crisis-will-affect-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bob Ras on the Future of the Bitcoin Price</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bob-ras-on-the-future-of-the-bitcoin-price/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bob-ras-on-the-future-of-the-bitcoin-price/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 13:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bob Ras]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78219</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bob Ras is a blockchain executive and the co-founder of the distributed ledger company Sologenic. Bob Ras on Where BTC Will Go In a recent interview, Ras explained his thoughts on the present banking crisis and what outcome it’s likely to hold for bitcoin in the long-term. He said: As big banks have been collapsing,<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bob-ras-on-the-future-of-the-bitcoin-price/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bob-ras-on-the-future-of-the-bitcoin-price/">Bob Ras on the Future of the Bitcoin Price</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bob Ras is a blockchain executive <a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/bitcoin-crypto-record-highs-blockchain-founder-sologenic-ras-currency-markets-2023-5" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">and the co-founder of</a> the distributed ledger company Sologenic.</p>
<h2>Bob Ras on Where BTC Will Go</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, Ras explained his thoughts on the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-provide-their-thoughts-on-latest-bitcoin-rally/" data-wpel-link="internal">present banking crisis</a> and what outcome it’s likely to hold for bitcoin in the long-term. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>As big banks have been collapsing, it seems clearer by the day that these investors see bitcoin as a hedge because of its decentralized censorship resistance and lack of counterparty risk. There are growing expectations that the Fed will loosen monetary policy and effectively inject a lot more liquidity into the market to shore up the financial system, and bitcoin is front running this scenario, pointing to a future that is effectively a return to relatively low rates. I wouldn&#8217;t be surprised if $40,000 could be reached by the end of this year.</p></blockquote>
<p><a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-could-more-than-double-and-hit-a-new-record-high-next-year-as-the-token-sees-a-big-shakeup-blockchain-exec-says/ar-AA1aOSSH" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">He continued with</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>The banking crisis helped to cement the narrative of bitcoin serving as a key store of value that lacks the sort of counterparty risk of holding funds by way of bank deposits.</p></blockquote>
<p>Ras was also quick to say what he thinks has been fueling the big bitcoin corrections we’ve been seeing. 2023 has been hugely different from 2022 in that it’s been somewhat bullish. 2022 saw bitcoin reach new lows and lose more than 70 percent of its value over the course of 12 short months.</p>
<p>In November of 2021, the currency hit a new all-time high of about $68,000, but just a year later, it fell into the mid-$16K range. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>A big reason why bitcoin has performed so well was that it was just really oversold during the collapse of FTX. Plus, there&#8217;s on-chain evidence that more and more people and institutions have been accumulating bitcoin during the lows, which essentially translated into a supply shock. With so few sellers left, any uptick in demand has an outsize impact on price.</p></blockquote>
<p>Despite all the positive sentiment about bitcoin and where he thinks it could go in the coming months, his message did contain a small bit of gloom and doom and a subsequent warning to investors. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The biggest risk would be a sharp credit crisis that causes a rapid contraction. In such a scenario, all assets would have a correlation of one with each other, including bitcoin and even gold. I&#8217;m not sure such a scenario would happen, but it&#8217;s possible and would unleash a tremendous amount of volatility not only for bitcoin, but all markets.</p></blockquote>
<h2>The Halving Will Really Help</h2>
<p>Still, however, he’s positive about where bitcoin will be next year, saying 2024’s halving will push it past its previous all-time high. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>When bitcoin&#8217;s halving kicks in a year from now, we&#8217;ll likely be well on our way past the previous all-time high.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bob-ras-on-the-future-of-the-bitcoin-price/">Bob Ras on the Future of the Bitcoin Price</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bob-ras-on-the-future-of-the-bitcoin-price/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Buncombe County in North Carolina Shuts Down Crypto Mining for One Year</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/buncombe-county-in-north-carolina-shuts-down-crypto-mining-for-one-year/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/buncombe-county-in-north-carolina-shuts-down-crypto-mining-for-one-year/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 17:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Moratorium]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[North Carolina]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78208</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Buncombe County commissioners in North Carolina are taking a page out of New York’s crypto playbook and are enforcing a one-year moratorium on all crypto mining operations so they can explore regulations and laws. North Carolina County Halts Crypto Mining Planning director Nate Pennington said in an interview: We don’t often bring a moratorium to<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/buncombe-county-in-north-carolina-shuts-down-crypto-mining-for-one-year/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/buncombe-county-in-north-carolina-shuts-down-crypto-mining-for-one-year/">Buncombe County in North Carolina Shuts Down Crypto Mining for One Year</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Buncombe County commissioners in North Carolina are taking a page out of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/some-want-the-crypto-moratorium-in-new-york-to-last-longer/" data-wpel-link="internal">New York’s crypto</a> playbook and are enforcing a <a href="https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/buncombe-county-oks-1-moratorium-113219118.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">one-year moratorium on all</a> crypto mining operations so they can explore regulations and laws.</p>
<h2>North Carolina County Halts Crypto Mining</h2>
<p>Planning director Nate Pennington said in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>We don’t often bring a moratorium to the table.</p></blockquote>
<p>However, he commented that because crypto mining is still relatively new and doesn’t run under any specific laws, this period will allow him and his fellow city council members to explore new ideas for ensuring the space remains safe for all who take part in it or benefit from it.</p>
<p>Chris Joyell – the healthy communities director with Mountain True – said the region’s people have been extremely helpful and “proactive” when it comes to the issue at hand. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Mountain True has seen several cryptocurrency mines operating in WNC, especially in Cherokee County, where they have proven to be a nuisance to neighbors and a threat to our environment.</p></blockquote>
<p>He said that right now, there are many concerns surrounding the potential noise of the mining machines. There is also a lot of worry regarding the pollution they allegedly emit, and he and his fellow constituents don’t want North Carolina air or water being ruined because people are looking to create blockchain careers for themselves. He continued with:</p>
<blockquote><p>There is no way to greenwash crypto mining. Let me repeat: As the value of bitcoin rebounds, the growth of cryptocurrency mining operations put North Carolina in danger of not being able to hit the goals set out by Gov. Cooper and the N.C. General Assembly with House Bill 951.</p></blockquote>
<p>Craig Deutsch has lived in Buncombe County for about ten years. He’s one of the few people who’s against the moratorium, saying that with crypto being such a revolutionary arena, he’s concerned the move could put North Carolina behind in terms of technical achievements. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I urge the county commissioners and planners to take the time to visit bitcoin mines, do research about bitcoin’s benefits to the environment&#8230; and listen to stories about the positive impacts of bitcoin for underserved and underbanked communities… At the end of the day, all bitcoin mining computers do is run code, and code is a form of constitutionally protected speech.</p></blockquote>
<p>Kimberly Stonebraker, who has lived in North Carolina since 1999, said to the commissioners:</p>
<blockquote><p>I urge you to keep an open mind.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Not Good for Residents?</h2>
<p>Finally, Ken Brame – a representative of the Sierra Club – said he fears crypto mining can do a lot of damage to residents. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We live out there for a reason. We need to take the time to figure out what regulations, what management we have in place to prevent that from happening in neighborhoods like mine.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/buncombe-county-in-north-carolina-shuts-down-crypto-mining-for-one-year/">Buncombe County in North Carolina Shuts Down Crypto Mining for One Year</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/buncombe-county-in-north-carolina-shuts-down-crypto-mining-for-one-year/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leticia James Introduces Bill That Would Birth Basic Crypto Regulation in New York</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leticia-james-introduces-bill-that-would-birth-basic-crypto-regulation-in-new-york/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leticia-james-introduces-bill-that-would-birth-basic-crypto-regulation-in-new-york/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto-regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Leticia James]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New York]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78210</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new bill proposed by New York Attorney General Leticia James would give her state a basic framework for crypto regulation. Among the provisions in the bill are exchanges being required to reimburse customers if they are the victims of fraud or theft. Leticia James Seeks to Introduce Basic Regulation New York and Leticia James<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leticia-james-introduces-bill-that-would-birth-basic-crypto-regulation-in-new-york/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leticia-james-introduces-bill-that-would-birth-basic-crypto-regulation-in-new-york/">Leticia James Introduces Bill That Would Birth Basic Crypto Regulation in New York</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new bill proposed by New York Attorney General Leticia James <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/new-york-attorney-general-seeks-new-crypto-powers-for-state-regulators/ar-AA1aMIFu" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">would give her state a basic</a> framework for crypto regulation. Among the provisions in the bill are exchanges being required to reimburse customers if they are the victims of fraud or theft.</p>
<h2>Leticia James Seeks to Introduce Basic Regulation</h2>
<p>New York and Leticia James have long held strong anti-crypto attitudes. Not long ago, the attorney general sued several digital currency companies including <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-attorney-generals-office-now-suing-ku-coin-exchange/" data-wpel-link="internal">Ku Coin</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leticia-james-sues-coin-ex-alleging-crypto-fraud/" data-wpel-link="internal">Coin Ex</a>, alleging both had taken part in various forms of fraud.</p>
<p>In addition, the state of New York has recently <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/some-want-the-crypto-moratorium-in-new-york-to-last-longer/" data-wpel-link="internal">instituted a two-year crypto</a> moratorium to ensure that no new digital currency mining companies can set up shop in the Empire State for the next 24 months. The goal is to make it so that all crypto companies run purely on clean energy and obey present environmental standards. Regarding her recent bill, James stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>We&#8217;re proposing common sense measures to protect investors and end the fraud and dysfunction that have become the hallmarks of cryptocurrency.</p></blockquote>
<p>Other provisions laid out in the bill include customers being informed of conflicts of interest amongst crypto companies. Also, they would be educated on various risks regarding their investments and the platforms they choose to work with. Lastly, crypto companies would not be permitted to borrow or lend customer assets, clearly a nod to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">the FTX debacle</a> in which customer funds were utilized to pay off loans and invest in luxury Bahamian real estate.</p>
<p>While the items laid out in the bill sound glorious, it would be a mistake to rush forward on the idea that it’s all lollipops and rainbows from here on out, the biggest reason being that James, as mentioned above, has not always liked crypto or held the most positive attitude towards it. Thus, crypto fans need to remain wary.</p>
<p>This is an idea held by many crypto analysts and legal experts including Andrew Hinkes, a partner at law firm K&amp;L Gates. In a recent tweet, Hinkes mentioned that the bill was “destined to fail” in the New York Congress given that it’s written by someone (James) who doesn’t understand crypto.</p>
<p>He explained that the provisions in the bill are virtually impossible to apply to decentralized organizations. He also mentioned that the market, as it stands, cannot provide the kinds of auditing and insurance that James would like to see initiated.</p>
<h2>Being Looked at Carefully</h2>
<p>Right now, the bill is in document form and being observed by New York regulators. They must give the “OK” on the bill for it to become law.</p>
<p>Since the fall of FTX seven months ago, crypto regulation appears to be on the minds of virtually every politician. The company <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-the-damage-caused-by-ftx-was-worse-than-initially-thought/" data-wpel-link="internal">accounted for more than</a> $200 billion in crypto funds being wiped off the digital slate permanently.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leticia-james-introduces-bill-that-would-birth-basic-crypto-regulation-in-new-york/">Leticia James Introduces Bill That Would Birth Basic Crypto Regulation in New York</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leticia-james-introduces-bill-that-would-birth-basic-crypto-regulation-in-new-york/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Opinion: Biden Will Go Down as the Most Anti-Crypto Leader in History</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-biden-will-go-down-as-the-most-anti-crypto-leader-in-history/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-biden-will-go-down-as-the-most-anti-crypto-leader-in-history/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 13:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OpEd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78213</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Between his shady infrastructure bill, attempting to shut the crypto industry out of traditional or standard financial products, and now a 30 percent tax proposal on all crypto mining operations, Joe Biden is arguably turning out to be the most anti-crypto “leader” in the history of the U.S. Biden + Crypto = Disasters! Crypto has<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-biden-will-go-down-as-the-most-anti-crypto-leader-in-history/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-biden-will-go-down-as-the-most-anti-crypto-leader-in-history/">Opinion: Biden Will Go Down as the Most Anti-Crypto Leader in History</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Between his shady <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-amendment-for-infrastructure-bill-leads-to-more-problems-and-infighting/" data-wpel-link="internal">infrastructure bill</a>, attempting to shut the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-biden-using-an-obama-era-program-to-ban-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">crypto industry out of traditional</a> or standard financial products, and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/biden-wants-to-tax-crypto-mining-companies-at-30/" data-wpel-link="internal">now a 30 percent tax</a> proposal on all crypto mining operations, Joe Biden is arguably turning out to be the most anti-crypto “leader” in the history of the U.S.</p>
<h2>Biden + Crypto = Disasters!</h2>
<p>Crypto has long been a taboo topic in American politics. As we all remember in 2019, some of the democratic hopefuls looking to make their way into the White House in 2020 built their campaigns on the ideas that crypto could be simplified. Men like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/andrew-yang-the-crypto-president/" data-wpel-link="internal">Andrew Yang</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-bloomberg-proposes-clarified-bitcoin-regulation-if-he-takes-the-white-house/" data-wpel-link="internal">Michael Bloomberg</a> said they would do all they could to make crypto laws easier to understand, and they would work to make the industry more mainstream.</p>
<p>However, neither figure was able to make waves with voters, and their plans ultimately came to immediate standstills.</p>
<p>In the end, democrats wound up with Joe Biden. The irony here is that in the beginning, Biden was touted as the man who would put <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/billybambrough/2020/11/15/why-joe-biden-could-be-big-for-bitcoin/?sh=389b95b5f688" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">crypto on the map</a>. He would make it a legitimate, mainstream asset class that could be utilized and enjoyed by all. Since then, however, he’s done the exact opposite, and his anti-crypto rhetoric has become all-too clear.</p>
<p>Things got off to a rocky start in the summer of 2021, just a few months after he was inaugurated. Biden signed a new infrastructure bill into law that instead of working to rebuild our roads, hospitals, and schools (like the word “infrastructure” would imply), contained verbiage aimed at crypto holders. They would be required to report all transactions exceeding specific numbers, and the IRS would likely come down hard on them every April 15 beginning in the year 2024.</p>
<p>Things didn’t stop there, however. Biden initiated several weak economic policies and signed multiple trillion-dollar spending bills into law that ultimately caused record inflation and brought crypto prices down to their lowest points in 2022. That period now stands as the shakiest ever for crypto.</p>
<p>Then, news spread that Biden was working to implement an Obama-era policy that would shut out all crypto businesses from traditional financial tools and services. Things like checking accounts, for example, would no longer be accessible to these firms, but just when you thought things couldn’t get any worse, America’s phony president announced he was urging Congress to consider a 30 percent tax proposal on all crypto mining businesses.</p>
<h2>Trying to Ruin the Mining Sector?</h2>
<p>This would undoubtedly bring the industry to a halt given mining’s where the money is at. It’s also what gives crypto life and brings new digital units into circulation. By defeating miners, you defeat the entire crypto arena.</p>
<p>At this stage, anyone who felt Biden would be America’s “crypto president” should be hiding in shame.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-biden-will-go-down-as-the-most-anti-crypto-leader-in-history/">Opinion: Biden Will Go Down as the Most Anti-Crypto Leader in History</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-biden-will-go-down-as-the-most-anti-crypto-leader-in-history/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=3910 metric#misses=5 metric#hit-ratio=99.9 metric#bytes=6623499 metric#prefetches=394 metric#store-reads=16 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=400 metric#store-misses=0 metric#sql-queries=17 metric#ms-total=245.34 metric#ms-cache=16.90 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.9939 metric#ms-cache-ratio=6.9 -->
