<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 03:07:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Small Nation of Bhutan Has Been Hoarding a Lot of Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-small-nation-of-bhutan-has-been-hoarding-a-lot-of-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-small-nation-of-bhutan-has-been-hoarding-a-lot-of-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 17:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bhutan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Duncan Bonfield]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77920</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bhutan is a small country lodged between India, Nepal, and China on the continent of Asia. Its biggest claims to fame are its architecture, its vast open landscapes… and the big crypto stash that the nation has allegedly been hiding from the world all this time. Bhutan Has Been Hiding a Lot of Crypto Bhutan<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-small-nation-of-bhutan-has-been-hoarding-a-lot-of-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-small-nation-of-bhutan-has-been-hoarding-a-lot-of-crypto/">The Small Nation of Bhutan Has Been Hoarding a Lot of Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bhutan is a small country lodged between India, Nepal, and China on the continent of Asia. Its biggest claims to fame are its architecture, its vast open landscapes… and the big crypto stash that the nation has <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/iainmartin/2023/04/15/the-tiny-kingdom-of-bhutan-secretly-held-millions-of-dollars-in-cryptocurrency/?sh=275021ab7f1d" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">allegedly been hiding from</a> the world all this time.</p>
<h2>Bhutan Has Been Hiding a Lot of Crypto</h2>
<p>Bhutan is a miniscule and obscure nation. It also doesn’t appear to have all the technological advancements of its neighbors. The region only began supporting cell phone usage about 20 years ago, and in many areas, traffic lights are still absent or in the process of being put up. One wouldn’t assume that a country like Bhutan would be all that into crypto or the technology that supports it, but new court documents suggest otherwise.</p>
<p>These papers revealed that the sovereign investment arm of Bhutan was a big customer of both Block Fi and Celsius, two crypto lending platforms that <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-in-the-age-of-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">went bust in 2022</a> (arguably the most bearish year on record for the crypto industry). The losses of the nation were never disclosed up until now. It is estimated that this investment division is worth just shy of $3 billion, meaning the country has more money stashed away than it’s been letting on all this time.</p>
<p>The investment firm is known as Druk Holding &amp; Investments. It’s believed the institution has been accumulating crypto since 2022, which is interesting because while the country was clearly able to gather millions of dollars in digital currency units over the course of a single year, it clearly chose the worst time to do so given how badly everything crashed during that time.</p>
<p>Right now, Druk says it’s sworn to secrecy about the matter of how much it’s lost, though it did say it engaged in a court battle with Block Fi that has since been settled. It’s not known how the money accumulated nor what the company was planning to do with all the funds. Druk’s CEO Ujjwal Deep Dahal commented in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>We do not have any comments as the matter with Block Fi has been settled. We are not able to comment due to confidentiality.</p></blockquote>
<p>Duncan Bonfield – chief executive of the International Forum of Sovereign Wealth Funds – also threw his two cents into the mix, stating:</p>
<blockquote><p>We have seen no real interest in cryptocurrency as an asset class, and we do not believe any of our members have an allocation to crypto in their portfolios.</p></blockquote>
<h2>You Couldn&#8217;t Even Visit</h2>
<p>Bhutan is a relative newcomer to “modern society” and visitors in many ways. The nation could not be traveled to until 1974, and that only occurred as a means of building its economy through tourism.</p>
<p>Prior to that, the nation had fallen victim to a pandemic that prohibited all foreigners from entering.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-small-nation-of-bhutan-has-been-hoarding-a-lot-of-crypto/">The Small Nation of Bhutan Has Been Hoarding a Lot of Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-small-nation-of-bhutan-has-been-hoarding-a-lot-of-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Anthony Scaramucci is Still a Big Bitcoin Fan</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/anthony-scaramucci-is-still-a-big-bitcoin-fan/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/anthony-scaramucci-is-still-a-big-bitcoin-fan/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 15:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthony Scaramucci]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jamie dimon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77917</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Anthony Scaramucci of Skybridge Capital says he’s never been more bullish on bitcoin as he is now. Scaramucci Has Good Reason to Love BTC In many ways, his words make sense, and Scaramucci has a big, giant reason to be bullish. After all, the world’s number one digital currency by market cap recently hit $30K<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/anthony-scaramucci-is-still-a-big-bitcoin-fan/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/anthony-scaramucci-is-still-a-big-bitcoin-fan/">Anthony Scaramucci is Still a Big Bitcoin Fan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Anthony Scaramucci of Skybridge Capital says <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/anthony-scaramucci-says-he-is-more-bullish-on-bitcoin-now-than-ever-before-incredibly-sturdy-bizarrely-anti-fragile-asset-class/ar-AA19UgZq" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">he’s never been more</a> bullish on bitcoin as he is now.</p>
<h2>Scaramucci Has Good Reason to Love BTC</h2>
<p>In many ways, his words make sense, and Scaramucci has a big, giant reason to be bullish. After all, the world’s number one digital currency by market cap <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">recently hit $30K for</a> the first time in about 11 months, and 2023 appears to be directing bitcoin on a healing path that’s likely to reverse all the damage done during the previous year, which was arguably the worst on record for BTC.</p>
<p>In a recent discussion, Scaramucci commented that bitcoin has been enduring some hardcore boom-bust cycles in which it goes up quite high then crashes down very low. He says this all coincides with the halving process, and how interesting (and coincidental, in many ways) bitcoin is going to endure another halving event next year in 2024.</p>
<p>He also says that the mainstream media has been giving bitcoin and crypto a lot more attention as of late. He commented that this is likely leading to a lot of the rising and falling we’re seeing in the BTC cycles. In addition, he says bitcoin wallets have never been available on such a large scale.</p>
<p>This, in turn, has led to a bit of an issue in that many fraud schemes have emerged in recent months and years, something that he feels has brought down the reputation and the legitimacy of the space. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>What happened almost right on time is the intersection of fraud and over-leverage, which always happens in the age of new technology… The technology that we have now can create a bee swarm.</p></blockquote>
<p>He says that there have been many elements leading up to the present anti-crypto stance taken by Gary Gensler, who heads the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Among them are the many crypto companies collapsing in America such as <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/celsius-network-is-next-crypto-company-to-file-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">Celsius</a>, and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block-fi-is-the-latest-crypto-company-to-go-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">Block Fi</a>.</p>
<p>Despite this, however, he’s convinced bitcoin is an “incredibly sturdy” and “anti-fragile asset class,” and he believes the currency is going to end the year in the $40,000 or $50,000 price range.</p>
<h2>Some Things Remain in the Way</h2>
<p>He further said that there are individuals out there that are going to do everything they can to bring bitcoin down. Among them are people like Charlie Munger – Warren Buffett’s right hand man – and Jamie Dimon, who’s the head of JPMorgan, arguably one of the biggest financial institutions in the world. Speaking about the latter, Scaramucci said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Jamie Dimon is probably the smartest person in financial services history since the original J.P. Morgan, and there&#8217;s no way if you got him unplugged and you got him with truth serum in him that he would say to you that bitcoin is a decentralized bedrock.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/anthony-scaramucci-is-still-a-big-bitcoin-fan/">Anthony Scaramucci is Still a Big Bitcoin Fan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/anthony-scaramucci-is-still-a-big-bitcoin-fan/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New York Town of Brasher Implements Crypto Moratorium</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-town-of-brasher-implements-crypto-moratorium/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-town-of-brasher-implements-crypto-moratorium/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 13:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brasher]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New York]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77914</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Right when we thought New York was going to become a more crypto-friendly state, the region of Brasher announced it is implementing a six-month cryptocurrency moratorium on all digital currency mining and related activities. Brasher Ain&#8217;t Too Keen on Crypto Mining The moratorium is set to go into effect on April 30 and will expire<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-town-of-brasher-implements-crypto-moratorium/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-town-of-brasher-implements-crypto-moratorium/">New York Town of Brasher Implements Crypto Moratorium</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Right when we thought New York was going to become a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-to-allow-crypto-mining-firm-block-fusion-to-set-up-shop/" data-wpel-link="internal">more crypto-friendly state</a>, the region of Brasher announced it is implementing a six-month cryptocurrency moratorium <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/brasher-town-board-places-six-221900643.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">on all digital currency</a> mining and related activities.</p>
<h2>Brasher Ain&#8217;t Too Keen on Crypto Mining</h2>
<p>The moratorium is set to go into effect on April 30 and will expire on October 31 unless it gets renewed by city council members. Representatives of the town of Brasher issued the following statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>The town board believes that such a moratorium will protect the public interest and welfare of the residents of the town until such comprehensive regulations are adopted. There are currently no regulations regulating cryptocurrency mining operations except the current moratorium within the town.</p></blockquote>
<p>Town Supervisor Mark A. Peets said Brasher currently doesn’t house any specific digital currency companies, though he mentioned they don’t want to let anyone in without proper regulation in place. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We&#8217;re not allowing cryptocurrency until we have regulations. Before we allow people to go into that business, we want to be able to come up with some rules and regulations.</p></blockquote>
<p>Right now, he believes there’s too much concern surrounding the amount of electricity that such operations often require. For the past several years, we <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-bitcoin-mining-may-require-more-energy-than-180-countries/" data-wpel-link="internal">have seen many reports</a> come out saying that bitcoin and crypto mining often uses more energy than third-world countries, and that this is putting Mother Earth on a deadly path. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>They&#8217;d be using a whole lot of electricity. It&#8217;s going to put a burden on the electric system that we are now supposed to use for other things. So, until we can regulate it properly in the town of Brasher through our zoning laws, we&#8217;re just not going to allow people to come because there&#8217;s a section in the town of Brasher where folks get their electricity from the Massena Electric Department, which is a cheap rate… In the MED section of the town, we want to have some regulations put in place before we allow something like that to happen within the town.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also said that while one company (which is unnamed at the time of writing) inquired about setting up shop within the region’s borders, he’s not even sure if Brasher has the kind of resources this enterprise is looking for. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>It&#8217;s not set up for what they want. They want three-phase power, and there is no three-phase power in that area. So, they can&#8217;t just put something in without us being able to look at our zoning laws before we even allow something.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Too Many Environmental Issues?</h2>
<p>Regarding further environmental impacts, Peets said:</p>
<blockquote><p>These devices pull off a lot of heat, so much that they would need air conditioning, or they would vent it out into the atmosphere.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-town-of-brasher-implements-crypto-moratorium/">New York Town of Brasher Implements Crypto Moratorium</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-town-of-brasher-implements-crypto-moratorium/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EOS Price Analysis: Bears In Control Below $0.90</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bears-in-control-below-0-90/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bears-in-control-below-0-90/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 05:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EOS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78500</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>EOS price started a fresh decline below the $0.880 level against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $0.850 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.851 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bears-in-control-below-0-90/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bears-in-control-below-0-90/">EOS Price Analysis: Bears In Control Below $0.90</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>EOS price started a fresh decline below the $0.880 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $0.850 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.851 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to decline if it stays below the $0.850 and $0.875 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>EOS price is struggling below $0.90 against the US Dollar, unlike <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-another-increase-to-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. The price might attempt to recover if there is a clear move above $0.875.</em></p>
<h2>EOS Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, EOS price saw a steady decline from the $0.912 resistance against the US Dollar. The price traded below the $0.90 and $0.88 levels to move into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>The decline gained pace below the $0.850 level. It even spiked below $0.820. A low is formed near $0.817 and the price is now consolidating losses. EOS is trading well below $0.850 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-signs-of-recovery-toward-1-0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $0.840 level. It is near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.9118 swing high to the $0.8170 low. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.851 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair.</p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $0.875 level or the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.9118 swing high to the $0.8170 low.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $0.875 level could start a steady increase toward the $0.90 level. The next major resistance might be $0.912. Any more gains might send the price toward the $1.00 level. On the downside, immediate support is near $0.820.</p>
<p>The next key support is near the $0.812 level. If there is a downside break below the $0.812 support, the price could test the $0.800 support in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_78501" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/EOS-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78501" class="size-full wp-image-78501" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/EOS-3.png" alt="EOS Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78501" class="wp-caption-text">EOS Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/EOSUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, EOS price is now trading below the $0.850 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to decline if it stays below the $0.850 and $0.875 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for EOS/USD is gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $0.820 and $0.800.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $0.850 and $0.875.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bears-in-control-below-0-90/">EOS Price Analysis: Bears In Control Below $0.90</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bears-in-control-below-0-90/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Might Protect $80</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-might-protect-80/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-might-protect-80/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 03:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78497</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin started a downside correction from the $95 zone against the US Dollar. LTC price is now trading below $90 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $85 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-might-protect-80/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-might-protect-80/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Might Protect $80</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Litecoin started a downside correction from the $95 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>LTC price is now trading below $90 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $85 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair remains supported for a fresh increase unless there is a clear move below $80.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Litecoin price is correcting gains from $95 against the US Dollar, similar to bitcoin. LTC price could resume its increase if it remains well supported above the $80 level.</em></p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, there was a decent increase in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-another-increase-to-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-aims-fresh-increase-above-1850/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Ethereum</a>, Ripple, and Litecoin against the US Dollar. Earlier, LTC formed a base above the $80 level and started a fresh increase.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above the $85 and $90 resistance levels. The price even climbed above the $92 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). However, the bears were active near the $95 zone. A high was formed near $95.00 and the price started a downside correction.</p>
<p>There was a move below the $90 level. The price traded below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $75.32 swing low to the $95.00 high. Besides, there was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $85 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>It is now trading below $90 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $85 level.</p>
<p>The next major resistance sits near the $90 level. A clear move above the $90 level could pump the price toward the $95 level. Any more gains might call for a test of $100. Immediate support is near the $82.80 level or the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $75.32 swing low to the $95.00 high.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $80 zone. A downside break below the $80 support might start a strong decline.</p>
<div id="attachment_78498" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Litecoin-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78498" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78498" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Litecoin-3.png" alt="Litecoin (LTC) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78498" class="wp-caption-text">Litecoin (LTC) Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Litecoin price is trading below $90 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price remains supported for a fresh increase unless there is a clear move below $80.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LTC/USD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $82.80 and $80.00</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $85 and $90.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-might-protect-80/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Might Protect $80</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-might-protect-80/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The U.K. Paves the Way for Bitcoin Futures Options</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-u-k-paves-the-way-for-bitcoin-futures-options/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-u-k-paves-the-way-for-bitcoin-futures-options/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 17:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Futures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[U.K.]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77910</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The London Stock Exchange Group (LSEG) has joined hands with Global Futures and Options (GFO-X) to give the U.K. access to regulated trading and clearing in both bitcoin index futures and options. The U.K. is Changing Its Attitude Towards Crypto The U.K. has had a very up-and-down history with bitcoin and digital currencies. Not long<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-u-k-paves-the-way-for-bitcoin-futures-options/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-u-k-paves-the-way-for-bitcoin-futures-options/">The U.K. Paves the Way for Bitcoin Futures Options</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The London Stock Exchange Group (LSEG) has joined hands with Global Futures and Options (GFO-X) to give the U.K. access to <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-ca/money/topstories/lseg-teams-with-digital-trading-platform-to-offer-bitcoin-futures-and-options/ar-AA19PDKk" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">regulated trading and clearing</a> in both bitcoin index futures and options.</p>
<h2>The U.K. is Changing Its Attitude Towards Crypto</h2>
<p>The U.K. has had a very up-and-down history with bitcoin and digital currencies. Not long ago, the country’s financial watchdog (known as the FCA) <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fca-rules-all-crypto-atms-in-the-uk-are-operating-illegally/" data-wpel-link="internal">announced that</a> all bitcoin ATMs would be banned from the region. The agency cited the use of bitcoin ATMs in fraud as the reason for the ban, suggesting investors could not be protected if they continued to utilize these machines.</p>
<p>But the U.K. is beginning to change its attitude towards the world of digital assets, recently voicing its desire to serve as a major bitcoin and blockchain hub of the world. This attitude stems from the <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/11/01/what-rishi-sunak-as-pm-means-for-the-uk-crypto-industry.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">country’s new prime minister</a>, who has stated he would like the U.K. to serve as the next big center for crypto-based innovation.</p>
<p>In addition, the nation has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-united-kingdom-announces-plans-for-new-crypto-regulations/" data-wpel-link="internal">become one of the first to instill major</a> digital asset regulation, citing the November 2022 <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">fall of FTX</a> as the reason why. The United Kingdom doesn’t want another instance like that, and it’s looking to ensure all crypto traders residing on the island remain safe and sound while trading virtual assets.</p>
<p>In addition to regulated trading and futures, the LSEG is also planning the release of a separate product dubbed Digital Asset Clear, which will enable cash-settled, dollar-denominated digital asset trading on the GFO-X. Once European Union officials give the greenlight on these services, they’re likely to become available during the fourth quarter of this year. GFO-X explained in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>GFO-X is taking the first steps to extracting efficiencies from new technologies within a traditional market structure, with the goal over time of delivering 24/7 trading to global regulated digital asset markets.</p></blockquote>
<p>Products like this are nothing new given organizations like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/cme-group/" data-wpel-link="internal">the CME Group</a> in Chicago have been offering bitcoin futures trading for some time, but it’s nice to know the breadth is expanding and that further organizations are beginning to see the light when it comes to futures options. This will only allow the digital currency arena to grow and become more mainstream and legitimate.</p>
<p>Arnab Sen – chief executive and co-founder of GFO-X – commented in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Recent market events in the trading of digital assets have highlighted the need for a safe, regulated venue where large financial institutions can trade at scale while keeping their clients’ assets protected.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Working Towards the Greater Good</h2>
<p>Frank Soussan – head of Digital Asset Clear – also threw his two cents into the mix with:</p>
<blockquote>
<p data-t="{&quot;n&quot;:&quot;blueLinks&quot;}">We look forward to working with GFO-X and market participants alike to build a liquid, regulated marketplace for these products and contributing to its safe growth and development.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-u-k-paves-the-way-for-bitcoin-futures-options/">The U.K. Paves the Way for Bitcoin Futures Options</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-u-k-paves-the-way-for-bitcoin-futures-options/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Report: With Recent Bitcoin Gains, &#8220;Hodling&#8221; Is Becoming More Common</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-with-recent-bitcoin-gains-hodling-is-becoming-more-common/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-with-recent-bitcoin-gains-hodling-is-becoming-more-common/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 15:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HODLing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77908</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has been doing quite well as of late. The currency just hit $30K for the first time in about 11 months, and everyone is on pins and needles about where the world’s number one digital currency will do next. The Bitcoin Price Hikes Are Leading to More Hodling The asset is doing so well,<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-with-recent-bitcoin-gains-hodling-is-becoming-more-common/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-with-recent-bitcoin-gains-hodling-is-becoming-more-common/">Report: With Recent Bitcoin Gains, &#8220;Hodling&#8221; Is Becoming More Common</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has been doing quite well as of late. The currency <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">just hit $30K for</a> the first time in about 11 months, and everyone is on pins and needles about where the world’s number one digital currency will do next.</p>
<h2>The Bitcoin Price Hikes Are Leading to More Hodling</h2>
<p>The asset is doing so well, in fact, that hodling has <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/bitcoin-hoarding-in-personal-wallets-signals-support-after-jump-to-30-000-bofa-says/ar-AA19Ko6p" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">become much more prominent</a> in recent weeks. Initially written out to be “holding,” the term was misspelled online as “hodling” and it’s been utilized ever since when talking about holding the asset in one’s wallet and refusing to sell it, no matter what the market conditions may be.</p>
<p>In a new report issued by Bank of America, it appears the practice of “hodling” is getting to be more common. Prior, many people were in the process of selling their digital assets given how poorly 2022 went. It was an embarrassment and a disgrace to see currencies like bitcoin lose more than 70 percent of their value (the asset fell from an all-time high of about $68,000 to the mid-$16K range), and there didn’t seem to be much sense in holding these currencies given how weak the prospects were.</p>
<p>But now, it looks like things are changing. The B of A report says:</p>
<blockquote><p>Investors transfer tokens from exchange wallets to their personal wallets when they intend to hold them (or HODL), indicating a potential decrease in sell pressure.</p></blockquote>
<p>It’s become clear that many more investors are gaining their trust of the digital currency world back. They are confident that things can return to normal, and that these assets still have a lot to offer regardless of last year’s pathetic results. Hong Fang – president of the digital currency exchange OKX – said in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin is becoming a very clear safe haven for a lot of the issues we’re having right now.</p></blockquote>
<p>He was commenting on the fact that the Federal Reserve made it known that <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/federal-reserve-hikes-rates-again-what-will-happen-to-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">2023 will not be a year</a> in which interest rate hikes stop, like so many analysts originally thought. In fact, Fed Chair Jerome Powell recently came out and said that inflation is still a problem in nations like the U.S., and he and his associates will do all they can to fight it (this includes pushing rates up even further).</p>
<h2>Staying Strong Regardless of the News</h2>
<p>Despite all this, it seems as though bitcoin is developing a thicker skin, and negative news is no longer hurting it the way it did last year. Nathan Batchelor – managing partner at analytics platform Biyond Trader – said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin has stopped reacting to bad news. This is a tell-tale sign of a strong buyers’ market.</p></blockquote>
<p>In the meantime, other assets are also pumping fast. Ethereum, for example, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-ethereum-shapella-upgrade-occurred-now-what/" data-wpel-link="internal">recently endured its</a> Shapella upgrade and rose to about $1,900 per unit.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-with-recent-bitcoin-gains-hodling-is-becoming-more-common/">Report: With Recent Bitcoin Gains, &#8220;Hodling&#8221; Is Becoming More Common</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-with-recent-bitcoin-gains-hodling-is-becoming-more-common/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vitalik Buterin Wants to Fix All ETH Scaling Issues Before the Next Bull Run</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vitalik-buterin-wants-to-fix-all-eth-scaling-issues-before-the-next-bull-run/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vitalik-buterin-wants-to-fix-all-eth-scaling-issues-before-the-next-bull-run/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 13:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shapella]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vitalik buterin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77906</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The bitcoin price is getting a lot of hype as of late given that it recently hit $30K for the first time in about 11 months. The news is no doubt good, but Ethereum is also doing quite well and hogging up the spotlight considering it just went through its Shapella upgrade, and now the<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vitalik-buterin-wants-to-fix-all-eth-scaling-issues-before-the-next-bull-run/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vitalik-buterin-wants-to-fix-all-eth-scaling-issues-before-the-next-bull-run/">Vitalik Buterin Wants to Fix All ETH Scaling Issues Before the Next Bull Run</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The bitcoin price is getting a lot of hype as of late given that it <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">recently hit $30K for</a> the first time in about 11 months. The news is no doubt good, but Ethereum is also doing quite well and hogging up the spotlight <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-ethereum-shapella-upgrade-occurred-now-what/" data-wpel-link="internal">considering it just went</a> through its Shapella upgrade, and <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/04/14/next-bull-rull-ethereum-founder-issues-bullish-prediction-after-game-changing-upgrade-helps-bitcoin-price-rally/?sh=25f743a0497f" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">now the co-founder</a> of ETH Vitalik Buterin is confident another bull run is on its way.</p>
<h2>Vitalik Buterin Has Big Plans for Ethereum</h2>
<p>However, he’s adamant that crypto scaling issues need to be fixed before it arrives or else the bull run is likely to suffer. In a recent interview, Buterin commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>If we dont fix scaling before the next bull run, people are going to be stuck paying $500 transaction fees.</p></blockquote>
<p>It’s unclear if he’s planning for this to be part of the next big upgrade, which hasn’t officially been announced yet. Thus far, the currency has endured two major upgrades over the course of eight months. The first took place in September and was known as <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/merge/" data-wpel-link="internal">The Merge</a>. It was a situation where the proof of work module that Ethereum relied on came to an end, and the currency moved to proof of stake.</p>
<p>This allowed the asset to become eco-friendlier in that it used far less energy, transactions became less expensive, and the network moved much quicker. With this new Shapella upgrade, the currency units that’ve been staked all this time are suddenly available for withdrawal. Buterin continued his discussion by stating:</p>
<blockquote><p>The Shapella upgrade closes the loop on some things that are part of the PoS [proof of stake] transition but did not make it in time for The Merge, withdrawals obviously being really important. The immediate next focus after this… is going to be scaling.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Could Bigger Investors Get Involved?</h2>
<p>The Shapella upgrade is getting a lot of attention from outside parties, and some analysts are confident the recent price surges Ethereum has endured as a result could wind up attracting the attention of Wall Street and institutional investors. Mona El Isa, the chief executive of crypto firm Avantgarde Finance, said in a recent statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>The highly anticipated Ethereum Shanghai upgrade is potentially game-changing and could be the catalyst towards digital assets becoming mainstream in the majority of funds… This newfound liquidity will be seen as a move to de-risking digital asset allocations by institutional investors, who have previously been put off by Ethereum’s old version that locked money in. With the removal of a major barrier, we would expect to see a rapid move towards investors staking Ethereum, which could prove bullish for the price of the asset long-term.</p></blockquote>
<p>At the time of writing, Ethereum – the world’s second largest digital currency by market cap and the number one competitor to bitcoin – has shot into the $1,900 range.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vitalik-buterin-wants-to-fix-all-eth-scaling-issues-before-the-next-bull-run/">Vitalik Buterin Wants to Fix All ETH Scaling Issues Before the Next Bull Run</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vitalik-buterin-wants-to-fix-all-eth-scaling-issues-before-the-next-bull-run/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Rally Could Extend above $0.08</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-rally-could-extend-above-0-08-2/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-rally-could-extend-above-0-08-2/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 05:08:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78489</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tron price started a fresh increase from the $0.0710 level against the US Dollar. TRX price is now trading above $0.0765 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.0742 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could continue to move<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-rally-could-extend-above-0-08-2/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-rally-could-extend-above-0-08-2/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Rally Could Extend above $0.08</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Tron price started a fresh increase from the $0.0710 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>TRX price is now trading above $0.0765 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.0742 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move up if it breaks the $0.0795 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>TRON price started a fresh increase above $0.0750 against the US Dollar, outpacing <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-another-increase-to-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. TRX’s price could rise further if it clears the $0.0795 resistance.</em></p>
<h2>Tron Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few sessions, Tron price started a decent increase from the $0.0710 support zone against the US Dollar. TRX’s price remained well-bid and was able to climb above the $0.0750 zone.</p>
<p>It traded above the $0.0765 and $0.0782 levels to move further into a positive zone. However, the bears were active below the $0.080 level. A high is formed near $0.0798 and the price is now consolidating gains. It is trading above $0.0765 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-more-gains-possible-above-0-072/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>On the upside, TRX is facing resistance near the $0.0795 level. The next major resistance is near the $0.080 level. A close above $0.080 could send the price toward the $0.0825 resistance zone.</p>
<p>Any more gains might send TRX price toward $0.085, above which the price could even rise toward $0.088. On the downside, initial support is near the $0.0768 level or the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.0668 swing low to the $0.0798 high.</p>
<p>There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.0642 on the 4-hours chart. The next major support is now forming near $0.0732 or the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.0668 swing low to the $0.0798 high.</p>
<p>If there is a downside break below the $0.0732 support, the price might revisit the $0.0710 support. Any more losses might call for a move toward the $0.0700 zone in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_78490" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/TRON-TRX-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78490" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78490" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/TRON-TRX-3.png" alt="Tron (TRX) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78490" class="wp-caption-text">Tron (TRX) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/TRXUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that TRX’s price is now trading above $0.0765 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move up if it breaks the $0.0795 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for TRX/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for TRX/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.0765 and $0.0742.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.0795, $0.080, and $0.085.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-rally-could-extend-above-0-08-2/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Rally Could Extend above $0.08</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-rally-could-extend-above-0-08-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
