<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 13:34:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>More Than $3 Billion in Silk Road Bitcoin Funds Appear</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/more-than-3-billion-in-silk-road-bitcoin-funds-appear/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/more-than-3-billion-in-silk-road-bitcoin-funds-appear/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 17:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ross ulbricht]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Silk Road]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75446</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It’s been so many years, and yet the shadows of the dark web platform Silk Road are still with us. Silk Road operated under the illicit hand of Ross Ulbricht and was known for being a market where individuals could pay for drugs, guns, and other illegal items with bitcoin and cryptocurrency. A Lot of Silk Road<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/more-than-3-billion-in-silk-road-bitcoin-funds-appear/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/more-than-3-billion-in-silk-road-bitcoin-funds-appear/">More Than $3 Billion in Silk Road Bitcoin Funds Appear</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It’s been so many years, and yet the shadows of the dark web platform <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/silk-road/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/silk-road/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668540093481000&amp;usg=AOvVaw03ji7wWn_XyC_56P8oI4iS" data-wpel-link="internal">Silk Road</a> are still with us. Silk Road operated under the illicit hand of Ross Ulbricht and was known for being a market where individuals could pay for drugs, guns, and other illegal items with bitcoin and cryptocurrency.</p>
<h2>A Lot of Silk Road Money Has Suddenly Turned Up</h2>
<p>Now, it appears the U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ) has <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/11/07/us-doj-announces-seizure-of-3-36b-in-cryptocurrency/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://techcrunch.com/2022/11/07/us-doj-announces-seizure-of-3-36b-in-cryptocurrency/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668540093481000&amp;usg=AOvVaw1PpgGzdJKA23YnbXKpKtOC" data-wpel-link="exclude">seized more than</a> $3 billion in BTC from a man that “unlawfully obtained” about 50,000 units of the world’s number one digital currency by market cap from the dark market back in 2012. James Zhong of Gainesville, Georgia pleaded guilty in early November to committing wire fraud in September of that year and now faces as many as 20 years in jail. To think… Ross Ulbricht may soon have a new cellmate, one that was a former customer.</p>
<p>The money was seized from Zhong’s home back in 2021. At the time, the money was worth a whopping $3.36 billion. The assets were found in a safe under the floor and on a single-board computer hidden under blankets in a popcorn tin in Zhong’s bathroom.</p>
<p>Over $600K in cash was also recovered from the dwelling, as well as 25 individual Casascius coins and several gold and silver bars, meaning the DOJ has recovered a massive amount of money.</p>
<p>The whereabouts of the bitcoin has been unknown to authorities for a minimum of ten years, according to U.S. attorney Damian Williams. <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/doj-seizes-usd3-36-billion-in-second-largest-bitcoin-recovery-on-record-6826287" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.investopedia.com/doj-seizes-usd3-36-billion-in-second-largest-bitcoin-recovery-on-record-6826287&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668540093481000&amp;usg=AOvVaw1GO73o_4_rwIVLLKdrRpJE" data-wpel-link="exclude">In a press release</a>, he commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>For almost ten years, the whereabouts of this massive chunk of missing bitcoin had ballooned into an over $3.3 billion mystery… This case shows that we won’t stop following the money, no matter how expertly hidden, even to a circuit board in the bottom of a popcorn tin.</p></blockquote>
<p>The event marks the largest crypto seizure by the DOJ in history and its second largest financial seizure.</p>
<p>Silk Road is widely considered one of the main factors that has prevented bitcoin and digital currencies from entering mainstream territory. Many are concerned that these assets are utilized for criminal activities and thus should not be permitted as payment tools for everyday items and services. It can be argued that Silk Road is part of the reason as to why so many individuals feel uncomfortable around digital assets.</p>
<h2>Ross Ulbricht Created the Organization</h2>
<p>As the man in charge, Ross Ulbricht operated under the pseudonym “Dread Pirate Roberts” and launched the site in 2011. The market was well-known for its money laundering activities and for allowing individuals to purchase and sell illegal drugs with and for bitcoin.</p>
<p>By 2013, however, the site had been fully shut down by authorities in the U.S. and Ulbricht was later <a href="https://www.cnet.com/tech/services-and-software/convicted-silk-road-founder-ross-ulbricht-sentenced-to-life-in-prison/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.cnet.com/tech/services-and-software/convicted-silk-road-founder-ross-ulbricht-sentenced-to-life-in-prison/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668540093481000&amp;usg=AOvVaw3lu2cnqX_vTkJHN-7Ni5oc" data-wpel-link="external">handed a life sentence</a> for his alleged crimes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/more-than-3-billion-in-silk-road-bitcoin-funds-appear/">More Than $3 Billion in Silk Road Bitcoin Funds Appear</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/more-than-3-billion-in-silk-road-bitcoin-funds-appear/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Abu Dhabi Creates the MEAACBA Organization to Organize and Regulate Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/abu-dhabi-creates-meaaba-organization-organize-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/abu-dhabi-creates-meaaba-organization-organize-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 15:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[abu dhabi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MEAACBA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75442</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Abu Dhabi has launched a new organization it’s calling the Middle East, Africa, and Asia Crypto and Blockchain Association (MEAACBA). The non-profit is built to bring industry leaders together to discuss the major challenges the crypto industry brings to the region and to see how best to integrate crypto into everyday life. The MEAACBA Will Seek to<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/abu-dhabi-creates-meaaba-organization-organize-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/abu-dhabi-creates-meaaba-organization-organize-crypto/">Abu Dhabi Creates the MEAACBA Organization to Organize and Regulate Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Abu Dhabi has <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-ae/news/other/abu-dhabi-launches-blockchain-and-cryptocurrency-body/ar-AA13RUCT" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.msn.com/en-ae/news/other/abu-dhabi-launches-blockchain-and-cryptocurrency-body/ar-AA13RUCT&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668540093486000&amp;usg=AOvVaw3IEEPQFI2NZskVFlA9gaur" data-wpel-link="external">launched a new organization</a> it’s calling the Middle East, Africa, and Asia Crypto and Blockchain Association (MEAACBA). The non-profit is built to bring industry leaders together to discuss the major challenges the crypto industry brings to the region and to see how best to integrate crypto into everyday life.</p>
<h2>The MEAACBA Will Seek to Strengthen the Crypto Space</h2>
<p>Among the financial companies that have already joined the MEAABA include Bit Oasis, a Dubai-based digital currency exchange; Mid Chains, a trading platform; Crypto.com; Binance, and Rain Financial in Bahrain. Abu Dhabi says it wants to become the world’s leading financial hub, and it hopes to make crypto a staple of living and working in the region.</p>
<p>The MEAACBA chairman Ahmed Al Zaabi explained in a recent speech:</p>
<blockquote><p>The UAE is heading to become one of the best international financial centers, and we want to be a recognized contributor to the development of the diversified and sustained development of the UAE economy. We strongly believe that MEAACBA will constantly contribute towards the bolstering of the UAE’s digital economy and adoption… and will have an impact in the region and globally.</p></blockquote>
<p>Abu Dhabi is widely considered amongst several industry heads to be in a great place when it comes to crypto adoption. Stuart Isted – general manager for the Middle East and Africa branches of Crypto.com – explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>If you look at the US and UK market, they don’t have the same regulatory framework and intent from the regulator to build out an industry from the ground up, which is what the UAE has done.</p></blockquote>
<p>The UAE has cemented its position in the digital currency arena by being one of the few nations out there to instill appropriate regulatory tactics for the growing arena. Just a few weeks ago, Dubai said that it was now <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dubai-is-instilling-a-new-set-of-crypto-rules/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dubai-is-instilling-a-new-set-of-crypto-rules/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668540093486000&amp;usg=AOvVaw0Azjti13i73iEQn0d_lICC" data-wpel-link="internal">working to initiate a</a> new set of crypto-based laws that would ensure all traders remain safe and secure when engaging in transactions and that illicit actors had fewer opportunities to get involved in blockchain.</p>
<p>Like all crypto fanatics, Abu Dhabi has been suffering from the ongoing crypto winter. Jehanzeb Awan – chairman of the new association and founding partner of J Awan &amp; Partners in Dubai – said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We have had some very nice springs and summers, but also cold and chilly winters. Businesses are built on principles, not seasons. Therefore, we need a lot of effort to bring all industry players together.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Building Things from the Bottom Up</h2>
<p>According to Joseph Dallago – chief executive and co-founder of Rain Financial – 2022 has presented several opportunities to focus on the fundamentals of the crypto space rather than just prices. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>A lot of people focus on the speculative nature of the industry, but this year is a chance to focus on the fundamentals of the industry.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/abu-dhabi-creates-meaaba-organization-organize-crypto/">Abu Dhabi Creates the MEAACBA Organization to Organize and Regulate Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/abu-dhabi-creates-meaaba-organization-organize-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blockchain And AI In Finance: How Opposites Attract</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-and-ai-in-finance-how-opposites-attract/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-and-ai-in-finance-how-opposites-attract/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 13:34:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76030</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain technology and artificial intelligence were designed to solve different tasks. However, they can also be used together to solve long-standing problems in different industries. Blockchain and AI are currently used in sectors such as the automobile industry, supply chain and logistics, healthcare, media and entertainment, insurance, and more. It is also being implemented by<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-and-ai-in-finance-how-opposites-attract/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-and-ai-in-finance-how-opposites-attract/">Blockchain And AI In Finance: How Opposites Attract</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain technology and artificial intelligence were designed to solve different tasks. However, they can also be used together to solve long-standing problems in different industries. Blockchain and AI are currently used in sectors such as the automobile industry, supply chain and logistics, healthcare, media and entertainment, insurance, and more. It is also being implemented by AIWORK to address long-standing issues plaguing the online video space.</p>
<p>There are plenty of use cases where a combination of both technologies can be used. One industry that is being completely transformed by blockchain and AI is the financial services industry. This article will take a look at the role blockchain, and AI are playing in transforming finance.</p>
<h4><strong>What Is Blockchain Technology And AI?</strong></h4>
<p>Blockchain technology is a familiar concept, where a shared, immutable ledger allows users to share data with multiple users and initiate and complete transactions. Blockchains also store data and transaction details and can track orders, accounts, payments, production, goods, etc. Blockchain technology guarantees the fidelity and security of data and information stored on it without needing a third party.</p>
<p>Artificial Intelligence (AI), on the other hand, refers to machines capable of simulating human intelligence. AI-powered machines are capable of performing tasks that would typically require human intervention. They can also think like humans, mimic actions, and exhibit various qualities associated with the human mind, such as learning and problem-solving. AI can also partake in decision-making processes, rationalize and take actions that have the best chance of achieving a specified outcome. AI can also learn from data sets provided to it and get smarter and more efficient over time.</p>
<h4><strong>What Do They Have In Common?</strong></h4>
<p>Blockchain technology and AI are the definition of “opposites attract” because they don’t have much in common. However, what they do have in common is that both are leading innovations in the world today and have several use cases, both individually and in tandem. However, both play entirely different roles. Blockchain technology acts as a decentralized, immutable, and secure storage, while AI can process vast amounts of data but is typically centralized and opaque.</p>
<p>Blockchain struggles with efficiency and scalability, while AI has problems when it comes to transparency and privacy. This makes them ideal for one another, as they can address each other’s weaknesses. Using blockchain provides trust, privacy, and accountability to AI and its processes, while AI provides scalability and efficiency to the blockchain.</p>
<h4><strong>How Are Blockchain And AI Chaning Finance?</strong></h4>
<p>The financial industry has always been a leader when it comes to innovation and the implementation of new technologies, as it needs to stay ahead of the curve when it comes to security and data protection. So how is implementing blockchain technology and AI changing the financial ecosystem? For starters, AI can process data at exponential speeds, allowing financial institutions to leverage a significant amount of data and extract more insights, automate any repetitive tasks, and help make processes more efficient.</p>
<p>Blockchain technology is complementing this by adding greater transparency to financial processes. It also enables better access to financial markets through decentralized finance (DeFi) and smart contracts.</p>
<p>So, blockchain technology and AI can greatly improve finance by processing data faster, enabling transparency and decentralization, and introducing smart contracts. Let’s understand how exactly.</p>
<h4><strong>Securing Payment Networks</strong></h4>
<p>One of the most significant benefits of blockchain technology is its ability to function as a borderless payment network and enable frictionless payments involving low transaction costs. However, despite these concerns, lingering concerns around security hindered adoption. However, leveraging AI can help identify any inconsistent account activity and trigger human involvement. Additionally, other AI-related technologies, such as biometrics and behavioral analysis, can further eliminate any vulnerabilities.</p>
<h4><strong>Greater Efficiency</strong></h4>
<p>Financial systems that implement blockchain and AI solutions are typically looking to deliver improved speed and quality of services. By combining the two technologies to drive business processes, financial institutions can maximize their returns while also providing greater value to their customers.</p>
<h4><strong>Cheaper And Faster Payments</strong></h4>
<p>Most bank transactions are slow and cumbersome. Compare this with blockchain-based cross-border payments, which are quick and inexpensive because they cut out the middleman from the transaction. Implementing AI can further increase the speed and efficiency of transactions by reducing human intervention. Additionally, AI can help banks automate payment workflows by implementing image recognition in financial documents and using natural language processing to support payments.</p>
<h4><strong>In Closing</strong></h4>
<p>The current financial industry is highly centralized. The implementation of blockchain technology and AI can usher in a new era for finance, characterized by faster transaction speeds, increased transparency, and better security. The integration of AI would make it possible to process large amounts of data, while blockchain would improve transparency, security, and data management. However, while both show considerable promise, both have to be carefully integrated with currency operations.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-and-ai-in-finance-how-opposites-attract/">Blockchain And AI In Finance: How Opposites Attract</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-and-ai-in-finance-how-opposites-attract/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>TokenSociety.io Announces Acquisition of the Dippies NFT Project</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tokensociety-io-announces-acquisition-of-the-dippies-nft-project/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tokensociety-io-announces-acquisition-of-the-dippies-nft-project/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 13:23:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76026</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TokenSociety Acquires All Dippies NFT IP And Will Continue To Develop Dippies NFT Initiatives While Integrating The NFT Project Into Existing Partnerships Cheyenne, Wyoming &#8211; December 15, 2022 &#8211; Token Society, Inc., a Web3 incubator and metaverse project launchpad, announced today the acquisition of all of the intellectual property and assets of the Dippies NFT<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tokensociety-io-announces-acquisition-of-the-dippies-nft-project/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tokensociety-io-announces-acquisition-of-the-dippies-nft-project/">TokenSociety.io Announces Acquisition of the Dippies NFT Project</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>TokenSociety Acquires All Dippies NFT IP And Will Continue To Develop Dippies NFT Initiatives While Integrating The NFT Project Into Existing Partnerships</em></p>
<p><strong>Cheyenne, Wyoming &#8211; December 15, 2022 &#8211;</strong> <a href="https://tokensociety.io/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Token Society, Inc.</a>, a Web3 incubator and metaverse project launchpad, announced today the acquisition of all of the intellectual property and assets of the <a href="https://www.dippies.io/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Dippies NFT</a> and Dippies Vans NFT Projects based on a vote by the Dippies community council.</p>
<p>Dippies is a music-driven NFT project which has collaborated with <a href="https://www.deathrowofficial.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Death Row Records</a>, Snoop Dogg, Champ Medici, and Steve Aoki. The project was launched in March 2022, initially sold 8,888 NFTs, and later released 11K+ Dippies Vans NFTs to NFT holders to be used in a play-to-earn (P2E) racing game and as the holders’ key to the Dippieverse metaverse. To date, the two NFT collections have traded a combined 9,345 ETH in secondary trading volume on Opensea.</p>
<p>Under the terms of the acquisition, TokenSociety.io shall continue to develop the DippiesRaces P2E racing game which will now be enhanced to include a multi-player augmented reality version that <a href="https://altar.is/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Altar, Inc.</a> will develop. In addition, the Dippies NFT and Dippies Vans NFT owners will also have access to several other P2E games and metaverse spaces currently being developed by TokenSociety including MERCHX, <a href="https://www.xr.casino/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">CasinoXR</a>, and <a href="https://unitea.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">UniteaMeta</a>.</p>
<p>TokenSociety shall also integrate the Dippies community into their ecosystem of Web2 and Web3 companies, granting Dippies NFT owners access to a long list of utilities including access to live events hosted by TokenSociety, major music festivals hosted by Unitea Music, and opportunities to participate in television shows and movies currently in development with <a href="https://www.archstoneent.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Archstone Entertainment</a>.</p>
<p>In addition, Dippies NFTs shall also be integrated into the <a href="https://shopx.co/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">SHOPX</a> Web3 e-commerce platform. This will grant owners of Dippies NFTs the ability to utilize their Dippies NFT to access the SHOPX app in lieu of the SHOPX Licensing Token in order to create token-gated e-commerce stores. TokenSociety will also work with the Dippies NFT owners to develop intellectual property and products with their Dippies NFTs which can be monetized on the SHOPX platform or other distribution channels.</p>
<p>“The original vision of the Dippies project was to build a global community of rebellious individuals helping to create a more free world through decentralized business ventures. TokenSociety acquired this ethos and will bring it to life with the growing list of projects and strategic partnerships within our ecosystem”  Scott H. Weissman, co-founder and CEO. He added,  “We are excited to work with the Dippies NFT owners to develop valuable IP while providing the best metaverse and IRL experiences for the community.”</p>
<p><strong>About Token Society, Inc.</strong></p>
<p>Token Society, Inc, aka TokenSociety.io, is a Web3 incubator and metaverse project launchpad that owns the Gay Aliens Society (Gen 1) NFT, Dippies NFT, and Dippies Vans NFT. In addition, the company has ownership in OTH Network, Unitea Music, Altar, Inc., CasinoXR, NFTPromo Media, and the <em>Men of the House</em> TV Show.</p>
<p>Website: <a href="https://tokensociety.io/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">tokensociety.io</a><br />
Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/TheTokenSociety" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/TheTokenSociety</a><br />
Medium: <a href="https://medium.com/@thetokensociety" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://medium.com/@thetokensociety</a></p>
<p><strong> </strong><strong>About Dippies NFT</strong></p>
<p>Dippies are modern-day adaptations of hippies, with the same values. Ones that are more in touch with society, but who are still quietly carving their own path. Rather than refusing to take part in the system, Dippies are building businesses to layer themselves out of the system. The Dippies Van NFTs can be used in the DippieRaces P2E game and tuned up in the DippieGarage. Vote on future initiatives for the Dippieverse and join IRL events with like-minded individuals.</p>
<p>Website: <a href="https://www.dippies.io/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.dippies.io/</a><br />
Discord: <a href="https://discord.com/invite/dippies" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://discord.com/invite/dippies</a><br />
Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/DippiesNFT" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/DippiesNFT</a><br />
Instagram: <a href="https://www.instagram.com/dippiesnft/?utm_medium=copy_link" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.instagram.com/dippiesnft/?utm_medium=copy_link</a><br />
YouTube: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCqSy3hXZx-W1JqC5ZnNFBvg/featured" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCqSy3hXZx-W1JqC5ZnNFBvg/featured</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tokensociety-io-announces-acquisition-of-the-dippies-nft-project/">TokenSociety.io Announces Acquisition of the Dippies NFT Project</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tokensociety-io-announces-acquisition-of-the-dippies-nft-project/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blockchain Gets a Major Push from JPMorgan</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-gets-a-major-push-from-jpmorgan/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-gets-a-major-push-from-jpmorgan/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 13:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[JPMorgan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75440</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The blockchain arena is getting a big boost from financial giant JPMorgan, which recently completed its first cross-border transaction using the technology that’s become so prominent in the crypto space. JPMorgan Is Giving Defi a Real Boost The transaction occurred in the decentralized finance (defi) arena, thus bringing one of the world’s largest monetary institutions to the<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-gets-a-major-push-from-jpmorgan/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-gets-a-major-push-from-jpmorgan/">Blockchain Gets a Major Push from JPMorgan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The blockchain arena is getting a big boost from financial giant JPMorgan, <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/billybambrough/2022/11/06/a-massive-step-jpmorgan-just-made-a-surprize-game-changing-bet-on-crypto-despite-2-trillion-bitcoin-ethereum-and-crypto-price-crash/?sh=76aa15a1652d" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.forbes.com/sites/billybambrough/2022/11/06/a-massive-step-jpmorgan-just-made-a-surprize-game-changing-bet-on-crypto-despite-2-trillion-bitcoin-ethereum-and-crypto-price-crash/?sh%3D76aa15a1652d&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668540093491000&amp;usg=AOvVaw3NrNRYcZfXskwv5dg9dOF9" data-wpel-link="exclude">which recently completed</a> its first cross-border transaction using the technology that’s become so prominent in the crypto space.</p>
<h2>JPMorgan Is Giving Defi a Real Boost</h2>
<p>The transaction occurred in the decentralized finance (defi) arena, thus bringing one of the world’s largest monetary institutions to the world of autonomous banking. The move is being hailed as a real clincher for digital currency, and many believe this will push the space to new heights and broader levels of mainstream attention.</p>
<p>JPMorgan utilized Polygon to perform the transaction. Polygon is a blockchain system based on Ethereum technology. It’s a modified version of AAVE and is designed to help ETH scale while giving traders the opportunity to lend and borrow digital funds without the aid of third parties.</p>
<p>Mikkel Morch – chairman at the digital asset hedge fund ARK36 – commented in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Crypto enthusiasts have never doubted that innovation coming out of this space (especially innovation in defi) has the potential to make international banking cheaper, faster, and more efficient. Now, the giants of traditional finance are starting to confirm that by using defi protocols as a viable solution for streamlining international monetary trade.</p></blockquote>
<p>The irony of the situation is that JPMorgan has not always been kind to crypto. It’s head executive Jamie Dimon has been a very vocal critic of bitcoin and other digital assets in the past. <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jamie-dimon-expresses-more-hate-for-btc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jamie-dimon-expresses-more-hate-for-btc/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668540093491000&amp;usg=AOvVaw0hsGbzR_Gv47zKaI3bdbPL" data-wpel-link="internal">As recently as two</a> months ago, Dimon said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I’m a major skeptic of crypto tokens, which you call currency, like bitcoin. They are decentralized Ponzi schemes, and the notion that it’s good for anybody is unbelievable. It is dangerous.</p></blockquote>
<p>At the same time, his company has never hesitated to get involved in the crypto space, thus suggesting that while Dimon himself isn’t a fan, he recognizes there’s money to be made and business to be had in the future. A few years back, the <a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/business-47240760" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.bbc.com/news/business-47240760&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668540093491000&amp;usg=AOvVaw2kiBEewQ2FxTCABY4H78EV" data-wpel-link="external">company unveiled its very own</a> digital asset and described it as such:</p>
<blockquote><p>It can be moved just the way cryptocurrencies can be moved. Stable value, very low cost.</p></blockquote>
<p>Marcus Sotiriou – an analyst at digital asset broker Global Block – expressed his surprise that JPMorgan of all companies would be the one to engage in such a transaction. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>It’s a bit surprising to see JP Morgan at the forefront of this trend given how critical the bank’s CEO has been of the cryptocurrency space. But as the adage goes, actions speak louder than words.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Singapore Is Now Exploring Defi</h2>
<p>The event was overseen by the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS), which has recently unveiled a pilot program through which the company will explore defi applications for wholesale funding markets.</p>
<p>Many believe this is the first step towards bridging the gap between standard banking and crypto.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-gets-a-major-push-from-jpmorgan/">Blockchain Gets a Major Push from JPMorgan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-gets-a-major-push-from-jpmorgan/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Bears In Action, Can They Clear The $100 Support?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bears-in-action-can-they-clear-the-100-support/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bears-in-action-can-they-clear-the-100-support/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 06:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76023</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline from the $118 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below the $110 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $109 on the 4-hours chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bears-in-action-can-they-clear-the-100-support/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bears-in-action-can-they-clear-the-100-support/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Bears In Action, Can They Clear The $100 Support?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline from the $118 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below the $110 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $109 on the 4-hours chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it breaks the $106 and $105 support levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin cash price is declining from the $118 zone against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-more-upsides-18k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. BCH/USD could decline heavily if there is a move below $105.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin cash price struggled to gain pace for a move above the $118 and $120 resistance levels. BCH formed a high near $117.43 and started a fresh decline.</p>
<p>There was a clear move below the $112 and $110 support levels. The bears even pushed the price below the $110 support and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-fresh-increase-possible-above-this-resistance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. It traded as low as $102.26 before there was an upside correction.</p>
<p>The price climbed above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $117.43 swing high to $102.26 low. However, the price is struggling to rise above the $110 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</p>
<p>It failed near the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $117.43 swing high to $102.26 low. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $109 on the 4-hours chart of the BCH/USD pair.</p>
<p>An immediate support on the downside is near the $107 zone. The next major support is near the $105 level, below which the bears might aim $100. The next target for them may perhaps be near the $90 level.</p>
<p>On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $109 level or the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). The first major resistance is near the $112 level. The main resistance sits near the $120 level.</p>
<p>Any more gains above $118 and $120 could set the pace for a move towards the $132 level. If there is a move above the $132 resistance, the price could rise towards the $140 zone.</p>
<div id="attachment_76024" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Bitcoin-Cash-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76024" class="size-full wp-image-76024" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Bitcoin-Cash-2.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76024" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Cash Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BCHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, bitcoin cash price is now trading below the $110 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it breaks the $106 and $105 support levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for BCH/USD is gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BCH/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $105 and $100.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $110 and $112.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bears-in-action-can-they-clear-the-100-support/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Bears In Action, Can They Clear The $100 Support?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bears-in-action-can-they-clear-the-100-support/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LBank Exchange Will List Tokamak Network (TOKAMAK) on December 16, 2022</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-tokamak-network-tokamak-on-december-16-2022/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-tokamak-network-tokamak-on-december-16-2022/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 19:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76020</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec 15, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list Tokamak Network (TOKAMAK) on December 16, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the TOKAMAK/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading at 13:00 UTC on December 16, 2022. As an on-demand Ethereum layer 2 platform, Tokamak<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-tokamak-network-tokamak-on-december-16-2022/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-tokamak-network-tokamak-on-december-16-2022/">LBank Exchange Will List Tokamak Network (TOKAMAK) on December 16, 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec 15, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list Tokamak Network (TOKAMAK) on December 16, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the TOKAMAK/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading at 13:00 UTC on December 16, 2022.</p>
<p>As an on-demand Ethereum layer 2 platform, <a href="https://etherscan.io/token/0x2be5e8c109e2197D077D13A82dAead6a9b3433C5" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Tokamak Network</a> (TOKAMAK) builds and connects layer 2 networks with multiple protocols integrated, including Optimistic Rollups, zk Rollups, Tokamak Plasma, and more. Its native token TOKAMAK will be listed on LBank Exchange at 13:00 UTC on December 16, 2022, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision.</p>
<p><strong>Introducing Tokamak Network</strong></p>
<p>Tokamak Network is an on-demand Ethereum layer 2 platform for building and connecting layer 2 networks. The vision is to make at least half of Ethereum transactions be stored and processed within Tokamak Layer 2 Network.</p>
<p>Ethereum is a powerful platform for decentralized applications, but it has limitations such as low TPS, high transaction fee, no customization, etc. To provide solutions, Tokamak Network supports easy layer 2 network deployment, enabling users to build customizable layer 2 networks and achieve more growth with easy development. DApp developers can build their own layer2 with customization in terms of the amount of fee, the types of layer2, the types of fee including their own native token, stable coin, any other erc20. In addition, Tokamak Network develops the cross-layer2 message protocol for connecting each other layer2s without going through the base layer. The custom layer 2 network can be connected to any other layer 2 in the Integrated environment.</p>
<p>Protocols integrated by Tokamak Network include Optimistic Rollups, a layer 2 solution with on-chain data computed off-chain, with its validity verified with a fraud-proof system; zk Rollups, a layer-2 solution with on-chain data computed off-chain, with its validity always fully verified with validity proof (a.k.a. zero knowledge proof); and Tokamak Plasma, a fully EVM-compatible Plasma implementation secured with continuous-rebase.</p>
<p>There’s also Tokamak Network Swap that provides a way to swap one token with another token. In particular, it supports additional functionality to make the swap between Tokamak Network-related tokens easily. And TONStarter, a decentralized launchpad platform for Layer 2 projects, developed by Tokamak Network, where anyone can launch their blockchain project.</p>
<p>With all above features, Tokamak Network will close the gap between crypto economics and traditional economy by bridging peoples and decentralized applications, improve the quality of life through providing easy to use, easy to access decentralized application environment for whole universe, incorporate and integrate blockchain everywhere to make the world a better, easier place by applying it to various sectors in everyday life.</p>
<p><strong>About TOKAMAK Token</strong></p>
<p>TON (“TOKAMAK” on LBank due to the ticker duplication) is the native token of Tokamak Network. The network is governed by TON stakeholders. Decentralized governance allows network upgrades, ecosystem expansion, and protocol improvement to be coordinated and enacted autonomously.</p>
<p>In addition, to accelerate TON and TONStarter ecosystem growth, Tokamak Network introduced TOS, the native token in TONStarter ecosystem. TOS token holders can participate a launched project using their staked TON to acquire project tokens.</p>
<p>Staking TON provides a higher level of security for one’s layer 2 network. With cryptoeconomics for validators, Tokamak Network provides a higher level of security and sustainability than token-less solutions. Tokamak Network ensures that all layer 2 networks are fully verified from day one.</p>
<p>Based on ERC-20, the initial issue amount of TON is 50,000,000. The total supply amount details can be checked on its <a href="https://price.tokamak.network/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">web page</a>. It will be listed on LBank Exchange at 13:00 UTC on December 16, 2022, investors who are interested in the Tokamak Network investment can easily buy and sell TOKAMAK token on LBank Exchange by then. The listing of TOKAMAK token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p>
<p><strong>Learn More about</strong> <strong>TOKAMAK Token:</strong></p>
<p>Official Website: <a href="https://tokamak.network/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://tokamak.network/</a></p>
<p>Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/tokamak_network" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://t.me/tokamak_network</a></p>
<p>Discord: <a href="https://discord.gg/J4chV2zuAK" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://discord.gg/J4chV2zuAK</a></p>
<p>Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/tokamak_network" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/tokamak_network</a></p>
<p>Facebook: <a href="https://www.facebook.com/OntherInc" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://www.facebook.com/OntherInc</a></p>
<p>Medium: <a href="https://medium.com/onther-tech" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://medium.com/onther-tech</a></p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media: </strong></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Facebook</a></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong></p>
<p>LBK Blockchain Co. Limited</p>
<p>LBank Exchange</p>
<p><a href="mailto:marketing@lbank.info">marketing@lbank.info</a></p>
<p><a href="mailto:business@lbank.info">business@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-tokamak-network-tokamak-on-december-16-2022/">LBank Exchange Will List Tokamak Network (TOKAMAK) on December 16, 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-tokamak-network-tokamak-on-december-16-2022/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LBank Exchange Will List HUMAN Token (HMT) on December 15, 2022</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-human-token-hmt-on-december-15-2022/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-human-token-hmt-on-december-15-2022/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 19:28:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76017</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec 12, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list HUMAN Token (HMT) on December 15, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the HMT/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading at 13:00 UTC on December 15, 2022. Opening a new era of potential for human<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-human-token-hmt-on-december-15-2022/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-human-token-hmt-on-december-15-2022/">LBank Exchange Will List HUMAN Token (HMT) on December 15, 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec 12, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list HUMAN Token (HMT) on December 15, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the HMT/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading at 13:00 UTC on December 15, 2022.</p>
<p>Opening a new era of potential for human workers and businesses, HUMAN Protocol supports the creation of decentralized and automated job markets. Its native token <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/human/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">HUMAN Token</a> (HMT) will be listed on LBank Exchange at 13:00 UTC on December 15, 2022, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision.</p>
<p><strong>Introducing HUMAN Protocol</strong></p>
<p>HUMAN Protocol facilitates the tokenization, evaluation and rewarding of contribution, whether that is clicking a CAPTCHA, verifying price feeds for DeFi, writing a customer review, or a news article. Many kinds of work can be tokenized with HUMAN Protocol. It is a vastly flexible tool that enables any project to request work from humans and machines, while providing the automated infrastructure for third party tools to validate the quality of work, and initiate payout over multiple chains.</p>
<p>The HUMAN Routing Protocol (“HUMAN-RP”) is a new blockchain coordination layer to mediate agreement between parties operating on HUMAN Protocol. Key features include operator discovery, fee agreement, consensus job standards, staking/slashing, and governance support to enable seamless consensus-based network upgrades. This new layer relies on the HUMAN Token (“HMT”) to power these new features. Thee HUMAN-RP is designed to operate on multiple Layer-1 networks so that HUMAN actors can choose the best network for their requirements.</p>
<p>Opening a new era of potential for the AI industry, HUMAN Protocol is first being applied to data annotation tasks.  The HUMAN App is the first portal through which Workers solve jobs for HMT. This is the beginning of HUMAN work: trustless, global labor markets, bringing workers closer to the rewards of their work, and empowering scientists to make machines that can serve HUMANity.</p>
<p>Any project can access vast workpools to complete data-labeling tasks through HUMAN Protocol. This is an open-source offering, with no barriers to entry. Reducing time, costs, and increasing label quality can drastically improve the ML industry.</p>
<p>Currently, the Protocol supports image annotation through hCaptcha, with ongoing work to integrate CVAT (semi-automated image and video annotation), Audino (audio annotation), and SLEAP.AI, a tool born out of the Salk Institute for Biological Studies. Because the Protocol is uniquely flexible, it can support any vertical, such as video, audio, and text.</p>
<p>But data annotation is just the beginning. <a href="https://docs.humanprotocol.org/papers/litepaper/grants-program" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Grants have been awarded to nine projects</a>, with a wide variety of use cases. The HUMAN open-source community is now working to support many other apps and use cases.</p>
<p><strong>About HMT Token</strong></p>
<p>HUMAN Token (HMT) is the native token of HUMAN Protocol, and it is used to fund the processing of digitized work, and reward workers for their contribution. HUMAN-RP offers governance and staking rights to holders of HMT. Whoever locks up their HMT earns the right to vote on certain aspects of the Routing Protocol. Locked up tokens could also grant lower gas fees or collateral conversion costs. Lastly, a discount mechanism may be introduced to reduce fees if paid in HMT instead of other collateral.</p>
<p>Based on ERC-20, HMT has a total supply of 1 billion (i.e., 1,000,000,000) tokens, of which 23.4% is provided for presale, 3.7% is provided for purchasers, 22.4% is allocated to strategic partners, 7.5% is allocated to the team, 9.6% is provided for CoinList, 10.2% is for ecofund allocation, 1% is for issuing foundation, 19.8% is for operating foundation, and the remaining 2.5% is allocated to advisors.</p>
<p>HMT token will be listed on LBank Exchange at 13:00 UTC on December 15, 2022, investors who are interested in the HUMAN Protocol investment can easily buy and sell HMT token on LBank Exchange by then. The listing of HMT token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p>
<p><strong>Learn More about HMT Token:</strong></p>
<p>Official Website: <a href="https://humanprotocol.org/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://humanprotocol.org/</a></p>
<p>Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/humanprotocol_official" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://t.me/humanprotocol_official</a></p>
<p>Discord: <a href="https://discord.gg/x2Qcshd7hE" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://discord.gg/x2Qcshd7hE</a></p>
<p>Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/human_protocol" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/human_protocol</a></p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media: </strong></p>
<p>l  <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> </a><a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a></p>
<p>l  <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener"> </a><a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a></p>
<p>l  <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener"> </a><a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Facebook</a></p>
<p>l  <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> </a><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a></p>
<p>l  <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> </a><a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a></p>
<p>l  <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener"> </a><a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong></p>
<p>LBK Blockchain Co. Limited</p>
<p>LBank Exchange</p>
<p><u>marketing@lbank.info</u></p>
<p><u>business@lbank.info</u></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-human-token-hmt-on-december-15-2022/">LBank Exchange Will List HUMAN Token (HMT) on December 15, 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-human-token-hmt-on-december-15-2022/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Celebrity Coin v2 (CCV2) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/celebrity-coin-v2-ccv2-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/celebrity-coin-v2-ccv2-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 19:23:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76014</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec 12, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed Celebrity Coin v2 (CCV2) on December 12, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the CCV2/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading. As a project from and backed by celebrities, Celebrity Coin is here to revolutionise<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/celebrity-coin-v2-ccv2-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/celebrity-coin-v2-ccv2-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">Celebrity Coin v2 (CCV2) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec 12, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed Celebrity Coin v2 (CCV2) on December 12, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the CCV2/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading.</p>
<p>As a project from and backed by celebrities, Celebrity Coin is here to revolutionise the global entertainment industry by building a place for future celebrities. Its native token <a href="https://bscscan.com/token/0x89c487B7f6eAf4d4Ef992baAdBFA1e462d3034f0" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Celebrity Coin v2</a> (CCV2) has been listed on LBank Exchange on December 12, 2022, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision.</p>
<p><strong>Introducing Celebrity Coin</strong></p>
<p>Celebrity Coin is a project that aims to revolutionise the entertainment industry and give everyone equal opportunities to succeed. It will decentralise the film industry by creating an ecosystem with transparent rewards catered to the participant’s role and contributions. They will experience something new by taking upon the role of creator, curator, translator, reviewer, viewer, etc.</p>
<p>The mission of Celebrity Coin is to solve typical problems within blockchain technology. It builds a decentralised marketplace and streaming platform for all generations to create and share their films, series, music, and comedy videos. By leveraging blockchain technology, Celebrity Coin guarantee a secure and transparent environment with secure payment processes. It also allows artists to create their own content as NFT and sell them via the marketplace.</p>
<p>In addition, Celebrity Coin will be launching C-Exchange in the near future. The work on it is almost done and the team is just doing some final tweaks to make it a perfect platform for its users to buy/sell/trade different currencies using Celebrity Coin’s token. It will be first of its kind platform that is easily accessible to everyone. Besides C-Exchange, there will be more upcoming projects including smart phone mining C-Machine, live events streaming, Celebrity Blockchain, CC-Sports, C-Store, NFT C-Player, and many more.</p>
<p>Celebrity Coin provides the best environment for artists to create multiple income streams for themselves. At the same time, it allows users to explore specific content by accessing its digital products. Moving forward, Celebrity Coin will create the biggest and most Participant-Centric Film Ecosystem.</p>
<p><strong>About CCV2 Token</strong></p>
<p>Celebrity Coin introduces its digital token Celebrity Coin v2 (CCV2) for payments and revenue management for artists and users. The token will provide new possibilities in the film making industry. Leveraging the speed and redundancy of a decentralised ecosystem, Celebrity Coin will be able to deliver thousands of videos per second in a very accessible decentralised manner, making it easily scalable for an increasing and popular demand. The smart contract on the blockchain makes it the best place whereby content creator can share their passion for art.</p>
<p>Based on BEP-20, CCV2 has a total supply of 60 million (i.e., 60,000,000) tokens, of which 4% is provided for ICO, 15% is provided for building projects, 13% is allocated to the team, 49% is provided for minting reward, 13% is provided for members, 1% is allocated for legal and listing, 1% will be used for server maintenance, 2% goes into the emergency fund, and the remaining 2% will be used for R&amp;D.</p>
<p>CCV2 has been listed on LBank Exchange at 12:00 UTC on December 12, 2022, investors who are interested in the Celebrity Coin investment can easily buy and sell CCV2 token on LBank Exchange right now. The listing of CCV2 token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p>
<p><strong>Learn More about</strong> <strong>CCV2 Token:</strong></p>
<p>Official Website: <a href="https://celebritycoin.net" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://celebritycoin.net</a><br />
Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/celebritycoingroup" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://t.me/celebritycoingroup</a><br />
Facebook: <a href="https://www.facebook.com/studionationuk" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://www.facebook.com/studionationuk</a></p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media: </strong></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Facebook</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong></p>
<p>LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
LBank Exchange<br />
<a href="mailto:marketing@lbank.info">marketing@lbank.info</a><br />
<a href="mailto:business@lbank.info">business@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/celebrity-coin-v2-ccv2-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">Celebrity Coin v2 (CCV2) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/celebrity-coin-v2-ccv2-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
