<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 14:12:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Will Bitcoin Suddenly Be More Volatile Than Ethereum?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/will-bitcoin-suddenly-be-more-volatile-than-ethereum/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/will-bitcoin-suddenly-be-more-volatile-than-ethereum/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 17:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[volatility]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77537</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For what appears to be the first time in about 24 months, many crypto heads and analysts are saying bitcoin – the world’s number one digital currency by market cap – will be more volatile in the coming future than its closest relative Ethereum, which has long been the number two crypto and bitcoin’s primary<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/will-bitcoin-suddenly-be-more-volatile-than-ethereum/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/will-bitcoin-suddenly-be-more-volatile-than-ethereum/">Will Bitcoin Suddenly Be More Volatile Than Ethereum?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For what appears to be the first time in about 24 months, many crypto heads and analysts are saying bitcoin – the world’s number one digital currency by market cap – <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/crypto-market-witnesses-odd-relationship-between-bitcoin-ether-volatility-metrics-1032178382" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">will be more volatile</a> in the coming future than its closest relative Ethereum, which has long been the number two crypto and bitcoin’s primary competitor.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Is on the Verge of Beating Ethereum in the Volatility Dept.</h2>
<p>The funny thing about a statement like this is that throughout its short history, Ethereum has always been more volatile than its daddy. This is largely because the asset came second and has a lot less experience in the space. It is also largely reflective of a secondary market which usually finds itself victimized by macroeconomic problems.</p>
<p>Still, per new technical analyses of both assets, it appears bitcoin is more likely to endure hardcore swings in the coming months than Ethereum. Jeff Anderson, chief banking officer at quantitative trading firm and liquidity provider Folkvang, commented in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin is in the spotlight again as cracks in [the] fractional reserve banking system cause distrust in fiat systems. Bitcoin dominance has ripped higher this month as the market scrambles for hard money and protection from impending fiat supply inflation.</p></blockquote>
<p>The discussion also comes at an odd time given how strong bitcoin has been over the last two months. BTC endured a very harsh 2022 given that in November of 2021, it reached a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit, and just 12 months later, the currency had fallen into the mid-$16K range. That’s a loss of more than 70 percent in just a single year.</p>
<p>Sadly, many additional assets (including Ethereum) chose to follow in its footsteps and contribute further to the crashes of the space, thus causing the digital currency industry to lose more than $2 trillion in overall valuation. It was a sad and ugly sight to see.</p>
<p>However, at the time of writing, the US and Europe are enduring harsh <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-more-banks-fell-bitcoin-rose-beyond-28k/" data-wpel-link="internal">banking crises</a> that have caused several financial platforms (i.e., Silvergate Bank, Silicon Valley Bank, and Signature Bank) to crash and burn within a few weeks of each other. During this period, bitcoin is enjoying a nine-month high and is trading in the $28K range, up roughly $12K from where it ended 2022.</p>
<p>Patrick Chu – director of institutional sales and trading at over-the-counter crypto tech platform Paradigm – threw his two cents into the conversation, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>The negative spread is reflective of the two assets increasingly viewed as similar, yet different proxies of risk. Both markets are much deeper and liquid than the rest of the coins with established use cases.</p></blockquote>
<h2>What Will Happen After the Next Upgrade?</h2>
<p>Jeff Anderson finished with:</p>
<blockquote><p>I do think there is real value in owning ETH variance into the Shanghai upgrade. The event risk there is underpriced, and options appear cheap.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/will-bitcoin-suddenly-be-more-volatile-than-ethereum/">Will Bitcoin Suddenly Be More Volatile Than Ethereum?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/will-bitcoin-suddenly-be-more-volatile-than-ethereum/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mark Cuban: To Hell with Gold, Go for Bitcoin!</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-to-hell-with-gold-go-for-bitcoin/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-to-hell-with-gold-go-for-bitcoin/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 15:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bill Maher]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mark Cuban]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77534</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Billionaire investor and crypto bull Mark Cuban is still a bitcoin fanatic. Despite everything that happened in 2022 and how bearish the market was, the space’s volatility and speculation has not put the owner of the Dallas Mavericks basketball team off from putting everything he has into bitcoin, the world’s number one digital currency by<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-to-hell-with-gold-go-for-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-to-hell-with-gold-go-for-bitcoin/">Mark Cuban: To Hell with Gold, Go for Bitcoin!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Billionaire investor and crypto bull Mark Cuban is <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/mark-cuban-told-bill-maher-that-buying-gold-is-dumb-and-he-wants-bitcoin-to-plunge-so-he-can-buy-even-more-these-are-3-simple-ways-to-gain-crypto-exposure/ar-AA16b8Hi" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">still a bitcoin fanatic</a>. Despite everything that happened in 2022 and how bearish the market was, the space’s volatility and speculation has not put the owner of the Dallas Mavericks basketball team off from putting everything he has into bitcoin, the world’s number one digital currency by market cap.</p>
<h2>Mark Cuban Still Loves BTC</h2>
<p>In a recent interview with Bill Maher, a famed talk show host, Cuban claimed that owning gold was the wrong way to go despite its reputation for being a hedge fund over the years. He says that gold, in many ways, is nowhere near as safe as BTC given that when you purchase gold, you don’t really own the bar, and thus your status as a gold possessor is always in question. For this reason, he continues to push bitcoin and its alleged benefits. Cuban said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I want bitcoin to go down a lot further so I can buy some more.</p></blockquote>
<p>Maher claimed to be very “anti-bitcoin” in the discussion, and said that he’s a gold owner. Cuban quickly rebuked this by saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>If you have gold, you&#8217;re dumb… Gold is not a hedge against anything, right? What it is, [it’s] a store of value and you don&#8217;t own the physical gold, do you? Gold is a store of value and so is bitcoin.</p></blockquote>
<p>He further stated that during times of crises, gold will not protect your wealth or portfolio the way it’s been touted to all these years. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>You don&#8217;t own the gold bar, and if everything went to hell in a handbasket and you had a gold bar, you know what would happen? Someone would beat the f*ck out of you or kill you and take your gold bar.</p></blockquote>
<p>Bitcoin investing appears to be returning to form in recent months given the state of the current <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-more-banks-fell-bitcoin-rose-beyond-28k/" data-wpel-link="internal">banking system in the</a> United States. Three banks (Silvergate, Signature, and Silicon Valley) have all crumbled within a few short weeks of each other, and many traders have since shot back to speculative assets – such as BTC – out of fear that the centralized, standard monetary system they’ve all grown up with is suddenly losing its legs.</p>
<h2>So Many Banks Are Failing</h2>
<p>With BTC now on the rise as so many smaller banks fail, it makes sense that the digital asset is on the verge of making a serious comeback. After all, we cannot forget that BTC was a quick and out-of-the-blue answer to the 2008 financial crisis, so it makes sense that bitcoin would endure heavy spikes (it’s already at a nine-month high) when so many traditional financial enterprises are crashing and burning.</p>
<p>During 2022, BTC lost more than 70 percent from its all-time high of $68K per unit.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-to-hell-with-gold-go-for-bitcoin/">Mark Cuban: To Hell with Gold, Go for Bitcoin!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-to-hell-with-gold-go-for-bitcoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Best Ways to Earn Passive Income with Crypto in 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/best-ways-to-earn-passive-income-with-crypto-in-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/best-ways-to-earn-passive-income-with-crypto-in-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 14:09:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78037</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mining cryptocurrency on blockchain platforms is a great way to earn cryptocurrency income! Ever wanted to mine Bitcoin but thought it was too expensive or a hassle? With AMGCrypto&#8217;s Bitcoin crypto mining service, you can start mining in less than 3 minutes. Best of all, start earning Bitcoin while you sleep, eat, walk, work and<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/best-ways-to-earn-passive-income-with-crypto-in-2023/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/best-ways-to-earn-passive-income-with-crypto-in-2023/">Best Ways to Earn Passive Income with Crypto in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em><strong>Mining cryptocurrency on blockchain platforms is a great way to <a href="https://www.amgcrypto.com" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">earn cryptocurrency income</a>!</strong></em></p>
<p>Ever wanted to mine Bitcoin but thought it was too expensive or a hassle? With AMGCrypto&#8217;s Bitcoin crypto mining service, you can start mining in less than 3 minutes. Best of all, <a href="https://www.amgcrypto.com" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">start earning Bitcoin</a> while you sleep, eat, walk, work and trade, even if it costs you nothing!</p>
<p><strong>How To Mine Bitcoin From Your Phone In 3 Minutes!</strong></p>
<p>Most cryptocurrency mining services require you to pay a fee or transfer some of your equipment&#8217;s computing power, but that&#8217;s not the case with AMGCrypto. AMGCrypto offers an easy registration process, all that is required to participate is to enter an email address and create an account. After signing up, users can immediately start mining bitcoins. Users can <a href="https://www.amgcrypto.com" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">earn up to $3000</a> in referral commissions by promoting AMGCrypto to others. Users can earn these commissions by sharing their unique referral links on social media, websites or other online platforms. AMGCrypto won&#8217;t charge you a penny to use its crypto cloud mining service, you get more money &#8211; it&#8217;s a win-win!</p>
<p><strong>What is AMGCrypto?</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://www.amgcrypto.com" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">AMGCrypto</a> is a popular and powerful crypto mining platform that is an excellent resource for earning passive crypto income. The platform is one of the world&#8217;s leading mining companies and your trusted partner. In order to take it to the next level, AMGCrypto has launched a free Bitcoin mining program, allowing you to passively earn Bitcoin. They promise to open bitcoin mining to everyone, regardless of technical know-how or financial resources, with no strings attached. Once you have mined 12USDT worth of bitcoins, you can transfer them to your account and trade them. Any profit you make is yours and you can <a href="https://www.amgcrypto.com" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">withdraw it to your personal wallet.</a></p>
<p>Currently, AMGCrypto also offers various mining contract options, such as $100, $480 and $1160 packages. Each has a unique ROI and has a specific contract length.</p>
<p>When participating in the following contracts, you will unlock more passive income:</p>
<table width="568">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td width="142"><strong>Contract price</strong></td>
<td width="142"><strong>Contract terms</strong></td>
<td width="142"><strong>Fixed return</strong></td>
<td width="142"><strong>Daily rate</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="142"><a href="https://www.amgcrypto.com/index/index/mall_form?id=38&amp;num=1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">$12</a></td>
<td width="142">1 Days</td>
<td width="142">$12+$1.2</td>
<td width="142">10%</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="142"><a href="https://www.amgcrypto.com/index/index/mall_form?id=31&amp;num=1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">$100</a></td>
<td width="142">3 Days</td>
<td width="142">$100+$5.1</td>
<td width="142">1.7%</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="142"><a href="https://www.amgcrypto.com/index/index/mall_form?id=32&amp;num=1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">$480</a></td>
<td width="142">7 Days</td>
<td width="142">$480+$67.2</td>
<td width="142">2%</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="142"><a href="https://www.amgcrypto.com/index/index/mall_form?id=33&amp;num=1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">$1160</a></td>
<td width="142">14 Days</td>
<td width="142">$1160+$354</td>
<td width="142">2.18%</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="142"><a href="https://www.amgcrypto.com/index/index/mall_form?id=34&amp;num=1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">$2800</a></td>
<td width="142">30 Days</td>
<td width="142">$2800+$1915.2</td>
<td width="142">2.28%</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-78039 aligncenter" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/04/Picture34-600x150.jpg" alt="" width="600" height="150" /></p>
<p><strong>Why choose AMGCrypto?</strong></p>
<p>AMGCrypto is taking the cryptocurrency trading world by storm, with professional trading tools you&#8217;d find on Wall Street, and trusted cloud mining services in over 176 countries. There are currently 3726K users earning cryptocurrency on AMGCrypto. The official website combined with a simple and stylish user interface gives you everything you need to be successful. Includes transparent and accurate information on earnings, allowing users to track their progress and estimate their potential earnings. The level of return remains the same no matter how long the investment is held. After the timeframe specified in the contract, you can withdraw your funds or continue investing. AMGCrypto fully guarantees the principal and income of each investment they make. It is these ingredients that come together to create a powerful crypto trading platform. Best of all, <a href="https://www.amgcrypto.com" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">your passive income</a> continues to grow as you play around with these advanced features.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78040 aligncenter" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/04/Picture35.jpg" alt="" width="553" height="323" /></p>
<p><strong>Advantages of this platform:</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://www.amgcrypto.com" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Sign up and get $12 bonus</a> instantly.</p>
<p>High profitability levels and daily payouts.</p>
<p>There are no other service or administrative fees.</p>
<p>You can generate more than 6 other currencies using the platform.</p>
<p>The company&#8217;s affiliate program allows you to refer friends and earn up to $3,000 in referral bonuses.</p>
<p>McAfee® security protection. Cloudflare® Security Protection.</p>
<p>Backed by a 100% uptime guarantee and 24/7 excellent technical support.</p>
<p><strong>How to increase my passive income?</strong></p>
<p>A hands-off approach to wealth creation. When used correctly, these opportunities can help you grow your crypto wealth on “autopilot” mode with minimal time investment. At the very least, they should take less time than any kind of active transaction.</p>
<p>Passive income is the goal of every investor and trader, and with AMGCrypto you can maximize your passive income potential easier than ever. The platform allows you to earn money by recommending the website to others. You can start making money even if you don&#8217;t invest. Reaching a certain number of individuals who invite active referrals will receive a fixed bonus of up to $3,000 at one time. With unlimited referrals, your earning potential is unlimited too!</p>
<p>If you want to learn more about AMGCrypto, please visit its official website <a href="https://www.amgcrypto.com" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.amgcrypto.com</a></p>
<p>Or if you have any questions, please feel free to contact the 24/7 support staff. They&#8217;ll answer any questions you may have and guide you to maximize your passive income potential!</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/best-ways-to-earn-passive-income-with-crypto-in-2023/">Best Ways to Earn Passive Income with Crypto in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/best-ways-to-earn-passive-income-with-crypto-in-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Billionaires Are Making a Serious Return to Form</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-billionaires-are-making-a-serious-comeback/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-billionaires-are-making-a-serious-comeback/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 13:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[billionaires]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Saylor]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77531</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin billionaires are back. Given how hairy 2022 was, we put out an article not too long ago talking about how badly these crypto-laden individuals were hit during the previous bear market, but at the time of writing, the world’s number one digital currency by market cap is on the verge of striking $30K per<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-billionaires-are-making-a-serious-comeback/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-billionaires-are-making-a-serious-comeback/">Bitcoin Billionaires Are Making a Serious Return to Form</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin billionaires <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-billionaires-are-back/ar-AA18MSWL" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">are back</a>. Given how hairy 2022 was, we put out an article not <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-magnates-like-changpeng-zhao-lost-a-ton-in-2022/" data-wpel-link="internal">too long ago talking</a> about how badly these crypto-laden individuals were hit during the previous bear market, but at the time of writing, the world’s number one digital currency by market cap is on the verge of striking $30K per unit, and it’s largely benefited from the recent banking crisis that’s occurred.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Billionaires Are Here Again</h2>
<p>Over the course of just seven days in late March, bitcoin rose by close to 40 percent. The asset is now at a nine-month high, and many additional crypto assets appear to be following in its footsteps. At press time, ETH – the second largest crypto in the world and the number one competitor to bitcoin – has swelled to about $1,836 per unit. This is roughly $100 more than its price position of about a week prior.</p>
<p>Alex Kuptsikevich – a senior market analyst at FX Pro – commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>The worse the banks are doing, the better the cryptocurrency is doing. The banking problems in the US and Europe have again highlighted the vulnerability of the traditional financial sector. Once again, investors&#8217; fears that keeping money in banks can be risky are coming to the surface.</p></blockquote>
<p>Among the people getting really excited during this time about the prospects of not just crypto but the megarich the space has produced is Mike Novogratz, a crypto bull and the manager of hedge fund Galaxy Digital. On social media, he wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>This is our time!! Let’s go team $BTC!! Let’s go $ETH!! The decentralized revolution is happening.</p></blockquote>
<p>Similar sentiment came from Michael Saylor, the bitcoin fanatic and former CEO of software giant MicroStrategy, which first began investing in BTC and adding the asset <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-microstrategy-bitcoin-bet-is-already-paying-off-big-time/" data-wpel-link="internal">to its balance sheet</a> in August of 2020. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>A timely review explaining why #bitcoin is superior to conventional banks, fiat currencies, staking networks, stable coins, and crypto exchanges; how $BTC helps defend against asset seizures, inflation fraud, bank failure, and counterparty risk.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Will the Asset Keep Spiking?</h2>
<p>Lastly, Tyler Winklevoss – one half of the executive pair running the Gemini exchange in New York – expressed his enthusiasm for the current bull run. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>$30K bitcoin by the end of the weekend? The US banking system is a modern-day caste system. There are those who are banked by Bulge bracket banks. There are those who are banked by regional banks, and there are those who are banked by no bank at all.</p></blockquote>
<p>Bitcoin is a shaky asset; there’s no questioning that. However, to see the asset roughly $12,000 higher now than where it ended 2022 is very appealing for most investors and traders given the asset lost more than 70 percent from its November 2021 all-time high over the course of 11 or 12 months.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-billionaires-are-making-a-serious-comeback/">Bitcoin Billionaires Are Making a Serious Return to Form</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-billionaires-are-making-a-serious-comeback/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Takes Hit, $0.092 Is The Key</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-takes-hit-0-092-is-the-key/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-takes-hit-0-092-is-the-key/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 05:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar Lumens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78033</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stellar lumen price is showing bearish signs below the $0.100 resistance zone against the US Dollar. XLM price is now trading below $0.100 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.1020 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could start<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-takes-hit-0-092-is-the-key/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-takes-hit-0-092-is-the-key/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Takes Hit, $0.092 Is The Key</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Stellar lumen price is showing bearish signs below the $0.100 resistance zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>XLM price is now trading below $0.100 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.1020 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start another decline if it fails to recover above the $0.100 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Stellar lumen price is trading below $0.100 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-more-gains-above-31k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. XLM price must stay above the $0.0920 support to avoid more losses.</em></p>
<h2>Stellar Lumen Price Analysis (XLM to USD)</h2>
<p>After a failed attempt near the $0.1090 zone, Stellar Lumen price started a fresh decline against the US Dollar. The XLM/USD pair traded below the $0.1020 support to move into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>There was a steady decline below the $0.1000 level and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-eyes-fresh-increase-above-0-112/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. The price even tested the $0.0920 level. A low is formed near $0.0921 and the price is now consolidating losses. XLM price is now trading below $0.096 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $0.096 level. It is close to the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.1089 swing high to the $0.0921 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $0.1000 zone. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.1089 swing high to the $0.0921 low. The first major resistance is near the $0.1020 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.1020 on the 4-hour chart.</p>
<p>A clear upside break above the $0.1020 zone might send the price toward $0.1050. Any more gains could lead the price toward the $0.1090 level or even $0.1120.</p>
<p>Initial support on the downside is near the $0.0925 level. The main support is near the $0.092 zone. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.0865 level in the near term, below which the price might even retest $0.0850.</p>
<div id="attachment_78034" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/04/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78034" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78034" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/04/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-2.png" alt="Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78034" class="wp-caption-text">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XLMUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that XLM price is now trading below $0.100 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start a major decline if there is a clear move below the $0.0920 support.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XLM/USD is losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for XLM/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.0920 and $0.090.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.0960, $0.100, and $0.1020.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-takes-hit-0-092-is-the-key/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Takes Hit, $0.092 Is The Key</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-takes-hit-0-092-is-the-key/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Price Analysis: XRP Turns Red Below $0.50</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-turns-red-below-0-50/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-turns-red-below-0-50/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 03:18:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78030</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple price started a fresh decline from the $0.540 zone against the US dollar. The price is now trading below $0.500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $0.5100 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Bittrex).<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-turns-red-below-0-50/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-turns-red-below-0-50/">Ripple Price Analysis: XRP Turns Red Below $0.50</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ripple price started a fresh decline from the $0.540 zone against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $0.500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $0.5100 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Bittrex).</li>
<li>The pair could extend losses if it stays below the $0.500 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ripple price is struggling below $0.500 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-more-gains-above-31k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. XRP price must stay above $0.4400 to avoid more downsides in the near term.</em></p>
<h2>Ripple Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, Ripple price attempted an upside break above the $0.5400 zone against the US Dollar. The XRP/USD pair failed to gain bullish momentum and formed a high near $0.5380.</p>
<p>The price declined below the $0.5000 support zone to move into a bearish zone. The bears took control and pushed the price below the $0.480 support zone. Besides, there was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $0.5100 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair.</p>
<p>It tested the $0.4400 support zone. A low is formed near $0.4403 and the price is now correcting losses. It is now trading above $0.500 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-dips-likely-to-be-supported-above-0-5/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. There was a minor increase above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.5382 swing high to the $0.4403 low.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near $0.4990. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.5382 swing high to the $0.4403 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $0.500 level. A clear move above the $0.4990 and $0.5000 resistance zones might start a fresh increase. In the stated case, the price could even surpass the $0.5200 resistance. Any more gains might send the price toward the $0.540 resistance.</p>
<p>Initial support on the downside is near $0.450. The next major support is near the $0.440 level. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.420 level, below which the price might even test $0.4000.</p>
<div id="attachment_78031" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/04/Ripple-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78031" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78031" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/04/Ripple-2.png" alt="Ripple Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78031" class="wp-caption-text">Ripple Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Ripple’s price is now trading below the $0.500 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could extend losses if it stays below the $0.500 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XRP/USD is now losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for XRP/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.4500, $0.4400, and $0.4200.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.4990 and $0.5000.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-turns-red-below-0-50/">Ripple Price Analysis: XRP Turns Red Below $0.50</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-turns-red-below-0-50/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Illinois Woman Gets Most of Her Stolen Crypto Back</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/illinois-woman-gets-most-of-her-stolen-crypto-back/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/illinois-woman-gets-most-of-her-stolen-crypto-back/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 17:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scam]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Federal Agents]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illinois]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77523</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Federal law enforcement agents have managed to take back as much as $24K from crypto scammers who had allegedly stolen the money from a resident of the Metro East area of Illinois. At the time of writing, no criminal evidence has been made public, and the agents have not made any arrests. Illinois Woman Is<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/illinois-woman-gets-most-of-her-stolen-crypto-back/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/illinois-woman-gets-most-of-her-stolen-crypto-back/">Illinois Woman Gets Most of Her Stolen Crypto Back</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Federal law enforcement agents <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/feds-seize-24k-in-cryptocurrency-scam-targeting-metro-east-woman/ar-AA18LU01" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">have managed to take back</a> as much as $24K from crypto scammers who had allegedly stolen the money from a resident of the Metro East area of Illinois. At the time of writing, no criminal evidence has been made public, and the agents have not made any arrests.</p>
<h2>Illinois Woman Is 75 Percent Victorious</h2>
<p>Crypto scams have become rather prominent in recent years, and with time, they just get bigger and bigger. Court records regarding the present case suggest the victimized woman contacted the O’Fallon Police Department in June of last year to say that she had been scammed by alleged crypto fraudsters who took a huge chunk of her money.</p>
<p>Prior to losing the funds, the woman had spoken via Twitter with what appeared to be a crypto influencer. Little did she know that this was, in fact, a scammer who was only impersonating the influencer, and the real person had no hand in what went down. The criminal told the woman that she should deposit as much as $32,000 in BTC into a trading account via the platform 3Twarriorstrading.com. She did so, and by the time she realized what was happening, she had already lost quite a bit of money.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, about three quarters of the stolen funds have been recovered. They will be returned to the victim in due time via a remission compensatory process. Stephen S. Webster – who heads the U.S. Secret Service Office in Springfield, Illinois – commented on the case, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>Unfortunately, new technology has made it easier for individuals abroad to take advantage of innocent victims throughout the United States. The U.S. Secret Service worked quickly with our partners at the U.S. Attorney&#8217;s Office in the Southern District of Illinois and O&#8217;Fallon Police Department to seize this cryptocurrency and prevent it from lining the pockets of criminals overseas.</p></blockquote>
<p>Residents of Illinois are not the only people vulnerable, and these kinds of scams <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/more-crypto-scams-are-happening-all-over-the-world/" data-wpel-link="internal">are happening all over</a> the world (and in greater numbers). Often, they take on the form of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/romance-scams/" data-wpel-link="internal">romance scams</a>, in which people looking for love online are targeted by cyberthieves who talk to them, get to know them, and eventually earn their trust.</p>
<h2>This Just Keeps Happening!</h2>
<p>Over time, they convince them of a grand (and new) digital currency investing opportunity, and say they’d be fools to skip it or miss out. The people then begin depositing funds into platforms that are hosted or run by larger rings of scammers. From there, they witness returns, though these numbers are often not real, and when they try to make withdrawals, that’s when things go haywire.</p>
<p>They often learn too late that they cannot take the money out unless they pay heavy fees or invest more money.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/illinois-woman-gets-most-of-her-stolen-crypto-back/">Illinois Woman Gets Most of Her Stolen Crypto Back</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/illinois-woman-gets-most-of-her-stolen-crypto-back/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Balaji Srinivasan: BTC Will Hit $1 Million in Two Months</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/balaji-srinivasan-btc-will-hit-1-million-in-two-months/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/balaji-srinivasan-btc-will-hit-1-million-in-two-months/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 15:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[balaji srinivasan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cathie Wood]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77520</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin is doing well as of late, and many analysts – including former Coinbase chief technology officer Balaji Srinivasan – believe the currency is going to hit unprecedented levels within the next few months. Balaji Srinivasan Is a Big Bitcoin Believer In a recent interview, Srinivasan said that hyperinflation could cause bitcoin to hit a<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/balaji-srinivasan-btc-will-hit-1-million-in-two-months/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/balaji-srinivasan-btc-will-hit-1-million-in-two-months/">Balaji Srinivasan: BTC Will Hit $1 Million in Two Months</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin is doing well as of late, and many analysts – including former Coinbase chief technology officer Balaji Srinivasan – believe <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/03/18/buy-now-2-trillion-fed-bazooka-triggers-shock-hyperinflation-warning-amid-bitcoin-ethereum-and-crypto-price-boom/?sh=72169c207f38" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">the currency is going</a> to hit unprecedented levels within the next few months.</p>
<h2>Balaji Srinivasan Is a Big Bitcoin Believer</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, Srinivasan said that hyperinflation could cause bitcoin to hit a price of about $1 million per unit. The clincher? He thinks this could happen as early as June of this year. For that to occur, bitcoin would need to endure a spike of more than 3,600 percent in just 60 days.</p>
<p>This is a crazy idea in a lot of ways. To be fair, Srinivasan is not the only person who had deemed bitcoin capable of hitting the million-dollar mark. In the past, industry heads <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/john-mcafee-1-million-for-btc-is-still-plausible/" data-wpel-link="internal">such as John McAfee</a> were quick to say that bitcoin had what it took to strike $1 million, while Cathie Wood of Ark Invest has mentioned that she thinks BTC is capable of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-btc-will-be-priced-at-1-5-million-in-2030/" data-wpel-link="internal">reaching such a milestone</a>.</p>
<p>The difference between their predictions and the one from Srinivasan, however, is that they fully acknowledged bitcoin would need time to hit this number. Somewhere in the vicinity of a few years, at least, where Srinivasan is claiming the move could happen extremely fast. Why? Because he thinks hyperinflation will happen fast, and this could push bitcoin beyond anything people initially believed plausible. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Why will it be so fast? Well, hyperinflation happens fast. We&#8217;ve seen digital pandemics (COVID), digital riots (BLM), and digital bank runs (SVB). Everything will happen very fast once people check what I&#8217;m saying and see that the Federal Reserve has lied about how much money there is in the banks. All dollar holders [will] get destroyed.</p></blockquote>
<p>The news of his prediction initially came about in a tweet. He dared any of his followers to bet against the U.S. entering hyperinflation, and he said he would pay anyone $1 million if they’re indeed right and he’s wrong. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>The counterparty gets the $1 million&#8230; We [need] to define hyperinflation in [bitcoin] vs. [U.S. dollars] terms because all other fiat currencies can and will be inflated away… I am moving $2 million into USDC for the bet. I will do it with [@jdcmedlock] and one other person, sufficient to prove the point.</p></blockquote>
<h2>The Fed Hasn&#8217;t Told the Truth</h2>
<p>Srinivasan is a firm believer that the Fed has lied to Americans, and that the country is going to run out of money very quickly. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The central bank, the banks, and the bank regulators have bankrupted all of us. They hid their insolvency from you, the depositors, and they&#8217;re about to print $2 trillion to hyperinflate the dollar. In the digital age, this will happen very quickly. So, buy bitcoin now and get your coins off exchanges.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/balaji-srinivasan-btc-will-hit-1-million-in-two-months/">Balaji Srinivasan: BTC Will Hit $1 Million in Two Months</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/balaji-srinivasan-btc-will-hit-1-million-in-two-months/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>As More Banks Fell, Bitcoin Rose Beyond $28K</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-more-banks-fell-bitcoin-rose-beyond-28k/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-more-banks-fell-bitcoin-rose-beyond-28k/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 13:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Credit Suisse]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77518</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The banking sector is burning up as of late, and the situation is allowing bitcoin to surge like crazy. At the time of this writing, bitcoin has moved beyond the $28,000 per unit mark, the highest it’s been since June of 2022. Bitcoin Rose Beyond $28K The news is crazy in that 2023, in many<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-more-banks-fell-bitcoin-rose-beyond-28k/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-more-banks-fell-bitcoin-rose-beyond-28k/">As More Banks Fell, Bitcoin Rose Beyond $28K</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The banking sector is burning up as of late, and <a href="https://www.livemint.com/market/cryptocurrency/bitcoin-rises-above-28-000-for-first-time-since-june-11679251216325.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">the situation is allowing</a> bitcoin to surge like crazy. At the time of this writing, bitcoin has moved beyond the $28,000 per unit mark, the highest it’s been since June of 2022.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Rose Beyond $28K</h2>
<p>The news is crazy in that 2023, in many ways, is turning into another version of 2019. As we all remember during that year, bitcoin incurred a certain degree of healing following the heavy blows and wounds it experienced in 2018, which up to that point, was considered the worst year on record for bitcoin. The previous year, BTC rose to its then all-time high of nearly $20K per unit, though by the end of 2018, the world’s number one digital currency by market cap had fallen into the mid-$3,000 range.</p>
<p>In 2019, the momentum behind bitcoin began to pick up, and the asset eventually ended the year about 50 percent higher than where it ended 2018. The currency ended 2019 in the mid-$7,000 range.</p>
<p>2022 was considered far worse than 2018. During that time, the crypto space lost more than $2 trillion in overall valuation as coins such as BTC lost more than 70 percent of their worth over the course of just 11 or 12 months. Bitcoin initially rose to a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit in November of 2021, though just a year later, it was trading in the mid-$16K range.</p>
<p>It was a sad and ugly sight to see, but perhaps things are finally back on track and those who lost everything in last year’s bear market have a chance of earning their money (and their respect) back. Ilan Solot – co-head of digital assets at Marex – commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin is correlated with liquidity conditions and real rates. Real rates have declined, liquidity conditions have expanded, and it looks as if we’re entering a new regime.</p></blockquote>
<p>The banking crisis has been going on for the last month or so, and thus far, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-just-got-higher-and-higher-in-mid-march/" data-wpel-link="internal">three major financial</a> institutions (Silvergate, Signature, and Silicon Valley Bank) have either gone under or announced plans to fully liquidate. Credit Suisse was the next big company on the bank death list, though the company has since been bought out by UBS, thus adding a few more years (at least) onto its life.</p>
<h2>The Aiding of Credit Suisse Appears to Have Done the Trick</h2>
<p>This appears to have worked well for bitcoin, which has shot up by more than $4,000 over 24 hours. Who would have known that it would be the complete demise of America’s financial sector that would finally give bitcoin and other digital assets the confidence they needed to move up?</p>
<p>Odd that it would take something this dramatic, but it also opens the door to a far less centralized (and much more private) financial industry.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-more-banks-fell-bitcoin-rose-beyond-28k/">As More Banks Fell, Bitcoin Rose Beyond $28K</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-more-banks-fell-bitcoin-rose-beyond-28k/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
