<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 17:20:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>LBank Welcomes Nigeria’s Push to Recognize Crypto as Investment Capital</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-welcomes-nigerias-push-to-recognize-crypto-as-investment-capital/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-welcomes-nigerias-push-to-recognize-crypto-as-investment-capital/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 17:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76169</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nigeria has put forward a significant legislation design that will further facilitate cryptocurrency adoption in the country with over 200 million inhabitants. Why this matters: If the Investments and Securities Act, 2007 (Amendment) Bill passes, the Nigerian securities and exchange commission (SEC) will recognize cryptocurrencies and other digital assets as capital for investment. Babangida Ibrahim,<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-welcomes-nigerias-push-to-recognize-crypto-as-investment-capital/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-welcomes-nigerias-push-to-recognize-crypto-as-investment-capital/">LBank Welcomes Nigeria’s Push to Recognize Crypto as Investment Capital</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Nigeria has put forward a significant legislation design that will further facilitate cryptocurrency adoption in the country with over 200 million inhabitants.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Why this matters:</strong> If the Investments and Securities Act, 2007 (Amendment) Bill passes, the Nigerian securities and exchange commission (SEC) will recognize cryptocurrencies and other digital assets as capital for investment.</p>
<ul>
<li>Babangida Ibrahim, Chairman of the House of Representatives Committee, shared in <a href="https://punchng.com/proposed-cryptocurrency-law-to-define-cbns-roles-reps/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">an interview</a> with local media outlet <em>Punch</em>, that the proposed bill will specify the roles of the Central Bank of Nigeria and the country&#8217;s SEC in regard to cryptocurrencies.</li>
<li>Ibrahim stated that the bill is not a complete shift away from restrictive laws in place, only a review of what could be done within the current legal framework. However, he does believe that Nigeria must keep up with global economic innovations.</li>
<li>Notably, the Nigerian Export Processing Zones Authority (NEPZA) stated in a press release in September that <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/cryptocurrency/a-virtual-free-zone-in-africa-is-being-discussed-with-binance/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">it considered partnering</a> with crypto exchange Binance to create a virtual free zone to promote economic growth.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Go deeper:</strong> The legal blueprint comes at a time when Nigeria has spent almost 2 years under <a href="https://www.spglobal.com/marketintelligence/en/news-insights/latest-news-headlines/cryptocurrency-usage-soars-in-nigeria-despite-bank-ban-70497781#:~:text=This%20is%20despite%20the%20country&#039;s,laundering%20and%20and%20terrorism%20financing." data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">a cryptocurrency ban for financial institutes</a>, and the country’s CBDC, the eNaira, has failed to reach widespread adoption.</p>
<ul>
<li>Since the launch of the CBDC in October 2021, it currently sits at an adoption rate <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-10-25/shunned-digital-currency-looks-for-street-credibility-in-nigeria?sref=323RPL5z" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">of only 0.5%</a> among the population.</li>
<li>Further endorsement of the eNaira could be hampered by the legal blueprint. “This bill is basically going to create more adoption of cryptocurrencies. Through regulation of this asset class, we might start to see taxing and legal registration if you want to build something in the blockchain space,” says Anointing Aha, Community Manager for Nigeria at global crypto exchange LBank.</li>
<li>For now, Nigeria seems to be moving towards further adoption, but nothing is set in stone. “Nigeria’s presidential election is coming up early next year, and a lot will depend on the new president,” Aha adds.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-welcomes-nigerias-push-to-recognize-crypto-as-investment-capital/">LBank Welcomes Nigeria’s Push to Recognize Crypto as Investment Capital</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-welcomes-nigerias-push-to-recognize-crypto-as-investment-capital/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Citron Research: Ethereum Is the Best Crypto for Shorting</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/citron-research-ethereum-is-the-best-crypto-for-shorting/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/citron-research-ethereum-is-the-best-crypto-for-shorting/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 17:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Andrew Left]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Citron Research]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75547</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Citron Research is betting big against cryptocurrencies. In particular, the company is focusing on Ethereum, which it claims is the best digital asset to short at the time of writing. Citron Research Is Pushing Ethereum Crypto has been treated rather unfairly throughout 2022. The year has arguably been the worst for the space, with several<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/citron-research-ethereum-is-the-best-crypto-for-shorting/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/citron-research-ethereum-is-the-best-crypto-for-shorting/">Citron Research: Ethereum Is the Best Crypto for Shorting</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Citron Research is betting big against cryptocurrencies. In particular, the company is focusing on Ethereum, <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/billybambrough/2022/11/17/reignited-gamestop-short-seller-reveals-the-surprise-cryptocurrency-its-betting-against-after-ftx-crash-hits-bitcoin-and-ethereum-price/?sh=4d3c4c9773f8" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">which it claims is the best</a> digital asset to short at the time of writing.</p>
<h2>Citron Research Is Pushing Ethereum</h2>
<p>Crypto has been treated rather unfairly throughout 2022. The year has arguably been the worst for the space, with several digital currency and blockchain <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-in-the-age-of-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">firms filing bankruptcy</a> and falling off the Earth’s grid. It’s a sad and ugly sight to see, and one that has only been boosted by the falling digital currency prices traders have been forced to endure.</p>
<p>Bitcoin – the world’s largest and most powerful digital currency by market cap – has lost more than 70 percent of its value in the last 13 months. In November of last year, the asset was trading at a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit, though now, the currency is trading in the mid-$16K range. Other mainstream assets, such as Ethereum, have followed suit, and overall, the digital currency space has lost more than $2 trillion in general valuation.</p>
<p>Citron Research thinks <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ethereum/" data-wpel-link="internal">Ethereum</a> serves a unique purpose, and it&#8217;s an asset that&#8217;s loved by many investors. While not as large as bitcoin, for example, the network of Ethereum continues to attract crypto developers, who see it as the prime blockchain in which to build the new assets or projects on. The network also recently underwent an upgrade from proof of work (PoW), which relies mainly on mining as bitcoin does, to proof of stake (PoS).</p>
<p>Ethereum now operates under the name “Ethereum 2.0,” and it is allegedly faster and is less bogged down by traffic and gas fees. The switch is known as <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/merge/" data-wpel-link="internal">the Merge</a>, and it has allegedly helped Ethereum become more energy efficient.</p>
<p>Citron says that it is once again for short selling following the FTX collapse. In a statement, the company commented that the situation is a classic one where everyone got involved because they simply assumed that those in charge knew what they were doing. The company mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>It proves there are many stocks out there that are elevated on the misconception that someone else did the homework… The U.S. government should be embarrassed that they let one person get so close to the inner sanctum of government and influence without even checking a tax return.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Andrew Left Doesn&#8217;t Care for Crypto</h2>
<p>The sentiment stemming from Citron shouldn&#8217;t come as a surprise given that its founder – a man named Andrew Left – has done nothing but bash crypto over the last several years. During a recent conference, Left said to the audience:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think crypto is just [a] complete fraud over and over and over. Maybe it is time to finally [listen] to skeptics instead of vilifying them.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/citron-research-ethereum-is-the-best-crypto-for-shorting/">Citron Research: Ethereum Is the Best Crypto for Shorting</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/citron-research-ethereum-is-the-best-crypto-for-shorting/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LBank Presents TechFest International Blockchain Summit In Bombay</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-presents-techfest-international-blockchain-summit-in-bombay/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-presents-techfest-international-blockchain-summit-in-bombay/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 17:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76166</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TechFest IIT Bombay is Asia&#8217;s Largest technology festival where the world’s leading crypto influencers gather with key government delegates, media and other investors to assist the global blockchain and cryptocurrency communities. It is one of the most prestigious events of the global cryptocurrency and blockchain ecosystem. Furthermore, the festival combines young minds and blockchain enthusiasts<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-presents-techfest-international-blockchain-summit-in-bombay/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-presents-techfest-international-blockchain-summit-in-bombay/">LBank Presents TechFest International Blockchain Summit In Bombay</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TechFest IIT Bombay is Asia&#8217;s Largest technology festival where the world’s leading crypto influencers gather with key government delegates, media and other investors to assist the global blockchain and cryptocurrency communities. It is one of the most prestigious events of the global cryptocurrency and blockchain ecosystem.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the festival combines young minds and blockchain enthusiasts in one place to provide knowledge about the industry to the community. The International Blockchain Summit of TechFest IIT Bombay is sponsored by LBank, a global crypto exchange, with a primary focus on providing crypto education. This TechFest is a three day event which attracts the students, alumni, and techn geeks who are said to be the sole essence of the summit.</p>
<h4>LBank’s Live Session at TechFest</h4>
<p>Notably, the <a href="http://www.lbank.com" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">top cryptocurrency exchange</a> LBank prioritizes knowledge sharing about blockchain space. Considering the main objective to achieve educating the community, the company is taking part in the panel discussion on “Tech and the environmental impact of Blockchain”. This discussion will be held on the second day of the summit with other top mentors in the industry.</p>
<p>The whole summit is all about learning and understanding the upcoming trends and red flags of the blockchain space. Moreover, LBank believes that the festival has a significant role in giving people the chance to network with peers, mentors, and idols as well as to gain professional growth.</p>
<p>However, the exchange would also love to celebrate the community&#8217;s participation and distribute some presents to the crypto enthusiasts. With so many eager participants teaming up with LBank, the event&#8217;s first day has started off well. Participants demonstrated a keen interest in learning about the potential applications of blockchain technology.</p>
<h4>About LBank</h4>
<p><a href="http://lbank.info" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LBank</a> is a top cryptocurrency exchange founded in 2015. It provides users with a platform to securely buy, sell, receive and hold Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies. With over 7 million users, LBank offers a wide range of payment options and competitive transaction fees, lowering the entry barrier to drive more adoption.</p>
<p>The platform supports more than 800+ trading pairs and 149+ fiat currencies. It offers services around crypto trading, specialized financial derivatives, and professional asset management services. LBank’s robust ecosystem allows users to leverage and build a well-rounded financial portfolio.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.info" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.info</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media:</strong></p>
<p>l<a href="https://www.newsfilecorp.com/redirect/vR47rSkMwG" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> Telegram</a><br />
l<a href="https://www.newsfilecorp.com/redirect/JZeKvUj8Kj" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> Twitter</a><br />
l<a href="https://www.newsfilecorp.com/redirect/GOeWGSQOPx" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> Facebook</a><br />
l<a href="https://www.newsfilecorp.com/redirect/bAvmJCPwNR" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> Linkedin</a></p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong></p>
<p>LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
Downtown, Dubai<br />
<u>media@lbank.info</u></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-presents-techfest-international-blockchain-summit-in-bombay/">LBank Presents TechFest International Blockchain Summit In Bombay</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-presents-techfest-international-blockchain-summit-in-bombay/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LBank Exchange Will List DiDimCoin (DDC) on December 23, 2022</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-didimcoin-ddc-on-december-23-2022/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-didimcoin-ddc-on-december-23-2022/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 16:35:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76162</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec 22, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list DiDimCoin (DDC) on December 23, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the DDC/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading at 6:00 UTC on December 23, 2022. As a blockchain-based global social commerce platform, DiDim maximizes<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-didimcoin-ddc-on-december-23-2022/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-didimcoin-ddc-on-december-23-2022/">LBank Exchange Will List DiDimCoin (DDC) on December 23, 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec 22, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list DiDimCoin (DDC) on December 23, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the DDC/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading at 6:00 UTC on December 23, 2022.</p>
<p>As a blockchain-based global social commerce platform, DiDim maximizes the true value of all users by introducing a platform that connects e-commerce, markets, exchanges, payments, and content. Its native token <a href="https://tronscan.org/#/token20/TG8AEC18tJUefG4z4wmp1e5QbeuQuQWunV" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">DiDimCoin</a> (DDC) will be listed on LBank Exchange at 6:00 UTC on December 23, 2022, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision.</p>
<p><strong>Introducing </strong><strong>DiDim</strong></p>
<p>E-commerce global business is growing rapidly every year, its market is expected to exceed $3.453 trillion by 2025. One of the reasons e-commerce has grown rapidly is the development of cross-border e-commerce, a new market called overseas direct purchase is opening, and as it grows rapidly, platforms that reflect it are emerging. DiDim global shopping mall APP is one of them.</p>
<p>The global shopping mall service of DiDim was established in 2018. Including its own apps, it operates shopping malls through social commerce such as WeChat, Taobao, and TikTok, and has marketing channels such as Baidu, Kwai Show, and bilibili to exert influence in the Chinese and global markets. As a global shopping center for DiDimgn Co., Ltd. It is designed for commodity trading in South Korea, China, the United States, Russia and Southeast Asia.</p>
<p>Utilizing blockchain technology, DiDim not only allows users to trade securely anytime, anywhere, but also to share information and benefits. The DiDim platform was launched to maximize the true value of all blockchain users by introducing a platform that connects e-commerce, markets, exchanges, payments, and content. The payment system within the DIDIM platform will be a more secure network, providing all users with sufficient satisfaction and rewards and a blockchain platform that connects users worldwide beyond everyday transactions.</p>
<p>In addition to traditional shopping malls, DiDim is also building the best virtual department stores with metaverse technology. Creating a new shopping trend in the non-face-to-face era through a luxury store called Luxury Hall. For the MZ generation, who is leading the new consumer market, DiDim provides special content that fits the consumption pattern. This Metaverse Department Store will offer everything that can be sold in virtual reality. It will be a new shopping mall concept where users can sell and pay through any payment method.</p>
<p>With all above features, DiDim presents a decentralized commerce protocol where anyone in the world can freely sell/buy products and share profits transparently. Various services such as payment, shopping, and rewards are introduced into the ecosystem provided by DiDimCoin.</p>
<p><strong>About DDC Token</strong></p>
<p>DiDimCoin (DDC) is the utility coin and payment coin for free e-commerce based on blockchain. It presents a new vision and goal for the e-commerce market with the aim of offering users the ability to purchase products through global shopping malls, building a commerce ecosystem that all ecosystem users can trust, using blockchain technology to ensure transparency of all transaction data, and maximizing the benefits of ecosystem users and investors.</p>
<p>Based on TRC-20, DDC has a total supply of 5 billion (i.e., 5,000,000,000) tokens, of which 40% is reserved for payment, and the rest 60% is allocated for partnerships, ecosystem, marketing, company operation, the team and advisors.</p>
<p>The DDC token will be listed on LBank Exchange at 6:00 UTC on December 23, 2022, investors who are interested in the DiDim investment can easily buy and sell DDC token on LBank Exchange by then. The listing of DDC token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p>
<p><strong>Learn More about</strong><strong> DDC Token:</strong><br />
Official Website: <a href="http://didim.io/index_en.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://didim.io/index_en.html</a><br />
Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/didimcoin" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://t.me/didimcoin</a><br />
Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/DidimCoin" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/DidimCoin</a><br />
Instagram: <a href="https://www.instagram.com/didimcoin/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.instagram.com/didimcoin/</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media: </strong></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Facebook</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong></p>
<p>LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
LBank Exchange<br />
<a href="mailto:marketing@lbank.info">marketing@lbank.info</a><br />
<a href="mailto:business@lbank.info">business@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-didimcoin-ddc-on-december-23-2022/">LBank Exchange Will List DiDimCoin (DDC) on December 23, 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-didimcoin-ddc-on-december-23-2022/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Lending Firm Genesis Global Halts Redemptions</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-lending-firm-genesis-global-halts-redemptions/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-lending-firm-genesis-global-halts-redemptions/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 15:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genesis Global]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75544</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Genesis Global Capital – a crypto lending company – has suspended all redemptions and related activity as it’s now one of the latest firms to be feeling the heat and buzz caused by the collapse of FTX. Genesis Global Is Stopping All Redemptions A spokesperson for Genesis Global is assuring followers that the move is<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-lending-firm-genesis-global-halts-redemptions/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-lending-firm-genesis-global-halts-redemptions/">Crypto Lending Firm Genesis Global Halts Redemptions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Genesis Global Capital – a crypto lending company – has <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/crypto-broker-genesis-suspends-loan-redemptions-bankman-fried-celebrities-sued/ar-AA14bEUm" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">suspended all redemptions</a> and related activity as it’s now one of the latest firms to be feeling the heat and buzz caused by the collapse of FTX.</p>
<h2>Genesis Global Is Stopping All Redemptions</h2>
<p>A spokesperson for Genesis Global is assuring followers that the move is only temporary. The stoppage is designed to help the company better understand what happened and protect itself from potential ripple effects following the exchange’s crash.</p>
<p>Right now, the company is working on establishing the liquidity it needs to ensure all traders meet the company’s present lending obligations. At the time of writing, trading and custody businesses with Genesis remain unaffected.</p>
<p>Joseph Edwards – an investment partner at Securitize Capital – said that the maneuver is not in the company’s best interest and could potentially cause people to be less trusting of it. He mentioned in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>This shouldn&#8217;t be seen as a step up, but rather as a step outwards given that Genesis has a number of significant regulated counterparties. There will be discomfort being felt among OTC desks in Europe and North America in particular.</p></blockquote>
<p>The digital currency space could be forever marred by the actions and bad press surrounding FTX, which for a while, was considered one of the top players in the industry. At only three years of age, FTX rose to prominence rather quickly, ultimately placing itself in the top five crypto exchanges. Its founder, a young 30-something named Sam Bankman-Fried, was lauded as a genius of sorts, and just before the company collapsed, his net worth was valued at just over $16 billion.</p>
<p>But it was in mid-November when <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">everything began hitting</a> the fan. SBF announced on social media that his company was experiencing a liquidity crunch and lacked funds to stay fully operational. He approached his larger rival and competitor Binance for assistance and spoke to that company’s founder Changpeng Zhao about a potential merger, which <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">appeared to be moving</a> forward for a while.</p>
<h2>FTX Has Put a Serious Stain on the Crypto Space</h2>
<p>Just a few days later, however, Binance announced that it would not be purchasing the smaller company, claiming that the issues FTX was facing were simply too big for it to handle. As a result, Sam Bankman-Fried quickly resigned from his post, and FTX – now billions of dollars in debt – was now <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">entering bankruptcy proceedings</a>. It was a sad and ugly sight to see, and one that caused many to view the crypto space in a very negative light.</p>
<p>The situation has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/congressional-house-committee-vows-to-investigate-ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">caused several members</a> of Congress to renew their calls for crypto regulation, saying that if such a company can fall apart in such a short period, virtually no one and nothing is safe, and the government needs to step in to ensure protections are in place.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-lending-firm-genesis-global-halts-redemptions/">Crypto Lending Firm Genesis Global Halts Redemptions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-lending-firm-genesis-global-halts-redemptions/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Janet Yellen: Following FTX, We MUST Regulate Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/janet-yellen-following-ftx-we-must-regulate-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/janet-yellen-following-ftx-we-must-regulate-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 13:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Janet Yellen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75542</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen – who despite being a renowned economist couldn’t predict that the U.S. was headed for its worst inflationary period in over 40 years – has stated that the fall of the FTX exchange is exactly why the country needs to focus on crypto regulation. Janet Yellen Discusses Crypto Regulation In a<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/janet-yellen-following-ftx-we-must-regulate-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/janet-yellen-following-ftx-we-must-regulate-crypto/">Janet Yellen: Following FTX, We MUST Regulate Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen – who despite being a renowned economist <a href="https://nypost.com/2022/06/01/janet-yellen-admits-she-was-wrong-about-inflation/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">couldn’t predict that</a> the U.S. was headed for its worst inflationary period in over 40 years – has <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/ftx-collapse-sparks-call-by-janet-yellen-for-more-effective-cryptocurrency-oversight/ar-AA14cbmZ" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stated that the fall</a> of the FTX exchange is exactly why the country needs to focus on crypto regulation.</p>
<h2>Janet Yellen Discusses Crypto Regulation</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, Yellen mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>The recent failure of a major cryptocurrency exchange and the unfortunate impact that has resulted for holders and investors of crypto assets demonstrate the need for more effective oversight of cryptocurrency markets. We have very strong investor and consumer protection laws for most of our financial products and markets that are designed to address these risks. Where existing regulations apply, they must be enforced rigorously so that the same protections and principles apply to crypto assets and services.</p></blockquote>
<p>Yellen is not the only one using the situation to push the call for crypto regulation. Not long ago, Maxine Waters – a democrat from California and head of the House Financial Services Committee – vowed that <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/congressional-house-committee-vows-to-investigate-ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">her team would examine</a> what happened with FTX and that they would see about implementing appropriate crypto regulation relatively soon so that situations like these couldn’t happen again.</p>
<p>In a statement, Waters mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>The fall of FTX has posed tremendous harm to over one million users, many of whom were everyday people who invested their hard-earned savings into the FTX cryptocurrency exchange, only to watch it all disappear within a matter of seconds. Unfortunately, this event is just one out of many examples of cryptocurrency platforms that have collapsed just this past year.</p></blockquote>
<p>Yellen further stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Going forward, it’s vital we do what is necessary to address these concerning risks and act to protect consumers and promote financial stability.</p></blockquote>
<p>FTX will likely go down in crypto history as one of the biggest blunders to ever occur. Long considered a top player in the digital asset space, the exchange ran into serious trouble in mid-November when it was allegedly experiencing a liquidity crunch, meaning it was lacking funds and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">required additional</a> help.</p>
<h2>Binance Said &#8220;No Way!&#8221;</h2>
<p>The company turned to its larger rival Binance and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">spoke of a potential merger</a>, and while it appeared things were moving in this direction for a few days, Binance eventually backed away and said that the problems FTX was facing were simply too big for it to handle. From there, FTX was forced to undergo <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">bankruptcy proceedings</a> and its founder Sam Bankman-Fried resigned from his post.</p>
<p>The idea of regulation has long been a hotly debated topic, with some claiming that it will make the crypto space more legitimate and mainstream, and others saying that regulation goes against everything digital currency stands for and subjects it to the same bad habits seen in traditional finance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/janet-yellen-following-ftx-we-must-regulate-crypto/">Janet Yellen: Following FTX, We MUST Regulate Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/janet-yellen-following-ftx-we-must-regulate-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Manager Alex Pack Says He Never Trusted FTX</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-manager-alex-pack-says-he-never-trusted-ftx/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-manager-alex-pack-says-he-never-trusted-ftx/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 17:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alex Pack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75539</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FTX appeared to be the golden player of the crypto space for the last three years, but some investors – including Alex Pack, who manages New York-based venture capital firm Hack VC – were never convinced of the company’s prowess, and they say the company showed serious “red flags” from the start. Alex Pack Says<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-manager-alex-pack-says-he-never-trusted-ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-manager-alex-pack-says-he-never-trusted-ftx/">Crypto Manager Alex Pack Says He Never Trusted FTX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX</a> appeared to be the golden player of the crypto space for the last three years, <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/cryptocurrency-investor-says-he-saw-serious-red-flags-with-ftx-founder-sam-bankman-fried/ar-AA14erqt" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">but some investors</a> – including Alex Pack, who manages New York-based venture capital firm Hack VC – were never convinced of the company’s prowess, and they say the company showed serious “red flags” from the start.</p>
<h2>Alex Pack Says There Were Issues with FTX from the Beginning</h2>
<p>Pack first met Sam Bankman-Fried, the man behind FTX, roughly four years ago. At the time, Bankman-Fried had not created the now infamous exchange and was instead seeking additional startup funds for Alameda Research, another company he was creating at the time. When they met in 2018, Pack was running a crypto firm called Dragonfly Capital, and Bankman-Fried was seeking what he calls “single-digit millions” for his new enterprise.</p>
<p>In the beginning, Pack said he was “captivated” by Bankman-Fried. He said he had a lot of presence for such a young man, and he was impressed with his intelligence and business acumen, though he said this only lasted for about a month or so. In a recent interview, he commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>I was captivated by him for the first month until he showed us everything.</p></blockquote>
<p>He stated that he continued to meet with Bankman-Fried over the next five to six months. During that time, he performed due diligence on both the crypto founder and the company he was founding and claimed that there were simply too many holes in the game. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>After spending months with him, we realized his risk-taking was catastrophic. We looked at it and saw red flags. Too much risk.</p></blockquote>
<p>At the time, he said that Alameda was facing roughly $10 million in overall losses, which caused many alarm bells to ring with him and his partners. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>We could never figure [it] out. Was it fraud? Was it massive risk-taking? Was it a bunch of honest mistakes?</p></blockquote>
<p>He also said Bankman-Fried was “hemorrhaging” money to pay for what would eventually be FTX. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>We asked him, &#8216;What&#8217;s going on here?’ Pretty nonchalantly, he said, &#8216;I can&#8217;t remember if I told you I had this idea for an exchange. For that reason, I&#8217;ve been spending most of my time on it, so we have been neglecting the core business.&#8217; There was a lot he would or wouldn&#8217;t share. There was a clear pattern of hidden massive risk. He never really showed Alameda&#8217;s books to any future investor. That&#8217;s where all the bad stuff was happening.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Sam Bankman-Fried Tells His Side of the Story</h2>
<p>Contrary to what Pack has stated, Sam Bankman-Fried recently posted a series of tweets discussing the encounters from his own point of view. The FTX founder said:</p>
<blockquote><p>They expressed interest in Alameda and [a] desire to help it grow. They understood the business. Alameda has never taken an external investor, but this seemed like a good opportunity.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-manager-alex-pack-says-he-never-trusted-ftx/">Crypto Manager Alex Pack Says He Never Trusted FTX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-manager-alex-pack-says-he-never-trusted-ftx/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Australia Hints Crypto Regulation Will Arrive in 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/australia-hints-crypto-regulation-will-arrive-in-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/australia-hints-crypto-regulation-will-arrive-in-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 15:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[australia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75537</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The government of Australia has hinted it’s going to be implementing cryptocurrency regulations in 2023. The announcement comes on the heels of the FTX collapse, which will likely go down as one of the biggest embarrassments of the crypto space. Australia Could Regulate Crypto Next Year Australian Treasurer Jim Chalmers has stated that regulators are<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/australia-hints-crypto-regulation-will-arrive-in-2023/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/australia-hints-crypto-regulation-will-arrive-in-2023/">Australia Hints Crypto Regulation Will Arrive in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The government of Australia has hinted it’s going <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-in/news/india/australian-government-expected-to-initiate-cryptocurrency-regulations-next-year-amid-ftx-s-collapse/ar-AA14dpGH" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">to be implementing cryptocurrency</a> regulations in 2023. The announcement comes on the heels of the FTX collapse, which will likely go down as one of the biggest embarrassments of the crypto space.</p>
<h2>Australia Could Regulate Crypto Next Year</h2>
<p>Australian Treasurer Jim Chalmers has stated that regulators are eager to ensure crypto traders remain protected. Chalmers acknowledges that digital currency trading in Australia is reaching new highs, and he’s concerned that so long as people continue investing in an unregulated space, what happened with FTX will happen again, and additional firms will either fall completely or run off with investors’ money. He figures that if people are not willing to step away, at least they can instill the necessary protections to ensure criminality remains at a minimum.</p>
<p>Chalmers said:</p>
<blockquote><p>These developments highlight the lack of transparency and consumer protection in the crypto market, which is why our government is taking action to improve the regulatory frameworks while still promoting innovation.</p></blockquote>
<p>In his recent discussion regarding crypto regulation, Chalmers pointed to the fall of FTX as one of the main reasons as to why the government is now so eager to move forward with regulatory action. FTX, at only three years of age, was considered one of the top exchanges in the space, though mid-November saw it suddenly swamped with problems, and founder Sam Bankman-Fried went to his larger rival Binance for help with this firm’s <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">alleged liquidity crunch</a>.</p>
<p>For a while, it appeared Binance <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">was going to buy</a> out the smaller firm, though this did not occur, as the larger exchange explained on social media that FTX was dealing with too many issues. From there, Sam <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">Bankman-Fried resigned</a> from his post and FTX became the latest crypto firm to engage in bankruptcy proceedings. It was a sad and ugly sight to see; one that will forever mar the image people once had of what was labeled one of crypto’s golden players.</p>
<h2>Could Regulation Make a Difference?</h2>
<p>Michael Bacina – a digital asset manager at Piper Alderman lawyers – said in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Regulatory certainty is key to rebuilding trust in relation to centralized exchanges, and while law cannot eliminate bad behavior, it can set powerful norms and standards which make that behavior easier to find. The challenge will be ensuring that regulation does as intended to effectively protect consumers without suppressing industry growth… When Australia brings in technology-enabling custody rules for centralized holders of crypto assets, we will either be a leader in the space or catching up, depending on how fast other jurisdictions, like Singapore and Europe, move to make rules.</p></blockquote>
<p>Australia has long <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/australias-asic-is-looking-to-regulate-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">hinted that it would</a> like to regulate crypto, though this is arguably the first time when the state appears to be dead serious about doing so.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/australia-hints-crypto-regulation-will-arrive-in-2023/">Australia Hints Crypto Regulation Will Arrive in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/australia-hints-crypto-regulation-will-arrive-in-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Congressional House Committee Vows to Investigate FTX</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/congressional-house-committee-vows-to-investigate-ftx/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/congressional-house-committee-vows-to-investigate-ftx/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 13:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Congress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75534</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The House Financial Services Committee has said that it is opening an investigation into fallen cryptocurrency exchange FTX and its disgraced head executive Sam Bankman-Fried. FTX Will Be the Subject of a Congressional Inquiry The announcement came from Maxine Waters, a democrat from California that heads the committee. She stated that the team also expects<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/congressional-house-committee-vows-to-investigate-ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/congressional-house-committee-vows-to-investigate-ftx/">Congressional House Committee Vows to Investigate FTX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The House Financial Services Committee has said that it is <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/house-to-probe-ftx-collapse-expects-sam-bankman-fried-to-testify/ar-AA14bIbP" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">opening an investigation</a> into fallen cryptocurrency exchange FTX and its disgraced head executive Sam Bankman-Fried.</p>
<h2>FTX Will Be the Subject of a Congressional Inquiry</h2>
<p>The announcement came from Maxine Waters, a democrat from California that heads the committee. She stated that the team also expects Bankman-Fried to testify on what occurred and hinted that Congress is using what happened with the company to get serious about developing regulation for the digital currency space.</p>
<p>Waters said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The fall of FTX has posed tremendous harm to over one million users, many of whom were everyday people who invested their hard-earned savings into the FTX cryptocurrency exchange, only to watch it all disappear within a matter of seconds. Unfortunately, this event is just one out of many examples of cryptocurrency platforms that have collapsed just this past year.</p></blockquote>
<p>The fall of FTX will likely go down as one of the crypto space’s biggest blunders. Beginning in 2019, the company rose to prominence over a three-year period, achieving billion-dollar greatness in a relatively short frame of time. Sam Bankman-Fried was lauded as a genius by many people, and his net worth – just before the company crashed – was valued at roughly $16 billion.</p>
<p>However, mid-November saw <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX approaching its larger</a> rival Binance for help. It was insinuated that the bigger company would potentially buy out the smaller one and aid it following the announcement of the firm’s “liquidity crunch,” and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">while a deal appeared</a> to be moving forward for roughly 24 hours, the larger exchange eventually backed off, claiming that FTX’s issues were simply too big to handle.</p>
<p>From there, FTX filed <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">bankruptcy and</a> Sam Bankman-Fried stepped down from his post. Patrick T. McHenry – a republican from North Carolina who also serves on the House Committee – explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>Oversight is one of Congress’ most critical functions, and we must get to the bottom of this for FTX’s customers and the American people It’s essential that we hold bad actors accountable so responsible players can harness technology to build a more inclusive financial system.</p></blockquote>
<p>Despite the confidence of the committee players, some – like Senator Sherrod Brown, an Ohio democrat – believes that Sam Bankman-Fried testifying is something of a fantasy, largely because he is now facing multiple investigations and lawsuits. Brown also mentioned that he doesn’t think SBF is the only person behind what’s happened, and that there are probably several people in the wings that need to answer for potential crimes.</p>
<h2>Many People Involved?</h2>
<p>Brown mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>’I think that a lot of them [need] to explain what they’ve done.</p></blockquote>
<p>FTX is not the only company to reach a sudden demise in 2022. Other firms, such as the Celsius Network and Voyager Digital have also been <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-in-the-age-of-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">forced into bankruptcy</a> proceedings following the heavy volatility this year has delivered.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/congressional-house-committee-vows-to-investigate-ftx/">Congressional House Committee Vows to Investigate FTX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/congressional-house-committee-vows-to-investigate-ftx/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
