<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 02:33:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Faces Uphill Task Near $27,250</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-27250/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-27250/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 02:38:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78364</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price is correcting losses from the $26,000 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading near $27,000 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $27,250 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-27250/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-27250/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Faces Uphill Task Near $27,250</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin price is correcting losses from the $26,000 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading near $27,000 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $27,250 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could start a fresh increase if it clears the $27,250 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin price is rising from $26,000 against the US Dollar. BTC might eye another increase if the bulls remain active above the $26,250 zone.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price started a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-29k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">fresh decline</a> below the $28,000 support zone. There was a clear move below the $27,500 and $27,200 support levels. The pair even tested the $26,000 support zone.</p>
<p>It traded as low as $25,810 and recently started a fresh increase. There was a break above the $26,500 resistance zone. The price gained pace once it broke the $26,800 resistance zone and the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $29,850 swing high to the $25,810 low.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is now trading near $27,000 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-extend-losses-below-27000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. Immediate resistance on the upside is near the $27,200 level. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $27,250 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>The next major resistance might be near the $27,850 zone or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $29,850 swing high to the $25,810 low.</p>
<p>A clear move above the trend line and $27,850 might send the price toward $28,500, above which the price might rise toward the $29,200 level. Any more gains might push the price toward the $30,000 zone. If there is no upside break, the price might start a fresh decline below the $26,750 level.</p>
<p>The first major support is near $27,250. The next key support is near the $27,000 level, below which the price might accelerate lower. In the stated case, the price could decline toward the $26,000 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_78365" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Bitcoin-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78365" class="size-full wp-image-78365" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Bitcoin-2.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78365" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XBTUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Bitcoin’s price is trading near $27,000 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start a fresh increase if it clears the $27,250 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $26,750 and $27,000.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $27,250, $27,850, and $28,500.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-27250/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Faces Uphill Task Near $27,250</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-27250/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 8 Best Cryptocurrencies to Invest in Australia in 2022</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-8-best-cryptocurrencies-to-invest-in-australia-in-2022/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-8-best-cryptocurrencies-to-invest-in-australia-in-2022/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Guest]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 19:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry and Adoption]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78357</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This article will share the eight best cryptocurrencies to invest in Australia in 2022. So, if you&#8217;re based in Australia and planning to invest in crypto this year, this article will help you make the best decision. In the same way, Australian investors are increasingly financing cryptocurrencies and adding them to their investment portfolios for<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-8-best-cryptocurrencies-to-invest-in-australia-in-2022/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-8-best-cryptocurrencies-to-invest-in-australia-in-2022/">The 8 Best Cryptocurrencies to Invest in Australia in 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This article will share the eight best cryptocurrencies to invest in Australia in 2022. So, if you&#8217;re based in Australia and planning to invest in crypto this year, this article will help you make the best decision.</p>
<p>In the same way, Australian investors are increasingly financing cryptocurrencies and adding them to their investment portfolios for diversity. In addition, there are around 15,000 cryptocurrencies, which are growing every day.</p>
<p>Because of that, choosing a suitable virtual currency to invest in is one of the essential elements in achieving a positive return on investment. Indeed, we want that you don&#8217;t lose money on bad choices. Further, to ensure your investment goes on the right, you must know <a href="https://www.business2community.com/au/cryptocurrency/buy-bitcoin" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">how to buy bitcoin in Australia</a>, the ways, and the steps guide. Generally, people pick the most well-known coins when investing in cryptocurrencies in Australia.</p>
<p>However, there are varied causes for picking a well-known cryptocurrency. Reason number one is security issues.</p>
<p>If you&#8217;re a beginner, it&#8217;s very important to learn how to buy bitcoin in Australia. Read on to get begun with the best Australian cryptocurrencies in 2022.</p>
<h3>Top 8 Profitable Cryptocurrency in Australia in 2022</h3>
<p>Here&#8217;re eight of the most profitable cryptocurrencies you can invest in after finding the perfect one. Let&#8217;s say something about each one below.</p>
<h3>Bitcoin (BTC) &#8211; The Most Popular Cryptocurrency 2022</h3>
<p>In addition, Bitcoin has been around for the most extended of any cryptocurrency. It was the first cryptocurrency publicized in 2009, celebrating the start of the cryptocurrency generation. Thus, it launched the foundation of digital money.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Bitcoin is still the most famous cryptocurrency for Australians to fund. Likewise, Bitcoin is the first decentralized online money, permitting wallet holders to achieve quick, safe, and cost-effective P2P trades.</p>
<p>Beyond all this, using Bitcoin, you may earn houses, luxury items, automobiles, services, food, and beverages, among other items. Despite this, numerous vendors now approach Bitcoin as gold instead of digital money.</p>
<p>Hence, Nakamoto restricted the total number to 21 million coins, and Bitcoin has evolved significantly expensive as its circulation has fallen. Moreover, Bitcoin gained a record of $65,000 in April 2021. But it may seem just overstated to indicate that it will shortly exceed $100,000. Bitcoin will surprise us soon as it did before.</p>
<h3>Ethereum (ETH) &#8211; Trade Just Anything With</h3>
<p>Ether (ETH) is the native currency on the Ethereum network, a well-known open-source ledger technology that allows decentralization. Thus, in 2013, Vitalik Buterin created the second-largest cryptocurrency, Ether. After that, in July 2015, the Ethereum blockchain became online, with 72 million ETH currencies pre-mined.</p>
<p>Except for Bitcoin, there is no lid on the number of Ether that may develop, making it potentially more adaptable. Further, those confused about which cryptocurrency to invest in should consider Ether. Despite this, Ethereum is open at significant sales that allow you to buy cryptocurrency online in Australia.</p>
<p>Furthermore, it has a variety of real-world applications. Its biggest power, though, is undoubtedly its fundamental ties to the Ethereum blockchain, which has overall recognition and credibility.</p>
<p>Also, its declared ambition is to allow users to &#8220;codify, secure, decentralize, and trade just about anything.&#8221;</p>
<p>Therefore, if completely recognized, it can boost whole economies. Moreover, Ether itself has extremely speedy transaction times. Also, its market worth has even risen dramatically over the last five years.</p>
<p>Accordingly, numerous top billionaires who purchase cryptocurrency in Australia visit cryptocurrency exchanges daily to grow their Ether asset portfolio. As a result, it is calculated that the importance of Ethereum will be at $7,190 by the end of December 2022. Great news for you.</p>
<h3>Dogecoin (DOGE) &#8211; The Most Attractive Coin</h3>
<p>DOGE has to be one of the leading cryptocurrencies to purchase this 2022. Dogecoin is one of the most attractive coins. Particularly with Elon Musk spearheading the discussion on Twitter every time.</p>
<p>Further, it is supported by one of the most significant futures in crypto. The community behind it also keeps pushing. Also, the coin, which utilizes an image of the Shiba Inu as its avatar, is accepted as a form of payment by some major companies, including the Dallas Mavericks, Kronos, and SpaceX, an American aerospace factory possessed by Elon Musk.</p>
<p>Hence, Dogecoin was made by two software engineers, Billy Markus and Jackson Palmer, in 2013. However, Markus and Palmer reportedly produced the coin as a parody, commenting on the wild hypothesis of the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p>So the fee of DOGE hit an all-time high of approximately 0.74 cents during the week when Musk was scheduled to appear on Saturday Night Live.</p>
<h3>Litecoin (LTC) &#8211; Litecoin &#8211; Second Bitcoin</h3>
<p>Accordingly, Litecoin (LTC) was established in 2011. Surely, it was the first cryptocurrency to follow in the footsteps of Bitcoin. Also, it has usually been referred to as &#8220;silver to Bitcoin&#8217;s gold.&#8221;</p>
<p>Hence, Charlie Lee, an MIT graduate and former Google engineer designed it.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Litecoin is founded on an open-source international payment network. It&#8217;s not maintained by any central authority and uses the script as a PoW, which can be decoded with the help of consumer-grade central processing units (CPUs).</p>
<p>Thus, Litecoin is like Bitcoin in many forms. For example, it has a quicker block generation rate and thus proposes a faster trade confirmation time. As a result, other than developers, numerous sellers accept Litecoin.</p>
<h3>Bitcoin Cash (BCH) &#8211; The Great Investment Choice</h3>
<p>Bitcoin Cash is the result of a hard fork of the Bitcoin blockchain, which happened in August 2017. It is a crypto that focuses on peer-to-peer online transactions and wants to make paying with crypto easy, simple, and cheap.</p>
<p>If you believe that cryptocurrency will continue to grow, you would also believe that Bitcoin will become less and less usable for typical transactions. But on the other hand, if you think that Bitcoin Cash and its workable solution to the scaling problem are the future of peer-to-peer transactions, then Bitcoin Cash is a wise investment choice.</p>
<h3>US Dollar Coin (USDC) &#8211; Great and Steady Coin</h3>
<p>Truly, US Dollar Coin (USDC) is another great and steady coin. It&#8217;s exchangeable on a 1:1 basis for US dollars, funded by dollar-denominated assets kept in segregated accounts with US-regulated financial institutions.</p>
<p>Likewise, USDC is charged by Ethereum. It makes a stablecoin just like Tether. Hence, the use case of USDC is similar to USDT. Such as investors utilizing it for arbitrage or crypto conversion opportunities.</p>
<h3>Ripple (XRP) &#8211; Low Transaction Fees</h3>
<p>The XRP is one of the most famous cryptocurrencies on this list. Surely, it&#8217;s a helpful token providing lower transaction fees and fast transactions. In addition, it helps make cross-border financial transactions more efficient. Hence, by working with financial institutions, Ripple lowers currency exchange rates and provides real-time exchange rates.</p>
<p>Further,Ripple, the company that issued XRP, has proved its reputation as the most sought-after partner of many countries in creating digital currencies. Also, Ripple&#8217;s technology is being operated by hundreds of banks to promote transactions across the world.</p>
<p>Before Ripple, banks usually had to use intermediates for cross-border transactions. Indeed, these were costly and could take days to finish. But, Ripple has significantly improved efficiencies in how cross-border transactions operate. For an investor, this shows that Ripple is providing real matter in the world beyond the basic stock or exchange of value premise.</p>
<h3>Tether (USDT)</h3>
<p>Unlike some cryptocurrency rivals, Tether is a type of &#8216;stable coin.&#8217; Stable coins attempt to peg their market value to an external reference. For Tether, this indicates it&#8217;s backed by regular &#8216;fiat&#8217; currencies such as UK pounds, US dollars, or the euro and hypothetically holds importance equal to one of those denominations.</p>
<p>As a result, Tether&#8217;s value, the theory runs, ought to be more consistent than other cryptocurrencies. Also, it cares to be favored by investors who are wary of the extreme volatility of other coins.</p>
<h3>Conclusion</h3>
<p>This article is a clear walkthrough of the eight best cryptocurrencies you must invest in if you are based in Australia. Which one offers an attractive upside potential for you in 2022.It&#8217;s time to find your best crypto that is perfect for you and make your first investment(if you&#8217;re a beginner). Then, start investing full of safety, low cost, and the simplest way.</p>
<p>Further, choosing one specific cryptocurrency as the best investment in Australia is not easy. So if you&#8217;re new to cryptocurrency, and looking for the best token for beginners, then start with Bitcoin.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Image by <a href="https://pixabay.com/users/pattyjansen-154933/?utm_source=link-attribution&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_campaign=image&amp;utm_content=363244" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Patty Jansen</a> from <a href="https://pixabay.com//?utm_source=link-attribution&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_campaign=image&amp;utm_content=363244" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Pixabay</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-8-best-cryptocurrencies-to-invest-in-australia-in-2022/">The 8 Best Cryptocurrencies to Invest in Australia in 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-8-best-cryptocurrencies-to-invest-in-australia-in-2022/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Opinion: Crypto Fans May Want to Wait on Their Calls for Regulation</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-fans-may-want-to-wait-on-their-calls-for-regulation/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-fans-may-want-to-wait-on-their-calls-for-regulation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 17:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Opinion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OpEd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Janet Yellen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jerome Powell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77806</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Everyone keeps talking about crypto regulation as of late. It appears the topic has gained a lot of steam since crypto exchange FTX collapsed into a steaming pile of bankruptcy and fraud. Regulation Should Wait Until We Can Replace Those in Charge Under normal circumstances, a situation like this would indeed serve as a bridge<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-fans-may-want-to-wait-on-their-calls-for-regulation/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-fans-may-want-to-wait-on-their-calls-for-regulation/">Opinion: Crypto Fans May Want to Wait on Their Calls for Regulation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Everyone keeps talking about crypto regulation as of late. It appears the topic has gained a lot of steam since crypto <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">exchange FTX collapsed</a> into a steaming pile of bankruptcy and fraud.</p>
<h2>Regulation Should Wait Until We Can Replace Those in Charge</h2>
<p>Under normal circumstances, a situation like this would indeed serve as a bridge to regulation, but in many ways, right now is probably the worst time to instill any sort of regulatory oversight in the crypto space.</p>
<p>There are many reasons for this, one big one being who’s in charge. When one considers the level of incompetence they’ve witnessed over the last few years, they realize that those tasked with running their countries (and ultimately, the world) aren’t up to the job. Look at Janet Yellen, for example. This is a woman <a href="https://www.britannica.com/biography/Janet-Yellen" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">with a Ph.D. in economics</a> from Yale. Serving as the United States’ current Treasury Secretary, Yellen commented in 2021 that she <a href="https://nypost.com/2022/06/01/janet-yellen-admits-she-was-wrong-about-inflation/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">felt inflation was a problem</a> that would ultimately fix itself.</p>
<p>You have a Ph.D. in economics and statements like <em>that</em> are coming out of your mouth? Under Yellen’s hand, the U.S. economy has fallen into a complete state of disarray. Food and gas prices have reached new highs, inflation is the worst it’s been in over 40 years, and job numbers continue to be disappointing. Do we really want someone like this to have anything to do with the crypto industry? She can’t even handle the arena of standard finance, which has been around for hundreds of years. What makes anyone think she’ll competently reside over the still infant digital currency space?</p>
<p>Fed chair Jerome Powell has also proven incapable. His solution <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-fed-bitcoins-worst-enemy-right-now/" data-wpel-link="internal">to everything has just</a> been to hike rates. Despite everything showing him regularly that this methodology isn’t working, he can’t seem to change his mind or implement new tactics for fighting the economic downfall of America.</p>
<h2>Nobody Knows What They&#8217;re Doing!</h2>
<p>Right now, crypto prices are trying to make a comeback after suffering at the hands of his rate hikes during 2022. In addition, many people have been shut out of the American dream and can no longer afford homes or cars or anything else that might require a loan given the interest rates are practically unaffordable, but in the end, not much has really changed. Inflation is still a problem, and what did Jerome Powell say recently about it? <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/federal-reserve-hikes-rates-again-what-will-happen-to-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">That 2023 would likely</a> be a year of continued hikes, meaning we can look forward to more of the same over the next seven months.</p>
<p>Some might think that regulation is the only thing that can save crypto from situations like FTX, but while there may be a degree of truth to this, fans may want to wait on their calls for regulation until the American political spectrum can endure a few necessary changes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-fans-may-want-to-wait-on-their-calls-for-regulation/">Opinion: Crypto Fans May Want to Wait on Their Calls for Regulation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-fans-may-want-to-wait-on-their-calls-for-regulation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>P2P Bitcoin Marketplace Paxful Is Shutting Down</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/p2p-bitcoin-marketplace-paxful-is-shutting-down/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/p2p-bitcoin-marketplace-paxful-is-shutting-down/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 15:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artur Schaback]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paxful]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ray Youssef]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77809</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Peer-to-peer (P2P) bitcoin marketplace Paxful has closed its doors, meaning the digital currency space is still not yet out of the woods when it comes to exterior, negative circumstances. Paxful Says Goodbye Paxful used to be one of the most prominent, well-known bitcoin marketplaces in the world. Employing 200 people, the company was run by<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/p2p-bitcoin-marketplace-paxful-is-shutting-down/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/p2p-bitcoin-marketplace-paxful-is-shutting-down/">P2P Bitcoin Marketplace Paxful Is Shutting Down</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Peer-to-peer (P2P) bitcoin marketplace Paxful <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/drugs-erratic-dismissals-and-feuding-founders-behind-bitcoin-marketplace-paxfuls-unraveling-1032221094" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">has closed its doors</a>, meaning the digital currency space is still not yet out of the woods when it comes to exterior, negative circumstances.</p>
<h2>Paxful Says Goodbye</h2>
<p>Paxful used to be one of the most prominent, well-known bitcoin marketplaces in the world. Employing 200 people, the company was run by Ray Youssef and Artur Schaback. The company was founded in 2015 and saw more than $5 billion in BTC trades at the hands of roughly 12 million users.</p>
<p>In a recent interview, however, Youssef claimed that <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/paxful/" data-wpel-link="internal">Paxful</a> has been trapped in the doldrums for some time, saying that “key staff departures” and “regulatory challenges” eventually made it so that the enterprise could no longer operate. He also said he’s been struggling to see eye to eye with his co-founder Schaback, and that their differences eventually got in the way of the firm’s future.</p>
<p>In addition, there have been several reports – either through former employees coming forward or in various lawsuits issued by past staffers – that the daily cannabis use from people like Youssef (currently 46 years of age) grew into something that aided in the depletion of the company’s resources. The former employees now engaged in lawsuits against Paxful say the enterprise suffered from unprofessional management that got in the way of the firm’s functionality.</p>
<p>Schaback is also suing Youssef in a separate lawsuit, claiming he was cut out of the company’s computer network and data information systems while he was on paternity leave. He also says Paxful’s coffers were looted by Youssef and his cronies and that his co-founder went so far as to try and avoid international sanctions on “transactions into and out of Russia.”</p>
<p>He mentioned in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>Mr. Youssef took unilateral action to permanently shut down Paxful. His plan has been going for the better part of 15 months, but thanks to our civil proceedings in the United States, his plan was discovered and thwarted.</p></blockquote>
<p>By contrast, Youssef is hitting back and said that Schaback was fired from his position as COO with the company due to his growing “incompetence and bad behavior.” He also said that Schaback was a huge contributing factor in the closure of the firm. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>It was clear to everyone at the company that Schaback did not have any understanding of what a COO was supposed to do.</p></blockquote>
<h2>How the Pair Met</h2>
<p>Youssef met Schaback at a 2014 bitcoin event. A year later, they formed what became Paxful, and it appeared that the company had been on a steady roll since that time. Who would have known that so many ugly cracks had been forming in the foundation? Schaback concluded with:</p>
<blockquote><p>We met because we believed the idea of bitcoin helps the little guy.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/p2p-bitcoin-marketplace-paxful-is-shutting-down/">P2P Bitcoin Marketplace Paxful Is Shutting Down</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/p2p-bitcoin-marketplace-paxful-is-shutting-down/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Opinion: Joe Biden Will Never Take Responsibility for Hurting Crypto or America&#8217;s Standing</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-joe-biden-will-never-take-responsibility-for-hurting-crypto-and-americas-standing/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-joe-biden-will-never-take-responsibility-for-hurting-crypto-and-americas-standing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 13:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Opinion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OpEd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Afghanistan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77811</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Joe Biden is responsible for a growing number of mishaps since he first entered the White House. He’s responsible for the collapse of the crypto space, the death of the American economy, the border crisis, the list goes on and on. The problem is that he’ll never admit to any of this, as he and<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-joe-biden-will-never-take-responsibility-for-hurting-crypto-and-americas-standing/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-joe-biden-will-never-take-responsibility-for-hurting-crypto-and-americas-standing/">Opinion: Joe Biden Will Never Take Responsibility for Hurting Crypto or America&#8217;s Standing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Joe Biden is responsible for a growing number of mishaps since he first entered the White House. He’s responsible for the collapse of the crypto space, the death of the American economy, the border crisis, the list goes on and on. The problem is that he’ll never admit to any of this, as he and his fellow nation haters are <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/janet-yellen-blames-everybody-else-for-the-financial-panic-svb-signature-banking-system-treasury-san-francisco-federal-reserve-e715ded3" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">consistently looking for</a> ways to shirk the blame onto others.</p>
<h2>Joe Biden: America&#8217;s &#8220;Loser-in-Chief&#8221;</h2>
<p>Not long ago, several members of the Biden administration issued a report blaming Trump for the country’s sloppy and reputation-altering <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/biden-administration-completes-long-awaited-reports-on-afghan-withdrawal/ar-AA19yLHu" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">exit from Afghanistan</a> in August of 2021. <em>Really</em>, Biden? Is this a sick joke of some kind? August of 2021… This was literally seven months after Trump left office. You had been in power for some time already. How on earth can you say the Afghanistan debacle is Trump’s fault?</p>
<p>We all watched in horror on television the <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/video/2021/aug/16/afghans-climb-on-to-plane-takeoff-attempt-flee-taliban-video" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">footage of people as they</a> clung to the side of a plane lifting off the ground. We all watched as more <a href="https://americanmilitarynews.com/2021/08/pics-videos-us-gave-85-billion-in-weaponry-to-afghans-now-the-taliban-has-tons-of-it/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">than $85 billion in</a> top-of-the-line equipment was left in Afghanistan for the Taliban to steal and become even stronger despite a 20-year campaign to remove its influence. We all watched as the <a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-58238497" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">military was pulled</a> out of the nation first and <a href="https://americanmilitarynews.com/2022/02/biden-abandoned-as-many-as-9000-americans-in-afghanistan-new-report-shows/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">American citizens and our</a> allies were left behind, many of whom are still trapped within Middle Eastern borders nearly two years later.</p>
<p>Biden, let’s be perfectly clear… <em>You</em> and <em>only you</em> are responsible for this mess. Not Trump, not any of his staffers, <em>just you</em>. You were warned multiple <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2021/09/28/us/politics/milley-senate-hearing-afghanistan.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">times by military personnel</a> that such a pullout would result in catastrophic results, but in the end, as usual, your ego got in the way, and you went forward with your ridiculous plan. It’s cost lives, and it has cost the U.S. its reputation.</p>
<p>If you had any presidential instinct, you would apologize profusely, swear to make things right, then take necessary action to ensure the future could remain intact. You would then resign and give someone with a more capable hand the opportunity to step in and fix what you’ve clearly destroyed, but you’ll never do this. You are <em>not</em> a leader; you’re a jester, and a <em>very weak</em> and unfunny one at that.</p>
<h2>&#8220;I&#8217;m Sorry&#8221; Are Words That Don&#8217;t Exist in His Vocabulary</h2>
<p>This same scenario applies to the crypto industry in many ways. By signing <a href="https://www.pbs.org/newshour/politics/biden-signs-1-7-trillion-bill-funding-government-operations" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">his name to an endless</a> array of trillion-dollar spending bills and making a long string of poor decisions regarding the U.S. economy, Biden has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/inflation-is-having-harsher-effects-on-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">given rise to a 40-year high</a> in inflation. He has brought the nation to its knees and caused the catastrophic destruction of a growing financial arena and cut many people out of the American dream.</p>
<p>But it’s clear, now, we will <em>never</em> get an apology from Joe Biden, much less action to resolve his endless mistakes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-joe-biden-will-never-take-responsibility-for-hurting-crypto-and-americas-standing/">Opinion: Joe Biden Will Never Take Responsibility for Hurting Crypto or America&#8217;s Standing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-joe-biden-will-never-take-responsibility-for-hurting-crypto-and-americas-standing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Interview with Jason Blick, AZUR Chairman</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/interview-with-jason-blick-azur-chairman/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/interview-with-jason-blick-azur-chairman/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 11:41:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78346</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Can you give us a brief overview of your special economic zone and what sets it apart from other zones? AZUR’s special economic zone is a true paradise for blockchain and crypto businesses, nestled in the beautiful island of Anguilla. Our zone is designed to provide the most attractive regulatory and fiscal environment for companies<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/interview-with-jason-blick-azur-chairman/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/interview-with-jason-blick-azur-chairman/">Interview with Jason Blick, AZUR Chairman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em><strong>Can you give us a brief overview of your special economic zone and what sets it apart from other zones?</strong></em></p>
<p>AZUR’s special economic zone is a true paradise for blockchain and crypto businesses, nestled in the beautiful island of Anguilla. Our zone is designed to provide the most attractive regulatory and fiscal environment for companies operating in this exciting industry.</p>
<p>But what really sets us apart from the rest of the crowd is our unwavering commitment to providing a comprehensive range of services that will help our clients succeed. From top-notch IT infrastructure to regulatory and compliance support, and from banking and financial services to legal and tax advisory, we&#8217;ve got you covered.</p>
<p>Believe me when I say that AZUR’s special economic zone is the perfect place for your business to thrive. The combination of a friendly business environment and our range of services makes us truly unique in the market.</p>
<p><em><strong>What inspired you to create a special economic zone? And why would this be attractive to bitcoin startups and workers?</strong></em></p>
<p>Having spent more years working in global financial services than I care to remember, I can confidently say that creating a special economic zone in Anguilla has a lot of potential. And that’s what inspired the team here at AZUR.</p>
<p>To start with, a bitcoin-friendly environment like AZUR is primed to attract investment from companies and individuals who are interested in cryptocurrency and blockchain technology, leading to the creation of new businesses, jobs, and ultimately boosting economic growth. This would be a welcome addition to Anguilla&#8217;s economy, which is currently heavily reliant on tourism.</p>
<p>Also, a crypto-friendly special economic zone will foster innovation in the field of blockchain technology, opening up new ideas and products that would not only benefit Anguilla, but the wider global community as well. In fact, by becoming a hub for cryptocurrency and blockchain technology, Anguilla could enhance its international reputation as a forward-thinking and innovative jurisdiction, which could help attract more visitors and investors to the island.</p>
<p>In addition to that, a special economic zone with clear regulations and guidelines for cryptocurrency and blockchain technology would provide much-needed regulatory clarity for businesses operating in the sector. This could attract businesses and investors who may have been hesitant to enter the market due to regulatory uncertainty, helping further boost the economy.</p>
<p>This would position Anguilla as a global leader in the field of blockchain technology and set it on the path to becoming a major player in the financial services industry.</p>
<p><strong><em>What steps do you take to ensure that the companies and individuals operating within your special economic zone comply with local laws and regulations, while still promoting innovation and growth in the bitcoin industry?</em></strong></p>
<p>One of the first steps towards ensuring compliance with local laws and regulations within the special economic zone is to establish a crystal-clear set of rules and regulations that applies to all businesses operating within the zone. This could include guidelines for compliance with local laws, as well as best practices for security and risk management.</p>
<p>We need to foster collaboration between businesses and regulators to promote innovation while still maintaining compliance. This could involve regular meetings and consultations to discuss emerging trends in the crypto industry and potential regulatory implications. By working together, businesses and regulators can ensure that the crypto industry continues to grow and innovate while still operating within the bounds of local laws and regulations. It&#8217;s all about striking the right balance.</p>
<p><em><strong>What steps has AZUR taken to attract cryptocurrency startups and workers to the SEZ?</strong></em></p>
<p>AZUR is all about tech, innovation, and sustainability &#8211; three key elements that are essential for success in the crypto space.</p>
<p>First of all, any fees and payments that we charge clients are all payable in bitcoin!</p>
<p>Also, for those looking to build a business in the cryptocurrency industry, AZUR SEZ provides a solid platform for knowledge-based companies, research organizations, and entrepreneurs. And let me tell you, that&#8217;s a major advantage.</p>
<p>AZUR also boasts advanced infrastructure and supportive eco-systems that are ideal for innovation and technological development. And for those who value environmental consciousness (which should be all of us, really), AZUR&#8217;s focus on creating a sustainable and eco-friendly environment is a big plus.</p>
<p>So, if you&#8217;re looking to grow your business in the cryptocurrency industry, AZUR has got your back. With our advanced infrastructure, supportive ecosystems, and sustainable environment, we&#8217;re perfectly aligned with the needs and values of the industry.</p>
<p><em><strong>Let’s say you’re speaking to the CEO of a new bitcoin startup, and they’re looking for reasons why AZUR is the answer to their location problems. How does AZUR appeal?</strong></em></p>
<p>When it comes to setting up business, startups of all kinds should definitely take a closer look at what AZUR SEZ has to offer. We&#8217;ve got a whole host of benefits that can make a real difference for businesses, such as streamlined regulations, tax breaks, and best-in-class infrastructure that blows the competition out of the water.</p>
<p>And for crypto startups in particular, AZUR is a total game-changer. With our clear and predictable regulatory environment, we can help you navigate the choppy waters of blockchain and cryptocurrency with confidence. Plus, our tax incentives can help you save some serious money.</p>
<p>To sum it up, crypto startups would be wise to consider AZUR SEZ as their new home base. With our focus on regulatory clarity, tax benefits, first-rate infrastructure, access to talent, and opportunities for networking, you&#8217;ll have everything you need to take your business to the next level.</p>
<p><em><strong>Looking ahead, what are your plans for expanding and evolving your special economic zone in the years to come, and how do you see the crypto landscape changing over this time period?</strong></em></p>
<p>The task of expanding and evolving a special economic zone (SEZ) is a multifaceted one that demands meticulous planning and flawless execution. AZUR, being the visionary organization that it is, is well aware of this and has devised a comprehensive strategy to take on the challenge.</p>
<p>By identifying the key industries and sectors that will drive growth, AZUR has laid the groundwork for attracting investment and promoting innovation. AZUR recognizes that in order to remain competitive, it is crucial to encourage the development of new technologies and products. As such, partnerships with research institutions, universities, and other organizations are key components of AZUR&#8217;s strategy.</p>
<p>Moreover, AZUR recognizes that SEZs are hotbeds of entrepreneurial activity and, therefore, have the potential to become thriving ecosystems for startups and small businesses. With this in mind, AZUR is committed to creating an environment that fosters entrepreneurship and supports the growth of new businesses.</p>
<p>As for the crypto landscape in general? The crypto world is always evolving, and there are some exciting developments on the horizon that could make a big difference.</p>
<p>First off, we could see more mainstream adoption of cryptocurrencies. As more big players get involved and governments start to regulate, it could become easier and more common to use crypto as a form of payment.</p>
<p>Another big challenge with crypto right now is scalability, but there are new solutions in the works that could speed things up and make transactions more affordable. This could be a game-changer for people who want to use crypto for everyday transactions.</p>
<p>Security is another big issue in the crypto space, with many high-profile hacks and scams in recent years. But there are some exciting new technologies being developed that could help make things more secure, such as multi-signature wallets, decentralized exchanges, and advanced cryptography.</p>
<p>There are also a lot of different cryptocurrencies and blockchain platforms out there, but they don&#8217;t always work well together. However, new interoperability solutions could help bridge these gaps and make it easier to move between different ecosystems.</p>
<p>Finally, DeFi is one of the most exciting areas of innovation in the crypto space right now. Decentralized finance allows people to lend, borrow, and trade money in a peer-to-peer, decentralized way, which has a lot of potential. It&#8217;s growing fast and could change the game for financial services.</p>
<p>Overall, there&#8217;s a lot happening in the crypto space right now, and we could see some major improvements in the years ahead. From mainstream adoption to improved scalability and enhanced security, the future of crypto looks bright.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/interview-with-jason-blick-azur-chairman/">Interview with Jason Blick, AZUR Chairman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/interview-with-jason-blick-azur-chairman/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Risk of Bearish Thrust Below $0.35</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-risk-of-bearish-thrust-below-0-35/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-risk-of-bearish-thrust-below-0-35/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 06:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78343</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ADA price is gaining bearish momentum below the $0.388 support zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $0.380 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a short-term rising channel forming with resistance near $0.376 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Coinbase). The price could continue to move<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-risk-of-bearish-thrust-below-0-35/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-risk-of-bearish-thrust-below-0-35/">Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Risk of Bearish Thrust Below $0.35</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>ADA price is gaining bearish momentum below the $0.388 support zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $0.380 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a short-term rising channel forming with resistance near $0.376 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Coinbase).</li>
<li>The price could continue to move down if it stays below the $0.38 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Cardano price is struggling below $0.388 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-29k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. ADA price could start a fresh increase if it clears the $0.380 and $0.388 resistance levels.</em></p>
<h2>Cardano Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, Cardano price saw a rejection pattern near the $0.398 zone against the US Dollar. The ADA/USD pair declined below the $0.388 and $0.380 support levels.</p>
<p>The price even declined below the $0.355 support and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). It revisited the $0.350 support zone. A low is formed near $0.3500 and the price is consolidating losses. It is now trading below $0.380 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-bears-in-control-below-0-4/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>Besides, there is a short-term rising channel forming with resistance near $0.376 on the 4-hour chart. On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $0.374 zone or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3966 swing high to the $0.3500 low.</p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $0.380 level. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3966 swing high to the $0.3500 low.</p>
<p>A clear upside break above the $0.380 level might send the price toward the $0.388 resistance. Any more gains could start a steady increase toward the $0.400 level or even $0.425. On the downside, immediate support is near the $0.360 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $0.350 level, below which the price may perhaps decline toward the $0.332 support level. Any more losses might call for a test of the $0.320 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_78344" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Cardano-Price-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78344" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78344" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Cardano-Price-2.png" alt="Cardano (ADA) Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78344" class="wp-caption-text">Cardano (ADA) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ADAUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that ADA price is now trading below $0.380 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $0.380 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ADA/USD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for ADA/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.360 and $0.350.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.380 and $0.388.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-risk-of-bearish-thrust-below-0-35/">Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Risk of Bearish Thrust Below $0.35</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-risk-of-bearish-thrust-below-0-35/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Could Drop Below $1,700</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-drop-below-1700/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-drop-below-1700/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 02:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78340</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum price is gaining bearish momentum below the $1,880 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH price is now trading below $1,850 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $1,820 on the 4-hour chart (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could continue<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-drop-below-1700/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-drop-below-1700/">Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Could Drop Below $1,700</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ethereum price is gaining bearish momentum below the $1,880 resistance against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>ETH price is now trading below $1,850 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $1,820 on the 4-hour chart (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it stays below $1,850 and $1,880.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ethereum price is declining below $1,850 against the US Dollar. ETH/USD remains at a risk of more downsides below the $1,700 support zone.</em></p>
<h2>Ethereum Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, Ethereum started a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-at-risk-of-downside-break/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">fresh decline</a> below $1,920 against the US Dollar. ETH price moved into a bearish zone below the $1,880 level.</p>
<p>A low was formed near $1,737 before the price started an upside correction. There was a move above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $2,020 swing high to the $1,737 low. Besides, there was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $1,820 on the 4-hour chart.</p>
<p>It is now trading below $1,850 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-faces-increase-in-bearish-pressure/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. On the upside, the price is now facing resistance near the $1,850 level.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $1,880 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $2,020 swing high to the $1,737 low, above which it could rise toward the $1,920 resistance zone. A clear move above the $1,880 and $1,920 resistance levels might call for a fresh move to $2,000. Any more gains could even send the price toward the $2,120 resistance zone or even $2,200 in the near term.</p>
<p>On the downside, initial support is near the $1,780 level. The next major support is now near the $1,740 level. A break below the $1,740 support could push the price to $1,700. If the bulls fail to protect the $1,700 support, the price might decline toward $1,650.</p>
<div id="attachment_78341" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Ethereum-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78341" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78341" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Ethereum-2.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78341" class="wp-caption-text">Ethereum Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Ethereum price is trading below $1,880 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, Ether’s price could continue to move down if it stays below $1,850 and $1,880.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for ETH/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $1,740, followed by the $1,700 zone.</p>
<p>Key Resistance$ Levels – $1,840 and $1,880.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-drop-below-1700/">Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Could Drop Below $1,700</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-drop-below-1700/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leaked Memo Suggests Democrats Are Trying to Kill the Crypto Industry</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leaked-memo-suggests-democrats-are-trying-to-kill-the-crypto-industry/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leaked-memo-suggests-democrats-are-trying-to-kill-the-crypto-industry/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 17:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[democrats]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[memo]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78309</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new memo shows that democrats really hate cryptocurrency. So much so, that they’re looking to instill new rules that would make it very hard to attain and keep. Democrats Wage War Against Crypto A leaked memo sent to democrat House financial services committee members reveals that left leaners are seeking to ensure all digital<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leaked-memo-suggests-democrats-are-trying-to-kill-the-crypto-industry/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leaked-memo-suggests-democrats-are-trying-to-kill-the-crypto-industry/">Leaked Memo Suggests Democrats Are Trying to Kill the Crypto Industry</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new memo shows that democrats really hate cryptocurrency. So much so, that they’re looking to instill new <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/05/12/leak-reveals-secret-democrat-plan-for-a-game-changing-us-crypto-crackdown-that-could-hit-the-price-of-bitcoin-and-ethereum/?sh=4dad93cf1568" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">rules that would make</a> it very hard to attain and keep.</p>
<h2>Democrats Wage War Against Crypto</h2>
<p>A leaked memo sent to democrat House financial services committee members reveals that left leaners are seeking to ensure all digital currencies, in the future, are classified as securities. This doesn’t necessarily mean they cannot be obtained, but they will be subjected to all kinds of new taxation rules that will make these assets very hard to keep. In addition, this will also likely cause hell for all kinds of crypto companies.</p>
<p>If it suddenly becomes law that every digital currency ever created must be categorized as a security, there are plenty of issuing companies that will probably be subjected to all kinds of fees and penalties from organizations like the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). If this happens, you can expect to see a whirlwind of negativity hitting the industry. Prices will easily collapse, and there’s a good chance several crypto companies will not survive. The memo reads as follows:</p>
<blockquote><p>The problem isn’t ambiguity. It’s mass non-compliance with existing laws. We can&#8217;t invent new accommodating regulatory structures simply because crypto companies refuse to follow clear rules of the road.</p></blockquote>
<p>The memo also clearly outlines an attempt from the republican party to protect both consumers and investors. Right wingers are working hard to ensure all crypto regulations are clear and justifiable, something the democrats are purportedly trying to get in the way of. The document continues:</p>
<blockquote><p>They [republicans] are working to provide clarity to the markets by carving out space for the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) in crypto&#8230; Republicans are proving that they really aren&#8217;t serious about protecting investors and consumers.</p></blockquote>
<p>Joe Biden and his legion of democrats have been waging an all-out war on the crypto arena since they first took the White House over two years ago. Men like Gary Gensler – head of the SEC – have worked hard to ensure all crypto companies are persecuted and attacked as though they are enemies of the state, and big names like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/" data-wpel-link="internal">Kraken</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">Coinbase</a> have fallen victim to their antics.</p>
<h2>Trying to Tie Things Up</h2>
<p>The memo further states:</p>
<blockquote><p>Both the SEC and CFTC are aligned on the fact that the SEC is the regulator to determine if crypto assets are securities, and the SEC has made clear that nearly all crypto assets are securities. End of story… Republicans want to reverse course and tie the hands of the SEC. The SEC must continue to lead the regulation of the U.S. crypto market, and Congress must do its part to provide them with the resources they need.</p></blockquote>
<p>The document, naturally, is earning criticism from digital currency analysts everywhere.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leaked-memo-suggests-democrats-are-trying-to-kill-the-crypto-industry/">Leaked Memo Suggests Democrats Are Trying to Kill the Crypto Industry</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leaked-memo-suggests-democrats-are-trying-to-kill-the-crypto-industry/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
