<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 17:38:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Study: Colorado Is One of the Most Active States for Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/study-colorado-is-one-of-the-most-active-states-for-crypto-trading/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/study-colorado-is-one-of-the-most-active-states-for-crypto-trading/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 17:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Colorado]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto activity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nevada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New York]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77706</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a recent poll, Colorado ranks amongst the highest states when it comes to crypto activity. Colorado Ranks High When It Comes to Crypto Activity The study was conducted by Cryptobetting.org. The platform looked at all the crypto activity occurring within the 50 states of the American union, and as it turns out, Colorado placed<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/study-colorado-is-one-of-the-most-active-states-for-crypto-trading/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/study-colorado-is-one-of-the-most-active-states-for-crypto-trading/">Study: Colorado Is One of the Most Active States for Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a recent poll, Colorado ranks <a href="https://kdvr.com/news/colorado-ranks-highly-for-interest-in-cryptocurrency-trading/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">amongst the highest states when</a> it comes to crypto activity.</p>
<h2>Colorado Ranks High When It Comes to Crypto Activity</h2>
<p>The study was conducted by Cryptobetting.org. The platform looked at all the crypto activity occurring within the 50 states of the American union, and as it turns out, Colorado placed eighth. The state is amongst the youngest regions of the country, and it’s also one <a href="https://kdvr.com/news/data/study-colorado-one-of-the-top-states-for-tech-workers/?ipid=promo-link-block1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">of the most tech-friendly</a> according to a separate poll.</p>
<p>All this makes sense in many ways given how the region has fallen victim to a wide array of digital currency scams in recent months. According to a statement by the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), several residents have fallen victim to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fbi-report-shows-colorado-residents-getting-duped-by-crypto-scams/" data-wpel-link="internal">crypto scams in Colorado</a> centering around USDC, a prominent stable currency. The statement also provided advice for how to avoid falling victim to a scam. It read:</p>
<blockquote><p>In a common scenario, the victim is approached on a social media platform, dating app, or discussion forum with a cryptocurrency investment opportunity. The victim is directed to a link or phone number to set up the investment account. This is a scam. The link or phone number is controlled by the fraudster, who has set up a fictitious support site. Once the victim transfers the funds, the fraudster disappears with the money.</p></blockquote>
<p>Naturally, a lot of crypto activity is going to give rise to a few bad actors here and there, so it seems accurate that the digital currency trading occurring within Colorado has grown in recent weeks to earn it a place on this poll’s list. The study also suggests that for every 100,000 people in the state, approximately 1,710 crypto-related searches occurred online. The state presently ties in this department with regions like Virginia and Massachusetts.</p>
<p>Despite Colorado’s high rank, it does not beat Nevada, which currently (as <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/study-nevada-is-the-most-crypto-friendly-state/" data-wpel-link="internal">it did last year</a>) lists as the top state for digital currency friendliness. That state saw close to 2,000 crypto-related searches online for every 100K people, thus beating out the Centennial State by a hefty margin. Among the lowest activity states was Mississippi, which only saw about 686 searches for every 100,000 residents.</p>
<p>The top five top crypto states were Nevada as number one, followed by California, New York, New Jersey, and Washington in that order.</p>
<h2>New York Is Crypto Friendly?!</h2>
<p>The inclusion of New York in the top five is a surprise given just how non-friendly the region’s regulators have been over the past several years. Things got off to a negative start in 2015 when the state introduced the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitlicense/" data-wpel-link="internal">BitLicense</a>, a document that proved so rigid and expensive it caused many digital currency companies to exit the Empire State for good.</p>
<p>NY attorney general Leticia James has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leticia-james-sues-coin-ex-alleging-crypto-fraud/" data-wpel-link="internal">also developed a habit</a> of going after several crypto firms in court.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/study-colorado-is-one-of-the-most-active-states-for-crypto-trading/">Study: Colorado Is One of the Most Active States for Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/study-colorado-is-one-of-the-most-active-states-for-crypto-trading/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The SEC Wants More Funds to Go After Crypto Companies</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-wants-more-funds-to-go-after-crypto-companies/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-wants-more-funds-to-go-after-crypto-companies/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kraken]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77703</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Gary Gensler – the head of the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) – is asking Congress to grant the agency even more funding so he and his fellow agents can continue their investigations into the crypto arena. Gary Gensler and the SEC Want More Money In a recent conference, Gensler described the crypto scene as<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-wants-more-funds-to-go-after-crypto-companies/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-wants-more-funds-to-go-after-crypto-companies/">The SEC Wants More Funds to Go After Crypto Companies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Gary Gensler – the head of the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) – is <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/gensler-urges-congress-to-increase-funding-for-sec-to-investigate-cryptocurrency-issues/ar-AA19ferY" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">asking Congress to grant</a> the agency even more funding so he and his fellow agents can continue their investigations into the crypto arena.</p>
<h2>Gary Gensler and the SEC Want More Money</h2>
<p>In a recent conference, Gensler described the crypto scene as the “Wild West” (how original – nobody’s <em>ever</em> used that term before) and asked that he be given the funds to hire more employees so that they can examine more digital currency firms, which he described as “rife” with non-compliance.</p>
<p>The conference occurred before the Subcommittee on Financial Services and General Government. Gensler discussed the ongoing changes and rapid growth of certain markets, a big one being digital currency. He said there are more people participating in the space than ever before. This puts them all at risk given how many of the enterprises allegedly don’t follow present financial rules and securities laws.</p>
<p>Right now, according to the SEC head, the Division of Enforcement and Examinations makes up roughly half of the agency’s staff. As it stands, the Division garnered more than 35,000 separate tips, referrals, and complaints from whistleblowers in 2022 alone.</p>
<p>Gensler has no doubt this will get worse over time if the SEC is not permitted to do all it can in the coming months and weeks to prevent further bad actors from having a hand in the growing digital currency industry. He said the Division brought more than 750 unique actions against crypto companies last year, but that this was not enough to get everyone that needed to be investigated. Overall, these actions led to nearly $6.5 million in penalty fees.</p>
<p>When asked by Wisconsin Democrat Rep. Mark Pocan if the SEC has adequate research to investigate the present crypto issues making their way to the top of the SEC’s priorities list, Gensler answered:</p>
<blockquote><p>We’re stretched thin, sir. This is a field that has [a] significant amount of non-compliance in it. We’ve increased our resources there, but we could always use more.</p></blockquote>
<p>The funding that Gensler is now suggesting would arrive as early as 2024 and permit the agency to fill another 170 separate positions. It would also grant full-year funding to all the people hired by the agency in 2023.</p>
<h2>Going After Every Company</h2>
<p>The SEC has developed a big goal to go after and persecute practically every single digital currency company in the last few weeks. For example, leading US digital currency exchange Coinbase has recently <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">received a Wells notice</a> from the SEC, suggesting the company could face legal action relatively soon.</p>
<p>The agency has also gone after Kraken, another Northern California-based digital trading platform. The enterprise was forced to part <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/" data-wpel-link="internal">with a $30 million penalty</a> fee and end all its staking services and activities.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-wants-more-funds-to-go-after-crypto-companies/">The SEC Wants More Funds to Go After Crypto Companies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-wants-more-funds-to-go-after-crypto-companies/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mike Novogratz Fights Top Economist Over BTC</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-novogratz-fights-top-economist-over-btc/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-novogratz-fights-top-economist-over-btc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 13:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mike Novogratz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Steve Hanke]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77701</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin bull and hedge fund manager Mike Novogratz has gotten into a bit of a battle with top economist Steve Hanke over bitcoin. The latter is against it, while the former is practically willing to bet everything he has on the asset. Mike Novogratz Comes to Bitcoin&#8217;s Aid In a recent tweet, Hanke took aim<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-novogratz-fights-top-economist-over-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-novogratz-fights-top-economist-over-btc/">Mike Novogratz Fights Top Economist Over BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin bull and hedge fund manager Mike Novogratz has <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/mike-novogratz-challenges-steve-hanke-after-the-top-economist-bashes-bitcoin-as-a-fool-s-game/ar-AA19dE50" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">gotten into a bit of a battle</a> with top economist Steve Hanke over bitcoin. The latter is against it, while the former is practically willing to bet everything he has on the asset.</p>
<h2>Mike Novogratz Comes to Bitcoin&#8217;s Aid</h2>
<p>In a recent tweet, Hanke took aim at bitcoin, calling it a “fool’s game.” He wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin is a highly speculative asset, not a currency. Unreliability, lack of stability, and susceptibility to fraud will continue to plague this cryptocurrency. Don&#8217;t be tricked; buying bitcoin is a fool&#8217;s game.</p></blockquote>
<p>In retaliation, Novogratz commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Steve, it has outperformed all assets [year to date] over two years and three years on a risk adjusted weighting (sharpe ratio). It&#8217;s been safer than JPM and Google. Run the numbers yourself.</p></blockquote>
<p>Novogratz has always been there to support bitcoin, even when nobody else is. He’s commented in the past that he thinks the price of BTC could potentially rise to $500,000 as we get closer to 2030, though frankly, if the asset simply <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-novogratz-will-be-happy-if-btc-reaches-30k-at-the-end-of-the-year/" data-wpel-link="internal">reaches a price of about</a> $30,000 by the end of the year, he’ll be happy with that considering the terrible bear run it had during 2022 and how hard it’s been for the asset to pull itself out of the doldrums.</p>
<p>2022 was arguably the worst year on record for bitcoin. The token lost more than 70 percent of its value over the course of 12 short months. Initially, the asset was trading at a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit. This was in November of 2021. From there, it incurred a series of losses that ultimately brought it down into the mid-$16K range by the end of 2022.</p>
<p>Now, however, the asset appears to be picking itself back up as at the time of writing, the currency is trading at $28,000. This is nowhere near where it was just a year and a half ago, but we’re certainly getting there.</p>
<p>There’s still a lot of room for healing, but the fact that BTC has the initiative to be pushing itself the way it is seems to be giving a lot of fans and investors hope that perhaps the negativity of the previous year can finally be put behind them. That $28,000 price shows that the currency has managed to add roughly $12,000 to its value in just a few months.</p>
<h2>Some, Like the SEC, Don&#8217;t Think Assets Like BTC Are Reliable</h2>
<p>Sadly, while there are certainly people out there who would agree with Novogratz that bitcoin is something unique, there are other parties that will probably side with Hanke like the SEC. In a recent statement, the agency said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The only money you should put at risk with any speculative investment is money you can afford to lose entirely.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-novogratz-fights-top-economist-over-btc/">Mike Novogratz Fights Top Economist Over BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-novogratz-fights-top-economist-over-btc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Earn Passive Income Cloud Mining With HappyMiner &#8211; A Quick Guide!</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/earn-passive-income-cloud-mining-with-happyminer-a-quick-guide/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/earn-passive-income-cloud-mining-with-happyminer-a-quick-guide/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 17:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78215</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are you interested in making passive income for extra security? Well, cloud mining is one of the best methods to generate passive income and it can be very effective. This article teaches you how to earn passive income cloud mining with HappyMiner. In order to expand your hashing power or rent more resources, you can<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/earn-passive-income-cloud-mining-with-happyminer-a-quick-guide/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/earn-passive-income-cloud-mining-with-happyminer-a-quick-guide/">Earn Passive Income Cloud Mining With HappyMiner &#8211; A Quick Guide!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are you interested in making <a href="https://happyminer.us/?livebitcoinnews" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">passive income</a> for extra security? Well, <a href="https://happyminer.us/?livebitcoinnews" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">cloud mining</a> is one of the best methods to generate passive income and it can be very effective. This article teaches you how to earn passive income cloud mining with HappyMiner.</p>
<p>In order to expand your hashing power or rent more resources, you can reinvest your profits into the cloud mining service. The US based cloud mining company HappyMiner provides such cloud mining services to investors.</p>
<p>Earn passive income cloud mining with <a href="https://happyminer.us/?livebitcoinnews" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">HappyMiner</a> by creating an account by visiting the HappyMiner website &gt; Select “sign up”  &gt; Enter the verification code &gt; Choose “Submit” &gt; Your account will be deposited with $10 to earn passive income cloud mining with HappyMiner.</p>
<p>One of the most profitable sources of passive income is the cloud mining of cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin, Dogecoin, Ethereum, and others. Read on to understand how to earn passive income cloud mining with HappyMiner.</p>
<h4>Earn Passive Income Cloud Mining With HappyMiner</h4>
<p>The act of mining cryptocurrencies using a remote datacenter’s shared computing power is known as “cloud mining.” Bitcoin miners known as HappyMiner are well known for their free Bitcoin mining services and it uses the latest mining technologies to increase profitability. You can sign up today and receive $10 instantly. In addition, HappyMiner offers an affiliate program via which customers may receive a up to 4.5% incentive for suggesting HappyMiner to their partners.</p>
<h4>Is HappyMiner Scam or Trustworthy?</h4>
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td width="277"><strong>HappyMiner</strong></td>
<td width="277"><strong>Scam Websites</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="277">Works under the license of the United States</td>
<td width="277">Do not have any licenses</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="277">A certified cloud mining company</td>
<td width="277">Do not have certificates (or have fake ones)</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="277">Your personal and financial information is protected by SSL on HappyMiner</td>
<td width="277">Scam websites do not guard but rather steal your information</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="277">Provides guaranteed 24-hour payouts</td>
<td width="277">Regular payouts are not guaranteed</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="277">To ensure the security of the cloud mining process, users must use real emails to register.</td>
<td width="277">Scam platforms do not care if you use a real or fake email.</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p>As we can see, the question is whether the HappyMiner scam or legit cloud mining platform makes no sense. With trusted companies, your funds are always safe. And in distinct to HappyMiner, scam websites are the real danger for you and your money.</p>
<h4>Cloud Mining Packages</h4>
<p>The $10, $100, $1200, and $6400 packages are some of the packages that <a href="https://happyminer.us/?livebitcoinnews" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">HappyMiner</a> provides. Each package offers a different ROI and contract length. Payouts are received daily and profits are fixed. Happy Miner gives you the option to either withdraw the funds or continue investing after the contract’s designated time period.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td width="138"><strong>Contract Price</strong></td>
<td width="138"><strong>Contract Terms</strong></td>
<td width="138"><strong>Fixed Return</strong></td>
<td width="138"><strong>Daily Rate</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="138">$10</td>
<td width="138">1 Day</td>
<td width="138">$10+$0.8</td>
<td width="138">8%</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="138">$100</td>
<td width="138">3 Days</td>
<td width="138">$100+$4.5</td>
<td width="138">1.5%</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="138">$500</td>
<td width="138">7 Days</td>
<td width="138">$500+$63</td>
<td width="138">1.8%</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="138">$1,200</td>
<td width="138">15 Days</td>
<td width="138">$1,200+$345</td>
<td width="138">1.92%</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="138">$3,000</td>
<td width="138">30 Days</td>
<td width="138">$3,000+$1,890</td>
<td width="138">2.1%</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="138">$6,400</td>
<td width="138">60 Days</td>
<td width="138">$6,400+$8,880</td>
<td width="138">2.31%</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<h4>How To Withdraw Money From HappyMiner?</h4>
<p>Log into your account &gt; Tap “Withdraws” &gt; Choose your wallet &gt; Enter the amount you wish to withdraw &gt; The money will be transferred to the wallet address</p>
<p>Step 1: Log into your account.</p>
<p>Step 2: Tap “Withdraws”.</p>
<p>Step 3: If this is your first withdrawal, pick your wallet.</p>
<p>Step 4: Enter the amount you wish to withdraw and $100 is the minimum withdrawal amount.</p>
<p>Step 5: The money will be transferred to the wallet address you already specified.</p>
<p>Step 6: It can take a few minutes for the transaction to be successfully completed.</p>
<h4>Wrapping Up</h4>
<p>HappyMiner is a reliable source for performing cloud mining services. What are you waiting for? Start creating an account and earn passive income cloud mining with HappyMiner. Visit its website at <a href="https://happyminer.us/?livebitcoinnews" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://happyminer.us/</a></p>
<p><strong>Social media links</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/happyminerUS" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener"><strong>Twitter</strong></a><strong>    </strong><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@happyminerUS" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener"><strong>Youtube</strong></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/earn-passive-income-cloud-mining-with-happyminer-a-quick-guide/">Earn Passive Income Cloud Mining With HappyMiner &#8211; A Quick Guide!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/earn-passive-income-cloud-mining-with-happyminer-a-quick-guide/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dana Nessel Discusses How You Can Avoid Crypto Scams</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dana-nessel-discusses-how-you-can-avoid-crypto-scams/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dana-nessel-discusses-how-you-can-avoid-crypto-scams/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 17:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto scams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dana Nessel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michigan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77692</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Michigan has become a state where crypto fraud runs rampant, and the region’s attorney general Dana Nessel is warning citizens about what they can do to ensure they never fall victim to digital currency scammers or fraud. Dana Nessel on How to Avoid Crypto Fraud In a statement, Nessel said older adults are often targeted<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dana-nessel-discusses-how-you-can-avoid-crypto-scams/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dana-nessel-discusses-how-you-can-avoid-crypto-scams/">Dana Nessel Discusses How You Can Avoid Crypto Scams</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Michigan has become a state where crypto <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/ag-nessel-and-michigan-state-police-issue-warning-on-the-dangers-of-cryptocurrency-and-bitcoin-scams/ar-AA19etOm" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">fraud runs rampant</a>, and the region’s attorney general Dana Nessel is warning citizens about what they can do to ensure they never fall victim to digital currency <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/scams/" data-wpel-link="internal">scammers</a> or fraud.</p>
<h2>Dana Nessel on How to Avoid Crypto Fraud</h2>
<p>In a statement, Nessel said older adults are often targeted by bad actors as they assume they’ll be unfamiliar with new technology waves or how applications work. Thus, they feel they’re the most vulnerable and can be convinced that a scam is, in fact, legitimate. Nessel said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Cryptocurrency is a new, complex market that causes confusion among even seasoned investors, and bad actors are exploiting this arena to victimize people of all ages.</p></blockquote>
<p>In a press release, Nessel as well as the Michigan State Police said nobody should withdraw cash at branches they often use or go to. This is the easiest way to get caught in something you’ll wind up regretting later. Also, never lie to branch tellers or other bank employees about why you’re withdrawing money. Sometimes, telling them the truth is all that’s needed to get authorities in play and ensure scammers are taken down.</p>
<p>Also, if anyone receives a phone call that offers instructions on how to get money out of an ATM, that call should be ignored. If a person does wind up answering the call, never leave it open or let the cell phone lie around. Nessel said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Residents should be wary of unsolicited requests from strangers on the phone or internet and especially requests to make bank withdrawals or deposits at cryptocurrency kiosks or bitcoin ATMs.</p></blockquote>
<p>In conclusion, legitimate crypto investment opportunities will never come from people you know, nor will they be delivered via social media pages. Thus, if you’re told to send someone money through Facebook or a similar platform, these words shouldn’t be adhered to. Also, be sure to inform authorities right away if you receive such communication.</p>
<p>Detective First Lt. James Ellis – commander of the MSP Cyber Section – said Michigan is becoming a hotbed of crypto crime, and that the wave is increasing across the country. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Online exchanges are being exploited more frequently with the account holders’ crypto being stolen, like a bank robber stealing funds from your bank&#8217;s safe, but much easier. Bad actors are also calling and emailing victims directly, duping them out of their crypto and cash with get rich schemes, romance scams, or by creating false emergencies that must be dealt with immediately, playing on the victim&#8217;s emotions.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Never Trust Someone You Don&#8217;t Know</h2>
<p>He concluded by saying you should never let someone you don’t know access your computer or accounts. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Never allow anyone you don&#8217;t know remote access to your computer or accounts when they offer assistance to help.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dana-nessel-discusses-how-you-can-avoid-crypto-scams/">Dana Nessel Discusses How You Can Avoid Crypto Scams</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dana-nessel-discusses-how-you-can-avoid-crypto-scams/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Could Ripple End Up Being Labeled a Commodity?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/could-ripple-end-up-being-labeled-a-commodity/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/could-ripple-end-up-being-labeled-a-commodity/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 15:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CFTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77689</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, it was announced that the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) had filed a lawsuit against Binance, the biggest and most popular digital currency trading platform in the world. There are many Ripple fans out there who are concerned that the suit could have drastic effects on XRP, the platform’s native token, and<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/could-ripple-end-up-being-labeled-a-commodity/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/could-ripple-end-up-being-labeled-a-commodity/">Could Ripple End Up Being Labeled a Commodity?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, it was announced that the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) had filed a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cftc-sues-binance-alleging-financial-violations/" data-wpel-link="internal">lawsuit against Binance</a>, the biggest and most popular digital currency trading platform in the world. There are many Ripple fans out there who are concerned that the suit <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/03/28/new-fears-ripples-xrp-braces-after-bitcoin-and-ethereum-binance-shock-triggers-crypto-price-chaos/?sh=3853bc5a380f" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">could have drastic</a> effects on XRP, the platform’s native token, and that the asset could experience volatility like never before.</p>
<h2>How Will Ripple Be Classified?</h2>
<p>Ripple has added about 40 percent to its price since the beginning of the year, suggesting that while it has certainly enjoyed the effects of the bull run, it hasn’t witnessed its price or value expand as much as bitcoin or Ethereum have. However, there are many analysts out there that are continuing to argue in favor of it, and they believe the currency has what it takes to completely revamp the digital currency arena in ways nobody thought possible.</p>
<p>Genevieve Roch-Decter, the chief executive of capital market advisory company Grit Capital, explained in a recently emailed statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>Despite new fears arising from the CFTC filing against Binance that XRP tokens could be considered commodities, XRP has surged over the last 24 hours in stark contrast to broader crypto markets.</p></blockquote>
<p>One of the reasons the present CFTC lawsuit against Binance is bringing so much attention to Ripple has to do with the latter’s present case with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Not long ago, the SEC <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-is-looking-to-file-legal-action-against-ripple/" data-wpel-link="internal">filed a lawsuit against</a> Ripple, claiming it violated numerous securities laws. Ripple has vowed to fight the lawsuit and at the time of writing, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-secs-case-against-ripple-could-result-in-a-massive-win-for-the-crypto-company/" data-wpel-link="internal">appears to be on the verge</a> of winning its case after gaining steam in a U.S. courtroom.</p>
<p>Many executives of Ripple – including chief technology officer David Schwartz – believe Ripple is more of a commodity, and thus shouldn’t fall under the jurisdiction of the SEC. This is why he and his team have agreed to fight the suit with all their might. On Twitter, Schwartz stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>XRP is a raw good that trades in commerce, and one XRP is treated as equivalent to every other XRP. That&#8217;s pretty much the definition of a commodity. No part of XRP&#8217;s value comes from anyone else&#8217;s legal obligations to XRP holders.</p></blockquote>
<h2>So Many Poorly Classified Tokens Out There</h2>
<p>The lawsuit between both the CFTC and Binance alleges that several digital assets in circulation right now – including bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin, and Binance’s USD token – are all commodities, and thus should be regulated by the agency. Schwartz is clearly of the opinion that Ripple also falls into this category, and thus the SEC needs to butt out and mind its own business.</p>
<p>The SEC has been in the process of bullying several digital currency companies as of late including Coinbase, which recently <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">received a Wells notice</a> from the agency.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/could-ripple-end-up-being-labeled-a-commodity/">Could Ripple End Up Being Labeled a Commodity?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/could-ripple-end-up-being-labeled-a-commodity/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rajeev Chandrasekhar: Crypto Is Quite Risky</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/rajeev-chandrasekhar-crypto-presents-quite-a-bit-of-risk/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/rajeev-chandrasekhar-crypto-presents-quite-a-bit-of-risk/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 13:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rajeev Chandrasekhar]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77685</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Rajeev Chandrasekhar – the minister of state for IT and electronics – said crypto could present a “legitimate case of macroeconomic risks,” in a recent report. He also said that a world without crypto regulation is a dangerous one. Rajeev Chandrasekhar on Crypto in India Chandrasekhar commented: It is a very legit case that crypto<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/rajeev-chandrasekhar-crypto-presents-quite-a-bit-of-risk/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/rajeev-chandrasekhar-crypto-presents-quite-a-bit-of-risk/">Rajeev Chandrasekhar: Crypto Is Quite Risky</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Rajeev Chandrasekhar – the minister of state for IT and electronics – <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/cryptocurrency-presents-a-legitimate-case-of-macroeconomic-risk-says-rajeev-chandrasekhar/ar-AA19cMAK" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said crypto could present</a> a “legitimate case of macroeconomic risks,” in a recent report. He also said that a world without crypto regulation is a dangerous one.</p>
<h2>Rajeev Chandrasekhar on Crypto in India</h2>
<p>Chandrasekhar commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>It is a very legit case that crypto represents macroeconomic risks. It represents many other types of risks. FTX and other cases reaffirm that crypto is not business as usual and crypto is not innovation. In India, crypto is not illegal if you buy them through legitimate channels of LRS (liberalized remittances scheme) which are RBI-approved dispensation on foreign exchange. It is your choice to lose money or make money, and the government does not get in the business of where you invest in and what you invest in, but we certainly have the obligation to explain to the Indian citizens that you can&#8217;t exchange rupee for crypto.</p></blockquote>
<p>He further stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>RBI is very clear on this and we should respect their views on how they chart out the crypto course and crypto roadmap. They have said CBDC (central bank digital currency) is the route, and I have no problem with that. It is the best way to do that without creating any downside risk to the economy.</p></blockquote>
<p>Chandrasekhar also said that he’s not concerned about the lack of funding going to tech startups and crypto companies as of late. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Peaks and troughs and ups and downs and business cycles are very inherent in startups. We are seeing a cycle that would&#8217;ve played anyway… Also, people are getting smart about where value lies and where IP is. Certainly, COVID and over stimulus in [the] U.S. and European economies and [the] Russia-Ukraine war have caused some significant headwinds in risk aversion… People are a lot more careful and prudent, which is causing valuation corrections.</p></blockquote>
<p>His thoughts towards regulation are concerning in many ways given how many people working in a regulatory capacity today are not fit to be doing so. Look at the U.S., for example, where virtually everyone in the federal government that’s now voicing support for crypto regulation accepted bribes and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-gave-a-lot-of-money-to-democrats-what-will-they-do-with-it/" data-wpel-link="internal">campaign donation funds</a> from Sam Bankman-Fried, the man behind FTX.</p>
<h2>The Mystery Behind FTX</h2>
<p>It does not seem possible that these individuals could <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-did-the-ftx-fall-expose-a-government-conspiracy/" data-wpel-link="internal">have had such close</a> ties to a criminal and not seen the kind of shady practices occurring behind the closed doors of his exchange. The idea could be that FTX was a setup of sorts. That the exchange would collapse after everyone had their chance to benefit from it and then they could swoop in and make their mark by taking away everyone’s financial freedom.</p>
<p>Chandrasekhar concluded by hinting India is a prime country to have its hand in all new technological ventures.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/rajeev-chandrasekhar-crypto-presents-quite-a-bit-of-risk/">Rajeev Chandrasekhar: Crypto Is Quite Risky</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/rajeev-chandrasekhar-crypto-presents-quite-a-bit-of-risk/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Michael Saylor, the Eternal BTC Bull, Just Bought More Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-the-eternal-btc-bull-just-bought-more-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-the-eternal-btc-bull-just-bought-more-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 17:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Saylor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroStrategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Silvergate]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77675</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Saylor – the man behind software giant MicroStrategy and a major crypto bull – has paid off a $200 million+ loan obtained from the now failed crypto bank Silvergate and has purchased even more bitcoin units, thus bringing the company’s total BTC holdings to nearly $4 billion. Michael Saylor Won&#8217;t Give Up on BTC<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-the-eternal-btc-bull-just-bought-more-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-the-eternal-btc-bull-just-bought-more-crypto/">Michael Saylor, the Eternal BTC Bull, Just Bought More Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Michael Saylor – the man behind software giant MicroStrategy and a major crypto bull – has paid off a $200 million+ loan <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/michael-saylors-microstrategy-snaps-another-164250827.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">obtained from the now failed</a> crypto bank Silvergate and has purchased even more bitcoin units, thus bringing the company’s total BTC holdings to nearly $4 billion.</p>
<h2>Michael Saylor Won&#8217;t Give Up on BTC</h2>
<p>On the one hand, this is a positive story. Saylor and MicroStrategy were literally billions of dollars in debt in 2022 thanks to the ongoing bear run. The price of bitcoin was hit extremely hard and wound up losing more than 70 percent of its value over the course of 12 short months, falling from its new all-time high of $68,000 per unit (achieved in November of 2021) and dipping into the mid-$16K range by the end of 2022. It was a sad and ugly sight to see.</p>
<p>Institutional players like MicroStrategy <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/microstrategy-dealt-heavy-blow-following-crypto-crash/" data-wpel-link="internal">suffered greatly</a>. The bitcoin-related decisions made by Saylor led to his <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-btc-bull-and-microstrategy-chief-executive-steps-down/" data-wpel-link="internal">official step down from</a> the CEO position he had held with the company for over 30 years, and he switched over to the role of executive chairman. The fact that the company has managed to pull itself out of the doldrums and ultimately pay off one of its biggest loans is a good sign that things are perhaps picking up not just for the enterprise, but for the digital currency space.</p>
<p>However, as we’ve seen by now, Saylor’s love of BTC <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/it-appears-michael-saylor-will-never-reject-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">has gone a little overboard</a> at times, and he arguably rushes into things without really thinking about them as much as he should. Right now, BTC and its altcoin cousins are enduring a bit of a bull run, a solid change from 2022. It’s nice to sit back and watch, though it would be incorrect to assume that we’re fully out of the darkness and there isn’t more space to improve and heal.</p>
<p>The fact remains that BTC is nowhere near where it was a year and a half ago, and the idea that Saylor would simply jump all the way back into the bitcoin bin without allowing more time to go by is a bit concerning. It suggests that he hasn’t really learned his lesson from the past yet, and thus MicroStrategy could be in for more pain before it’s able to fully remove the bandages from its former wounds.</p>
<p>In late March, Saylor issued the following statement on Twitter:</p>
<blockquote><p>MicroStrategy repaid its $205M Silvergate loan at a 22 percent discount.</p></blockquote>
<h2>So Many Banks Are Collapsing</h2>
<p>Silvergate was one of several banks to crumble and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-crashed-following-news-of-silvergate-shutdown/" data-wpel-link="internal">collapse in recent weeks</a>, with others being Silicon Valley and Signature.</p>
<p>The financial catastrophe has also spread to Europe, with institutions <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-more-banks-fell-bitcoin-rose-beyond-28k/" data-wpel-link="internal">such as Credit Suisse</a> being on the verge of crashing and burning before it was saved by a $3 billion-bearing UBS.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-the-eternal-btc-bull-just-bought-more-crypto/">Michael Saylor, the Eternal BTC Bull, Just Bought More Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-the-eternal-btc-bull-just-bought-more-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Can Bitcoin Assist in the Tokenization of Additional Assets?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/can-bitcoin-assist-in-the-tokenization-of-additional-assets/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/can-bitcoin-assist-in-the-tokenization-of-additional-assets/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 15:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Morgan McKenney]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tokenization]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77672</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Assets like bitcoin and Ethereum have soared in recent weeks, and the sudden bull run is causing many big financial players – such as Fidelity and BlackRock – to increase their stakes in the crypto space and try to do more with digital tokens. Bitcoin Could Give Rise to Further Tokenization The bull run has<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/can-bitcoin-assist-in-the-tokenization-of-additional-assets/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/can-bitcoin-assist-in-the-tokenization-of-additional-assets/">Can Bitcoin Assist in the Tokenization of Additional Assets?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Assets like bitcoin and Ethereum have soared in recent weeks, and the <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/03/27/looming-300-trillion-crypto-earthquake-revealed-amid-huge-bitcoin-and-ethereum-price-pump/?sh=7f1da0144277" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">sudden bull run is causing</a> many big financial players – such as <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fidelity-and-black-rock-keep-expanding-their-crypto-influence/" data-wpel-link="internal">Fidelity and BlackRock</a> – to increase their stakes in the crypto space and try to do more with digital tokens.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Could Give Rise to Further Tokenization</h2>
<p>The bull run has gotten so many people excited that according to a new report issued by crypto infrastructure provider Taurus, roughly $300 trillion in private assets could be digitized in the coming future. The report reads:</p>
<blockquote><p>Tokenization could open worlds not imagined yet to private assets in a similar way to how the internet and e-commerce transformed many industries over the last two decades.</p></blockquote>
<p>2023 is, thus far, turning out to be the complete opposite of 2022. While there’s still a long way to go and an even higher degree of healing to be had before assets like bitcoin are once again at their November 2021 highs, the space appears to be turning itself around from the horrible bearish conditions it faced during the previous 12 months.</p>
<p>2022 was arguably the worst year on record for crypto. During that time, assets like bitcoin lost more than 70 percent of their value, and they crashed and burned like nobody’s business. This led to the entire space losing more than $2 trillion in overall valuation. For many, the situation was particularly dire as they had likely put more than they could afford into the space, hoping to get rich over time.</p>
<p>Now, however, the prices of assets like bitcoin appear to be turning themselves around. The currency recently reached a nine-month high of about $28,000 per unit, and while the asset has again been rocked <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cftc-sues-binance-alleging-financial-violations/" data-wpel-link="internal">due to recent</a> (and negative) news surrounding Binance, it’s unlikely the asset will stay down for the count for long.</p>
<p>In the report’s early sections, Jacques Iffland – partner at Lenz &amp; Staehelin and chair of the Capital Markets and Technology Association (CMTA) – explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>Tokenization opens the door to a broad universe of new possibilities, which the financial industry is only starting to comprehend and embrace.</p></blockquote>
<p>Morgan McKenney – chief executive of the Provenance Blockchain Foundation – also threw his two cents into the mix, commenting:</p>
<blockquote><p>Private funds are very restricted in terms of liquidity options, and by natively issuing shares on-chain, they can then open up marketplaces to give investors the opportunity to exit.</p></blockquote>
<h2>This Will Help Crypto Reach Its Ultimate Goal</h2>
<p>Furthermore, the tokenization of various assets could ultimately make them more accessible to the public and thus bring the initial dreams and goals of crypto closer to becoming realities.</p>
<p>The driving force behind crypto was that everyone should have a chance to invest and garner financial services and tools that will allow them to live applicable lives, something that standard financial institutions can often restrict.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/can-bitcoin-assist-in-the-tokenization-of-additional-assets/">Can Bitcoin Assist in the Tokenization of Additional Assets?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/can-bitcoin-assist-in-the-tokenization-of-additional-assets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
