<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 11:36:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Saudi Arabia and South Korea Join Hands to Establish More Blockchain Gaming</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/saudi-arabia-and-south-korea-team-up-to-establish-more-blockchain-gaming/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/saudi-arabia-and-south-korea-team-up-to-establish-more-blockchain-gaming/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 17:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain gaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wemade]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78069</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>South Korea and Saudi Arabia are teaming up in the name of blockchain. The southern region of the latter country has joined hands with Wemade – a video game developer in Korea – to help boost both blockchain and gaming in Saudi Arabia. Saudi Arabia Wants to Lead Blockchain Gaming Initiatives In a recent statement,<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/saudi-arabia-and-south-korea-team-up-to-establish-more-blockchain-gaming/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/saudi-arabia-and-south-korea-team-up-to-establish-more-blockchain-gaming/">Saudi Arabia and South Korea Join Hands to Establish More Blockchain Gaming</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>South Korea and Saudi Arabia are teaming up in <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-ae/news/world/saudi-arabia-teams-up-with-south-korea-s-wemade-to-power-gaming-and-blockchain-sectors/ar-AA1aiEdQ" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">the name of blockchain</a>. The southern region of the latter country has joined hands with Wemade – a video game developer in Korea – to help boost both blockchain and gaming in Saudi Arabia.</p>
<h2>Saudi Arabia Wants to Lead Blockchain Gaming Initiatives</h2>
<p>In a recent statement, a representative from the Ministry of Investment in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/saudi-arabia/" data-wpel-link="internal">Saudi Arabia</a> said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We are very excited for Wemade’s progress in expanding its activities in Saudi Arabia and are looking forward to continuing supporting Wemade’s footprint through connecting it to strategic partners in the sector. This progress would be yet another step further into realizing the national objective of becoming a hub for gaming and e-sports in line with the national gaming and e-sports strategy.</p></blockquote>
<p>The goal is to ensure Saudi Arabia remains a global hub for both expansion initiatives and investments. One way to do this is to garner business opportunities through foreign nations. South Korea has long been a leader in both the crypto and blockchain arenas, and representatives are confident individuals working with Wemade will bring the knowledge and expertise the nation&#8217;s leaders are looking for to the table.</p>
<p>Wemade has been at the center of several partnerships over the past few months. Back in February, for example, the company teamed up with Savvy Games’ Nine66, which was supported through a public investment fund. The goal is to ensure training and educational content are available to future generations of blockchain gamers and that regional events get the sponsorship opportunities and funds they seemingly deserve.</p>
<p>Charles Huh – global investment officer at Wemade – explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>As the demand for games and blockchain technologies continues to grow in Saudi Arabia, we are committed to showcasing our capabilities and delivering innovative solutions that meet their needs. We believe that our partnership with [the Saudi ministry] will not only benefit both parties, but also create new opportunities in the global game industry.</p></blockquote>
<p>Wemade was founded in the year 2000 and has brought many prominent gaming titles to market including the “Legend of Mir” series, which is presently enjoyed by more than 1,000 individual gamers across the globe. Another prominent product established by the firm is Wemix.</p>
<h2>Expansion Over the Next Seven Years</h2>
<p>The gaming world in Saudi Arabia is expanding like nobody’s business. The region is the leader of the Arabian economy, and it’s estimated that the gaming sector of the nation will grow by as much as 250 percent through the year 2030. These results stem from a recent YouGov poll, which also believes that e-sports will lead to this expansion.</p>
<p>Said growth would also mean that the GDP of Saudi Arabia will likely surge by at least 50 times over the next seven years, and by that year, gaming consumption could be just under $7 billion.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/saudi-arabia-and-south-korea-team-up-to-establish-more-blockchain-gaming/">Saudi Arabia and South Korea Join Hands to Establish More Blockchain Gaming</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/saudi-arabia-and-south-korea-team-up-to-establish-more-blockchain-gaming/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Companies Are Using Blockchain to Try and Make the World Safer</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/companies-are-using-blockchain-to-try-and-make-the-world-safer/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/companies-are-using-blockchain-to-try-and-make-the-world-safer/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 15:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fision]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Holke Brammer]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78067</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain was always designed to make the world a better, stronger place, and there are many entrepreneurs and companies out there working towards that goal. How Blockchain Is Keeping the Planet Well One of those people is Holke Brammer, who has a PhD in political economy from Stanford. In a recent interview, he commented on<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/companies-are-using-blockchain-to-try-and-make-the-world-safer/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/companies-are-using-blockchain-to-try-and-make-the-world-safer/">Companies Are Using Blockchain to Try and Make the World Safer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain was always designed to make the world a better, stronger place, and there are many entrepreneurs and <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/04/25/greenpilled-meet-5-entrepreneurs-engineering-social-good-on-the-blockchain/?sh=2a8aecb6468f" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">companies out there working</a> towards that goal.</p>
<h2>How Blockchain Is Keeping the Planet Well</h2>
<p>One of those people is Holke Brammer, who has a PhD in political economy from Stanford. In a recent interview, he commented on the work that ultimately got him involved (and interested) in both blockchain and blockchain applications:</p>
<blockquote><p>I studied how we get good long-term policies in democracies, which is obviously non-trivial… I worked on large scale innovation processes in Germany between civil society and the German state, organizing the largest hackathon around COVID. It was the largest hackathon so far with 28,000 people. We basically took the challenges from COVID, from track and tracing COVID, to how do small businesses apply for state subsidies, to how do we deal with domestic violence.</p></blockquote>
<p>Brammer is all about open innovation, in which ideas are placed together as a means of establishing things like decentralization for both individuals and institutions. He is now working with Protocol Labs, a prominent blockchain startup, and is leading a newly launched vehicle called Hypercerts Foundation.</p>
<p>The goal of the organization is to provide special rewards and incentives to those who are trying to utilize blockchain’s prowess to better the planet and make it safe for future generations. In a recent blog post for the company, Brammer wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>Imagine a world where positive impact was one of the most highly valued creations in our society.</p></blockquote>
<p>In terms of blockchain being used for social good, it appears the concept is really building steam as of late according to people like Simona Pop. As the co-founder of Ethereum bounties, Pop was quick to mention that there are now major players in the mix such as UNICEF, who recently tried to introduce a new digital token in 2019.</p>
<p>As a Romanian who escaped her country’s revolution, Pop studies DAOs and governance, and seeks to find new ways to bring people together so that they can share ideas and missions for protecting Mother Earth. She explained in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>At the core of it, it is about redesigning the whole model. Re-engineering the whole flow of resources, but as I always say, it is tough building a new boat when you are firmly standing in the current one with its focus on extraction.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Ensuring Traceability for Products</h2>
<p>One of the big things that blockchain is being used for now – aside from verifying digital currency transactions – is ensuring the trustworthiness of specific items or goods. For example, a company called The Fision is now using <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-fision-uses-blockchain-to-ensure-the-trustfulness-of-its-clothing-line/" data-wpel-link="internal">blockchain to measure</a> the journeys its cotton T-shirts take from creation to winding up in the hands of buyers.</p>
<p>Blockchain ensures all the materials are sustainable and traceable.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/companies-are-using-blockchain-to-try-and-make-the-world-safer/">Companies Are Using Blockchain to Try and Make the World Safer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/companies-are-using-blockchain-to-try-and-make-the-world-safer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Daniel Shin, Co-Founder of Terra USD, Charged in South Korea</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/daniel-shin-co-founder-of-terra-usd-charged-in-south-korea/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/daniel-shin-co-founder-of-terra-usd-charged-in-south-korea/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 13:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Daniel Shin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Do Kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra USD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78065</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Prosecutors in South Korea have filed charges against Daniel Shin, the co-founder of Terraform Labs (the firm behind Terra USD) alongside Do Kwon, who was recently arrested while traveling through Europe. Daniel Shin Is Facing Charges in South Korea Shin is the man – aside from Kwon – who reportedly brought Terra USD to life.<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/daniel-shin-co-founder-of-terra-usd-charged-in-south-korea/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/daniel-shin-co-founder-of-terra-usd-charged-in-south-korea/">Daniel Shin, Co-Founder of Terra USD, Charged in South Korea</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Prosecutors in South Korea have <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/south-korea-indicts-co-founder-of-failed-terrausd-cryptocurrency/ar-AA1ak8qz" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">filed charges against</a> Daniel Shin, the co-founder of Terraform Labs (the firm behind Terra USD) alongside Do Kwon, who was recently arrested <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-executive-do-kwon-arrested-in-montenegro/" data-wpel-link="internal">while traveling through</a> Europe.</p>
<h2>Daniel Shin Is Facing Charges in South Korea</h2>
<p>Shin is the man – aside from Kwon – who reportedly brought Terra USD to life. The currency and the respective company behind it came crashing down in the summer of last year in what was believed to be the first major casualty (at that time) of the crypto winter that oversaw most of 2022, but there is evidence to suggest something more sinister occurred.</p>
<p>Terra USD was considered an algorithmic stable coin, meaning it didn’t have any collateral (i.e., gold, fiat currencies, etc.) supporting it. The only thing ensuring its “stable” condition was the fact that traders seemed to believe in it.</p>
<p>Either this belief vanished very fast or something shady happened because in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-luna-token-has-experienced-a-dramatic-drop/" data-wpel-link="internal">the summer of 2022</a>, the currency broke down like an old car and roughly $40 billion in investor funds vanished without a trace. Everyone lost their wealth in a matter of seconds, and the currency was no more.</p>
<p>At first, it seemed like the crypto winter was getting worse, but then news came about that Kwon and many of the executives working on Terra USD <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-case-against-crypto-exec-do-kwon-just-got-a-lot-hairier/" data-wpel-link="internal">transferred much of their funds</a> into BTC just weeks before the crash was recorded.</p>
<p>Many authorities felt that the company men knew the enterprise was about to come crashing down or that this was a rug pull of some sort. In any case, they took it like investors were going to get slapped in the face while those in charge would not experience any repercussions.</p>
<p>Kwon instantly became a fugitive when authorities decided to issue a warrant for his arrest, though according to his social pages, this never occurred, and his fugitive status was something concocted by the mainstream media. He said he <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-exec-do-kwon-says-hes-willing-to-cooperate-following-arrest-warrant/" data-wpel-link="internal">was busy coding in</a> his living room and that he was more than willing to cooperate with the police.</p>
<p>He was arrested just a few months ago while trying to board a plan in Montenegro, a small European country. He was caught with various phony IDs, which makes one wonder if perhaps the fugitive status is, indeed, real.</p>
<h2>Wasn&#8217;t Involved?</h2>
<p>Now, it looks like Shin is next. Heck, they both shared offices together. Perhaps now they can share an eight-by-nine cell. As many as ten separate individuals have been charged for their alleged roles in the collapse of the Terra USD platform. They – along with Shin – are facing fraud charges and have been accused of violating capital-markets laws and regulations surrounding electronic transactions and fundraising.</p>
<p>Lawyers for Shin say he left Terra in 2020, and thus wasn’t part of the crash.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/daniel-shin-co-founder-of-terra-usd-charged-in-south-korea/">Daniel Shin, Co-Founder of Terra USD, Charged in South Korea</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/daniel-shin-co-founder-of-terra-usd-charged-in-south-korea/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ordinal ApeCoin (oAPE) Offers Easy Access To The Bitcoin Ordinals Market</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ordinal-apecoin-oape-offers-easy-access-to-the-bitcoin-ordinals-market/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ordinal-apecoin-oape-offers-easy-access-to-the-bitcoin-ordinals-market/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 11:36:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78664</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ordinal ApeCoin (oAPE) announces its innovative approach to access the booking Bitcoin Ordinals market through a widely available Ethereum token, oAPE. By combining the representation of the Bitcoin Apes ordinals collection with decentralized autonomous organization (DAO) principles, oAPE revolutionizes the way stakeholders engage with the ecosystem. Ordinal ApeCoin’s native token, oAPE, serves as the fuel for<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ordinal-apecoin-oape-offers-easy-access-to-the-bitcoin-ordinals-market/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ordinal-apecoin-oape-offers-easy-access-to-the-bitcoin-ordinals-market/">Ordinal ApeCoin (oAPE) Offers Easy Access To The Bitcoin Ordinals Market</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ordinal ApeCoin (oAPE)<strong> announces its innovative approach to access the booking Bitcoin Ordinals market through a widely available Ethereum token, oAPE</strong>. By combining the representation of the Bitcoin Apes ordinals collection with decentralized autonomous organization (DAO) principles, oAPE revolutionizes the way stakeholders engage with the ecosystem.</p>
<p>Ordinal ApeCoin’s native token, oAPE, serves as the fuel for the Ordinal ApeCoin ecosystem, offering holders the unique opportunity to become part of a dynamic community-driven project. <strong>Each oAPE token represents a share of the Bitcoin Apes ordinals collection, byte-perfect inscriptions of the most renowned NFT collection on the Ethereum blockchain, Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC)</strong>.</p>
<p><em>&#8220;Each oAPE token represents a share of the Bitcoin Apes ordinals collection, byte-perfect inscriptions of the most renowned NFT collection on the Ethereum blockchain, Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC)&#8221;</em></p>
<p>The core strength of oAPE lies in its DAO structure and robust fund of Ordinals held by the foundation in a secure vault. <strong>The oApeCoin DAO gives token holders the power to influence key decisions concerning governance rules</strong>, project allocations, partnerships, and other relevant matters. This decentralized governance approach ensures that the community’s voice is heard and considered, fostering an inclusive environment for all stakeholders.</p>
<p>Ordinal ApeCoin represents the next generation of community-driven projects, <strong>combining the appeal of the popular Bitcoin Ordinals with decentralized governance</strong>. By aligning the interests of the community with the project’s development, oAPE paves the way for a truly collaborative ecosystem.</p>
<p>For more information about Ordinal ApeCoin and to join the oApeCoin DAO, please visit</p>
<p><a href="https://www.oapecoin.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.oapecoin.com</a> or follow Ordinal ApeCoin on Twitter at <a href="https://twitter.com/oapecoin" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/oapecoin</a></p>
<p><strong>About Ordinal ApeCoin (oAPE)</strong></p>
<p>Ordinal ApeCoin (oAPE) is an ERC-20 token built on the Ethereum blockchain, providing fractional ownership in the Bitcoin Apes ordinals collection. With a strong focus on community-driven governance, oAPE enables token holders to actively participate in shaping the future of the ecosystem, establishing a new era of collaborative projects.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ordinal-apecoin-oape-offers-easy-access-to-the-bitcoin-ordinals-market/">Ordinal ApeCoin (oAPE) Offers Easy Access To The Bitcoin Ordinals Market</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ordinal-apecoin-oape-offers-easy-access-to-the-bitcoin-ordinals-market/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Eyes Fresh Increase Above $0.092</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-eyes-fresh-increase-above-0-092/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-eyes-fresh-increase-above-0-092/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 05:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar Lumens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78661</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stellar lumen price started a downside correction from the $0.0945 zone against the US Dollar. XLM price is now trading above $0.090 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $0.0916 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-eyes-fresh-increase-above-0-092/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-eyes-fresh-increase-above-0-092/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Eyes Fresh Increase Above $0.092</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Stellar lumen price started a downside correction from the $0.0945 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>XLM price is now trading above $0.090 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $0.0916 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start another increase if it clears the $0.092 and $0.094 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Stellar lumen price is trading above $0.090 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-key-resistance-near-28-5k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. XLM’s price must stay above the $0.090 support to rise again.</em></p>
<h2>Stellar Lumen Price Analysis (XLM to USD)</h2>
<p>After forming a base above the $0.085 level, Stellar lumen price started a fresh increase against the US Dollar. The XLM/USD pair broke the $0.090 resistance zone to move into a positive zone.</p>
<p>The price even cleared the $0.0920 resistance and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-surge-if-it-clears-0-090/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. The upward move was such that the price spiked to $0.0940 before it corrected lower. There was a drop below the $0.092 support level. There is a break below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.0861 swing low to the $0.0943 high.</p>
<p>Besides, there was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $0.0916 on the 4-hour chart. However, the bulls were active near the $0.0920 level.</p>
<p>XLM is now trading above $0.090 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $0.092 zone. The next major resistance is near the $0.0945 level. A clear move above the $0.0945 level might send the price toward the $0.0965 level.</p>
<p>Any more gains could lead the price toward the $0.1000 level or even $0.1050. Initial support on the downside is near the $0.090 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.0861 swing low to the $0.0943 high.</p>
<p>The next major support sits near the $0.0880 level. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.0865 level in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_78662" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Stellar-Lumen-XLM.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78662" class="size-full wp-image-78662" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Stellar-Lumen-XLM.png" alt="Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price " width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78662" class="wp-caption-text">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XLMUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that XLM’s price is now trading above $0.090 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start another increase if it clears the $0.092 and $0.0945 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XLM/USD is losing momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for XLM/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.090 and $0.088.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.092, $0.0945, and $0.0950.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-eyes-fresh-increase-above-0-092/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Eyes Fresh Increase Above $0.092</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-eyes-fresh-increase-above-0-092/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Price Analysis: Bulls In Control Above $0.50</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-in-control-above-0-50/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-in-control-above-0-50/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 03:18:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78658</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple price is facing resistance near the $0.550 level against the US dollar. The price is now trading above $0.50 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.5280 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Kraken). The pair could<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-in-control-above-0-50/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-in-control-above-0-50/">Ripple Price Analysis: Bulls In Control Above $0.50</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ripple price is facing resistance near the $0.550 level against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $0.50 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.5280 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start another major increase above the $0.450 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ripple price is rising above $0.510 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-key-resistance-near-28-5k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. XRP price must stay above the $0.500 support to remain in a bullish zone.</em></p>
<h2>Ripple Price Analysis</h2>
<p>After a successful break above the $0.480 level, Ripple price gained bullish momentum against the US Dollar. The XRP/USD pair broke the $0.50 resistance to move into a positive zone.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above the $0.512 resistance and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-upside-break-looms-at-0-485/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. The bulls even pushed the price above the $0.5250 resistance. A high is formed near $0.5464 and the price is now consolidating gains.</p>
<p>It is now trading above $0.500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, the price is facing resistance near $0.5450. The next major resistance is near the $0.5500 level.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $0.5500 resistance zone might start a strong increase. In the stated case, the price could even surpass the $0.5650 resistance. Any more gains might send the price toward the $0.600 resistance. Initial support on the downside is near the $0.5250 level or the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.4433 swing low to the $0.5464 high.</p>
<p>There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.5280 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair. The next major support is near the $0.500 level.</p>
<p>The 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.4433 swing low to the $0.5464 high is also near the $0.495 level. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.480 level, below which the price might even test $0.4650.</p>
<div id="attachment_78659" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Ripple.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78659" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78659" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Ripple.png" alt="Ripple Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78659" class="wp-caption-text">Ripple Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Ripple price is now trading above the $0.50 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start another major increase above the $0.550 resistance.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XRP/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for XRP/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.528, $0.525, and $0.500.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.5450 and $0.5500.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-in-control-above-0-50/">Ripple Price Analysis: Bulls In Control Above $0.50</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-in-control-above-0-50/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sphere Financial Inc: Transforming the World of Finance with Ground breaking Blockchain Solutions</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sphere-financial-inc-transforming-the-world-of-finance-with-ground-breaking-blockchain-solutions/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sphere-financial-inc-transforming-the-world-of-finance-with-ground-breaking-blockchain-solutions/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 17:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78643</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sphere Financial Inc (SFI), a disruptive force in the finance industry, is revolutionizing the financial landscape with its unparalleled blockchain solutions. By empowering individuals and businesses worldwide with decentralized and all-inclusive approaches, SFI is redefining traditional finance and ushering in a new era of possibilities. Founded by visionary leaders disillusioned with exploitative banking practices, SFI<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sphere-financial-inc-transforming-the-world-of-finance-with-ground-breaking-blockchain-solutions/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sphere-financial-inc-transforming-the-world-of-finance-with-ground-breaking-blockchain-solutions/">Sphere Financial Inc: Transforming the World of Finance with Ground breaking Blockchain Solutions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sphere Financial Inc (SFI), a disruptive force in the finance industry, is revolutionizing the financial landscape with its unparalleled blockchain solutions. By empowering individuals and businesses worldwide with decentralized and all-inclusive approaches, SFI is redefining traditional finance and ushering in a new era of possibilities.</p>
<p>Founded by visionary leaders disillusioned with exploitative banking practices, SFI is on a mission to construct a financial ecosystem that transcends borders and extends opportunities to all. The company&#8217;s comprehensive suite of blockchain solutions caters to diverse industry needs, offering innovative solutions that address the pain points of traditional finance.</p>
<p>At the core of SFI&#8217;s mission is the creation of an accessible and inclusive financial ecosystem. The company drives innovation by constantly pushing boundaries, all while placing customers at the forefront of its operations. SFI&#8217;s commitment to customer-centricity, innovation, excellence, and long-term vision sets the company apart in its relentless dedication to sculpting the financial landscape.</p>
<p>SFI&#8217;s commitment to staying ahead of industry trends and embracing technological advancements is reflected in the expertise of its DeFi specialists, known as the DeBrain. This exceptional team ensures that SFI remains at the forefront of the rapidly evolving DeFi landscape, maximizing returns for clients through their cutting-edge strategies.</p>
<p>A ground breaking partnership with Satoshi AI, an industry-leading AI company, has revolutionized operational efficiency and accuracy in mining operations. By leveraging Satoshi AI&#8217;s advanced AI technologies, SFI has enhanced mining capabilities, optimizing resource allocation and improving overall profitability.</p>
<p>SFI&#8217;s ground breaking offerings extend beyond mining solutions. The company&#8217;s SpheriART platform enables creators to transform their digital creations into valuable assets through NFT minting. This innovative platform unlocks new opportunities for artists and content creators, bridging the gap between art and finance.</p>
<p>As part of its commitment to redefine the financial experience, SFI is preparing to launch Esfera, an upcoming wallet that promises convenience and security in decentralized finance. Esfera will provide users with a seamless and user-friendly interface, making decentralized finance accessible to all.</p>
<p>For more information about Sphere Financial Inc and its ground breaking blockchain solutions, please visit <a href="https://sphereinc.io/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://sphereinc.io/</a></p>
<p><strong>About Sphere Financial Inc:</strong></p>
<p>Sphere Financial Inc (SFI) is a disruptive force in the finance industry, offering unparalleled blockchain solutions that empower individuals and businesses worldwide. Through decentralized and all-inclusive approaches, SFI is redefining traditional finance, creating a financial ecosystem that transcends borders and extends opportunities to all. With a comprehensive suite of blockchain solutions, cutting-edge technology, and a commitment to customer-centricity, SFI is transforming the world of finance for a better future.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sphere-financial-inc-transforming-the-world-of-finance-with-ground-breaking-blockchain-solutions/">Sphere Financial Inc: Transforming the World of Finance with Ground breaking Blockchain Solutions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sphere-financial-inc-transforming-the-world-of-finance-with-ground-breaking-blockchain-solutions/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Four Men Indicted in North Korea Illicit Crypto Case</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/four-men-indicted-in-north-korea-illicit-crypto-case/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/four-men-indicted-in-north-korea-illicit-crypto-case/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 17:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[North Korea]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sanctions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78063</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>North Korea is back in the news when it comes to crypto. It appears the country just won’t go away and is still doing all it can to get its paws on illicit digital currencies, but countries like the United States are fighting back. North Korea Is At It Again It has been revealed that<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/four-men-indicted-in-north-korea-illicit-crypto-case/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/four-men-indicted-in-north-korea-illicit-crypto-case/">Four Men Indicted in North Korea Illicit Crypto Case</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>North Korea is back in the news when it comes to crypto. It appears the country just won’t go away and is still doing all it can to get its paws on illicit digital currencies, but countries like the United States are fighting back.</p>
<h2>North Korea Is At It Again</h2>
<p>It has been revealed <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/04/24/us/politics/justice-dept-cryptocurrency-north-korea.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">that the Justice Department</a> (DOJ) has indicted four men for allegedly stealing and laundering digital assets on behalf of an online criminal syndicate based in North Korea. The men are also accused of buying goods with USD in the past as a means of avoiding other sanctions.</p>
<p>The charges were filed in three separate cases in Washington. The coins are alleged to have been obtained by members of the Lazarus Group, which is an infamous hacking organization that has worked hard to garner illicit digital currencies in the past as the means of funding the ongoing nuclear program in North Korea.</p>
<p>The organization has targeted a wide array of digital currency enterprises in the past including <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/axie-infinity-gets-some-of-its-stolen-crypto-back/" data-wpel-link="internal">Axie Infinity</a>, and it’s believed members have stolen <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-north-korea-has-stolen-more-than-1-billion-in-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">more than $1 billion</a> in crypto.</p>
<p>The first charge saw a banker from China being indicted. He is 39-year-old Sim Hyon Sop, and he – along with three separate traders – are believed to have used international mixers and other means to convert stolen digital currencies by North Korean nationals into fiat currencies that were then used to buy illegal goods or fund ongoing nuclear missile production.</p>
<p>In the other indictments, the men who took part in the crimes were not named, though it’s been stated that these individuals used fake identities to garner blockchain jobs in the United States. From there, they utilized their access to said companies to garner more funds, which at the time of writing, are believed to exceed $12 million, all of which passed through Sim’s crypto wallet.</p>
<p>Overall, it’s believed that these individuals took part in more than 1,500 illicit trades, and that their customers – aside from North Korea – were traders and other companies seeking to engage in financial activities without the proper licenses to back themselves up.</p>
<h2>Trying to Fight Back</h2>
<p>While it may appear that North Korea is an unstoppable enemy when it comes to crypto crime, several nations in Europe and the U.S. have shown that they will not stand for illegal trickery and theft and have taken implicit actions to garner stolen funds back.</p>
<p>For example, not long ago, the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/norway-takes-back-stolen-crypto-from-north-korea/" data-wpel-link="internal">nation of Norway managed</a> to locate some of the money stolen from the Axie Infinity online crypto gaming platform that was stolen in 2022 and retrieve some of it. The U.S. has also implemented sanctions against crypto mixers like Tornado Cash to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/north-korea-crypto-mixer-tornado-cash-sanctioned-by-u-s/" data-wpel-link="internal">ensure that the means</a> North Korea uses to steal crypto remain limited.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/four-men-indicted-in-north-korea-illicit-crypto-case/">Four Men Indicted in North Korea Illicit Crypto Case</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/four-men-indicted-in-north-korea-illicit-crypto-case/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fision Uses Blockchain to Ensure the Trustfulness of Its Clothing Line</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-fision-uses-blockchain-to-ensure-the-trustfulness-of-its-clothing-line/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-fision-uses-blockchain-to-ensure-the-trustfulness-of-its-clothing-line/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 15:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cotton]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fision]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78060</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A company called The Fision is using blockchain to create new apparel. T-shirts, to be precise. The firm creates the shirts and sends them out to potential buyers. The big clincher is that they’re made only from trustfully sourced cotton, and blockchain technology is utilized to ensure that all the shirts sent out are fully<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-fision-uses-blockchain-to-ensure-the-trustfulness-of-its-clothing-line/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-fision-uses-blockchain-to-ensure-the-trustfulness-of-its-clothing-line/">The Fision Uses Blockchain to Ensure the Trustfulness of Its Clothing Line</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A company called The Fision is using <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/startup-launched-blockchain-traceable-good-100700159.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">blockchain to create new apparel</a>. T-shirts, to be precise. The firm creates the shirts and sends them out to potential buyers. The big clincher is that they’re made only from trustfully sourced cotton, and blockchain technology is utilized to ensure that all the shirts sent out are fully transparent and traceable from the beginning.</p>
<h2>The Fision Is Using Blockchain</h2>
<p>Josh Gelder – CEO of The Fision – explained in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>Our team is comprised of industry veterans and fueled by a desire to communicate the truth about the environmental and societal costs of the current industry. We see the future of fashion being transparent, and we came together to embark on making real industry change that aligns with our mission-driven values. We hope to showcase to consumers and to our peers alike what is possible utilizing tomorrow’s technologies today so that it becomes the industry norm of the future. We aim to inspire change, to share what we uncover, and to encourage all brands to do the same.</p></blockquote>
<p>The big thing about <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/blockchain/" data-wpel-link="internal">blockchain</a> is its alleged lack of need for middlemen or third parties to confirm information like transactions. This has been the primary notion behind the technology given that it’s mainly used to power the crypto industry.</p>
<p>However, blockchain can also be used to ensure the traceability of specific elements or goods. People want to make sure that they are buying from trusted sources and that the items used to make the products in question were not stolen or garnered through illicit practices.</p>
<p>For example, if you’re worried about palm oil production and you want to make sure your palm oil only comes from lawful, sustainable fields, the blockchain can help you ensure this by showing where the palm oil came from.</p>
<p>The Fision is a B-Corp, meaning that while it’s a money-making corporation, it has tied itself to a specific social cause and/or environmental issue as a means of allegedly trying to better the world. The T-shirts the company sells come from 80 percent Good Earth cotton, meaning the materials come from sustainable farming methods that promote soil health. Gelder continued his comments with:</p>
<blockquote><p>Good Earth Cotton is not only innovative, but also a climate positive leader. Good Earth Cotton’s regenerative farming method allows the soil to sequester more carbon than the entire cotton growth life cycle emits, which is a natural fit for us. We incorporate recycled cotton to encourage [circularity], to reinforce moving away from a purely extractive model and to further reduce the amount of water used in the creation of the T-shirts.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Offering Clean, Sustainable Clothing</h2>
<p>The remaining 20 percent of the cotton used from the T-shirts comes from fully recycled sources.</p>
<p>All the T-shirts are made in Los Angeles.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-fision-uses-blockchain-to-ensure-the-trustfulness-of-its-clothing-line/">The Fision Uses Blockchain to Ensure the Trustfulness of Its Clothing Line</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-fision-uses-blockchain-to-ensure-the-trustfulness-of-its-clothing-line/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=3724 metric#misses=5 metric#hit-ratio=99.9 metric#bytes=6611665 metric#prefetches=318 metric#store-reads=67 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=399 metric#store-misses=0 metric#sql-queries=14 metric#ms-total=198.61 metric#ms-cache=18.77 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2760 metric#ms-cache-ratio=9.5 -->
