<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 04:55:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Opinion: Congress Should Not Be Permitted to Engage in Crypto Trading</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-congress-should-not-be-permitted-to-engage-in-crypto-trading/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-congress-should-not-be-permitted-to-engage-in-crypto-trading/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 17:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Congress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76376</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With January having arrived, the new Congress has convened. While at the time of writing, the House of Representatives is still struggling to elect or even nominate a republican speaker, we can rest assured that things are going to go quite well for crypto in the coming months and that the country is now well<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-congress-should-not-be-permitted-to-engage-in-crypto-trading/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-congress-should-not-be-permitted-to-engage-in-crypto-trading/">Opinion: Congress Should Not Be Permitted to Engage in Crypto Trading</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With January having arrived, the new Congress has convened. While at the time of writing, the House of Representatives is still struggling to elect or even <a href="https://www.dailysignal.com/2023/01/04/round-four-still-no-speaker-house/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">nominate a republican speaker</a>, we can rest assured that things are going to go quite well for crypto in the coming months and that the country is now well on its way towards garnering a small bit of healing from all the trouble it’s been through since Biden entered the fray.</p>
<h2>Congress Needs to Stay Out of Crypto</h2>
<p>One of the big things this new Congress is expected to vote on is <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-in/money/markets/united-states-lawmakers-expected-to-prohibit-stock-and-crypto-trading-in-upcoming-congress-session/ar-AA15Uzkw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">crypto and stock trading</a> amongst lawmakers. Congress has long been talking about such a maneuver, but it’s failed to really act on it, likely because one of the main reasons that members of Congress even get <a href="https://www.rt.com/op-ed/545848-us-politicians-trading-stocks-bill/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">rich is because they are</a> privy to stock information prior to members of the public.</p>
<p>With this knowledge, they can sell or buy before anyone else and add hefty sums to their portfolios. In many ways, this is insider trading, and if any everyday citizen was to take part in such activity, they would likely be arrested and jailed. Insider trading has always been a crime, and this serves as another clear example of the hypocrisy and jaded rules that cloud Washington.</p>
<p>But this time, there is genuine hope the new Congress will do the right thing and ensure that no regulator – whether they be a senator or a member of the House – be permitted to engage in either crypto or stock trades while they sit in office. They can trade items all they want, but they need to vacate their seats if they are going to take part in such activity.</p>
<h2>Too Many Opportunities for Criminality</h2>
<p>In 2022, the world of crypto came crashing down when it was announced that the space’s golden boy FTX was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">filing bankruptcy</a> and that Sam Bankman-Fried <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-ftx-exec-sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-fraud/" data-wpel-link="internal">was going to face trial</a> for fraud. One of the scary points of this story is that SBF is alleged to have given <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-gave-a-lot-of-money-to-democrats-what-will-they-do-with-it/" data-wpel-link="internal">donations to many politicians</a> (primarily democrats) in the form of user funds. As it turns out, even after the arrest of SBF, many of these politicians have refused to say if they are going to give the money back.</p>
<p>This situation alone should be enough to convince incoming lawmakers that politics and crypto don’t go together. There is no way all these politicians – given their close ties to FTX and SBF – didn’t see what was going on with the exchange. This was clearly a mark of criminality in both the crypto space and in the U.S. government, and if lawmakers are to remain in power, they must focus less on using their power to get rich and more on assisting the people they were hired to serve.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-congress-should-not-be-permitted-to-engage-in-crypto-trading/">Opinion: Congress Should Not Be Permitted to Engage in Crypto Trading</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-congress-should-not-be-permitted-to-engage-in-crypto-trading/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Andy Greenberg Is Publishing a New Book on BTC&#8217;s Traceability</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/andy-greenberg-is-publishing-a-new-book-on-btcs-traceability/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/andy-greenberg-is-publishing-a-new-book-on-btcs-traceability/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 15:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Andy Greenberg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[traceability]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76374</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Andy Greenberg – a technology journalist – has a new book coming out called “Tracers in the Dark: The Global Hunt for the Crime Lords of Cryptocurrency.” Andy Greenberg Has a New BTC Book Coming Out The book details the early 2021 incident in which the Colonial Pipeline was hacked by cyberthieves who demanded bitcoin<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/andy-greenberg-is-publishing-a-new-book-on-btcs-traceability/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/andy-greenberg-is-publishing-a-new-book-on-btcs-traceability/">Andy Greenberg Is Publishing a New Book on BTC&#8217;s Traceability</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Andy Greenberg – a technology journalist – <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/criminals-thought-crypto-was-untraceable-they-were-wrong/ar-AA15M9ve" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">has a new book coming</a> out called “Tracers in the Dark: The Global Hunt for the Crime Lords of Cryptocurrency.”</p>
<h2>Andy Greenberg Has a New BTC Book Coming Out</h2>
<p>The book details the early 2021 incident in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fbi-halts-bitcoin-ransomware-attack-on-colonial-pipeline/" data-wpel-link="internal">which the Colonial Pipeline</a> was hacked by cyberthieves who demanded bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies in exchange for its release. The Department of Justice (DOJ) was able to recover half of the payment that was sent and take the funds back, thus resulting in the thieves receiving a lot less money than they had anticipated.</p>
<p>The book is a testament to the traceability of crypto, which is often labeled as anonymous and immune to prying eyes. Greenberg claims this is not true and discusses the matter in detail in the book.</p>
<p>He explained that the way the traceability happens is when agencies collapse bitcoin addresses into single identities. He says there are certain patterns that occur on the blockchain, even when transactors utilize multiple addresses to send or receive crypto funds, and that organizations such as the DOJ are now able to read those patterns with greater ease and discover who the money is going to and who it’s coming from. They can then intercede if necessary.</p>
<p>In the book, Greenberg writes:</p>
<blockquote><p>In bitcoin, for good and for ill, everyone was witness to every payment… [which] offered an enormous collection of data to analyze. Who could say what sorts of patterns might give away users who thought they were cleverer than those watching them?</p></blockquote>
<p>One of the big “characters” in the book is a woman named Sarah Meiklejohn, who studied at the University of California at San Diego in 2011. Working to get her PhD, Sarah heard about bitcoin while focusing on privacy research, and she became intrigued by the technology behind it.</p>
<h2>Finding the Patterns</h2>
<p>In taking a broader look at the blockchain, she was able to decipher many of the patterns that the book discusses and that agencies like the Department of Justice are now able to utilize when studying criminal activity. Greenberg writes:</p>
<blockquote><p>She scanned her blockchain database for every multi-input transaction, linking all those double, triple, or even hundredfold inputs to single identities. The result immediately reduced the number of potential bitcoin users from twelve million to date to around five million, slicing away more than half of the problem… Many bitcoin wallets only allowed spenders to pay the entire [number] of coins sitting at a certain address. Each address was like a piggy bank that [must] be smashed open to spend the coin inside. Spend less than the whole amount in that piggy bank and the leftovers [must] be stored in a newly created piggy bank.</p></blockquote>
<p>Crypto crime has become a much larger subject following the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">fall of FTX</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/andy-greenberg-is-publishing-a-new-book-on-btcs-traceability/">Andy Greenberg Is Publishing a New Book on BTC&#8217;s Traceability</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/andy-greenberg-is-publishing-a-new-book-on-btcs-traceability/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Caroline Ellison: What We Were Doing with FTX was Wrong</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/caroline-ellison-what-we-were-doing-with-ftx-was-wrong/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/caroline-ellison-what-we-were-doing-with-ftx-was-wrong/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 13:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Caroline Ellison]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76372</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Caroline Ellison – the 28-year-old girlfriend of Sam Bankman-Fried and the former CEO of Alameda Research, a company founded by SBF – has admitted in recent testimony that she knew what was happening with FTX was wrong. Caroline Ellison on FTX: It Was Wrong The big bang for FTX comes in the shape of Alameda,<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/caroline-ellison-what-we-were-doing-with-ftx-was-wrong/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/caroline-ellison-what-we-were-doing-with-ftx-was-wrong/">Caroline Ellison: What We Were Doing with FTX was Wrong</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Caroline Ellison – the 28-year-old girlfriend of Sam Bankman-Fried and the former CEO of Alameda Research, a company founded by SBF – has <a href="https://www.thestreet.com/investing/cryptocurrency/i-knew-what-i-was-doing-was-wrong-says-ftx-co-founder" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">admitted in recent testimony</a> that she knew what was happening with FTX was wrong.</p>
<h2>Caroline Ellison on FTX: It Was Wrong</h2>
<p>The big bang for FTX comes in the shape of Alameda, which borrowed money from the crypto exchange in the form of user funds to pay off separate debts. Both companies were required to remain individual entities. In conjoining them both together through the borrowing of assorted funds, it’s likely that Sam Bankman-Fried engaged in illegal activities.</p>
<p>It is also alleged that some of those user funds went towards paying for luxury Bahamian properties for the exchange’s employees and executives.</p>
<p>Ellison has recently pled guilty to multiple federal charges and has sworn to cooperate with prosecutors against her boyfriend SBF in exchange for leniency. In recent testimony, she laid out the situation involving Alameda and FTX and said that she knew the activities she and her constituents were engaging in were wrong. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I knew that it was wrong… From 2019 through 2022, I was aware that Alameda was provided access to a borrowing facility on FTX.com, the cryptocurrency exchange run by Mr. Bankman-Fried. In practical terms, this arrangement permitted Alameda access to an unlimited line of credit without being required to post collateral, without having negative balances, and without being subject to margin calls on FTX.com&#8217;s liquidation protocols. If Alameda&#8217;s FTX accounts had significant negative balances in any particular currency, it meant that Alameda was borrowing funds that FTX&#8217;s customers had deposited on the exchange.</p></blockquote>
<p>With her testimony, the situation is looking rather grim for Sam Bankman-Fried, who was recently <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-ftx-exec-sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-fraud/" data-wpel-link="internal">extradited back to the</a> United States. He is presently awaiting trial at his parents’ California home. Ellison said that at first, she had no problem hiding the relationship between Alameda and FTX from customers. She commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>I agreed with others to borrow several billion dollars from FTX to repay those loans.</p></blockquote>
<p>In an interview in late November, Sam Bankman-Fried said that he had made a lot of mistakes during his time at FTX and that he had no intention of hurting anyone. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I made a lot of mistakes. There are things I would give anything to be able to do over again. I didn&#8217;t ever try to commit fraud on anyone.</p></blockquote>
<h2>The SEC Has Stepped In</h2>
<p>In a civil complaint against Sam Bankman-Fried, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) said that the crypto exec engaged in long-term fraud that resulted in billions of dollars getting lost. The complaint reads:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bankman-Fried was orchestrating a massive, years-long fraud, diverting billions of dollars of the trading platform’s customer funds for his own personal benefit and to help grow his crypto empire.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/caroline-ellison-what-we-were-doing-with-ftx-was-wrong/">Caroline Ellison: What We Were Doing with FTX was Wrong</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/caroline-ellison-what-we-were-doing-with-ftx-was-wrong/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Bulls Aim A Push To $150</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bulls-aim-a-push-to-150/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bulls-aim-a-push-to-150/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 05:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76697</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin cash started a decent increase above the $120 and $125 resistance levels against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above the $125 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $130 on the 4-hours chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bulls-aim-a-push-to-150/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bulls-aim-a-push-to-150/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Bulls Aim A Push To $150</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin cash started a decent increase above the $120 and $125 resistance levels against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above the $125 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $130 on the 4-hours chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair must clear $135 and $138 to continue higher in the near term.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin cash price is climbing above $125 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-more-gains-above-23k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. BCH/USD could start a fresh surge if it clears the $135 level.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin cash price formed a decent support base above the $115 level. BCH started a recovery wave and was able to clear the $120 resistance zone.</p>
<p>The price climbed above the $122 and $125 resistance levels. The pair is now trading above the $125 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). The recent surge was such that the price even traded above the $135 level. A high is formed near $138 before there was a minor decline.</p>
<p>There was a move below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-dips-remain-attractive-near-115/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">upward move</a> from the $116 swing low to $138 high. It is now trading above the $125 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $135 level. The next major resistance is near the $138 level, above which the price may perhaps rise towards the $150 level. Any more gains above $150 could set the pace for a move towards the $165 level in the coming days.</p>
<p>An immediate support on the downside is near the $130 level. There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support near $130 on the 4-hours chart of the BCH/USD pair.</p>
<p>The first major support sits near the $128 level. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $116 swing low to $138 high. The next major support is near $125, below which the bears might aim $120. The next target for them may perhaps be near the $112 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_76698" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Bitcoin-Cash-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76698" class="size-full wp-image-76698" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Bitcoin-Cash-3.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76698" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Cash Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BCHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, bitcoin cash price is now trading above the $125 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price must clear $135 and $138 to continue higher in the near term.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for BCH/USD is gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BCH/USD is near the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $130 and $125.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $135 and $138.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bulls-aim-a-push-to-150/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Bulls Aim A Push To $150</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bulls-aim-a-push-to-150/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mark Cuban: A New Form of Crypto Crime Will Emerge This Year</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-a-new-form-of-crypto-crime-will-emerge-this-year/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-a-new-form-of-crypto-crime-will-emerge-this-year/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 17:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mark Cuban]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wash trading]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76367</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Throughout 2022, there were many trends surrounding crypto crime. Many romance scams popped up, clearly proving it was a popular method amongst cyberthieves of getting money that wasn’t theirs. We also saw examples of exchange fraud like with FTX. Now, billionaire investor and crypto bull Mark Cuban says a new crime trend will occur in<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-a-new-form-of-crypto-crime-will-emerge-this-year/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-a-new-form-of-crypto-crime-will-emerge-this-year/">Mark Cuban: A New Form of Crypto Crime Will Emerge This Year</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Throughout 2022, there were many trends surrounding crypto crime. Many <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/romance-scam/" data-wpel-link="internal">romance scams</a> popped up, clearly proving it was a popular method amongst cyberthieves of getting money that wasn’t theirs. We also saw examples of exchange fraud like with FTX. Now, billionaire investor and crypto bull Mark Cuban says <a href="https://www.thestreet.com/investing/cryptocurrency/billionaire-mark-cuban-warns-of-potential-new-crypto-scandal-fraud" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">a new crime trend will</a> occur in 2023, though he freely admits he’s suggesting this based purely on his own thoughts, and he has no evidence to suggest it will truly occur.</p>
<h2>Mark Cuban: A New Danger Is Coming</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, Cuban says that wash trades are likely to become very prominent in the year 2023, though he says this idea stems from instinct, not from fact-based data. He stated that the problem will occur mostly on centralized exchanges, such as what we’ve seen with FTX, and he thinks the problem will expand from there.</p>
<p>Cuban said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think the next possible implosion is the discovery and removal of wash trades on central exchanges. There are supposedly tens of millions of dollars in trades and liquidity for tokens that have very little utilization. I don&#8217;t see how they can be that liquid… I don&#8217;t have any specifics to offer to support my guess.</p></blockquote>
<p>The U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) describes wash trading as follows:</p>
<blockquote><p>Wash Trading (is) entering into, or purporting to enter into, transactions to give the appearance that purchases and [even] sales have been made, without incurring market risk or changing the trader&#8217;s market position.</p></blockquote>
<p>Basically, a wash trade occurs when artificial interest is stirred in a financial product (i.e., a new crypto token) to make way for what’s called a pump and dump. The hype surrounding the coin is pumped up so much that everyone buys it, thus inflating the price. From there, the executives that created the token make off with the money they’ve made and the asset crashes and burns, leaving all investors in the dust.</p>
<p>As it turns out, bitcoin is not immune to wash trades. A 2022 study conducted by <em>Forbes</em> says that about half the exchange volumes reported by bitcoin and crypto trading platforms are fake. The study read:</p>
<blockquote><p>More than half of all reported trading volume is likely to be fake or non-economic… The global daily bitcoin volume for the industry was $128 billion on June 14. That is 51 percent less than the $262 billion one would get by taking the sum of self-reported volume from multiple sources.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Using Customers&#8217; Money</h2>
<p>If Cuban is correct, this would ultimately take the crypto crime of the last year in an entirely different direction.</p>
<p>Throughout 2022, we saw examples of companies in FTX (and now allegedly <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-sues-crypto-lending-network-celsius-and-its-former-ceo/" data-wpel-link="internal">the Celsius Network</a>) using customer funds <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-ftx-exec-sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-fraud/" data-wpel-link="internal">for their own personal gains</a>. With FTX, their money was used to reportedly buy Bahamian real estate.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-a-new-form-of-crypto-crime-will-emerge-this-year/">Mark Cuban: A New Form of Crypto Crime Will Emerge This Year</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-a-new-form-of-crypto-crime-will-emerge-this-year/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New York Sues Crypto Lending Network Celsius and Its Former CEO</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-sues-crypto-lending-network-celsius-and-its-former-ceo/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-sues-crypto-lending-network-celsius-and-its-former-ceo/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 15:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celsius]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Leticia James]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New York]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76365</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The state of New York and its attorney general Leticia James are suing former crypto lending network Celsius for allegedly engaging in fraud and misusing customer funds. New York Comes Down Hard on Celsius The sentiment is that FTX wasn’t the only company to use traders’ money for personal gains this year. Celsius really rang<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-sues-crypto-lending-network-celsius-and-its-former-ceo/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-sues-crypto-lending-network-celsius-and-its-former-ceo/">New York Sues Crypto Lending Network Celsius and Its Former CEO</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The state of New York and its attorney general Leticia James <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/new-york-state-sues-former-celsius-ceo-over-alleged-cryptocurrency-fraud/ar-AA160HiC" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">are suing former crypto</a> lending network Celsius for allegedly engaging in fraud and misusing customer funds.</p>
<h2>New York Comes Down Hard on Celsius</h2>
<p>The sentiment is that FTX wasn’t the only company to use traders’ money for personal gains this year. Celsius really rang a lot of negative bells last summer when it first announced it was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/another-mega-bitcoin-crash-is-in-the-books/" data-wpel-link="internal">going to be halting all withdrawals</a> given that speculation and the volatility of the market had become way too big for its executives to handle. The halts would be put in place indefinitely and customers had no idea regarding when they would be able to get their money back.</p>
<p>Things didn’t quite stop there, however. It was just a few weeks later when the company announced that it was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/celsius-network-is-next-crypto-company-to-file-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">entering bankruptcy proceedings</a>. Celsius said it was going to seek other ways of retaining capital and staying afloat without having to worry about what angry lenders would do to retaliate against it for not making loan payments.</p>
<p>There were all kinds of hoopla around the company as it was announced that Celsius executives were working on a plan to give <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/celsius-is-planning-to-give-customer-funds-back/" data-wpel-link="internal">customers their money back</a>, though now, it looks like that may have just been for show, and when one puts the pieces together for Celsius, they cannot help but be reminded of FTX, which followed the same distinct patterns and pathways.</p>
<p>Think about it. Celsius files for bankruptcy and then the CEO, Alex Mashinsky, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/celsius-ceo-alex-mashinsky-steps-down/" data-wpel-link="internal">resigns from his post</a>. In the case of FTX, the story is the same. The company filed <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">bankruptcy and then</a> the CEO, Sam Bankman-Fried, resigned from his post. It’s now been alleged that FTX used customer funds to purchase luxury items for the company’s executives, so why wouldn’t Celsius’ tale conclude with the same measures?</p>
<p>The similarities are there, and for whatever reason, we couldn’t quite put them together until now. James and her state are taking a stance against Celsius and its top executive, claiming they boasted low-risk investments while repeatedly exposing customers to high risks. This allowed them to make off with user funds and keep the activity hidden from prying eyes.</p>
<h2>No More Business for You!</h2>
<p>James also says that Mashinksy made false claims about the safety and strategies of the firm. She is now looking to get him barred from doing business within New York’s borders forever. She is also seeking to impose financial penalties and establish a plan that would force him to compensate cheated or affected investors of Celsius.</p>
<p>New York has been coming down hard on crypto companies, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-to-pay-hefty-penalty-fees-to-new-york-lawmakers/" data-wpel-link="internal">a recent example being</a> Coinbase, which was forced to pay more than $100 million to settle with the state’s regulators for allegedly not complying with their anti-money laundering rules.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-sues-crypto-lending-network-celsius-and-its-former-ceo/">New York Sues Crypto Lending Network Celsius and Its Former CEO</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-sues-crypto-lending-network-celsius-and-its-former-ceo/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Is Now 14 Years of Age!</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/happy-birthday-bitcoin-is-now-14-years-of-age/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/happy-birthday-bitcoin-is-now-14-years-of-age/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 13:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76361</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto fans everywhere are wishing bitcoin – the world’s number one digital currency by market cap – a happy birthday, as just a few weeks ago, the beloved asset turned 14. Bitcoin Is 14 Years Old Bitcoin’s whitepaper was officially introduced on Halloween of 2008, but it wasn’t until January of 2009 that the currency<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/happy-birthday-bitcoin-is-now-14-years-of-age/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/happy-birthday-bitcoin-is-now-14-years-of-age/">Bitcoin Is Now 14 Years of Age!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto fans everywhere are wishing bitcoin – the world’s number one digital currency by market cap – a happy birthday, as just a few weeks ago, the <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/bitcoin-celebrates-birthday-7090803" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">beloved asset turned</a> 14.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Is 14 Years Old</h2>
<p>Bitcoin’s whitepaper was officially introduced on Halloween of 2008, but it wasn’t until January of 2009 that the currency began getting mined and added to blockchain circulation. While the whitepaper may have been the asset’s first real introduction to the world, many see that first instance of mining as bitcoin’s true birthing moment, which is why so many choose to celebrate in January rather than in October.</p>
<p>Bitcoin has been declared dead hundreds of times since it first came to fruition. Its rise to the top has been long, hard, and tumultuous as we’re still seeing today. Look, for example, where bitcoin was when November of 2021 came about, and look at where the currency is now. In the former period, the asset was trading at a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit. Everyone felt that the asset was on top of the world and could never be removed from its position.</p>
<p>However, this clearly wasn’t the case as we’re now witnessing in full view. Once 2022 came into play, bitcoin was battered by bearish conditions that ultimately caused it to fall rapidly and lose more than 70 percent of its overall value. The currency ended the year trading in the mid-$16,000 range, a huge dip for what was once considered the most powerful investing tool of its time.</p>
<p>Bitcoin has also been hurt by a wide number of external factors, a big one being fraud and criminal activity which littered 2022. Examples include the fall of popular digital <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">currency exchange FTX</a>. At the time of the company’s collapse, bitcoin appeared to be trying to make a comeback. The currency was trading for just over $20K, but once the news sprung forward that FTX was crashing and burning, it dropped by several thousand dollars.</p>
<p>While it’s easy to assume bitcoin is done for and the crypto space has had its run, one can see that the currency is only battered – not beaten. BTC, for all it has been through, has surpassed some tough barriers and gotten through some rough tests, and it’s come out relatively strong on the other end.</p>
<h2>The Currency Is Still Here</h2>
<p>Bitcoin is down for the count after all the negative events of the previous 12 months, though it has retained some of its inner power. It’s not like the currency has disappeared altogether; it’s still here, which means it still has enough juice in its tank to put up a fight, and it’s not like bitcoin hasn’t made comebacks in the past.</p>
<p>Let’s all wish BTC a happy birthday and hope for the best in 2023!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/happy-birthday-bitcoin-is-now-14-years-of-age/">Bitcoin Is Now 14 Years of Age!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/happy-birthday-bitcoin-is-now-14-years-of-age/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EOS Price Analysis: Rally Could Resume Above $1.12</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-rally-could-resume-above-1-12/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-rally-could-resume-above-1-12/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 06:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EOS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76681</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>EOS price started a fresh increase above the $1.00 resistance against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above $1.0 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $1.065 on the 4-hours chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-rally-could-resume-above-1-12/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-rally-could-resume-above-1-12/">EOS Price Analysis: Rally Could Resume Above $1.12</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>EOS price started a fresh increase above the $1.00 resistance against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $1.0 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $1.065 on the 4-hours chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move up if it clears the $1.12 and $1.15 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>EOS price is rising above $1.00 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-more-gains-above-23k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. The price could resume its increase if it clears the $1.12 and $1.15 resistance levels.</em></p>
<h2>EOS Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This week, EOS price started a fresh increase from the $0.95 zone against the US Dollar. The price gained pace and was able to clear the $1.00 resistance zone.</p>
<p>The price broke the $1.05 resistance zone and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-0-95/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. The bulls even pushed the price above the $1.10 level. However, the bears appeared near the $1.12 zone. A high is formed near $1.122 and the price is now consolidating gains.</p>
<p>On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $1.11 level. The first major resistance is near the $1.12 level, above which the price could rise steadily.</p>
<p>In the stated case, it could rise towards the $1.15 level. Any more gains might send the price towards the $1.20 level. On the downside, an immediate support is near the $1.09. It is near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1.01 swing low to $1.122 high.</p>
<p>The next key support is near the $1.065. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $1.065 on the 4-hours chart of the EOS/USD pair.</p>
<p>The trend line is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1.01 swing low to $1.122 high. If there is a downside break below the $1.065 support, the price could revisit the $1.02 support.</p>
<div id="attachment_76682" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/EOS-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76682" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-76682" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/EOS-2.png" alt="EOS Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76682" class="wp-caption-text">EOS Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/EOSUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, EOS price is now trading above the $1.00 level and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could continue to move up if it clears the $1.12 and $1.15 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4-hours MACD – The MACD for EOS/USD is gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4-hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $1.065 and $1.020.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $1.12 and $1.20.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-rally-could-resume-above-1-12/">EOS Price Analysis: Rally Could Resume Above $1.12</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-rally-could-resume-above-1-12/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Uptrend Intact Above $85</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-uptrend-intact-above-85/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-uptrend-intact-above-85/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 03:58:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76678</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin started a strong increase above $85 against the US Dollar. LTC price is now trading above $82 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a connecting bullish trend line forming with support near $88.00 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair remains supported for more<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-uptrend-intact-above-85/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-uptrend-intact-above-85/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Uptrend Intact Above $85</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Litecoin started a strong increase above $85 against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>LTC price is now trading above $82 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a connecting bullish trend line forming with support near $88.00 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair remains supported for more gains unless there is a clear move below $85.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Litecoin price is rising steadily above $85 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-more-gains-above-23k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. LTC price could continue to move up if it remains well supported above the $85 level.</em></p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few sessions, there was a decent increase in bitcoin, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-bulls-aim-1800-or-higher/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">ethereum</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-in-control-above-0-38/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">ripple</a>, and litecoin against the US Dollar. Earlier, LTC formed a base above the $82 level and started a fresh increase.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above the $85 and $88 resistance levels. The price even climbed above the $90 level and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). However, the bears were active near the $95 zone. A high was formed near $93.16 and the price started a downside correction.</p>
<p>There was a move below the $90 level. The price declined below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $81.67 swing low to $93.16 high.</p>
<p>The price is now trading above $85 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $88.00 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair. The pair is also supported above the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $81.67 swing low to $93.16 high.</p>
<p>The first major support is near the $88 level and the trend line. If there is a downside break below the $88 support, the price could accelerate lower towards the $85 level in the near term.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $92 and $93 levels. A clear move above the $93 level could pump the price towards the $100 level. The next major resistance sits near the $108 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_76679" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Litecoin-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76679" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-76679" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Litecoin-2.png" alt="Litecoin (LTC) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76679" class="wp-caption-text">Litecoin (LTC) Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, litecoin price is clearly trading above $85 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price remains supported for more gains unless there is a clear move below $85.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LTC/USD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $88 and $85</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $93 and $100.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-uptrend-intact-above-85/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Uptrend Intact Above $85</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-uptrend-intact-above-85/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
