<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 02:53:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Regain Strength Above $85</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-regain-strength-above-85/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-regain-strength-above-85/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 02:58:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78890</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin started a steady increase above $82 against the US Dollar. LTC price is now trading above $82 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance at $77.40 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-regain-strength-above-85/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-regain-strength-above-85/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Regain Strength Above $85</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Litecoin started a steady increase above $82 against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>LTC price is now trading above $82 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance at $77.40 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could rise further if it clears the $91 and $94 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Litecoin price is showing positive signs above $85 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-bulls-aim-fresh-uptrend/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. LTC price could climb further if there is a clear move above $91.</em></p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few sessions, there were mostly positive moves in Bitcoin, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-recover-to-1900/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Ethereum</a>, Ripple, and Litecoin against the US Dollar. Earlier, LTC formed a base above the $71 level and started a fresh increase.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above the $75 and $78 resistance levels. During the increase, there was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance at $77.40 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair. The pair even cleared the $85 resistance zone.</p>
<p>There was a move above the 50% Fib retracement level of the key decline from the $97.53 swing high to the $71.09 low. It is now trading above $85 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $91.20 level. It is close to the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the key decline from the $97.53 swing high to the $71.09 low. A clear move above the $91.20 level could push the price toward the $93.35 level.</p>
<p>The next major resistance sits near the $95 level. Any more gains might send the price toward the $100 level. On the downside, initial support is near the $84.40 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $80 level. If there is a downside break below the $80 support, the price could accelerate lower toward the $77.20 level in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_78891" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Litecoin-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78891" class="size-full wp-image-78891" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Litecoin-3.png" alt="Litecoin (LTC) Price" width="1835" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78891" class="wp-caption-text">Litecoin (LTC) Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">chart</a>, Litecoin price is clearly trading above $85 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could rise further if it clears the $91 and $94 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LTC/USD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $84.40 and $80.00</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $91.20 and $93.35.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-regain-strength-above-85/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Regain Strength Above $85</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-regain-strength-above-85/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former Coinbase Employee to Serve Two Years in Jail</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-coinbase-employee-to-serve-two-years-in-jail/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-coinbase-employee-to-serve-two-years-in-jail/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 17:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[insider trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ishan Wahi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78280</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Former Coinbase product manager Ishan Wahi will serve two years behind bars after he took part in a crypto-based insider trading scheme. Former Coinbase Manager Heading to Prison As a former employee of one of the world’s largest and most renowned crypto trading platforms, Wahi gained access to specific knowledge that ultimately made him privy<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-coinbase-employee-to-serve-two-years-in-jail/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-coinbase-employee-to-serve-two-years-in-jail/">Former Coinbase Employee to Serve Two Years in Jail</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Former Coinbase product manager Ishan Wahi will serve two <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-ca/money/topstories/coinbase-ex-manager-sentenced-to-2-years-in-prison-in-us-insider-trading-case/ar-AA1aXYI6" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">years behind bars</a> after he took part in a crypto-based insider trading scheme.</p>
<h2>Former Coinbase Manager Heading to Prison</h2>
<p>As a former employee of one of the world’s largest and most renowned crypto trading platforms, Wahi gained access to specific knowledge that ultimately made him privy to price activity regarding certain coins. As the product manager, he would often learn about which coins <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-coinbase-employee-guilty-of-insider-trading-to-be-sentenced-in-may/" data-wpel-link="internal">would be listed</a> on Coinbase and when. From there, he would pass this information along to his brother and a family friend and together, they would purchase these coins prior to their listings on Coinbase.</p>
<p>As soon as they earned their spots on the trading platform, the coins’ prices would go up. This would garner profit for Wahi and his associates, and they would then sell the coins, thus cashing in on their gains. This is considered an insider trading situation given that he had access to information that wouldn’t have been made available to standard traders or investors.</p>
<p>While in court, Wahi was joined by several family members and friends. He expressed remorse for his actions and said he felt bad about all the trouble he had caused those he cared about. In a statement, he mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>I made a huge mistake that will follow me for the rest of my life.</p></blockquote>
<p>However, his apologetic tone did nothing to <a href="https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2023/05/1-5m-crypto-scheme-leads-to-2-year-prison-term-for-ex-coinbase-manager/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lessen the disgust and rage</a> of US attorney for the Southern District of New York Damian Williams, who was quick to condemn Ishan’s actions and say that he “violated the trust” of his employer. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Today’s sentence should send a strong signal to all participants in the cryptocurrency markets that the laws decidedly do apply to them.</p></blockquote>
<p>Prior to Ishan’s sentencing, his brother Nikhil pled guilty in a separate case regarding his involvement in the scheme. He was later sentenced to serve ten months in prison. The third-party friend – a man named Ramani – was able to escape prosecution by fleeing to international territory. He remains at large as of this writing.</p>
<p>It is estimated that Wahi and his team made off with more than $1 million in profits and traded more than 50 separate digital assets.</p>
<h2>So Many Bad Stories!</h2>
<p>Coinbase has been the subject of several bits of unwanted publicity over the past few months. For instance, the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">company was recently served</a> with a Wells notice by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), which claimed that charges were likely in the trading platform’s midst.</p>
<p>Coinbase executives were quick to take issue with the notice. They claimed they had met with representatives of the SEC over 30 times during a nine-year period to ensure their company’s operations were compliant. Coinbase has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-is-boosting-its-fight-against-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">since filed suit against</a> the agency.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-coinbase-employee-to-serve-two-years-in-jail/">Former Coinbase Employee to Serve Two Years in Jail</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-coinbase-employee-to-serve-two-years-in-jail/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Shoots Up as Inflation Slides a Tad</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-shoots-up-as-inflation-slides-a-tad/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-shoots-up-as-inflation-slides-a-tad/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 15:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Inflation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78277</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin endured a slight rise in mid-May after numbers emerged suggesting inflation was potentially easing up. Inflation May Be Dying Down a Bit Regions like the U.S. and the U.K. have been subjected to the highest inflation seen in roughly 40 or 50 years. Things like gas prices, food prices, and the costs of other<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-shoots-up-as-inflation-slides-a-tad/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-shoots-up-as-inflation-slides-a-tad/">Bitcoin Shoots Up as Inflation Slides a Tad</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin endured a slight rise in mid-May after numbers <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-rises-slightly-after-key-inflation-data-comes-in-better-than-feared/ar-AA1b0MMd" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">emerged suggesting inflation</a> was potentially easing up.</p>
<h2>Inflation May Be Dying Down a Bit</h2>
<p>Regions like the U.S. and the U.K. have been subjected to the highest inflation seen in roughly 40 or 50 years. Things like gas prices, food prices, and the costs of other goods and services have risen tenfold over the past year or so, and it’s becoming much harder to put one’s money to positive use.</p>
<p>The economies of both countries have cracked under the weight of weak leaders and financial tactics that saw things like hiking rates and the dissolvement of people’s ability to afford cars and homes. The good news is that inflation has lessened somewhat. Not by much, but today, a little chipping here and there can go a long way.</p>
<p>The consumer price index report shows inflation is now just under the five percent mark, which is slightly less than what many analysts and economists expected. Callie Cox – an analyst at investment firm e-Toro – commented in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>When it comes to inflation data, bitcoin embraces its identity as a riskier asset. Bitcoin has outperformed the S&amp;P 500 on five out of the last six CPI days, and it&#8217;s on track to make it six out of seven with today&#8217;s gains… Inflation is coming down, just as the Fed intended, and that&#8217;s easing fears about the economy&#8217;s future. Lower inflation also supports the case for the end of rate hikes, and higher rates are what started the crypto winter over a year ago.</p></blockquote>
<p>Steven Lubka – managing director at Swan Bitcoin – also threw his two cents into the mix, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>Ultimately, this represents an easing of tight liquidity conditions, an environment in which bitcoin has done extremely well historically.</p></blockquote>
<p>Never was bitcoin put through more suffering and tension than in 2022. During that time, inflation was the highest it had been in several decades, and the Federal Reserve – as a means of combating the problem – was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-fed-bitcoins-worst-enemy-right-now/" data-wpel-link="internal">consistently hiking rates</a> to the point that they began to take serious tolls on the prices of BTC and its altcoin cousins.</p>
<h2>A Year of Suffering for Crypto</h2>
<p>During this period, bitcoin lost more than 70 percent of its value and fell from the $68,000 all-time high it achieved in November of 2021 to about $16,600. Things didn’t stop there, however, and several digital currencies chose to follow in its footsteps, thus contributing to the crypto industry losing more than $2 trillion in overall valuation in under 12 months. It was a sad and ugly sight to see.</p>
<p>Putting all this aside, while inflation may be easing somewhat, BTC is not quite out of the woods yet as the Fed has made it clear 2023 will <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-fed-hikes-rates-again-but-analysts-think-bitcoin-will-surge-soon/" data-wpel-link="internal">still be a year of further</a> rate hikes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-shoots-up-as-inflation-slides-a-tad/">Bitcoin Shoots Up as Inflation Slides a Tad</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-shoots-up-as-inflation-slides-a-tad/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sam Bankman-Fried Wants 10 Criminal Charges Tossed Out</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-wants-10-criminal-charges-tossed-out/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-wants-10-criminal-charges-tossed-out/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 13:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[criminal charges]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78275</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sam Bankman-Fried – the former head of the digital currency exchange FTX, which collapsed into a burning heap of bankruptcy and fraud last November – is asking the judge overseeing his case to dismiss most of the criminal charges against him. Bankman-Fried Seems to Imply Things Are Rigged Against Him Right now, Sam Bankman-Fried is<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-wants-10-criminal-charges-tossed-out/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-wants-10-criminal-charges-tossed-out/">Sam Bankman-Fried Wants 10 Criminal Charges Tossed Out</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sam Bankman-Fried – the former head of the digital currency exchange FTX, which collapsed into a burning heap of bankruptcy and fraud last November – is <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/indicted-ftx-founder-sam-bankman-012707413.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">asking the judge overseeing</a> his case to dismiss most of the criminal charges against him.</p>
<h2>Bankman-Fried Seems to Imply Things Are Rigged Against Him</h2>
<p>Right now, Sam Bankman-Fried is facing 13 separate criminal charges. He and his lawyers are requesting that the judge toss out a total of ten, thus bringing the end count to three. The situation is an odd one given that they are not requesting all the charges be dismissed outright. Even if the former crypto executive gets his way, it’s likely he’ll still face certain penalties, so is this just a gimmick to try and reduce his time behind bars?</p>
<p>Attorneys for Bankman-Fried commented in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>Rather than wait for traditional civil and regulatory processes following their ordinary course to address the situation, the government jumped in with both feet, improperly seeking to turn these civil and regulatory issues into federal crimes… The FTX debtors have worked so extensively with the government and are so enmeshed in the investigation, analysis, and strategy of the government&#8217;s case, that they must be considered part of the &#8216;prosecution team.’</p></blockquote>
<p>FTX will likely go down as one of the biggest debacles of the digital currency space. The exchange – which first opened its doors for business in 2019 – rose to prominence three years later to become one of the top five digital currency trading platforms in the world. Its founder and chief executive Sam Bankman-Fried was lauded as a genius by many, and his net worth was in the billions towards the end of 2022.</p>
<p>Sadly, this reputation was short-lived as in mid-November, SBF complained of a liquidity crunch on social media. He said he <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>needed fast cash</strong></a> to keep his business in operation, and he eventually turned to his biggest rival Binance about a possible buyout. While things <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>appeared to be moving</strong></a> in that direction for some time, Binance eventually backed <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>away from the deal</strong></a>, claiming the problems FTX was facing were simply too big for it to handle.</p>
<h2>The Problems Didn&#8217;t Stop</h2>
<p>From there, the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>company filed bankruptcy</strong></a> and SBF resigned from his post. Things would have been bad enough if they had stopped there, but the trash meter kept rising. It was later discovered that SBF had utilized customer funds to invest in luxury Bahamian real estate and to pay off loans taken out by his other company Alameda Research. He <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftxs-disgraced-founder-has-been-arrested/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>was eventually arrested</strong></a> and extradited back to the United States. He has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-ftx-exec-sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-fraud/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>entered a not guilty plea</strong></a> and is awaiting trial at his <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-to-await-trial-at-his-parents-house/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>parents’ California home</strong></a>.</p>
<p>Bankman-Fried is also believed to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-faces-more-charges-for-his-political-contributions/" data-wpel-link="internal">have had extreme influence</a> in the world of American politics, donating heavily to democrat politicians.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-wants-10-criminal-charges-tossed-out/">Sam Bankman-Fried Wants 10 Criminal Charges Tossed Out</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-wants-10-criminal-charges-tossed-out/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana (SOL) Price Analysis: Bulls Aim Recovery To $18.50</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/solana-sol-price-analysis-bulls-aim-recovery-to-18-50/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/solana-sol-price-analysis-bulls-aim-recovery-to-18-50/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 05:08:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78877</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Solana price started a decent increase above the $15.50 resistance against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above $15.50 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $15.40 on the 4-hour chart of the SOL/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/solana-sol-price-analysis-bulls-aim-recovery-to-18-50/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/solana-sol-price-analysis-bulls-aim-recovery-to-18-50/">Solana (SOL) Price Analysis: Bulls Aim Recovery To $18.50</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Solana price started a decent increase above the $15.50 resistance against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $15.50 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $15.40 on the 4-hour chart of the SOL/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair must clear $17.50 and $17.75 to continue higher in the near term.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Solana price is trading above $15.50 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-bulls-aim-fresh-uptrend/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. SOL could start a strong increase if it clears the $18.50 resistance.</em></p>
<h2>Solana (SOL) Price Analysis</h2>
<p>SOL price found support near the $13.20 zone. The price remained well-bid and recently started a decent increase above the $14.00 level. The bulls were able to push the price above $15.00.</p>
<p>It broke the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the main decline from the $22.33 swing high to the $13.21 low. It is now trading above $15.50 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/solana-sol-price-analysis-rally-seems-far-from-over/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $15.40 on the 4-hours chart of the SOL/USD pair.</p>
<p>On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $17.50 level. The next major resistance is near the $17.75 zone. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the main decline from the $22.33 swing high to the $13.21 low.</p>
<p>Any more gains might send SOL price towards the $18.50 resistance zone, above which the price could accelerate higher. The next major resistance sits near the $22.00 level.</p>
<p>On the downside, initial support is near the $16.00 level. The next major support is near the trend line zone at $15.40 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). A downside break below the $15.40 support level push the price toward the $14.20 support.</p>
<p>Any more losses might open the doors for more losses toward the $13.20 low in the coming sessions. The next major support is near $12.00.</p>
<div id="attachment_78878" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/SOL.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78878" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78878" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/SOL.png" alt="Solana (SOL) Price " width="1835" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78878" class="wp-caption-text">Solana (SOL) Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/SOLUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Solana price is clearly trading above $15.50 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price must clear $17.50 and $17.75 to continue higher in the near term.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $15.40 and $14.20.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $17.50, $17.75, and $18.50.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/solana-sol-price-analysis-bulls-aim-recovery-to-18-50/">Solana (SOL) Price Analysis: Bulls Aim Recovery To $18.50</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/solana-sol-price-analysis-bulls-aim-recovery-to-18-50/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Bulls Aim Fresh Uptrend</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-bulls-aim-fresh-uptrend/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-bulls-aim-fresh-uptrend/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 03:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78874</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price started a fresh increase above the $27,500 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above $27,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $28,000 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-bulls-aim-fresh-uptrend/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-bulls-aim-fresh-uptrend/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Bulls Aim Fresh Uptrend</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin price started a fresh increase above the $27,500 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $27,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $28,000 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to rise if it stays above the $27,400 support zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin price is showing positive signs above $28,000 against the US Dollar. BTC might correct lower but dips could be limited below the $27,400 zone.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price started a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-rally-above-this-resistance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">steady increase</a> from the $25,000 support zone. The price gained and cleared many hurdles near the $26,500 and $27,000 levels.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above the $27,500 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). The price even rallied above the $28,000 resistance zone. However, the bears were active near the $29,000 zone. A high was formed near $29,050 and the price is now consolidating gains.</p>
<p>The price traded below $28,800 but is well above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $24,750 swing low to the $29,050 high. The price is now trading well above $27,500 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-soon-revisit-28500/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>Immediate resistance on the upside is near the $29,000 level. The first major resistance is near the $29,250 level, above which the price could rise toward the $30,000 zone.</p>
<p>Any more gains might send the price toward the $31,200 zone. If there is no upside break, the price might start a downside correction below $28,500.</p>
<p>The next key support is near the $28,000 level. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $28,000 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair. Any more losses might call for a move toward the $27,400 support zone or the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $24,750 swing low to the $29,050 high.</p>
<div id="attachment_78875" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Bitcoin-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78875" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78875" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Bitcoin-2.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1835" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78875" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XBTUSD/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">chart</a>, Bitcoin price is trading above $27,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to rise if it stays above the $27,400 support zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $28,000 and $27,400.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $29,000, $29,250, and $30,000.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-bulls-aim-fresh-uptrend/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Bulls Aim Fresh Uptrend</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-bulls-aim-fresh-uptrend/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>23-Year-Old Pleads Guilty to Crypto Twitter Hack from Three Years Ago</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/23-year-old-pleads-guilty-to-crypto-twitter-hack-of-three-years-ago/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/23-year-old-pleads-guilty-to-crypto-twitter-hack-of-three-years-ago/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 17:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Joseph James O'Connor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78272</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Three years ago, the world watched in horror as one of the most prominent crypto scams to ever occur on Twitter unfolded before their very eyes. Man Faces Prison for Twitter Crypto Hack in 2020 Many high-profile accounts – including those of Bill Gates, Elon Musk, and former president Barack Obama – were hacked and<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/23-year-old-pleads-guilty-to-crypto-twitter-hack-of-three-years-ago/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/23-year-old-pleads-guilty-to-crypto-twitter-hack-of-three-years-ago/">23-Year-Old Pleads Guilty to Crypto Twitter Hack from Three Years Ago</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Three years ago, the world watched in horror as one of the most <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/twitter-hack-leads-to-120000-in-stolen-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">prominent crypto scams</a> to ever occur on Twitter unfolded before their very eyes.</p>
<h2>Man Faces Prison for Twitter Crypto Hack in 2020</h2>
<p>Many high-profile accounts – including those of Bill Gates, Elon Musk, and former president Barack Obama – were hacked and featured posts about a phony bitcoin giveaway. The person committing the crime announced that anyone who sent BTC to specific addresses would see their money doubled. This, sadly, didn’t happen, and those who sent their money in merely saw it disappear from their digital wallets. The hacker made off with more than $120K in BTC before getting caught.</p>
<p>It later turned out that the culprit <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/graham-clark-revealed-as-the-alleged-twitter-btc-perpetrator/" data-wpel-link="internal">was 17 years old</a>. He agreed to a plea bargain that would see him spend three years in a juvenile detention center. Up to this point, it was always thought that he acted alone, though today, a new suspect has <a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/twitter-bitcoin-scam-elon-musk-joe-biden-man-pleads-guilty-2023-5" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">been taken into custody for</a> being part of the scam. 23-year-old Joseph James O’Connor – who was only 20 when he took part in the Twitter attack – is a British citizen who was found in Spain and was extradited to the U.S. to face his sentencing.</p>
<p>At the time of the attack, roughly 130 Twitter accounts were singled out by O’Connor and his cronies. In addition, the account of Binance – the world’s largest and most popular digital currency exchange – also saw its account overtaken by the hackers. Upon noticing what was going on, Twitter was quick to issue a halt to the activity and put out the following statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>We detected what we believe to be a coordinated social engineering attack by people who successfully targeted some of our employees with access to internal systems and tools.</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition to taking part in the Twitter hack, the Department of Justice (DOJ) has issued a statement saying that O’Connor and his pals were engaged in various SIM-swapping hacks that allowed them to gain control of users’ phones so they could access further crypto accounts from there. Lastly, it is believed O’Connor also blackmailed an unnamed public figure with private Snapchat photos and stole close to $800,000 in crypto from an anonymous business.</p>
<p>Assistant Attorney General Kenneth A. Polite, Jr. – who has a knack for always being involved in crypto-related scam cases – commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>O&#8217;Connor&#8217;s criminal activities were flagrant and malicious, and his conduct impacted multiple people&#8217;s lives. He harassed, threatened, and extorted his victims, causing substantial emotional harm.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Not Privy to the Same Plea Conditions</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, O’Connor has entered a guilty plea, though as a legal adult, he will not be privy to the same conditions as his partner three years ago.</p>
<p>He will be sentenced later in the month and is facing more than 70 years behind bars.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/23-year-old-pleads-guilty-to-crypto-twitter-hack-of-three-years-ago/">23-Year-Old Pleads Guilty to Crypto Twitter Hack from Three Years Ago</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/23-year-old-pleads-guilty-to-crypto-twitter-hack-of-three-years-ago/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>As Banks Fall, Crypto Gains More Popularity</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-banks-fall-crypto-gains-more-popularity/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-banks-fall-crypto-gains-more-popularity/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[banks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78270</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin, Ethereum, and many other mainstream forms of crypto are gaining a lot of traction and additional popularity as the banking crisis grows. Crypto Is Getting a Lot of Respect Not long ago, one of the banks to join the ongoing list of financial failures was First Republic. The organization’s assets were doled out by<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-banks-fall-crypto-gains-more-popularity/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-banks-fall-crypto-gains-more-popularity/">As Banks Fall, Crypto Gains More Popularity</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin, Ethereum, and many other mainstream forms of crypto <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/05/10/have-the-floodgates-opened-excitement-building-as-10-trillion-crypto-price-earthquake-looms-for-bitcoin-and-ethereum/?sh=48016bdf51cb" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">are gaining a lot</a> of traction and additional popularity as the banking crisis grows.</p>
<h2>Crypto Is Getting a Lot of Respect</h2>
<p>Not long ago, one of the banks to join the ongoing list of financial <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/first-republic-bank-is-gone-what-will-happen-to-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">failures was First Republic</a>. The organization’s assets were doled out by government officials to JPMorgan Chase, a monetary giant that also played a similar role in the Great Recession banking crisis of 2008 and 2009.</p>
<p>The fact remains that the world of standard finance is getting quite shaky under Biden and his incompetent, democrat cronies, and there are many people who no longer feel as confident in standard banks as they once did. They’re turning to bitcoin and crypto to keep their financials safe and sound, and this is an attitude that appears to be growing every day.</p>
<p>Elliot Han – the head of crypto, blockchain, and digital asset investment at Cantor Fitzgerald – commented in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>We’re seeing a lot more maturity. Now, have the floodgates opened? No, I don’t think so, but I think you see a lot more that has come into the [space]. You’re seeing a lot more experimentation.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also pointed to the idea that crypto regulation is getting closer and closer. The calls for regulation have been growing intensely over the past several months given the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">crash of FTX</a>, one of the world’s largest and most popular digital currency exchanges. Bradley Duke – co-chief executive at ETC Group – commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>While a well-conceived regulatory framework for crypto will improve investor confidence and encourage enterprise and job creation, the opposite – a lack of a framework for crypto – creates uncertainty and the retraction of the sector as we are seeing in the U.S. today.</p></blockquote>
<p>Right now, crypto regulation – while important – is non-existent, and taking on more of a bullying form through organizations like the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The agency has long been criticized for its ways of enforcing its will upon crypto companies rather than trying to reason with them or work things out with the industry. Rather, it’s made a habit of going after all major crypto firms and trying to force them into conditions that the SEC – and only the SEC – sees fit.</p>
<h2>The SEC is a Bully</h2>
<p>Among the companies the agency has targeted are Coinbase and Kraken. The former received a Wells notice <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">from the agency informing</a> it that it would likely face charges in the coming future, while Kraken was made to part with a $30 million penalty fee and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/" data-wpel-link="internal">cease all its crypto staking</a> activities and services.</p>
<p>Coinbase took serious issue with the notice in that representatives claim to have met with SEC heads roughly 30 times over a nine-year period to ensure the company was fully compliant.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-banks-fall-crypto-gains-more-popularity/">As Banks Fall, Crypto Gains More Popularity</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-banks-fall-crypto-gains-more-popularity/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Naupada Police In India Arrest Crypto Scammers</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/naupada-police-in-india-detain-crypto-scammers/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/naupada-police-in-india-detain-crypto-scammers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 13:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scam]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Naupada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shubransh Nayak]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78266</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An IIT Kanpur student named Shubransh Nayak and several of his friends were detained by Naupada police after evidence emerged they were involved in a crypto fraud scheme. Naupada Police Investigate Crypto Scam A police report issued the following statement: The initial complaint is of ₹2.5 lakh, but the scam could burgeon to several crores<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/naupada-police-in-india-detain-crypto-scammers/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/naupada-police-in-india-detain-crypto-scammers/">Naupada Police In India Arrest Crypto Scammers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An IIT Kanpur student named Shubransh Nayak and several <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-in/news/other/thane-naupada-police-detains-iit-kanpur-student-and-his-associate-in-cryptocurrency-fraud/ar-AA1aXBfv" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">of his friends were detained</a> by Naupada police after evidence emerged they were involved in a crypto fraud scheme.</p>
<h2>Naupada Police Investigate Crypto Scam</h2>
<p>A police report issued the following statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>The initial complaint is of ₹2.5 lakh, but the scam could burgeon to several crores since we are expecting more complainants  to approach us.</p></blockquote>
<p>The trouble began when Sushil Kangya and several other residents of the Naupada area began sending complaints to police authorities saying they had been victimized by the crypto companies Dronx.Biz and BNB Pool. The residents said they had lost money to assorted scammers and needed help in retrieving their funds back.</p>
<p>Kangya said he and his sister were approached by Nayak and his associate Pankaj Pandhi and were offered a chance to invest in a crypto platform that would ultimately grant them eight percent in returns each day. They were also told these returns would increase if more people chose to get involved in the scheme.</p>
<p>This should have been a huge red flag for the parties in question given that crypto returns can never be guaranteed. Thus, it’s impossible to assume that one will – for sure – get any sort of specific funds back when they invest in the industry given how volatile and speculative it can be.</p>
<p>Kangya explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>Initially, we invested ₹ 2.5 lakhs and got returns for a few months. Later, the returns stopped. When we asked Shubhransh and Pankaj about non-payment of the returns, they showed us a few videos of the prime minister allegedly promoting the organizations and that the companies were genuine.</p></blockquote>
<p>There were several allegedly phony promotions about the company saying that it had the support of India’s prime ministry and various government members, but these have not been verified. Kangya continued with:</p>
<blockquote><p>When we realized that it was a scam, we asked for the refund of our money, but we were threatened with dire consequences.</p></blockquote>
<p>Sanjay Dhumal – the senior police inspector at the Naupada police station who’s been investigating the case – said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We received the letter from complainant Sushil Kangya against two companies named DRONX BIZ and DRONX BNB Pool which are into MLM and [were] involved in a cryptocurrency scam. The names of people running it are Rajesh Bapodra, a diamond merchant who lives in Kandivali; Krish Reddy, alias Phanni Beejam from Hyderabad; Shubhransh Nayak; Dr. Peter Dhanraj; Avinash Upadhyay; and Pankaj Pandhi. Based on the complaint lodged by Kangya, we have detained them for [an] investigation. As of now, no FIR has been registered against them.</p></blockquote>
<h2>So Many Crypto Problems!</h2>
<p>Crypto crime has become rather rampant in the past few years.</p>
<p>Scams like these are also particularly common and often take on the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/romance-scams/" data-wpel-link="internal">form of romantic partners</a> looking for dates.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/naupada-police-in-india-detain-crypto-scammers/">Naupada Police In India Arrest Crypto Scammers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/naupada-police-in-india-detain-crypto-scammers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=3897 metric#misses=5 metric#hit-ratio=99.9 metric#bytes=6638771 metric#prefetches=400 metric#store-reads=16 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=405 metric#store-misses=0 metric#sql-queries=17 metric#ms-total=159.64 metric#ms-cache=13.60 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.8001 metric#ms-cache-ratio=8.5 -->
