<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 01:41:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Could Gain Pace Above $1,250</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-gain-pace-above-1250/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-gain-pace-above-1250/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 01:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76308</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum price is slowly moving higher from the $1,180 level against the US Dollar. ETH price is now trading above $1,180 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $1,195 on the 4-hours chart (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could start a decent increase<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-gain-pace-above-1250/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-gain-pace-above-1250/">Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Could Gain Pace Above $1,250</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ethereum price is slowly moving higher from the $1,180 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>ETH price is now trading above $1,180 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $1,195 on the 4-hours chart (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could start a decent increase if it clears the $1,250 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ethereum price is struggling below $1,250 against the US Dollar. ETH/USD could start a decent increase if it clears the $1,250 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Ethereum Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, ethereum <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-attempt-fresh-increase-above-1240/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">remained well bid</a> above the $1,165 level against the US Dollar. ETH price formed a base and slowly moved higher above the $1,180 level.</p>
<p>The price climbed above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the key decline from the $1,351 swing high to $1,150 low. Ether price is now trading above $1,180 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-turns-red-again-risk-of-more-downsides/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support near $1,195 on the 4-hours chart.</p>
<p>However, the price is now facing a major hurdle near the $1,230 level. The first major resistance is near the $1,250 level. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the key decline from the $1,351 swing high to $1,150 low. The next major resistance is near the $1,274 zone.</p>
<p>The main resistance is near the $1,300 zone. A clear move above the $1,274 and $1,300 resistance levels might call for a fresh move to $1,350. Any more gains could even send the price towards the $1,400 resistance zone or even $1,450 in the near term.</p>
<p>On the downside, an initial support is near the $1,200 level and the trend line. The next major support is now near the $1,180 level. A break below the $1,180 support could push the price to $1,150. If the bulls struggle to protect the $1,150 support, the price might decline towards $1,080.</p>
<div id="attachment_76309" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Ethereum.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76309" class="size-full wp-image-76309" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Ethereum.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76309" class="wp-caption-text">Ethereum Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Ethereum price is clearly trading above $1,200 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, ether price could start a decent increase if it clears the $1,250 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $1,200, followed by the $1,150 zone.</p>
<p>Key Resistance$ Levels – $1,250 and $1,275.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-gain-pace-above-1250/">Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Could Gain Pace Above $1,250</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-gain-pace-above-1250/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Offers Proof of Bitcoin Reserves to Calm Traders&#8217; Fears</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-offers-proof-of-bitcoin-reserves-to-calm-traders-fears/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-offers-proof-of-bitcoin-reserves-to-calm-traders-fears/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75769</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance, the world’s largest and most popular digital currency exchange, has announced a new program that will give all current and future crypto investors proof of its present bitcoin and Ethereum reserves. Binance Tries to Show It&#8217;s Not Like FTX The goal is to shed light on the issue of transparency and show the company<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-offers-proof-of-bitcoin-reserves-to-calm-traders-fears/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-offers-proof-of-bitcoin-reserves-to-calm-traders-fears/">Binance Offers Proof of Bitcoin Reserves to Calm Traders&#8217; Fears</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance, the world’s largest and most popular digital currency exchange, <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/binance-launches-proof-system-bitcoin-141925970.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">has announced a new program</a> that will give all current and future crypto investors proof of its present bitcoin and Ethereum reserves.</p>
<h2>Binance Tries to Show It&#8217;s Not Like FTX</h2>
<p>The goal is to shed light on the issue of transparency and show the company is nothing like FTX, the now failed digital currency exchange that came to fruition only three years ago in 2019. Binance was initially in line to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">purchase the digital currency</a> exchange when it began experiencing financial problems, though the company later decided that the issues FTX was facing were too big for it to handle, and it <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">wound up backing out</a> of the deal.</p>
<p>In any case, it looks like Binance is taking a lesson from the fiasco that is FTX and trying to not only separate itself from the now deceased company, but also show people why it and the crypto arena in general can still be trusted.</p>
<p>Right now, the company has made clear how much BTC and ETH it has in its reserves tank, though it’s not stopping here. The company has issued a statement suggesting it has more crypto units to its name, and information about those reserves will be made available in the coming weeks.</p>
<p>The statement says:</p>
<blockquote><p>When we say proof of reserves, we are specifically referring to those assets that we hold in custody for users. This means that we are showing evidence and proof that Binance has funds that cover all our users’ assets 1:1, as well as some reserves.</p></blockquote>
<p>At the time of this article’s writing, Binance has released a screenshot showing that it has more than 582,000 bitcoin units stashed away. Right now, there are just over 572,000 units of bitcoin stored on the exchange that are owned by individual traders. From this information alone, we can assume that Binance has enough money to cover everybody’s stashes and potential losses (should they occur) while still having a little left over.</p>
<p>This may appear positive at first glance, but there are several traders out there who feel this isn’t enough. Binance anticipated this attitude and provided steps in a recent press release discussing how traders can verify this data for themselves and ensure their units are privately accounted for.</p>
<h2>See for Yourself!</h2>
<p>The release said:</p>
<blockquote><p>For those who want to go a step further and independently verify their funds, they can copy the source code into a python application and cross reference it themselves.</p></blockquote>
<p>FTX was long considered the golden child of the digital currency world, and its founder and chief executive, Sam Bankman-Fried, was lauded as a genius by many for his ability to potentially take a major company as far as he reportedly did in just three years.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-offers-proof-of-bitcoin-reserves-to-calm-traders-fears/">Binance Offers Proof of Bitcoin Reserves to Calm Traders&#8217; Fears</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-offers-proof-of-bitcoin-reserves-to-calm-traders-fears/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mark Cuban Still Believes in Crypto&#8217;s Power</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-still-believes-in-cryptos-power/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-still-believes-in-cryptos-power/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 15:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mark Cuban]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Voyager Digital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75766</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Billionaire investor and crypto bull Mark Cuban has not lost faith in digital currencies. Despite all the problems that have been occurring with FTX and the price of bitcoin, Cuban still feels that there’s a lot the space can offer. Mark Cuban Remains Confident in Crypto In a recent interview, he mentioned: Separate the signal<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-still-believes-in-cryptos-power/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-still-believes-in-cryptos-power/">Mark Cuban Still Believes in Crypto&#8217;s Power</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Billionaire investor and crypto bull Mark Cuban <a href="https://www.thestreet.com/investing/cryptocurrency/ftx-collapse-billionaire-mark-cuban-remains-a-crypto-follower" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">has not lost faith in digital</a> currencies. Despite all the problems that have been <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">occurring with FTX</a> and the price of bitcoin, Cuban still feels that there’s a lot the space can offer.</p>
<h2>Mark Cuban Remains Confident in Crypto</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, he mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Separate the signal from the noise. There&#8217;s been a lot of people making a lot of mistakes, but it doesn&#8217;t change the underlying value.</p></blockquote>
<p>He doesn’t think the space is in any danger of tanking given that so many people continue to invest in digital currencies and there are so many doors open to it. He admits that while FTX and other bad actors have delivered some wounds, he doesn’t think any of them are fatal. These are a few bad companies in a larger industry that is likely to last based on the power of the technology behind it.</p>
<p>Mark Cuban is currently the subject of a crypto-based lawsuit. Several investors of Voyager Digital – a firm <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-in-the-age-of-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">that went bust in 2022</a> – say they lost all their life savings due to investing their money in the company, which Cuban had spent quite a bit of time promoting. They say they would not have placed their money into the company had Cuban not been their spokesperson. The suit also named Stephen Ehrlich, the former CEO of Voyager.</p>
<p>The lawsuit mentions:</p>
<blockquote><p>Cuban and Ehrlich, as will be explained, went to great lengths to use their experience as investors to dupe millions of Americans into investing — in many cases, their life savings — into the deceptive Voyager platform and purchasing Voyager earn program accounts (EPAs), which are unregistered securities. As a result, over 3.5 million Americans have now all but lost over $5 billion in cryptocurrency assets.</p></blockquote>
<p>The bankruptcy of Voyager Digital happened as a direct <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-luna-token-has-experienced-a-dramatic-drop/" data-wpel-link="internal">result of the Terra Luna</a> coin’s collapse in the summer of last year. Citing his faith in the digital currency market, Cuban wrote on Twitter:</p>
<blockquote><p>A basic question. Why have I invested in crypto? Because I believe smart contracts will have a significant impact in creating valuable applications. I have said from day one [that] the value of a token is derived from the applications that run on its platform and the utility they create. What has not been created is an application that is ubiquitous. One that is obviously needed by everyone, and they are willing to go through the learning curve to use. Maybe it never comes. I hope and think it will.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Crypto Is Like Streaming Music</h2>
<p>He also said that the crypto industry is a lot like the streaming industry, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>The best analogy I can use is the early days of streaming. The sh*t people had to do to listen to a 16K stream of music was insane.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-still-believes-in-cryptos-power/">Mark Cuban Still Believes in Crypto&#8217;s Power</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-still-believes-in-cryptos-power/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Oregon Tells Residents to Avoid Crypto Investments</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/oregon-tells-residents-to-avoid-crypto-investments/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/oregon-tells-residents-to-avoid-crypto-investments/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 13:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oregon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75763</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The state of Oregon has put out a notice to all its residents warning them that investing in crypto could be a costly mistake. Oregon to Investors: Avoid Crypto The warning stems from the Oregon Division of Financial Regulation (DFR) and comes fresh off the heels of the FTX collapse, which arguably sent ripples throughout<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/oregon-tells-residents-to-avoid-crypto-investments/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/oregon-tells-residents-to-avoid-crypto-investments/">Oregon Tells Residents to Avoid Crypto Investments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The state of Oregon has put out a notice to all its <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/caution-urged-state-issues-cryptocurrency-041900070.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">residents warning them</a> that investing in crypto could be a costly mistake.</p>
<h2>Oregon to Investors: Avoid Crypto</h2>
<p>The warning stems from the Oregon Division of Financial Regulation (DFR) and comes fresh off the heels of the FTX collapse, which arguably sent ripples throughout the space and caused many analysts, traders, and industry heads alike to be stunned with surprise. Nobody expected what has been labeled the industry’s golden player over the last three years to fall into a dismal array of crime and failure.</p>
<p>The warning tells Oregon investors to diversify their portfolios as much as they can and to steer clear of largely unregulated products which, unfortunately, include cryptocurrencies. In the statement, DFR administrator TK Keen explains:</p>
<blockquote><p>It is important to know the risks involved with cryptocurrency or any investment opportunities. No investment opportunities are risk-free, and you should always do your homework on where you are sending your money. This is especially true when cryptocurrency is involved.</p></blockquote>
<p>Further discussing what’s been <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">happening with FTX</a>, Keen commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Investing in cryptocurrency is extremely risky given what&#8217;s going on right now. It&#8217;s important to not invest more than you can afford to lose or put all of your assets in one bucket.</p></blockquote>
<p>The DFR is also warning residents to keep their eyes and ears open for crypto scams, many of which show up on social media platforms like TikTok and Discord. The release mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>These schemes make numerous misrepresentations about the investment and its rate of return through TikTok and Discord, making it difficult to later track down these misrepresentations and the individuals involved. The investment offerings are often targeted at people who have recently lost money on investments in cryptocurrency or stocks.</p></blockquote>
<p>Once crypto funds are gone, they are extremely difficult to track down and retrieve, meaning most of the time, money that gets lost to a scam gets lost for good. Thus, the DFR is telling investors to be extremely cautious about what they choose to put their money in and to only invest funds they can afford to lose.</p>
<h2>2022 Was a Bad Year for Crypto</h2>
<p>2022 was arguably the darkest year for crypto, and while 2023 has indeed arrived, many in the space are still reeling from the problems that occurred over the previous 12 months. Aside from all the issues that arrived due to FTX and the collapse of so many other companies, the prices of the world’s leading digital currencies also took heavy hits, with bitcoin losing more than 70 percent of its value and dropping from its November 2021 all-time high of about $68,000 per unit into the $16K range.</p>
<p>It was a sad and ugly sight to see, and something that’s probably going to take a very long time to fix.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/oregon-tells-residents-to-avoid-crypto-investments/">Oregon Tells Residents to Avoid Crypto Investments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/oregon-tells-residents-to-avoid-crypto-investments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LBank Exchange Will List Weber (WBC) on January 1, 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-weber-wbc-on-january-1-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-weber-wbc-on-january-1-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 08:58:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76287</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec 30, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list Weber (WBC) on January 1, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the WBC/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading at 8:00 UTC on January 1, 2023. As a next-generation Web 3.0 integrated platform, Weber PROJECT<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-weber-wbc-on-january-1-2023/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-weber-wbc-on-january-1-2023/">LBank Exchange Will List Weber (WBC) on January 1, 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec 30, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list Weber (WBC) on January 1, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the WBC/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading at 8:00 UTC on January 1, 2023.</p>
<p>As a next-generation Web 3.0 integrated platform, Weber PROJECT provides various services based on know-how built up over the years as a blockchain specialist. Its native token <a href="https://etherscan.io/token/0x304782E7C56919299414d8848b3De14cc6D58357" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Weber</a> (WBC) will be listed on LBank Exchange at 8:00 UTC on January 1, 2023, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision.</p>
<p><strong>Introducing </strong><strong>Weber PROJECT</strong></p>
<p>Weber PROJECT aims to become a leading platform for the next-generation Web 3.0 integrated platform-based business, focusing on the know-how it has built as a company specializing in blockchain. In order to improve the problems that existing Web 3.0 platforms have to solve and to keep the important value of Web 3.0 in using the platform, it was developed to participate in the platform ecosystem by using WBC, a key token.</p>
<p>There are various services provided by Weber PROJECT, including Weberowser, Weple, Weaper, Werverage, Wearego, and more. Weberowser is a blockchain-based web browser used as the basic base of the Weber platform. Cookies accumulated during Internet use are saved as much as possible, reducing the burden of resources used on hardware devices when using the Internet and providing a fast user experience. If a user participates in the improvement of Weberowser through provision of usage information or feedback while using it, WBC token is provided as a reward accordingly.</p>
<p>Weple, a PC and mobile messaging platform that supports interaction with DApps on the Weber platform, provides an interface that is familiar to users who have difficulty thinking about existing blockchains and cryptocurrencies, and provides an interface that existing messaging platforms could not provide. It is a next-generation blockchain messaging platform that maintains growth and development and improves the point where incentives did not coexist, so that owners, advertisers, and users mutually benefit, and above all, ethical issues can be dealt with immediately.</p>
<p>Additionally, Weaper, a blockchain-based social network service, has been developed so that users can upload helpful posts through their posts, and visitors can evaluate them and receive compensation in WBC. There’s also a decentralized and distributed cloud system called Werverage that processes various contents and data of the Weber platform. It is a storage sharing system created by adding incentives to the network based on IPFS. WBC is also paid as a reward to ecosystem participants who provide surplus storage.</p>
<p>Last but not least, the Weber platform is a decentralized global blockchain Web 3.0 platform that is not only used in one country, and a tangible solution that can be used in real life, when paying for public transportation services such as buses, taxis, and subways around the world. Weber has built the Wearego system so that it can be used. Through this, wherever users go in the world, they can easily pay for fares and use public transportation through Weber&#8217;s Wearego platform, without having to prepare a separate currency exchange to use public transportation.</p>
<p>In addition to above services, Weber intends to expand its business areas such as partnerships and collaborations with various related companies and platforms in the future in order to provide other services and expand its business areas such as streaming services and games.</p>
<p><strong>About WBC Token</strong></p>
<p>WBC is the native token of Weber PROJECT. By issuing dedicated tokens for the Weber platform, the team builds a new ecosystem through its own platform to develop services and open the next-generation Web 3.0 era. Based on ERC-20, WBC has a total supply of 2 billion (i.e., 2,000,000,000) tokens, of which 10% is provided for token sale, 5% is allocated to the foundation, and the remaining 85% is provided for the ecosystem.</p>
<p>The WBC token will be listed on LBank Exchange at 8:00 UTC on January 1, 2023, investors who are interested in the Weber PROJECT investment can easily buy and sell WBC token on LBank Exchange by then. The listing of WBC token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p>
<p><strong>Learn More about</strong><strong> WBC Token:</strong></p>
<p>Official Website: <a href="http://weberproject.io" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://weberproject.io</a></p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media: </strong></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Facebook</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong></p>
<p>LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
LBank Exchange<br />
<a href="mailto:marketing@lbank.info">marketing@lbank.info</a><br />
<a href="mailto:business@lbank.info">business@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-weber-wbc-on-january-1-2023/">LBank Exchange Will List Weber (WBC) on January 1, 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-weber-wbc-on-january-1-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jim Chanos: Crypto Is Like the Dotcom Era All Over Again</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jim-chanos-crypto-is-like-the-dotcom-era-all-over-again/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jim-chanos-crypto-is-like-the-dotcom-era-all-over-again/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 17:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dotcom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jim Chanos]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75727</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Renowned short-seller Jim Chanos has stated that the current crypto environment is like the “dotcom era on steroids,” and he thinks the recent collapse of popular digital currency exchange FTX is the start of a long and negative era for digital currency. Jim Chanos: Crypto&#8217;s Future Looks Bleak Chanos predicted that Texas energy company Enron<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jim-chanos-crypto-is-like-the-dotcom-era-all-over-again/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jim-chanos-crypto-is-like-the-dotcom-era-all-over-again/">Jim Chanos: Crypto Is Like the Dotcom Era All Over Again</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Renowned short-seller Jim Chanos has stated <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/billybambrough/2022/11/23/dot-com-era-on-steroids-heres-how-bad-the-22-trillion-bitcoin-and-crypto-ftx-price-crash-could-get/?sh=1067d9615cc8" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">that the current crypto</a> environment is like the “dotcom era on steroids,” and he thinks the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">recent collapse of</a> popular digital currency exchange FTX is the start of a long and negative era for digital currency.</p>
<h2>Jim Chanos: Crypto&#8217;s Future Looks Bleak</h2>
<p>Chanos predicted that Texas energy company Enron would collapse in 2001, and he was right. How ironic that the man tasked with cleaning up the Enron mess, John Ray III, is <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/john-ray-iii-ftx-is-the-most-mismanaged-company-ive-ever-seen/" data-wpel-link="internal">now tasked with cleaning</a> up what’s left of FTX. Chanos is taking this to heart and sees the crypto space enduring a long and hard voyage following the crash of what many players thought was the industry’s golden child.</p>
<p>In a recent interview, he stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Asset prices are the staunchest defense attorney and harshest prosecutor for financial fraud. It&#8217;s only when people begin losing money that you begin to get a public outcry.</p></blockquote>
<p>In the late 90s and early 2000s, the dotcom era was in full force. With the birth of the internet arriving just years prior, many websites were being built, domains were being bought, and tech companies (several of which failed down the line) came to fruition. Anyone who invested during those years were likely seeing heavy returns, but they had no idea what was to come.</p>
<p>Not long after, the Nasdaq wound up losing close to 80 percent of its overall value given how poorly the space performed in later years. Today, the dotcom era has become a staple of economic downfall, and Chanos thinks this is the beginning of the end for crypto. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>People were losing money in the dotcom era for about a year, but it wasn&#8217;t until the Enron and WorldCom scandals hit that the federal government really geared up its efforts to look at corporate wrongdoing. This will be the same thing. People have lost a lot of money in crypto, and there&#8217;s going to be a political outcry now to regulate this system and bring people to justice.</p></blockquote>
<p>The good news is that he doesn’t think the crypto meltdown that’s likely to occur will spread to other aspects of America’s monetary system. He claimed:</p>
<blockquote><p>I don&#8217;t think this is contagion through the credit markets.</p></blockquote>
<h2>So Many Bad Things in 2022</h2>
<p>To say that 2022 was a bad year for crypto would be an understatement, and it’s not like things began with the collapse of FTX. Since the beginning of the year, bitcoin appeared set on bringing its own price down every chance it got. Despite hitting a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit prior to the start of 2022, it finished the year out trading in the $16K range. That’s a loss surpassing 70 percent.</p>
<p>Several <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-in-the-age-of-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">digital currency companies</a> – like Celsius and (of course) FTX – were also forced to file bankruptcy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jim-chanos-crypto-is-like-the-dotcom-era-all-over-again/">Jim Chanos: Crypto Is Like the Dotcom Era All Over Again</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jim-chanos-crypto-is-like-the-dotcom-era-all-over-again/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Deviants the Most Diverse and Upcoming NFT collection of 2023 Offers Discounted NFT Prices and Guaranteed Airdrop Rewards</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/deviants-the-most-diverse-and-upcoming-nft-collection-of-2023-offers-discounted-nft-prices-and-guaranteed-airdrop-rewards/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/deviants-the-most-diverse-and-upcoming-nft-collection-of-2023-offers-discounted-nft-prices-and-guaranteed-airdrop-rewards/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 16:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76281</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Users in the mint pass allowlist can purchase for only 0.06 ETH instead of 0.08 ETH Public Mint Pass price and will receive guaranteed $RVV token airdrop rewards. A maximum of 8,000 Deviants Mint Pass NFTs will be sold starting from Jan 3, 2023 1pm UTC. Are you ready for the biggest NFT collection of<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/deviants-the-most-diverse-and-upcoming-nft-collection-of-2023-offers-discounted-nft-prices-and-guaranteed-airdrop-rewards/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/deviants-the-most-diverse-and-upcoming-nft-collection-of-2023-offers-discounted-nft-prices-and-guaranteed-airdrop-rewards/">Deviants the Most Diverse and Upcoming NFT collection of 2023 Offers Discounted NFT Prices and Guaranteed Airdrop Rewards</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Users in the mint pass allowlist can purchase for only 0.06 ETH instead of 0.08 ETH Public Mint Pass price and will receive guaranteed $RVV token airdrop rewards.</li>
<li>A maximum of 8,000 Deviants Mint Pass NFTs will be sold starting from Jan 3, 2023 1pm UTC.</li>
</ul>
<p>Are you ready for the biggest NFT collection of 2023?</p>
<p>Well, the <a href="https://twitter.com/TheDeviantsNFT?s=09" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Deviants</a> from the <a href="https://twitter.com/Astra__Nova?s=09" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Astra Nova</a> MetaRPG game are dropping their <a href="https://astranovaofficial.medium.com/everything-you-need-to-know-about-deviants-mint-pass-how-you-can-get-involved-5757c4129d2c" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Deviants Mint Pass NFTs</a> in January.</p>
<p>Delve into the immersive, adventurous gameplay backed up with the most beneficial perks, web3 gaming has ever seen through the Deviants NFTs. These 10,000 fully animated VFX enabled in-game characters will open a door to the exciting interstellar journey of the Astra Nova game on <a href="https://astranovaofficial.medium.com/the-deviants-of-astra-nova-will-be-on-hedera-ethereum-let-us-explain-ee9c1eaaf3b5" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Hedera</a>.</p>
<p>These characters have 15 different species and have over 520 traits making them one of the most diverse NFT collections of all time. The Astra Nova team has spent over a year and vast resources perfecting the Deviants and they&#8217;re no joke in terms of production quality! The Deviants NFT also has its own dedicated <a href="https://astranovaofficial.medium.com/deviants-nft-roadmap-and-the-team-behind-it-862946e7c868" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Roadmap</a> and has a very detailed plan for its in-game characters.</p>
<p>Holders of the Deviants Mint Pass will be able to claim their Deviants NFT on the launch date towards the end of January. The <a href="https://astranovaofficial.medium.com/the-deviants-mint-pass-event-explained-jan-3rd-jan-20th-6b65b76aca7b" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Deviants Mint Pass Event</a> enables early users to buy into the Deviants’ collection at a discounted price and guarantees Airdrop Rewards for whitelisted users.</p>
<p>The public mint pass price of the Deviants NFT is 0.08 ETH, but Allowlisted users will be able to mint them for just 0.06 ETH. The Airdrop rewards, which is a total of 30 million $RVV or approximately $240,000 USD worth awaits the users.</p>
<p><strong>What are the Deviants?</strong></p>
<p>The game’s post-apocalyptic theme spotlights the <a href="https://astranovaofficial.medium.com/deviant-art-the-terrorizing-tikes-who-call-astra-nova-home-175519d1c003" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">original inhabitants of Astra Nova</a> – the Deviants. Players will encounter these 3D collectible characters as they step into the Astra Nova macrocosm. Each Deviant has its unique design and story, and owning one unlocks many aspects of Astra Nova’s game world, and secret quests.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Deviants are the key to unpacking the hidden history of Astra Nova. Beyond the game, Deviant NFTs offer holders early access to game development, concept art previews, and lore distribution with its own dedicated webcomic series. You can read more about their utility over <a href="https://astranovaofficial.medium.com/astra-novas-deviants-to-launch-with-extensive-utility-and-rewards-for-holders-df2c2b1b7ca6" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p><strong>How to Sign Up for the Allowlist and Airdrop?</strong></p>
<p>Users who want to qualify for the allowlist and get the guaranteed airdrop and the lowest cost for minting Deviants need to follow the required actions on this <a href="https://heymint.xyz/astranova" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">page</a>. The mint pass event lasts until January 20. Users should have a wallet for Ethereum, like Metamask,to mint the Deviants Mint Pass NFT and a Hedera-based wallet, such as <a href="https://www.bladewallet.io/astranova/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Blade Wallet</a>, to receive the Airdrop rewards.</p>
<p><strong>Deviants Mint Pass Supply Allocation</strong></p>
<p>Deviants are a collection of 10,000 NFTs. The exact launch of the Deviants NFT would be announced after the Deviants Mint Pass Event gets over.</p>
<p>There is a maximum of 8,000 Deviants Mint Pass NFTs up for grabs from Jan 3rd &#8211; Jan 20th 2023. However, only half, or 4,000, of that will go to an “allowlist,” a list of users who qualify for the token airdrop and mint pass. A total of 3,500 will be allocated to a public mint pass, letting users mint Deviants for a lower price but slightly higher than those in the allowlist at 0.08 ETH. Lastly, 500 will go to a free mint pass list, allowing users to mint Deviants for zero costs.</p>
<ul>
<li>Max Deviants Mint Pass supply: 8,000</li>
<li>Allowlist Deviants Mint Pass: 4,000</li>
<li>Public Deviants Mint Pass: 3,500</li>
<li>Free Mint Pass supply: 500</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Where to buy the Deviants Mint Pass NFT?</strong></p>
<p>Go to <a href="http://mint.deviantsnft.com" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Deviants Mint Portal</a> to mint your Deviants Mint Pass NFTs. Mint will be live from January 3rd,2023 1 pm UTC.</p>
<h4><strong>About Astra Nova</strong></h4>
<p>Astra Nova is a free-to-play Web3 MetaRPG on Hedera. It features AAA graphics and is built on Unreal Engine 5. The game stretches gaming experiences with its ever-evolving storyline, unique action adventure quests, multiplayer battle royales, stealth missions, speed runs, special quests tailored to NFTs, solo missions, customizable RPG character races, and a lot more. Astra Nova has several partners and backers, including Hedera Hashgraph, Microsoft Founder&#8217;s Hub, Nvidia inception program, Polygon DAO, BTS Ventures, Wise Crypto, Blade Wallet, GameEon, and several Indie Game Studios.</p>
<p><strong>Follow us on:</strong></p>
<p>Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/TheDeviantsNFT" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/TheDeviantsNFT</a><br />
Discord: <a href="https://discord.gg/astranova" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://discord.gg/astranova</a><br />
Medium: <a href="https://astranovaofficial.medium.com" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://astranovaofficial.medium.com</a><br />
Website: <a href="https://astranova.world/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://astranova.world/</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/deviants-the-most-diverse-and-upcoming-nft-collection-of-2023-offers-discounted-nft-prices-and-guaranteed-airdrop-rewards/">Deviants the Most Diverse and Upcoming NFT collection of 2023 Offers Discounted NFT Prices and Guaranteed Airdrop Rewards</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/deviants-the-most-diverse-and-upcoming-nft-collection-of-2023-offers-discounted-nft-prices-and-guaranteed-airdrop-rewards/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cathie Wood: BTC Will Reach $1 Million in 2030</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-btc-will-reach-1-million-in-2030/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-btc-will-reach-1-million-in-2030/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 15:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cathie Wood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75724</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cathie Wood – who’s always been the crypto bull of crypto bulls – isn’t giving up on the world’s number one digital currency by market cap. In fact, she’s reiterating her love of the coin and claiming that 2030 will be the year in which BTC reaches the long-awaited $1 million price. Cathie Wood Thinks<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-btc-will-reach-1-million-in-2030/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-btc-will-reach-1-million-in-2030/">Cathie Wood: BTC Will Reach $1 Million in 2030</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cathie Wood – who’s always been the crypto bull of crypto bulls – isn’t giving up on the world’s number one digital currency by market cap. In fact, she’s reiterating her love of the coin and claiming that 2030 will be the year in <a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/bitcoin-outlook-million-2030-crypto-cathie-wood-ark-ftx-collapse-2022-11" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">which BTC reaches</a> the long-awaited $1 million price.</p>
<h2>Cathie Wood Thinks Bitcoin Will Be Huge in Seven Years</h2>
<p>Bitcoin had a very hard year in 2022. Just a few months prior to 2022’s start, the world’s primary cryptocurrency reached a new all-time high of $68,000 per unit. This was achieved in November of 2021.</p>
<p>As soon as the new year rang in, a series of losses began. At first, bitcoin fell into the $40K range. Then, a few months later, it was at $30K. From there, it fell to $20K and before long, the currency was trading in the $15K &#8211; $16K range. This is where it ended the year, and it’s also the window that 2023 is getting its start on. There’s a lot of work to do and recovery to be had, and many are hoping the next 12 months will offer something in the form of a quick (or at least steady) fix.</p>
<p>2022 also saw the collapse of many crypto companies, some of which were alleged bad actors. FTX, the once golden player of the industry, is believed to have used customer <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/evan-luthra-a-victim-of-crypto-exchange-ftx-shares-his-story/" data-wpel-link="internal">funds to purchase luxury</a> condominiums and other items for its employees before crashing in ugly fashion. There are billions of dollars lost at the time of writing, and Wood has stated that the incident is likely to turn many institutional investors <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-ftx-has-done-harsh-damage-to-the-crypto-space/" data-wpel-link="internal">off to crypto trading</a> for good.</p>
<p>Still, she believes bitcoin and many of its altcoin cousins will recover from everything that’s happened in recent days. While things may take a while, she says there’s a good side to everything that’s happened in that it’s weeded out all the weak players, ensuring only the strong survive to keep the crypto space lasting and on sturdy legs. She commented in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Sometimes you need to battle test. You need to go through crises&#8230; to see the survivors.</p></blockquote>
<p>Wood further stated that some institutional investors could end up liking bitcoin and crypto even more if they’re willing to study the situation appropriately and do their homework regarding what happened. She mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Once they actually do the homework and see what&#8217;s happened here, I think they might actually be more comfortable moving into bitcoin, and perhaps ether, as a first stop because they&#8217;ll understand it more.</p></blockquote>
<h2>The Asset Could Still Be on Top</h2>
<p>She believes, in the long run, that bitcoin is going to come out on top following this incident, especially because inflation continues to run high, and the economy is looking weaker by the second. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We think bitcoin is coming out of this smelling like a rose.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-btc-will-reach-1-million-in-2030/">Cathie Wood: BTC Will Reach $1 Million in 2030</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-btc-will-reach-1-million-in-2030/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New York Signs Crypto Moratorium into Law</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-signs-crypto-moratorium-into-law/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-signs-crypto-moratorium-into-law/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 13:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kathy Hochul]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New York]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75722</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It’s happened, folks. We’ve always known New York wasn’t crazy about cryptocurrency, but this new law its governor has recently passed clearly takes its dislike of the industry to a whole new level. The law will limit crypto mining within the state and guarantees safe passage only to firms that utilize green energy. New York<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-signs-crypto-moratorium-into-law/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-signs-crypto-moratorium-into-law/">New York Signs Crypto Moratorium into Law</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It’s happened, folks. We’ve always known New York wasn’t crazy about cryptocurrency, but this new law its governor <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/other/new-law-requires-new-york-cryptocurrency-mining-to-use-renewable-energy/ar-AA14sXLA" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">has recently passed</a> clearly takes its dislike of the industry to a whole new level. The law will limit crypto mining within the state and guarantees safe passage only to firms that utilize green energy.</p>
<h2>New York Puts Limits on Crypto Mining</h2>
<p>The bill <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-new-york-crypto-moratorium-is-still-causing-a-big-fight/" data-wpel-link="internal">has been on the table</a> for many weeks, though New York Governor Kathy Hochul has been slow to make a clear decision on it. She’s now <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-governor-hochul-facing-real-pressure-to-sign-crypto-moratorium/" data-wpel-link="internal">facing extensive pressure</a> from legislators and eco-friendly advocates alike. Hochul has signed the bill into law, meaning the Empire State is getting off on a much stricter foot now that 2023 has been rung in.</p>
<p>In a statement, Hochul defended her signing of the bill. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I am signing this legislation into law to build on New York&#8217;s nation-leading Climate Leadership and Community Protection Act, the most aggressive climate and clean energy law in the nation, while also continuing our steadfast efforts to support economic development and job creation in upstate New York.</p></blockquote>
<p>Verbiage of the new law states the following:</p>
<blockquote><p>The continued and expanded operation of cryptocurrency mining operations running proof of work authentication methods to validate blockchain transactions will greatly increase the amount of energy usage in the state of New York and impact compliance with the Climate Leadership and Community Protection Act.</p></blockquote>
<p>The maneuver is earning a lot of criticism from crypto fans <a href="https://nypost.com/2022/11/22/kathy-hochul-signs-crypto-moratorium-bill-despite-veto-push-by-eric-adams/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">across the board including</a> New York City Mayor Eric Adams. In the past, Adams has stated that he’s very passionate about crypto and even wants it <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eric-adams-wants-crypto-taught-in-nyc-schools/" data-wpel-link="internal">taught in New York</a> City public schools. This is certainly going to get in the way of that.</p>
<p>Last June, Adams said he was going to talk to Hochul about vetoing the bill. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>I’m going to ask the governor to consider vetoing the bill that is going to get in the way of cryptocurrency upstate. When you look at the billions of dollars that are spent on cryptocurrency, New York is the leader. We can’t continue to put barriers in place.</p></blockquote>
<p>Clearly, his words meant nothing to Hochul, who took over for the disgraced Andrew Cuomo in 2021. Her signing of the bill has also garnered criticism from the Chamber of Digital Commerce, which said in a press release:</p>
<blockquote><p>The approval will set a dangerous precedent in determining who may or may not use power in New York State.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Bad Thing for the State?</h2>
<p>John Warren – CEO of bitcoin mining firm GEM Mining – also threw his two cents in, saying:</p>
<blockquote>
<p data-t="{&quot;n&quot;:&quot;blueLinks&quot;}">The regulatory environment in New York will not only halt their target (carbon-based fuel proof of work mining), but will also likely discourage new, renewable-based miners from doing business with the state due to the possibility of more regulatory creep.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-signs-crypto-moratorium-into-law/">New York Signs Crypto Moratorium into Law</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-signs-crypto-moratorium-into-law/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
