<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 03:26:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Could Rally Above $2,000</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-rally-above-2000/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-rally-above-2000/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 03:28:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79031</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum price is moving higher above the $1,880 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH price is now trading above $1,880 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $1,930 on the 4-hours chart (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could climb further if it<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-rally-above-2000/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-rally-above-2000/">Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Could Rally Above $2,000</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ethereum price is moving higher above the $1,880 resistance against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>ETH price is now trading above $1,880 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $1,930 on the 4-hours chart (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could climb further if it stays above the $1,900 support zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ethereum price is rising above the $1,880 level against the US Dollar. ETH/USD could rise further if it clears the $2,000 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Ethereum Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few sessions, Ethereum saw a decent increase above the $1,820 level against the US Dollar. ETH price was able to gain pace for a move above the $1,880 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>The bulls even pushed the price above the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-eyes-more-gains-above-1920/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">$1,920 resistance zone</a>. A high is formed near $1,976 and the price is now consolidating gains. It is trading above the $1,950 level. It is also above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward wave from the $1,823 swing low to the $1,976 high.</p>
<p>Ether’s price is showing positive signs above $1,880 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-recover-to-1900/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support near $1,930 on the 4-hours chart.</p>
<p>Immediate resistance on the upside is near the $1,975 level. The next major resistance is near the $2,000 zone. A clear move above the $2,000 level could send the price toward $2,080. Any more gains could even send the price toward the $2,200 resistance zone or $2,250 in the near term.</p>
<p>On the downside, initial support is near the $1,930 level and the trend line. The next major support is now near the $1,900 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward wave from the $1,823 swing low to the $1,976 high.</p>
<p>A break below the $1,900 support could push the price to $1,825. Any more losses could lead the price towards $1,750.</p>
<div id="attachment_79032" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79032" class="size-full wp-image-79032" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1835" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-79032" class="wp-caption-text">Ethereum Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Ethereum’s price is trading above the $1,880 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, Ether’s price could climb further if it stays above the $1,900 support zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $1,930, followed by the $1,900 zone.</p>
<p>Key Resistance$ Levels – $2,000 and $2,080.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-rally-above-2000/">Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Could Rally Above $2,000</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-rally-above-2000/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Opinion: Bitcoin Could Be a Big Topic in Next Year&#8217;s Presidential Election</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-bitcoin-could-be-a-big-topic-in-next-years-presidential-election/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-bitcoin-could-be-a-big-topic-in-next-years-presidential-election/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 17:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Opinion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OpEd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[election]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78432</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Will crypto and bitcoin be big talking points in next year’s presidential election? Everything looks like they will be, though it’s hard to say for sure. Bitcoin Could Be a Major Subject in Next Year&#8217;s White House Race For the most part, it’s not like crypto hasn’t made its way into the world of presidential<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-bitcoin-could-be-a-big-topic-in-next-years-presidential-election/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-bitcoin-could-be-a-big-topic-in-next-years-presidential-election/">Opinion: Bitcoin Could Be a Big Topic in Next Year&#8217;s Presidential Election</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Will crypto and <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">bitcoin</a> be big talking points in next year’s presidential election? Everything looks like they will be, though it’s hard to say for sure.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Could Be a Major Subject in Next Year&#8217;s White House Race</h2>
<p>For the most part, it’s not like crypto hasn’t made its way into the world of presidential politics in the past. As we all remember in 2019 and 2020, there were several democratic hopefuls that sought to enhance their campaigns with crypto promises. <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/andrew-yang-the-crypto-president/" data-wpel-link="internal">Andrew Yang</a>, for example, an entrepreneur and businessman, said one of his big plans was to make all crypto regulations easy to understand in America and rewrite them all in plain English, thus ending the many frustrations of crypto investors all over the country.</p>
<p>The same announcement came by way of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-bloomberg-proposes-clarified-bitcoin-regulation-if-he-takes-the-white-house/" data-wpel-link="internal">Michael Bloomberg</a>, the former mayor of New York City. However, neither of these men were able to arouse much attention from voters, and it wasn’t long before they opted to suspend their campaigns and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-presidential-candidate-andrew-yang-drops-out-of-race/" data-wpel-link="internal">step away from the</a> presidential game.</p>
<p>However, one can easily argue that that was a different time. Crypto didn’t have the reputation that it does now. Also, over the past several years, we have seen a man – Joe Biden – run America into the ground. He has employed economic tactics that have <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-fed-bitcoins-worst-enemy-right-now/" data-wpel-link="internal">ultimately caused the Fed</a> to fall into a compromised spot. They have regularly implemented rate hikes as a means of fighting inflation, and this caused crypto prices to fall like they never had before.</p>
<p>Biden has also sought to do everything he can to make crypto investors’ lives difficult. From a phony <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-amendment-for-infrastructure-bill-leads-to-more-problems-and-infighting/" data-wpel-link="internal">infrastructure bill</a> to an <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-biden-using-an-obama-era-program-to-ban-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">Obama-era policy</a> designed to shut crypto firms out of the standard monetary club, Biden has made a real name for himself as the most anti-crypto leader in history.</p>
<p>However, despite all this, we’ve also seen bitcoin’s “<a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/why-bitcoin-is-once-again-considered-a-safe-haven/" data-wpel-link="internal">safe haven</a>” reputation grow over the past several months as banks throughout America and Europe continue to fall. Institutions like Silicon Valley Bank, Signature Bank, and First Republic Bank <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-provide-their-thoughts-on-latest-bitcoin-rally/" data-wpel-link="internal">have all collapsed</a>, and bitcoin’s price has only shot up during the ordeals. Thus, it appears many believe bitcoin to be a solid hedge against the failures of USD and other forms of fiat.</p>
<h2>So Much Has Happened in Recent Years</h2>
<p>The circumstances have undoubtedly changed over the past three or four years, and the stage has been set for crypto to potentially be a big topic in the political spectrum next year. Its reputation has grown, there are likely more people investing in it, and thus it’s also likely that they’ve been more affected by the goings-on of 2022 and 2023.</p>
<p>Not to mention there are already several presidential candidates – from <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-candidate-robert-kennedy-jr-has-big-plans-for-the-crypto-space/" data-wpel-link="internal">Robert Kennedy Jr.</a> to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vivek-ramaswamy-is-making-crypto-a-big-part-of-his-white-house-campaign/" data-wpel-link="internal">Vivek Ramaswamy</a> – that have announced big bitcoin plans should they take the White House next year.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-bitcoin-could-be-a-big-topic-in-next-years-presidential-election/">Opinion: Bitcoin Could Be a Big Topic in Next Year&#8217;s Presidential Election</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-bitcoin-could-be-a-big-topic-in-next-years-presidential-election/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dylan LeClair: BTC Can End All Financial Corruption</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dylan-leclair-btc-can-end-all-financial-corruption/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dylan-leclair-btc-can-end-all-financial-corruption/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 15:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dylan LeClair]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[financial corruption]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78429</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dylan LeClair – the head of market research at media company BTC Inc., which reports on all things crypto and blockchain – is a maximalist that’s convinced bitcoin could potentially end all corruption and shortcomings in the standard financial industry. Dylan LeClair Thinks Highly of BTC In a recent interview, he commented: The money is<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dylan-leclair-btc-can-end-all-financial-corruption/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dylan-leclair-btc-can-end-all-financial-corruption/">Dylan LeClair: BTC Can End All Financial Corruption</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dylan LeClair – the head of market research at media company BTC Inc., which reports on all things crypto and blockchain – is a maximalist <a href="https://www.thestreet.com/cryptocurrency/news/bitcoin-2023-bitcoin-is-the-solution-to-the-corruption-of-money" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">that’s convinced bitcoin could</a> potentially end all corruption and shortcomings in the standard financial industry.</p>
<h2>Dylan LeClair Thinks Highly of BTC</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, he commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>The money is corrupt, and everything else is corrupted as a result.</p></blockquote>
<p>LeClair has a lot of points. Bitcoin and other digital currencies were designed as alternatives to standard finance, a space that has long been dominated by third parties, prying eyes, and middlemen saying what we can and cannot do with our money. They look at our job histories and other personal aspects of our lives and decide if we can gain access to specific products and services from there.</p>
<p>Bitcoin and crypto, however, don’t care about these things. So long as you have an internet connection and a digital wallet, that’s all you really need to concern yourself with. You can begin trading, investing in, selling, and buying digital assets as you see fit. The point of crypto was to give unbanked individuals or people that cannot gain access to traditional finance opportunities to garner the products and items they need for ordinary, day-to-day survival.</p>
<p>In regions <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/could-btc-revamp-the-financial-industry-of-africa/" data-wpel-link="internal">such as Africa</a>, for example, which has long been hurt by the ongoing political and financial corruption of standard banks and centralized institutions, bitcoin and crypto have long been proposed as potential solutions to these problems, so the idea of crypto working as an alternate method to standard finance is not new.</p>
<p>However, LeClair went further in his statements and mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>When you dig down to the roots of government – of the money, of how power systems and society [are] structured today – you really come to understand that the base level of this whole game is corrupted. The incentives at the base layer of society [are] corrupted in the form of corrupt money. [It] got abstracted to gold receipts, gold IOUs, gold certificates of deposits, and ultimately, that was corrupted because you had to trust someone not to mess with your gold.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also mentioned that the world of standard finance has endured tons of failures, and crypto is the perfect outlet to help those that have been affected by those failures attain monetary solutions to their ongoing issues. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>The orange pill is the fact that we have an engineering solution to fix the money, and it&#8217;s this big abstract concept that people aren&#8217;t familiar with.</p></blockquote>
<h2>So Many Banks Are Crashing!</h2>
<p>Right now, many standard <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-provide-their-thoughts-on-latest-bitcoin-rally/" data-wpel-link="internal">institutions have failed</a>. The list presently contains names such as Signature Bank, Silicon Valley Bank, and First Republic Bank.</p>
<p>As these banks have fallen, bitcoin’s price and the prices of many digital assets have shot up.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dylan-leclair-btc-can-end-all-financial-corruption/">Dylan LeClair: BTC Can End All Financial Corruption</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dylan-leclair-btc-can-end-all-financial-corruption/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Presidential Hopeful Robert Kennedy Jr. Has Big Ideas Regarding the Crypto Space</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-candidate-robert-kennedy-jr-has-big-plans-for-the-crypto-space/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-candidate-robert-kennedy-jr-has-big-plans-for-the-crypto-space/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 13:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robert Kennedy Jr.]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78426</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Just yesterday, Live Bitcoin News published an article talking about republican presidential candidate Vivek Ramaswamy and his big plans for bitcoin should he take the White House next November. Interestingly, he’s not the only presidential hopeful that’s betting big on bitcoin. Robert F. Kennedy Jr. – a democratic candidate who’s hoping to take the nomination<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-candidate-robert-kennedy-jr-has-big-plans-for-the-crypto-space/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-candidate-robert-kennedy-jr-has-big-plans-for-the-crypto-space/">Presidential Hopeful Robert Kennedy Jr. Has Big Ideas Regarding the Crypto Space</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Just yesterday, <em>Live Bitcoin News</em> published an article <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vivek-ramaswamy-is-making-crypto-a-big-part-of-his-white-house-campaign/" data-wpel-link="internal">talking about republican</a> presidential candidate Vivek Ramaswamy and his big plans for bitcoin should he take the White House next November. Interestingly, he’s not the only presidential hopeful that’s betting big on bitcoin. Robert F. Kennedy Jr. – a democratic candidate who’s hoping to take the nomination from Biden early next year – is also saying he’s going to do big things <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/presidential-candidate-robert-f-kennedy-jr-to-accept-campaign-donations-in-bitcoin-outlines-plan-for-crypto/ar-AA1bucUD" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">when it comes to cryptocurrency</a>.</p>
<h2>Robert Kennedy Is a BTC Fan, It Seems</h2>
<p>Not long ago, during the Miami Bitcoin Conference, Kennedy made an appearance and announced that his campaign is accepting bitcoin and crypto donations. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Our campaign will be the first presidential campaign in history to accept bitcoin donations through the Lightning Network, and today, we move one step closer to the future. Today, we show the world the power, durability, and flexibility of bitcoin.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also mentioned that as the president, he will ensure all Americans have the right to crypto holdings, and that the government will never do anything to get in the way of this. His comments are clear throwbacks to the nasty maneuvers Americans have witnessed over the past two years involving the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), its <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-wants-more-funds-to-go-after-crypto-companies/" data-wpel-link="internal">head Gary Gensler</a>, and the many members of the Biden administration, which have done nothing positive for crypto and instead appear dead set on making their lives hard.</p>
<p>For one thing, an infrastructure bill was implemented in the summer of 2021 – the first year of Biden’s false presidency – that was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-amendment-for-infrastructure-bill-leads-to-more-problems-and-infighting/" data-wpel-link="internal">aimed less at rebuilding</a> roads, schools, and hospitals (like the word infrastructure would imply) and more towards making crypto investors pay more come tax time starting in the year 2024.</p>
<p>In addition, Biden has implied he’s looking to instill <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-biden-using-an-obama-era-program-to-ban-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">an Obama-era policy</a> that will shut out all digital currency companies from standard finance, thus making it hard for them to garner access to bank accounts, credit cards, and other products that could help their operations float along.</p>
<p>Lastly, Biden’s faulty economic plans have caused the Fed to hike rates repeatedly, which really hurt crypto prices in 2022 and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-fed-bitcoins-worst-enemy-right-now/" data-wpel-link="internal">brought them to record lows</a>. Kennedy mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>First, I will defend the right of self-custody of bitcoin and other digital assets. You should be able to own your private keys the same as you own the keys to your car or your wallet.</p></blockquote>
<h2>No Mining Tax!</h2>
<p>He also stated complete disagreement with Biden’s plans to implement <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/biden-wants-to-tax-crypto-mining-companies-at-30/" data-wpel-link="internal">a 30 percent tax</a> on all crypto mining operations, claiming that he is an advocate for home-based crypto mining. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I don&#8217;t think the government has the right to demand access to your bitcoin key or… any of your passwords. To say otherwise is to cede essential territory to the surveillance state.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-candidate-robert-kennedy-jr-has-big-plans-for-the-crypto-space/">Presidential Hopeful Robert Kennedy Jr. Has Big Ideas Regarding the Crypto Space</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-candidate-robert-kennedy-jr-has-big-plans-for-the-crypto-space/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Could Rally Further above $0.12</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-rally-further-above-0-12/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-rally-further-above-0-12/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 05:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar Lumens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79028</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stellar lumen price is rising toward the $0.120 resistance zone against the US Dollar. XLM price is now trading above $0.10 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.100 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could start another increase<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-rally-further-above-0-12/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-rally-further-above-0-12/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Could Rally Further above $0.12</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Stellar lumen price is rising toward the $0.120 resistance zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>XLM price is now trading above $0.10 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.100 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start another increase if it clears the $0.115 and $0.120 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Stellar lumen price is trading above $0.10 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-bulls-in-control-above-29500/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. XLM price must stay above the $0.120 support to rise further.</em></p>
<h2>Stellar Lumen Price Analysis (XLM to USD)</h2>
<p>After forming a base above the $0.075 level, Stellar Lumen price started a fresh increase against the US Dollar. The XLM/USD pair broke the $0.088 resistance zone to move into a positive zone.</p>
<p>The price even cleared the $0.0950 resistance and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-extend-gains-above-0-092/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. The upward move was such that the price spike to $0.1180 before the bears appeared. A high was formed near $0.1177 and the price is now consolidating gains.</p>
<p>XLM is now trading above $0.10 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.100 on the 4-hour chart.</p>
<p>The price is also stable above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.0752 swing low to the $0.1177 high. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $0.114 zone. The next major resistance is near the $0.118 level.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $0.118 level might send the price toward the $0.120 level. Any more gains could lead the price toward the $0.1250 level or even $0.1320 in the coming sessions.</p>
<p>Initial support on the downside is near the $0.100 level and the trend line. The next major support sits near the $0.0965 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.0752 swing low to the $0.1177 high.</p>
<p>The main support is near the $0.092 zone. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.085 level in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_79029" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79029" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-79029" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM.png" alt="Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price" width="1835" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-79029" class="wp-caption-text">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XLMUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that XLM price is now trading above $0.10 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start another increase if it clears the $0.114 and $0.12 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XLM/USD is gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for XLM/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.100 and $0.0965.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.115, $0.120, and $0.132.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-rally-further-above-0-12/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Could Rally Further above $0.12</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-rally-further-above-0-12/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Price Analysis: Bulls Aim Fresh Surge To $0.52</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-aim-fresh-surge-to-0-52/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-aim-fresh-surge-to-0-52/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 04:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79025</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple price started a downside correction from the $0.5250 zone against the US dollar. The price is now trading near $0.482 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $0.472 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Kraken).<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-aim-fresh-surge-to-0-52/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-aim-fresh-surge-to-0-52/">Ripple Price Analysis: Bulls Aim Fresh Surge To $0.52</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ripple price started a downside correction from the $0.5250 zone against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading near $0.482 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $0.472 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a fresh increase above the $0.495 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ripple price is consolidating near $0.482 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-bulls-in-control-above-29500/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. XRP price must stay above the $0.470 support to start a fresh increase.</em></p>
<h2>Ripple Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, Ripple price saw a downside correction below the $0.500 support against the US Dollar. The XRP/USD pair even declined below the $0.4650 level.</p>
<p>The price traded as low as $0.4460 before the bulls appeared. The price started a fresh increase above the $0.4650 resistance zone. It cleared the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.5263 swing high to the $0.4460 low.</p>
<p>There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $0.472 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair. XRP is now trading near $0.482 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bears-aim-break-below-0-45/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near $0.485. The next major resistance is near the $0.495 level or the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.5263 swing high to the $0.4460 low. A clear move above the $0.495 resistance zone might start a strong increase.</p>
<p>In the stated case, the price could even surpass the $0.500 resistance. Any more gains might send the price toward the $0.5250 resistance.</p>
<p>Initial support on the downside is near the $0.470 level. The next major support is near the $0.465 level. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.450 level, below which the price might even test $0.440.</p>
<div id="attachment_79026" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79026" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-79026" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple.png" alt="Ripple Price" width="1835" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-79026" class="wp-caption-text">Ripple Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Ripple’s price is now trading near the $0.482 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start a fresh increase above the $0.495 resistance.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XRP/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for XRP/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.472, $0.465, and $0.450.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.495 and $0.50.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-aim-fresh-surge-to-0-52/">Ripple Price Analysis: Bulls Aim Fresh Surge To $0.52</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-aim-fresh-surge-to-0-52/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vivek Ramaswamy Is Making Crypto a Big Part of His White House Campaign</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vivek-ramaswamy-is-making-crypto-a-big-part-of-his-white-house-campaign/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vivek-ramaswamy-is-making-crypto-a-big-part-of-his-white-house-campaign/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 17:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vivek Ramaswamy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78423</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto is likely to be a big topic in next year’s presidential election, and republican candidate Vivek Ramaswamy is proof of this. Vivek Ramaswamy is Making Crypto Part of His Presidential Policy In a recent interview, Ramaswamy commented that he’s not only accepting bitcoin donations to his campaign, but he’s also looking to unveil new<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vivek-ramaswamy-is-making-crypto-a-big-part-of-his-white-house-campaign/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vivek-ramaswamy-is-making-crypto-a-big-part-of-his-white-house-campaign/">Vivek Ramaswamy Is Making Crypto a Big Part of His White House Campaign</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto is likely to be a big topic in next year’s presidential election, and republican candidate Vivek Ramaswamy is <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/gop-presidential-candidate-vivek-ramaswamy-bets-big-on-bitcoin-in-2024/ar-AA1bqgQ1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">proof of this</a>.</p>
<h2>Vivek Ramaswamy is Making Crypto Part of His Presidential Policy</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, Ramaswamy commented that he’s not only accepting bitcoin donations to his campaign, but he’s also looking to unveil new regulations that will lessen the taxation of crypto mining companies. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>The thriving bitcoin universe should actually better empower me to do what I want to do as the U.S. president, which is to stabilize the U.S. dollar as a unit of measurement and put the Federal Reserve back in its place with that as its single mandate.</p></blockquote>
<p>His comments come after Joe Biden <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/biden-wants-to-tax-crypto-mining-companies-at-30/" data-wpel-link="internal">commented that he was looking</a> to implement a 30 percent tax rate on all crypto mining companies as a means of limiting their energy usage and promoting positive climate change tactics.</p>
<p>Not long ago, President Donald Trump unveiled a string of new <a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/business-63995563" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">non-fungible tokens</a> (NFTs) and made more than $1 million in profit through the sale of said digital assets. Ramaswamy has commented that he’s not looking to unveil new NFTs of his own anytime soon. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Right now, I&#8217;m more focused on policy. It also just gives people the choice to donate to the campaign in bitcoin and signal that we&#8217;re not threatened by it.</p></blockquote>
<p>More than anything, he wants crypto miners to be able to perform their duties freely in America. He doesn’t want the United States to become <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-crypto-mining-clampdown-in-china-is-not-over/" data-wpel-link="internal">the next China</a>, which ultimately made all crypto activity illegal about two years back. Regarding Biden’s mining taxation plans, Ramaswamy said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think that it&#8217;s wrong and unfair and is not an appropriate use of federal power.</p></blockquote>
<p>He stated that he feels the taxation will ultimately limit innovation and prevent entrepreneurship from thriving in the digital currency arena. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>We&#8217;ll put that into the rules and preserve freedom to mine by rescinding and committing against any special taxes for the utilization of energy for purposes of mining.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Will Bitcoin Be a Payment Tool in the U.S.?</h2>
<p>He was also quick to mention that the U.S. dollar has been severely crippled under Biden and that assets like bitcoin could eventually become valid alternative payment methods in the U.S. should the dollar continue to thin and weaken. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The insecurities that the defenders of fiat money have with respect to the rise of bitcoin is similar to the insecurities that I see amongst public schools and the teachers’ unions and the administrators of public schools with respect to school choice. I will be the opposite of what public schools are to school choice.</p></blockquote>
<p>Right now, the U.S. has taken a very anti-crypto attitude given regulators like Gary Gensler – head of the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) – are <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-wants-more-funds-to-go-after-crypto-companies/" data-wpel-link="internal">working to persecute</a> every crypto company they come across.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vivek-ramaswamy-is-making-crypto-a-big-part-of-his-white-house-campaign/">Vivek Ramaswamy Is Making Crypto a Big Part of His White House Campaign</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vivek-ramaswamy-is-making-crypto-a-big-part-of-his-white-house-campaign/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Woman Named Sarita Discovered Her Husband&#8217;s Crypto Holdings Following Their Divorce</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/a-woman-named-sarita-discovered-her-husbands-crypto-holdings-following-their-divorce/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/a-woman-named-sarita-discovered-her-husbands-crypto-holdings-following-their-divorce/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 15:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[divorce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sarita]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78420</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A woman named Sarita divorced her husband a few years back. Nothing seemed odd at first; people get divorced all the time. However, when her husband (who makes $3 million per year) declared no assets, she became suspicious. Sarita Discovers Her Ex-Spouse&#8217;s Hidden Crypto Stash Following a year of discovery, Sarita found out that her<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/a-woman-named-sarita-discovered-her-husbands-crypto-holdings-following-their-divorce/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/a-woman-named-sarita-discovered-her-husbands-crypto-holdings-following-their-divorce/">A Woman Named Sarita Discovered Her Husband&#8217;s Crypto Holdings Following Their Divorce</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A woman named Sarita divorced her husband a few years back. Nothing seemed odd at first; people get divorced all the time. However, <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/a-husband-hid-500000-in-bitcoin-during-a-divorce-and-got-busted-by-a-crypto-hunter/ar-AA1btUrt" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">when her husband</a> (who makes $3 million per year) declared no assets, she became suspicious.</p>
<h2>Sarita Discovers Her Ex-Spouse&#8217;s Hidden Crypto Stash</h2>
<p>Following a year of discovery, Sarita found out that her husband had at least half a million in assorted <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">crypto</a> funds to his name and didn’t declare them in the divorce proceedings. By not reporting them, he figured he could get away with smaller alimony payments or something along those lines, but it appears this deception has now worked against him.</p>
<p>Sarita – which is an alias for the woman – says she was married to her husband for over a decade. She said she was quite shocked when she found out about her ex’s digital holdings, mentioning in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>I know of bitcoin and things like that. I just didn’t know much about it. It was never even a thought in my mind because it’s not like we were discussing it or making investments together&#8230; It was a shock.</p></blockquote>
<p>Many divorce attorneys say crypto holdings are often difficult to locate or realize during separation proceedings in that many of the laws have not kept up with the digital assets arena. Thus, one can easily hide said assets during a divorce and get away with it, granted their former spouse or their lawyer aren’t privy to the way things work.</p>
<p>Kim Nutter says she was one of the first lawyers in her native state of Florida to begin exploring crypto practices in 2015. She commented that she’s worked hard to ensure all sides of the divorce table are required to relay their digital holdings during separation proceedings. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I still think the law is trying to catch up with this novel form of currency, even though it’s been around for quite a while. What I find in litigation is because this is so new to all of us, even the most seasoned attorneys, unless you’re really going out of your way to study this, educating the court, knowing what to ask for, and finding the right experts, it’s much more of a scramble to me than other areas of law which had been around much longer.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Lot of Crypto in Divorce Proceedings, Now</h2>
<p>Divorce attorney Kelly Burris also threw her two cents in, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>If you have a spouse that’s very tech savvy and one that isn’t, it can be somewhat easy to hide those assets. The thing with cryptocurrency is it’s not regulated by any kind of centralized bank, so usually you can’t subpoena somebody and get documents and information related to somebody’s cryptocurrency holdings.</p></blockquote>
<p>She says that 40 to 50 percent of her divorce cases now involve crypto.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/a-woman-named-sarita-discovered-her-husbands-crypto-holdings-following-their-divorce/">A Woman Named Sarita Discovered Her Husband&#8217;s Crypto Holdings Following Their Divorce</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/a-woman-named-sarita-discovered-her-husbands-crypto-holdings-following-their-divorce/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Company Strike is Relocating to El Salvador</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-company-strike-is-relocating-to-el-salvador/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-company-strike-is-relocating-to-el-salvador/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 13:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[El Salvador]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Strike]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78418</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin payments company Strike has anticipated that it will grow across 65 countries in the coming years and expand its list of clients to roughly three billion souls. Strike Wants a Change of Scenery Jack Mallers – CEO of the Chicago-based company – explained in a recent interview: We think there are billions of people<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-company-strike-is-relocating-to-el-salvador/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-company-strike-is-relocating-to-el-salvador/">Bitcoin Company Strike is Relocating to El Salvador</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin payments company Strike has <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/05/21/whos-laughing-now-bitcoin-price-braced-for-3-billion-user-shock-as-strike-ceo-slams-coinbase-ethereum-bnb-xrp-cardano-dogecoin-polygon-and-solana/?sh=3e5f3bcbe501" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">anticipated that it will grow</a> across 65 countries in the coming years and expand its list of clients to roughly three billion souls.</p>
<h2>Strike Wants a Change of Scenery</h2>
<p>Jack Mallers – CEO of the Chicago-based company – explained in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>We think there are billions of people that want a money app with those characteristics and capabilities contrasted to a clouded world of crypto exchanges and hidden, unregistered licensing regimes and 1,000 different coins.</p></blockquote>
<p>Strike says it’s also going to be moving its headquarters to El Salvador, the Central American nation that has proven very bitcoin friendly over the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-fully-legal-in-el-salvador-beginning-september-7/" data-wpel-link="internal">past two years given</a> it was the first to label the world’s largest digital currency as legal tender. This means that many companies are now required to accept it as a method of payment alongside USD, which the country has long depended on.</p>
<p>Mallers continued with:</p>
<blockquote><p>Two years ago, people would have made fun of me [for our] headquarters in El Salvador to launch a product for three billion people, but now Coinbase is fighting with [Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) chair] Gary Gensler. Who’s laughing now?</p></blockquote>
<p>He is, of course, referring to a situation in which a Wells notice <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">was sent to Coinbase</a>, America’s leading digital currency exchange, citing potential securities violations that the company would be tried for. The company took serious issue with the notice given, according to executive statements, it had met with representatives of the SEC several times over a nine-year period to ensure compliance. Mallers said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think bitcoin stands alone [in] just how obvious it is that it is owned by nobody. Every other instrument in this industry has a founding team, a foundation, and they issued some [tokens] privately and handed them out in auctions before they went live, and that sounds a lot more like a security.</p></blockquote>
<p>Mallers also mentioned that his company chose USDT (Tether) over Circle and Coinbase’s USDC stable currency given that he feels people outside of the United States don’t really “trust” the former company. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>If I’m being totally honest, Circle is built for American institutions.</p></blockquote>
<p>While Circle may not be appreciated outside of American institutions, Tether has raised quite a bit of controversy over the years and is <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stable-coin-tether-buys-over-200-million-worth-of-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">continuing to do so with</a> its recent announcement that it’s purchased loads of BTC.</p>
<h2>Trying to Make the App Better</h2>
<p>Maneula Rios – the vice president of product with Strike – said the company is also focusing on making its app more user friendly. Rios said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Our end goal is to address the seven to eight billion people in every single country. If you are in the United States, the apps are gorgeous. There&#8217;s a high bar for design. Unfortunately, that&#8217;s not the case when you download apps abroad.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-company-strike-is-relocating-to-el-salvador/">Bitcoin Company Strike is Relocating to El Salvador</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-company-strike-is-relocating-to-el-salvador/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=3965 metric#misses=5 metric#hit-ratio=99.9 metric#bytes=6630483 metric#prefetches=398 metric#store-reads=16 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=403 metric#store-misses=0 metric#sql-queries=17 metric#ms-total=225.69 metric#ms-cache=13.75 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.8086 metric#ms-cache-ratio=6.1 -->
