<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 08:20:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Source Hut Ends All Crypto Project Permissions</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/source-hut-ends-all-crypto-project-permissions/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/source-hut-ends-all-crypto-project-permissions/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 17:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drew DeVault]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illicit Activity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Source]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75412</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Source Hut – an open-source repository – has stated it’s not going to permit any more projects that delve into the digital currency or blockchain arenas. The idea is that these assets and the technology behind them are too often used for fraudulent means, and the platform doesn’t want its software, its name, or reputation tarnished should<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/source-hut-ends-all-crypto-project-permissions/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/source-hut-ends-all-crypto-project-permissions/">Source Hut Ends All Crypto Project Permissions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Source Hut – an open-source repository – has stated <a href="https://www.techrepublic.com/article/open-source-repository-sourcehut-removes-all-cryptocurrency-projects/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.techrepublic.com/article/open-source-repository-sourcehut-removes-all-cryptocurrency-projects/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668540094973000&amp;usg=AOvVaw1iYq0UqNOKPNh3ITeHs6gQ" data-wpel-link="external">it’s not going to permit</a> any more projects that delve into the digital currency or blockchain arenas. The idea is that these assets and the technology behind them are too often used for fraudulent means, and the platform doesn’t want its software, its name, or reputation tarnished should illicit actors decide to utilize its services.</p>
<h2>Source Hut Is Doing Away with Crypto Permissions</h2>
<p>The decision was made by founder and creator Drew DeVault. In an interview, he commented that digital currencies are often featured in “get rich quick” schemes, which he believes bring down both the financial and technology sectors equally. He says digital currencies have been utilized to take advantage of ill-educated people during times of economic strife and that they’ve ultimately been persuaded to invest in projects and assets that haven’t served them well.</p>
<p>He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Few to no legitimate use cases for this technology have been found. Instead, it is mostly used for fraudulent ‘get-rich-quick’ schemes and to facilitate criminal activity such as ransomware, illicit trade, and sanctions evasion. These projects often encourage large-scale energy waste and electronics waste, which contributes to the declining health of Earth’s environment. The presence of these projects on Source Hut exposes new victims to these scams and is harmful to the reputation of Source Hut and its community.</p></blockquote>
<p>To an extent, even the most experienced traders can see where DeVault is coming from. Since crypto first exploded onto the scene in late 2008, the space has been marred with problems involving thieves and illicit players. Many have created scams and false investing opportunities as a means of taking advantage of those who simply don’t know better.</p>
<p>2022 – 14 years later – has shown this in full fashion with the amount of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/romance-scam/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/romance-scam/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668540094973000&amp;usg=AOvVaw3_wUIi88tiKh_nvNh-9-ht" data-wpel-link="internal">romance scams</a> and similar situations occurring on a regular basis. Many of these scams operate via the same protocols. Someone gets a potential victim to invest their money into a crypto platform. From there, they see their money grow and grow and they begin to get excited, thinking they’re going to be rich overnight.</p>
<h2>Too Much Illicit Activity?</h2>
<p>Once they try to make a withdrawal, however, the site is either inaccessible or they are asked to invest more. In any case, they never get access to the funds and ultimately lose out on the money they first invested given it’s in an account controlled by illicit actors.</p>
<p>At the same time, this is just one angle of a growing industry that has also seen a lot of good. The crypto space was initially designed to give players full financial independence and autonomy. They are free from prying eyes, third parties, and middlemen that have a say in what they can and can’t do with the money they’ve earned.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/source-hut-ends-all-crypto-project-permissions/">Source Hut Ends All Crypto Project Permissions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/source-hut-ends-all-crypto-project-permissions/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jebara Igbara Guilty of Crypto Fraud Scheme</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jebara-igbara-guilty-of-crypto-fraud-scheme/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jebara-igbara-guilty-of-crypto-fraud-scheme/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 15:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[instagram]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jebara Igbara]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ponzi scheme]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75408</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Instagram celebrity Jebara Igbara has pled guilty to running a multimillion-dollar Ponzi scheme involving bitcoin. Jebara Igbara Guilty of Crypto Ponzi Scheme Igbara – who has amassed several million followers on social media – entered a guilty plea for his alleged crimes and could be sentenced to as many as ten full years in a federal prison. Often<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jebara-igbara-guilty-of-crypto-fraud-scheme/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jebara-igbara-guilty-of-crypto-fraud-scheme/">Jebara Igbara Guilty of Crypto Fraud Scheme</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="adn ads" data-message-id="#msg-a:r-64883070781358036" data-legacy-message-id="1843e8007887bae1">
<div class="gs">
<div class="">
<div id=":n3" class="ii gt">
<div id=":mk" class="a3s aiL ">
<div dir="ltr">
<p>Instagram celebrity Jebara Igbara has pled guilty to <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/instagram-personality-e2-80-98jay-mazini-e2-80-99-pleads-guilty-to-bitcoin-scam-and-ponzi-scheme/ar-AA13Fnbu" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/instagram-personality-e2-80-98jay-mazini-e2-80-99-pleads-guilty-to-bitcoin-scam-and-ponzi-scheme/ar-AA13Fnbu&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537723870000&amp;usg=AOvVaw3_I9_kk-O_vprOb_sc11If" data-wpel-link="external">running a multimillion-dollar</a> Ponzi scheme involving <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitcoin/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537723870000&amp;usg=AOvVaw3soNu348_PWkOxqw51p_j2" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>.</p>
<h2>Jebara Igbara Guilty of Crypto Ponzi Scheme</h2>
<p>Igbara – who has amassed several million followers on social media – entered a guilty plea for his alleged crimes and could be sentenced to as many as ten full years in a federal prison. Often going by the name Jay Mazini, Igbara is 27 years of age and has built a reputation for being a generous person. His social pages often feature videos of him passing out cash to people at grocery stores, airports, fast-food joints, and other public venues likely to attract tons of people.</p>
<p>Court documents claim:</p>
<blockquote><p>By posting such videos, Igbara created a public persona of himself as a person of substantial means.</p></blockquote>
<p>Now, however, it’s questionable how all this money was obtained as Igbara’s company Halal Capital is alleged to have taken part in a crypto scam between the years 2019 and 2021. Prosecutors claim the defendant had taken investors’ funds on the promise of investing them accordingly into appropriate crypto outlets, though it appears this never occurred.</p>
<p>In early 2021, Igbara put out a promotion saying he would pay top dollar for a single bitcoin. At the time, the world’s number one digital currency was trading in the high $40K range. While he did receive bitcoins from various followers, he never sent them any money, and instead engaged in phony wire transfers and other illicit activity to make off with their crypto assets.</p>
<p>In a statement, Igbara commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>While I did receive bitcoin, I did not pay for it.</p></blockquote>
<p>One seller alleges that he was in a deal with Igbara to earn more than $2.5 million for as many as 50 individual bitcoin units. Sadly, the seller never received more than $500K.</p>
<p>In a classic Ponzi scheme move, Igbara took some of the money he received down the line to pay off early investors, thus using money from point B to pay those who were at point A. He continued his statement with:</p>
<blockquote><p>Unfortunately, I’m a human being at the end of the day. I have a conscience, so regarding the Halal Capital scheme, I was taking the funds and paying off. It was just from A to B.</p></blockquote>
<p>At press time, he has pled guilty to several charges including wire fraud, wire fraud conspiracy, and money laundering. He is likely to face anywhere between eight and ten years in jail, though his crimes often carry sentences exceeding 20 years.</p>
<h2>Paying Everyone Back</h2>
<p>He has also agreed to part with as much as $10 million in personal property as a means of paying back those he conned. The judge overseeing the case said to him:</p>
<blockquote><p>You’ll be required to pay the full amount of each victim’s losses.</p></blockquote>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jebara-igbara-guilty-of-crypto-fraud-scheme/">Jebara Igbara Guilty of Crypto Fraud Scheme</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jebara-igbara-guilty-of-crypto-fraud-scheme/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Jersey Unveils New String of Crypto Regulations</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-jersey-unveils-new-string-of-crypto-regulations/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-jersey-unveils-new-string-of-crypto-regulations/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 13:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BitLicense]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto-regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New Jersey]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75410</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New Jersey wants to turn itself into the most crypto friendly region in America. That’s why it’s introducing the “Digital Assets and Blockchain Regulation” Act, which will permit decentralized autonomous organizations (DAOs) to establish themselves within the state’s borders and issue stock certificates and create tax incentives for digital currency firms. New Jersey Is Establishing New Digital<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-jersey-unveils-new-string-of-crypto-regulations/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-jersey-unveils-new-string-of-crypto-regulations/">New Jersey Unveils New String of Crypto Regulations</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New Jersey <a href="https://whyy.org/articles/new-jersey-legislature-industry-friendly-cryptocurrency-rules/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://whyy.org/articles/new-jersey-legislature-industry-friendly-cryptocurrency-rules/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537723441000&amp;usg=AOvVaw06SQEWXyOZOtmCMeX4Qz8o" data-wpel-link="external">wants to turn itself into the most</a> crypto friendly region in America. That’s why it’s introducing the “Digital Assets and Blockchain Regulation” Act, which will permit decentralized autonomous organizations (DAOs) to establish themselves within the state’s borders and issue stock certificates and create tax incentives for digital currency firms.</p>
<h2>New Jersey Is Establishing New Digital Currency Laws</h2>
<p>New Jersey has been up and down in its relationship with digital assets. While some of the regulations it’s passed for the industry have been relatively positive (some exist as a means of boosting blockchain integration), others legislative maneuvers have prevented politicians or political candidates from accepting digital currencies or non-fungible tokens (NFTs) as donations or gifts.</p>
<p>With this new Digital Assets and Blockchain Regulation Act, New Jersey wants to cement itself as the ultimate haven virtual currency businesses can really get along in. The new bill was sponsored by republican senator Robert Singer, who claimed that this would make the state more business friendly in the growing world of digital assets. He said he would like New Jersey to be the exact opposite of New York, which he stated has been “very restrictive” in terms of crypto innovation.</p>
<p>In a recent interview, he stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>We want to be more industry friendly. I don’t want to be restrictive. I want to be open-minded, but I also want to do protection of the consumer.</p></blockquote>
<p>His ideas regarding New York are on point. The Empire State has been one of the most hostile states towards bitcoin and the digital asset arena beginning with its <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitlicense/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitlicense/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537723441000&amp;usg=AOvVaw3wSoNW-JaSdyD12fk67h7d" data-wpel-link="internal">BitLicense</a> requirements which started in the year 2015. Many virtual currency companies have either been forced to leave New York or restrict their activity within the state given how tough the regulations and fees invoked by the BitLicense are known to be.</p>
<p>In addition, the state assembly recently <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-governor-hochul-facing-real-pressure-to-sign-crypto-moratorium/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-governor-hochul-facing-real-pressure-to-sign-crypto-moratorium/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537723441000&amp;usg=AOvVaw1s7ekf8kVLHAR7fNH029pS" data-wpel-link="internal">passed a mining moratorium</a> that would ban all new crypto mining businesses from setting up shop within New York’s borders.</p>
<p>Singer further stated that while the bill is not perfect, it’s in a good position and will provide a solid learning experience for New Jersey lawmakers. He says they can learn as things go along, and he’s looking forward to implementing positive changes. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Like any new idea, there are certainly some pitfalls to it, but I think in general, there is a whole group of people out there that want to know that they can invest their money without Uncle Sam always looking over their shoulder.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Keeping Things in Check</h2>
<p>The Office of Legislative Services (OLS) has also put out the following statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>The industry is not yet fully established, and OLS cannot know the extent of the administrative workload that will be placed on the departments resulting from the provisions of the bill.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-jersey-unveils-new-string-of-crypto-regulations/">New Jersey Unveils New String of Crypto Regulations</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-jersey-unveils-new-string-of-crypto-regulations/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The White House Thinks BTC Has Just Boosted Crime</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-white-house-thinks-btc-has-just-boosted-crime/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-white-house-thinks-btc-has-just-boosted-crime/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 17:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[white house]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75406</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>According to White House officials, bitcoin – though it has its benefits – has increased ransomware cases across the country. The White House Isn&#8217;t Confident in BTC A White House spokesperson (who remains anonymous) recently commented in an interview: When bitcoin became more widely used, we saw a huge jump in ransomware because it was a way<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-white-house-thinks-btc-has-just-boosted-crime/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-white-house-thinks-btc-has-just-boosted-crime/">The White House Thinks BTC Has Just Boosted Crime</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to White House officials, bitcoin – <a href="https://venturebeat.com/security/the-surprising-relationship-between-bitcoin-and-ransomware-is-investigated-in-white-house-summit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://venturebeat.com/security/the-surprising-relationship-between-bitcoin-and-ransomware-is-investigated-in-white-house-summit/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537724428000&amp;usg=AOvVaw1gU-DTOvCx2jldsP-Vp96W" data-wpel-link="exclude">though it has its benefits</a> – has increased ransomware cases across the country.</p>
<h2>The White House Isn&#8217;t Confident in BTC</h2>
<p>A White House spokesperson (who remains anonymous) recently commented in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>When bitcoin became more widely used, we saw a huge jump in ransomware because it was a way to move money across borders. It’s a borderless threat, and we [need] to tackle it in a borderless way. The threat has clearly evolved.</p></blockquote>
<p>The government house is now coordinating with approximately 36 countries at the time of writing to establish a new bitcoin ransomware-fighting program that will ensure issues like this become a thing of the past. The spokesperson said:</p>
<blockquote><p>As we know, ransomware is an issue that knows no borders and affects each of the Counter Ransomware Initiative countries — our businesses, our critical infrastructure, and our citizens — and it’s only getting more challenging.</p></blockquote>
<p>Crypto has been at the forefront of American politics over the past several months. Things began in such a manner when Biden issued a new crypto <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-is-the-biden-crypto-executive-order-all-its-cracked-up-to-be/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-is-the-biden-crypto-executive-order-all-its-cracked-up-to-be/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537724428000&amp;usg=AOvVaw0R5tI8X1-9rj3v2Iv6TdaF" data-wpel-link="internal">executive order requiring</a> all financial agencies in the nation to explore digital currencies to better understand their benefits and disadvantages. The order also opened the door to a digital dollar. The Treasury has been <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-treasury-wants-to-regulate-crypto-and-fast/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-treasury-wants-to-regulate-crypto-and-fast/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537724428000&amp;usg=AOvVaw3G2o9kwMEvgbDYJn6wWYgM" data-wpel-link="internal">researching crypto hard</a> since then, though no official reports about what the White House is planning to do beyond this point have been issued.</p>
<p>The organization involving the 36 nations has come to be known as the Counter Ransomware Initiative (CRI), and it was formed during a virtual global summit designed to halt ransomware permanently. The group will also work with as many as 13 businesses in the private sector to see what information they can pass along about how to fight the growing threat.</p>
<p>The White House spokesperson said:</p>
<blockquote><p>This is just a first round of getting companies’ perspectives to ensure that we’re not doing this the traditional government way, which is government-to-government only. We’re pulling in the private sector because of their unique visibility, capability, and insights into it.</p></blockquote>
<p>Erich Kron – a security awareness advocate at KnowBe4 – offered his two cents, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>Ransomware has become a serious issue on a global scale, so it is no surprise that so many nations continue to band together to deal with the threat… The urgency to find a solution for the problem is only heightened.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Trying to Push Back</h2>
<p>Jeff Williams – co-founder and CTO of Contrast Security – mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Additionally, we must push back on the industry when it attempts to obfuscate visibility into weak security practices and technologies with claims that it will compromise intellectual property (it won’t) or make it easier for attackers (it doesn’t). We need far more insight into how the software we trust with the most important things in our lives has been secured.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-white-house-thinks-btc-has-just-boosted-crime/">The White House Thinks BTC Has Just Boosted Crime</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-white-house-thinks-btc-has-just-boosted-crime/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tim Draper Thinks Women Will Really Help BTC</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tim-draper-thinks-women-will-save-btc/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tim-draper-thinks-women-will-save-btc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 15:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tim Draper]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[women]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75403</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What will bring bitcoin back from the brink of disaster? According to famed venture capitalist and digital currency enthusiast Tim Draper, the answer is women. Tim Draper: Women Are the Answer The crypto space has been doing very poorly as of late. The industry has fallen by more than $2 trillion in valuation and some of the largest,<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tim-draper-thinks-women-will-save-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tim-draper-thinks-women-will-save-btc/">Tim Draper Thinks Women Will Really Help BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What will bring <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitcoin/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537724433000&amp;usg=AOvVaw39s3RElKOkJmQnYTjZO7ga" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a> back from the brink of disaster? According to famed venture capitalist and digital currency enthusiast Tim Draper, <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/johnkoetsier/2022/11/03/women-will-save-bitcoin-chatting-with-bitcoin-maximalist-tim-draper/?sh=306f25401183" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.forbes.com/sites/johnkoetsier/2022/11/03/women-will-save-bitcoin-chatting-with-bitcoin-maximalist-tim-draper/?sh%3D306f25401183&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537724433000&amp;usg=AOvVaw3dfaaXD53V6u_uKQmDNqMw" data-wpel-link="exclude">the answer is women</a>.</p>
<h2>Tim Draper: Women Are the Answer</h2>
<p>The crypto space has been doing very poorly as of late. The industry has fallen by more than $2 trillion in valuation and some of the largest, mainstream digital assets – including bitcoin – are down by 70 percent or more from their 2021 November highs. It’s an ugly sight to see, and many analysts are conflicted about when bitcoin and its altcoin cousins could come back.</p>
<p>Draper said the space has long been dominated by men, though he’s confident more women will be getting involved in crypto. He says they could be the ones that ultimately save the industry from crashing and burning completely. He stated in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Long-term, it’s going to be all about the women. Women control 80 percent of retail spending, and they are only one of six bitcoin wallets.</p></blockquote>
<p>He’s also confident people who engage in HODLing – those who hold on for dear life and don’t sell their crypto assets at any cost – will have their faith in BTC rewarded and that the space is going to come back like never before. Draper mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>The HODLers, the passionate people realizing bitcoin is an anthropological leap forward, they’re the ones who are buying now and hanging in there.</p></blockquote>
<p>He commented also that one of the big reasons crypto dropped so badly was spectators bought into the arena and ultimately sold BTC and other digital assets the same days that they sold their tech stocks. Draper believes women and retailers will eventually bring the arena back, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>Once the retailers realize that they can save two percent by accepting bitcoin, and once women realize they get their food, their clothing, and their shelter all in bitcoin, they’re not going to want government coins. They’re going to want bitcoin; they’re going to want something that is decentralized, open, transparent, [and] global&#8230; They’re going to want a currency that is just better, that will go up in value&#8230; versus one that you [need] to get rid of.</p></blockquote>
<p>Draper also commented that many of the people who are HODLing crypto at this time happen to be women. Instead of purchasing groceries or a new pair of shoes, they are instead buying bitcoin and other digital assets to diversify their portfolios and manage their wealth.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Can Fight Inflation</h2>
<p>Completing his discussion, he’s also sure that the inflation we’re dealing with right now will propel bitcoin to new heights. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin will start being recognized as an inflation hedge. I remember my dad giving me $1,000,000 confederate dollars. I said, ‘How much is this worth?’ and he started laughing&#8230; ‘It’s not worth anything.’</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tim-draper-thinks-women-will-save-btc/">Tim Draper Thinks Women Will Really Help BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tim-draper-thinks-women-will-save-btc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitstamp Is Bringing Its Services to Luxembourg</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitstamp-is-bringing-its-services-to-luxembourg/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitstamp-is-bringing-its-services-to-luxembourg/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 13:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitstamp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[luxembourg]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75400</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitstamp is the oldest digital currency exchange in the world. Not long ago, it announced it’s set to begin doing business in the European nation of Luxembourg, and it will soon offer its services to crypto traders in that region. Bitstamp Is Cementing Itself in Luxembourg Jean-Baptiste Graftieaux – CEO of Bitstamp – said in an interview: We<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitstamp-is-bringing-its-services-to-luxembourg/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitstamp-is-bringing-its-services-to-luxembourg/">Bitstamp Is Bringing Its Services to Luxembourg</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitstamp is the oldest digital currency exchange in the world. Not long ago, it announced it’s set to begin doing business in the <a href="https://www.computerweekly.com/feature/The-worlds-oldest-cryptocurrency-exchange-prefers-doing-business-in-Luxembourg" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.computerweekly.com/feature/The-worlds-oldest-cryptocurrency-exchange-prefers-doing-business-in-Luxembourg&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537718428000&amp;usg=AOvVaw3I-QeUNxcV8IJ7pTyzQalr" data-wpel-link="external">European nation of Luxembourg</a>, and it will soon offer its services to crypto traders in that region.</p>
<h2>Bitstamp Is Cementing Itself in Luxembourg</h2>
<p>Jean-Baptiste Graftieaux – CEO of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitstamp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitstamp/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537718428000&amp;usg=AOvVaw2eTE857d-VvCrqGv89BWMA" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitstamp</a> – said in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>We have a combination of engineers and product people who understand crypto or fintech. We also have experts in information security area and data protection. These are important for us to be best in class in terms of technology and cyber security. We also need strong customer support people. We have real human beings in our customer support instead of bots because customers want to work with real people.</p></blockquote>
<p>When talking about why his company decided to settle on Luxembourg, the CEO mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>When we looked around the European region for places to do business, the only country with the appetite to endorse this innovation was Luxembourg. It was still considered early days for cryptocurrencies, and there was virtually no regulatory framework. This meant that any company that wanted to become an established exchange had to go to each of the countries where it wanted to operate and help the government define regulations and licensing. Luxembourg is a small country, but very international and connected. It’s a good place to do business and engage with the local authorities in the sense that everyone knows each other. We worked closely with the government on how to regulate Bitstamp and to figure out what kind of license was required. In the end, we became authorized as a payment institution in Luxembourg.</p></blockquote>
<p>The firm has endured quite a bit of trouble surrounding its licensing procedures. Graftieaux also discussed that, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>Regulations and licensing are important to our business because they boost our credibility in the market. We’re looking forward to the day when it’s easier to get licensed in countries around the world.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Making Sure All Is Correct</h2>
<p>He also said that the company has worked harder to ensure audits go accordingly and that any fraudulent activity is picked up on. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>You can look at a transaction, but you don’t see all the underlying data on the sender and recipient. What you see is that there has been a transaction of one or more bitcoins from one wallet to another or from one address to another, but what you don’t know today is the owner of the wallet or address. Nevertheless, with this address, what’s happening very regularly is that if there is a fraud or an offence committed with a bitcoin address, the law enforcement agencies will reach out to the different crypto players to see if they have clients associated to that specific address, and if so, to share that information.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitstamp-is-bringing-its-services-to-luxembourg/">Bitstamp Is Bringing Its Services to Luxembourg</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitstamp-is-bringing-its-services-to-luxembourg/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SILK Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/silk-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/silk-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 08:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75947</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec. 9, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed SILK on December 9, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the SILK/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading. As the first web3 esports with earnings, Spider Tanks enables players to earn for their play through<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/silk-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/silk-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">SILK Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec. 9, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed SILK on December 9, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the SILK/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading.</p>
<p>As the first web3 esports with earnings, Spider Tanks enables players to earn for their play through its complex and brilliantly designed reward economy. Its native token <a href="https://etherscan.io/token/0xb045f7f363fe4949954811b113bd56d208c67b23" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">SILK</a> has been listed on LBank Exchange at 13:00 UTC on December 9, 2022, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision.</p>
<p><strong>Introducing </strong><strong>Spider Tanks</strong></p>
<p>Spider Tanks is a blockchain-based PVP brawler created by award-winning Netherlands based GAMEDIA and brought to players by Gala Games. Players choose between a number of Tank Bodies and Weapons in the garage, then battle it out in one of the many Spider Tanks arena maps. And since all tank parts are owned as NFTs, they can be upgraded, then sold on the secondary market at any time the player chooses.</p>
<p>Different game modes of Spider Tanks present different strategic and team-based challenges to always keep gameplay fresh. TEAM DEATHMATCH is an all-out brawl style match where the team with the most kills gets the victory. Players need to create killer destructive combinations with their teams, and let the chaos ensure. CAPTURE THE CHICKEN is a mode where player’s team&#8217;s goal is to capture as many moving chickens as possible and become a Spider Tanks chicken master. And in CAPTURE THE FLAG, the team who holds the only one flag in their possession the longest will be victorious in the match.</p>
<p>Spider Tanks is free to play, but also incorporates a variety of play-to-earn mechanics, centering around skill-based competition, resource collection, and a player-driven upgrade cycle. It builds an ecosystem where a web of participants including NFT holders, players, and game developers revolves around playing Spider Tanks matches and receiving Victory Points that can be submitted for game token reward distribution.</p>
<p>Whether the player wants to play with a small group of close friends, or tests their skills in high-stakes competition, Spider Tanks will be the worldwide play-to-earn esports for them. Players can enjoy the free to play game or compete with other players by purchasing fully tradable Weapons, Tanks and Bodies in the Spider Tanks store for advantages to the upgrade cycle, rarity head starts and more.</p>
<p><strong>About SILK Token</strong></p>
<p>Based on ERC-20, SILK is the game token of Spider Tanks ecosystem. It can be acquired by involving oneself in the Spider Tanks ecosystem through playing and winning games, as well as by operating nodes and other ecosystem products. SILK can also be spent in a number of ways, the chief of which is purchasing upgrades for a Tank Item NFT.</p>
<p>SILK will always be the only currency of the Spider Tanks ecosystem, and as that ecosystem grows in size, supply will not increase in-kind. With a soft cap of 100 million (i.e., 100,000,000) tokens, SILK&#8217;s economy is tied to the amount of players, SILK being generated, and SILK being spent and adjusts emission rates automatically.</p>
<p>The SILK token has been listed on LBank Exchange at 13:00 UTC on December 9, 2022, investors who are interested in the Spider Tanks investment can easily buy and sell SILK token on LBank Exchange now. The listing of SILK token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p>
<p><strong>Learn More about</strong> <strong>SILK Token:</strong></p>
<p>Official Website: <a href="https://www.spidertanks.game/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.spidertanks.game/</a><br />
Discord: <a href="http://galagames.chat/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://galagames.chat/</a>   &amp;  https://www.spidertanks.game/<br />
Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/GoGalaGames" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/GoGalaGames</a>   &amp;  <a href="https://twitter.com/spider_tanks" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/spider_tanks</a><br />
YouTube: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/GalaGames" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/c/GalaGames</a><br />
Facebook: <a href="https://galagames.chat/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://galagames.chat/</a><br />
Reddit: <a href="https://www.instagram.com/spidertanks/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.instagram.com/spidertanks/</a><br />
Instagram: <a href="https://www.instagram.com/spidertanks/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.instagram.com/spidertanks/</a><br />
Medium: <a href="https://medium.com/@spidertanks" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://medium.com/@spidertanks</a></p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media: </strong></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Facebook</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong></p>
<p>LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
LBank Exchange<br />
<a href="mailto:marketing@lbank.info">marketing@lbank.info</a><br />
<a href="mailto:business@lbank.info">business@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/silk-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">SILK Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/silk-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PET CASTLE PROTOCOL (PCP) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/pet-castle-protocol-pcp-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/pet-castle-protocol-pcp-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 07:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75944</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec. 9, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed PET CASTLE PROTOCOL (PCP) on December 9, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the PCP/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading. Building a blockchain-based pet community, Pet Castle Platform provides pet related online and offline<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/pet-castle-protocol-pcp-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/pet-castle-protocol-pcp-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">PET CASTLE PROTOCOL (PCP) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec. 9, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed PET CASTLE PROTOCOL (PCP) on December 9, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the PCP/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading.</p>
<p>Building a blockchain-based pet community, Pet Castle Platform provides pet related online and offline services including Pet ID Card, Pet Business Card, and Pet Castle Urban Theme Park that consists of pet hospital, pet academy, pet beauty, pet café, pet funeral, pet commodities store, and so on. Its native token <a href="https://bscscan.com/token/0x84dE7F1244B354C37a0f8a3A774062305D7006fd" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">PET CASTLE PROTOCOL</a> (PCP) has been listed on LBank Exchange at 8:00 UTC on December 9, 2022, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision.</p>
<p><strong>Introducing Pet Castle Platform</strong></p>
<p>Launched in June 2022 by PET CASTLE Ltd., a company established in March 2022, Pet Castle Platform is currently active as a blockchain-based pet community. It’s built for pets, pet owners, and pet business partners, and can be used quickly and conveniently anytime, anywhere through the mobile app or PC browser. PET CASTLE PROTOCOL (hereinafter referred to as “PCP”) is issued by PET CASTLE Ltd.</p>
<p>There are two kinds of card in the Pet Castle that one can create with free membership service. The first is the Pet ID Card, an NFT-certified ID card for companions who take care of their pets. This is to issue cards to companions so that they can use various services quickly and conveniently within the platform. Users can save their pet photos and videos in the ID card album, and they can also have pedigree analysis results and prevent disease through DNA testing provided free of charge. The platform plans to cooperate with the companion animal industries, including pet hospital, pet insurance companies and service companies that require identity verification.</p>
<p>The second is the Pet Business Card for the presidents (veterinarians) who run the pet business. Through the Pet Castle App, domestic and foreign pet hospitals, pet kindergartens, pet cafes, pet beauty shops, and pet hotel owners can create cards by themselves and do business directly with the companions (or butlers). In addition, pet helpers such as Pet Sitters can create and promote Pet Business Cards by themselves, and it is programmed so that companions can book services and purchase products through quick connection.</p>
<p>At the same time, the offline business will be launched soon. Pet Castle Urban Theme Park is the business that provides pets and the owner of pets with the service like pet hospital, pet academy, pet beauty, pet cafe, pet funeral, pet commodities store, and so on. It will be franchised with lots of franchisee in the domestic market and global one as well. PET CASTLE PROTOCOL’s ecosystem will be enlarged both through online platform and through offline franchise business in the future.</p>
<p>The Pet Castle Platform is growing as a comprehensive platform that can be a refreshing solution by identifying and analyzing the various needs and difficulties that companions are experiencing. Based on the Pet Castle Platform, PCP balances supply and demand in the changing market, and continues to grow as a payment method for Korea&#8217;s best comprehensive companion animal platform and a virtual asset that guarantees future value. Together with the owners and companion animals, PCP will become a driving force in leading an innovative society that respects companion animals.</p>
<p><strong>About PCP Token</strong></p>
<p>PET CASTLE PROTOCOL (PCP) is the native token of Pet Castle Platform. Based on BEP-20, it has a total supply of 5 billion (i.e., 5,000,000,000) tokens, of which 5% is provided for initial funding, 10% will be used for marketing, 30% goes into the exchange pool, 15% is provided for reward to users and partners, 10% is allocated to the team and advisor, 20% will be used for R&amp;D and operating, and the remaining 10% is reserved.</p>
<p>PCP token has been listed on LBank Exchange at 8:00 UTC on December 9, 2022, investors who are interested in the Pet Castel Platform investment can easily buy and sell PCP token on LBank Exchange right now. The listing of PCP token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p>
<p><strong>Learn More about</strong> <strong>PCP Token:</strong></p>
<p>Official Website: <a href="https://petcastle.io" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://petcastle.io</a></p>
<p>Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/+C5OvGVPAWyYwMjU1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://t.me/+C5OvGVPAWyYwMjU1</a></p>
<p>Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/PCP_PetCastle/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/PCP_PetCastle/</a></p>
<p>Facebook: <a href="https://www.facebook.com/Petcastleprotocol" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://www.facebook.com/Petcastleprotocol</a></p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media: </strong></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Facebook</a></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong></p>
<p>LBK Blockchain Co. Limited</p>
<p>LBank Exchange</p>
<p><a href="mailto:marketing@lbank.info">marketing@lbank.info</a></p>
<p><a href="mailto:business@lbank.info">business@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/pet-castle-protocol-pcp-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">PET CASTLE PROTOCOL (PCP) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/pet-castle-protocol-pcp-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New York Continues to Not Care About Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-continues-to-not-care-about-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-continues-to-not-care-about-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 17:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BitLicense]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kathy Hochul]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New York]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75398</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York really doesn’t care about cryptocurrency, and the re-election of Governor Kathy Hochul is proof of this. New York Just Doesn&#8217;t Get It During this year’s midterm elections, Hochul ran against Lee Zeldin, who arguably had one of the most competitive republican campaigns in the Empire State in years. Right now, New York is facing a<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-continues-to-not-care-about-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-continues-to-not-care-about-crypto/">New York Continues to Not Care About Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York really doesn’t care about cryptocurrency, and <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/the-fate-of-crypto-mining-is-back-on-the-table-in-new-york/ar-AA13VEDA" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/the-fate-of-crypto-mining-is-back-on-the-table-in-new-york/ar-AA13VEDA&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537717630000&amp;usg=AOvVaw2_mmA_Pj2tidgQjZe9z1DE" data-wpel-link="external">the re-election of</a> Governor Kathy Hochul is proof of this.</p>
<h2>New York Just Doesn&#8217;t Get It</h2>
<p>During this year’s midterm elections, Hochul ran against Lee Zeldin, who arguably had one of the most competitive republican campaigns in the Empire State in years. Right now, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-governor-hochul-facing-real-pressure-to-sign-crypto-moratorium/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-governor-hochul-facing-real-pressure-to-sign-crypto-moratorium/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537717630000&amp;usg=AOvVaw0uV_wYwq8AzATCp-4JowqA" data-wpel-link="internal">New York is facing a bill</a> that’s been passed by the state legislature. The bill would enforce a moratorium on the crypto mining space and prevent all new digital currency mining companies from setting up shop within the region’s borders.</p>
<p>Zeldin has mentioned numerous times he would end the bill and prevent its passage if he were elected governor. In his campaign against Hochul, he clearly addressed many issues New York was facing. He discussed crime and inflation, items that Hochul – in the past – has refused to acknowledge. He also clearly won the one and only debate between himself and the democrat incumbent, and it appeared he was on a solid track to make native New Yorkers view the conservative party differently.</p>
<p>Sadly, this was not meant to be. Despite being a clear winner in many areas and having some solid ideas in place for the state, New York – as usual – chose to go blue and voted Hochul in for a second term despite her clear lack of attention to the well-being of those living in her state. Now, the crypto moratorium is back on the table, and Hochul has until the end of the year to decide if she’s going to sign it into law. Clearly, the people of New York don’t care about crypto enough to get rid of her.</p>
<p>New York has developed a reputation for being a very anti-crypto state. A big contributor to this is the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitlicense/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitlicense/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537717630000&amp;usg=AOvVaw2oI0R66233KwSXukvFUFB4" data-wpel-link="internal">BitLicense</a>, which was enacted in the year 2015. Many crypto companies left New York completely or were forced to end all their services there due to the harsh regulatory tactics enforced by the BitLicense. Acquiring one also came with monster-sized fees and given that the crypto space was still very much in its infancy at that time, several of these firms couldn’t afford to hawk up the required funds.</p>
<h2>The Bill Is Damaging</h2>
<p>John Olsen – the New York state lead for the Blockchain Association – explained that the moratorium would arguably make a lot of miners leave the state. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think you would see a swift exodus. Should the governor sign the bill, I think you would see a swift exodus of any miners that aren’t almost solely reliant on renewable energy. It’s a difficult time for the industry. New York probably wouldn’t be worth it if it doesn’t have [a] strong signal to the industry that it’s welcome here&#8230; That starts with a veto of that bill.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-continues-to-not-care-about-crypto/">New York Continues to Not Care About Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-continues-to-not-care-about-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
