<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 03:15:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/cropped-fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Key Breakout Resistance at $98</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-key-breakout-resistance-at-98/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 03:18:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79260</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin is consolidating losses near the $96 level against the US Dollar. LTC price is now trading below $98 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $97.00 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could gain [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-key-breakout-resistance-at-98/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Key Breakout Resistance at $98</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Litecoin is consolidating losses near the $96 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>LTC price is now trading below $98 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $97.00 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $97 and $98 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Litecoin price is showing positive signs above $92 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-restart-rally-above-this-resistance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. LTC price could climb again if there is a clear move above $98.</em></p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few sessions, there were mostly range moves in Bitcoin, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-aims-fresh-run-to-2000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a>, Ripple, and Litecoin against the US Dollar. Earlier, LTC started a downside correction from the $115 resistance.</p>
<p>The price traded below the $105 and $100 levels. However, the bulls were active near the $92 zone. The price is now consolidating losses and trading above $95. It even spiked a few times above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $114.98 swing high to the $91.88 low.</p>
<p>However, the bears were active near the $98 resistance zone. It is now consolidating below $98 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $97 level.</p>
<p>There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $97.00 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair. A clear move above the $98 level could push the price toward the $104 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $114.98 swing high to the $91.88 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance sits near the $110 level. Any more gains might send the price toward the $115 level. On the downside, initial support is near the $94 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $92 level. If there is a downside break below the $92 support, the price could accelerate lower toward the $82 level in the near term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79261" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79261" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-1.png"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-79261" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-1.png" alt="Litecoin (LTC) Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-1.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-1-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-1-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-1-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-1-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-1-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-1-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79261" class="wp-caption-text">Litecoin (LTC) Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, Litecoin’s price is trading below $98 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $97 and $98 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LTC/USD is now losing pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $94 and $92</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $97 and $98.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-key-breakout-resistance-at-98/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Key Breakout Resistance at $98</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DWP Executive John Chen Suspended After Engaging in Crypto Mining</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dwp-executive-john-chen-suspended-after-engaging-in-crypto-mining/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 17:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DWP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[John Chen]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78540</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>John Chen, an executive working with the Los Angeles Department of Water and Power (DWP), has been placed on administrative leave after he took part in crypto mining companies that allegedly go against the values and ethics of his agency. John Chen in Hot Water Chen reportedly earns more than $300K a year through his [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dwp-executive-john-chen-suspended-after-engaging-in-crypto-mining/">DWP Executive John Chen Suspended After Engaging in Crypto Mining</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>John Chen, an executive working with the Los Angeles Department of Water and Power (DWP), has been placed on <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/dwp-executive-placed-leave-amid-001223319.html">administrative leave after</a> he took part in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/crypto-mining/">crypto mining</a> companies that allegedly go against the values and ethics of his agency.</p>
<h2>John Chen in Hot Water</h2>
<p>Chen reportedly earns more than $300K a year through his job with the DWP. He has served, for the past few years, as the department’s director, though having been part of a crypto mining company in Colorado since 2018, his constituents say his outside business ventures don’t sit in line with those of the department. Thus, he’s no longer employed while the other executives further examine his activities.</p>
<p>It’s also alleged, through various court documents, that Chen is the manager of a mining data center in North Dakota. In the end, Chen was given an ultimatum… Either remain solely with the department and leave his outside ventures to others or be relieved of his duties… Chen chose the latter.</p>
<p>Cynthia McClain-Hill – president of the DWP board of commissioners – says she and her associates were shocked and displeased when they found out about Chen’s outside business dealings. In an interview, she stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I would expect that employees at DWP, and in particular employees at his level, would be giving their full-time attention to the city and the city’s business.</p></blockquote>
<p>Chen was quick to defend himself, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>It’s an investment. I’m not running it. There’s outside staff that are running it.</p></blockquote>
<p>To be fair, the associates of Chen aren’t displeased with him taking part in bitcoin. They acknowledge that this is a free country and people can pursue whatever makes them happy so long as their actions don’t hurt or disband others. Their concerns lie in the fact that he has a very demanding job, and thus taking part in other business ventures suggests he’s not devoting the proper amount of attention to his DWP duties.</p>
<p>Bob Stern – who worked to draft the public campaign and ethics laws of the city – said his main concern lies with Chen not being able to devote all he needs to the DWP job given he’s allegedly tied up with crypto mining. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Is he giving L.A. what he’s earning? Is he performing 40 hours a week?</p></blockquote>
<h2>Does This <em>Really</em> Warrant Concern?</h2>
<p>Further documentation surrounding the situation shows Chen allegedly partnered with companies in both Singapore and China to bring the Colorado firm to fruition. Also, he secured an economic development deal with Colorado Springs Utilities to garner lesser rates for electricity.</p>
<p>This all seems like an odd reason to get into a huff. If Chen is doing everything on his own time, like he clearly states, and he’s doing a good job with the DWP, what is the big deal?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dwp-executive-john-chen-suspended-after-engaging-in-crypto-mining/">DWP Executive John Chen Suspended After Engaging in Crypto Mining</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tools for Humanity Garners More than $100 Million to Build Digital &#8220;World Coin&#8221;</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tools-for-humanity-garners-more-than-100-million-to-build-digital-world-coin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 15:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain capital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tools for Humanity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World Coin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78537</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tools for Humanity – a company that has introduced a new digital token known as World Coin – has recently garnered as much as $115 million in a new series C funding round led by Blockchain Capital. The company has announced that the funds will go towards growing the breadth of World Coin, as well [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tools-for-humanity-garners-more-than-100-million-to-build-digital-world-coin/">Tools for Humanity Garners More than $100 Million to Build Digital &#8220;World Coin&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tools for Humanity – a company that has introduced a new <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/tools-humanity-secures-115-million-130102805.html">digital token known</a> as World Coin – has recently garnered as much as $115 million in a new series C funding round led by Blockchain Capital. The company has announced that the funds will go towards growing the breadth of World Coin, as well as developing alternatives to CAPTCHA tests.</p>
<h2>Tools for Humanity Garners a Lot of Cash</h2>
<p>World Coin aims to be one of the few fully democratic digital tokens out there in that the executives behind it hope to distribute the token to as many people as possible (hopefully everyone in the world). In addition, all who hold the asset will share equally in the wealth, and nobody can hold more than other parties like they would with bitcoin, Ethereum, and mainstream digital coins.</p>
<p>Spencer Bogart – a general partner at Blockchain Capital – explained in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>It was this idea of creating a new primitive for the internet that can enable any application to easily and quickly distinguish between machines and humans, or bots and humans. That was something that took me working more closely with our engineering team to really appreciate how big of a problem that already is.</p></blockquote>
<p>He further stated that bots have been major problems for blockchain and crypto projects, and thus Tools for Humanity is working hard on making sure they never come about to prevent innovation in the industry again. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>[CAPTCHA] has been fairly effective for distinguishing between bots and humans. That&#8217;s no longer the case with more advanced automated systems, especially things being powered by AI.</p></blockquote>
<p>Not long ago, Blockchain Capital came <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-capital-plunks-money-into-eyeball-scanning-technology/">under fire for investing</a> in some rather questionable technology. To be exact, it was an eyeball-scanning orb built to give all users what are referred to as “World IDs.” Describing the venture, Bogart explained in a separate interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>The root of what defines humans is biometrics, and my first thought was, ‘Why create this custom hardware to go scan eyeballs?’ Like, billions of people are already walking around with an iPhone. Why don’t we use Face ID, right? The problem is that human facial structures do not have sufficient randomness or entropy to distinguish between unique humans at the scale of tens of millions or hundreds of millions of people… I didn’t think about the fact that once you get past one hundred million people, there are going to be a lot of people that look like Spencer Bogart.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Lot of Big Names at the Table</h2>
<p>Right now, it’s unclear how much money Blockchain Capital has invested in World Coin and the remaining ventures of Tools for Humanity.</p>
<p>However, the funding round was no doubt large and saw the participation of many big-name venture capital firms including Bain Capital Crypto and Distributed Global.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tools-for-humanity-garners-more-than-100-million-to-build-digital-world-coin/">Tools for Humanity Garners More than $100 Million to Build Digital &#8220;World Coin&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>&#8220;Tuttle Twins&#8221; Cartoon Features Entire Episode on Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tuttle-twins-cartoon-features-entire-episode-on-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 13:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Daniel Harmon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tuttle Twins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78534</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The “Tuttle Twins” – a conservative children’s cartoon series – recently featured an entire episode that discusses bitcoin and the notions of digital currency. &#8220;Tuttle Twins&#8221; Brings BTC to Children Normally, the “Tuttle Twins” is all about trying to teach children to think for themselves and develop critical skills that will help them in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tuttle-twins-cartoon-features-entire-episode-on-bitcoin/">&#8220;Tuttle Twins&#8221; Cartoon Features Entire Episode on Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The “Tuttle Twins” – a conservative children’s cartoon series – <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/tv/news/tuttle-twins-cartoon-about-life-and-liberty-goes-viral-with-bitcoin-and-the-beast-episode/ar-AA1bLsEH">recently featured an entire</a> episode that discusses bitcoin and the notions of digital currency.</p>
<h2>&#8220;Tuttle Twins&#8221; Brings BTC to Children</h2>
<p>Normally, the “Tuttle Twins” is all about trying to teach children to think for themselves and develop critical skills that will help them in the modern world. Thus, it makes perfect sense that bitcoin would be a major topic of the show. As we edge deeper into a digital age, there may be a time when the children watching the show, as adults, will be required to utilize bitcoin and other crypto assets for everyday purchases and transactions.</p>
<p>The bitcoin discussion came about during an episode called “Tuttle Twins: Bitcoin and the Beast.” It is currently making the rounds on several social platforms and garnering a lot of buzz. The show’s creator Daniel Harmon explained in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>People are really resonating with the message. We had one fan comment about how they were trying to explain bitcoin to someone for seven years. We did in 20 minutes what they couldn’t do in seven years. So, that’s really rewarding to see. People are understanding it, especially how money that’s hard to create is so beneficial to society.</p></blockquote>
<p>The episode – which describes bitcoin as “hard money” – recites the following about digital currency:</p>
<blockquote><p>Digital money that can be sent directly from one person to another without any bank or government involved, and the best part: it’s hard money. Bitcoin is very hard to make more of. Each new coin gets added to the supply only after a computer works very hard to solve a math problem where there’s no shortcut, and solving it costs a lot of energy and time.</p></blockquote>
<p>Harmon continued with:</p>
<blockquote><p>I don’t think they are hearing these kinds of messages in other forms of media, for the most part. They’re not getting it in schools, not getting it in culture, and for us to talk very clearly about things like rights to life, liberty, and property, about things like bitcoin, inflation, entrepreneurship in a way that kids can understand is very refreshing to parents. It’s something that they’ve been craving for a long time. They’re very much noticing that it doesn’t exist elsewhere. That’s why the show is having its success.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Money that Can&#8217;t Be Controlled</h2>
<p>Bitcoin is becoming a rough topic in that many countries – particularly the United States – are working hard to implement socialist, woke agendas into their societies along with poor economic tactics that have brought <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-provide-their-thoughts-on-latest-bitcoin-rally/">about the deaths of various</a> banks and caused inflation to rise through the roof.</p>
<p>Bitcoin is money that cannot be controlled by the government, which explains – according to Ron DeSantis – why Biden and his entourage of nation haters are <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/florida-governor-ron-desantis-defends-crypto-and-bashes-the-idea-of-cbdcs/">trying so hard to ruin</a> it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tuttle-twins-cartoon-features-entire-episode-on-bitcoin/">&#8220;Tuttle Twins&#8221; Cartoon Features Entire Episode on Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Bulls Aim Another Rally To $0.085</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bulls-aim-another-rally-to-0-085/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 05:08:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79246</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tron price started a fresh increase from the $0.0725 level against the US Dollar. TRX price is now trading below $0.0780 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.0770 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could continue to move [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bulls-aim-another-rally-to-0-085/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Bulls Aim Another Rally To $0.085</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Tron price started a fresh increase from the $0.0725 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>TRX price is now trading below $0.0780 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.0770 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move up if it breaks the $0.078 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>TRON price started a fresh increase above $0.0755 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-restart-rally-above-this-resistance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. TRX’s price could rise further if it clears the $0.078 resistance.</em></p>
<h2>Tron Price Analysis</h2>
<p>After a downside correction, Tron price found support near the $0.0760 zone against the US Dollar. TRX’s price formed a base and recently started a fresh increase from the $0.0762 low.</p>
<p>There was a break above the $0.0770 and $0.0775 levels. The price climbed above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.0804 swing high to the $0.0762 low. TRX is now trading below $0.078 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-more-gains-possible-above-0-08/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.0770 on the 4-hours chart. On the upside, TRX is facing resistance near the $0.0782 level. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.0804 swing high to the $0.0762 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $0.080 level. A close above $0.080 could send the price toward the $0.0820 resistance zone.</p>
<p>Any more gains might send TRX price toward $0.0832, above which the price could even rise toward $0.085. On the downside, initial support is near the $0.077 level and the trend line. The next major support is now forming near $0.0760.</p>
<p>If there is a downside break below the $0.0760 support, the price might revisit the $0.0720 support. Any more losses might call for a move toward the $0.070 zone in the near term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79247" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79247" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/TRON-TRX-1.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-79247" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/TRON-TRX-1.png" alt="Tron (TRX) Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/TRON-TRX-1.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/TRON-TRX-1-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/TRON-TRX-1-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/TRON-TRX-1-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/TRON-TRX-1-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/TRON-TRX-1-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/TRON-TRX-1-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79247" class="wp-caption-text">Tron (TRX) Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/TRXUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a> indicates that TRX’s price is now trading below $0.078 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move up if it breaks the $0.080 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for TRX/USD is now losing momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for TRX/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.077 and $0.076.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.078, $0.082, and $0.085.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bulls-aim-another-rally-to-0-085/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Bulls Aim Another Rally To $0.085</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Could Restart Rally Above This Resistance</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-restart-rally-above-this-resistance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 03:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79242</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price is attempting a fresh increase from the $29,800 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above $30,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,800 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-restart-rally-above-this-resistance/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Could Restart Rally Above This Resistance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin price is attempting a fresh increase from the $29,800 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $30,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,800 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could start a fresh increase if it clears the $31,500 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin price is rising from $29,800 against the US Dollar. BTC might eye another increase if the bulls remain active above the $30,000 zone.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price remained in a range after it failed to clear the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-more-upsides-above-31250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$31,500 resistance</a>. BTC was rejected a couple of times but the bulls were active above near the $30,000 zone.</p>
<p>The recent swing low was formed near $29,715 before the price moved higher. The bulls were able to push the price above the $30,200 and $30,250 levels. There was a move above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $31,525 swing high to the $29,715 low.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is now trading above $30,500 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-bulls-in-control-above-29500/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. Immediate resistance on the upside is near the $30,750 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,800 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>The trend line is just below the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $31,525 swing high to the $29,715 low. The next major resistance might be near the $31,500 zone.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $31,450 and $31,500 resistance levels might send the price toward $32,500. Any more gains might push the price toward the $34,000 zone. If there is no upside break, the price might start a fresh decline below the $30,450 level.</p>
<p>The first major support is near $30,000. The next key support is near the $29,750 level, below which the price might accelerate lower. In the stated case, the price could decline toward the $28,200 level.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79244" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79244" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-2.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-79244" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-2.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-2.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-2-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-2-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-2-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-2-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-2-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-2-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79244" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XBTUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, Bitcoin’s price is trading above $30,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start a fresh increase if it clears the $31,500 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD is now losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $30,000 and $29,750.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $30,800, $31,500, and $32,500.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-restart-rally-above-this-resistance/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Could Restart Rally Above This Resistance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vietnam&#8217;s Crypto Boom: Attracting Top Blockchain Projects</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vietnams-crypto-boom-attracting-top-blockchain-projects/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Gautham]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 17:35:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry and Adoption]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79210</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Vietnam&#8217;s economy is undergoing a digital revolution, with a projected compound annual growth rate of 8.9% in the digital economy from 2022 to 2026. This growth rate surpasses that of 51 other countries worldwide, including economic powerhouses like China, the US, the UAE, and all European countries, according to the FT-Omdia Digital Economy Index. Experts [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vietnams-crypto-boom-attracting-top-blockchain-projects/">Vietnam&#8217;s Crypto Boom: Attracting Top Blockchain Projects</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Vietnam&#8217;s economy is undergoing a digital revolution, with a projected compound annual growth rate of 8.9% in the digital economy from 2022 to 2026. This growth rate surpasses that of 51 other countries worldwide, including economic powerhouses like China, the US, the UAE, and all European countries, according to the FT-Omdia Digital Economy Index. Experts attribute this projected success to several factors, including Vietnam&#8217;s youthful population, government policies fostering an enabling environment for innovation, and a substantial influx of foreign investment and investors that are driving the country&#8217;s digital landscape.</p>
<p>The flourishing ecosystem of tech start-ups with a focus on innovation and entrepreneurship has extended its reach to the world of cryptocurrencies, leading to a proliferation of blockchain projects and initiatives in Vietnam. Chainalysis, a blockchain analytics firm, revealed that Vietnam secured the top spot in the 2022 Cryptocurrency Adoption Ranking.</p>
<p>The Vietnamese population&#8217;s interest lies in blockchain services that address the gaps prevalent in the country&#8217;s financial system. Payment solutions, investment opportunities for retail investors, and convenient acquiring products for small and medium-sized businesses are particularly popular. Despite rapid technological advancements, Vietnam&#8217;s population remains underbanked, with only about 60% of Vietnamese adults having a bank account, according to a report by the National Payments Corporation of Vietnam (Napas).</p>
<p>The demand for blockchain services that work with cryptocurrencies and offer a user-friendly interface is evident from the growing number of active users on the <a href="https://mineplex.finance/en">CrossFi</a> blockchain. This blockchain serves as the foundation for various decentralized financial and payment services. Within a year, the user base of CrossFi products attracted 5,000 active participants from Vietnam, and this number is projected to grow three to six times over the next couple of years.</p>
<p>The CrossFi blockchain offers a range of payment solutions, including fast transfer services for swift cross-border transactions. It also enables the issuance and acquisition of tokens at private, corporate, and government levels, covering cryptocurrencies, stablecoins, and digital twins. Additionally, CrossFi facilitates the tokenization of banking services and loyalty programs. Their crypto-acquiring platform provides ready-made solutions for enterprises and businesses, utilizing payment cards, POS-terminals, and self-service terminals.</p>
<p>The remarkable growth in the number of users utilizing CrossFi blockchain solutions can be attributed to several key factors:</p>
<p><strong>Wide range of products</strong>: CrossFi offers an extensive selection of solutions, encompassing both traditional banking services with fiat currencies and services related to cryptocurrencies. Exchange transactions and money transfers can be completed swiftly and effortlessly, even without deep technical expertise. This comprehensive approach appeals to a broader audience, attracting individuals already familiar with traditional banking and those keen to explore the world of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Focus on Entrepreneurship</strong>: CrossFi-based products cater to the specific needs of the business community by providing a diverse range of business-specific offerings. Entrepreneurs, who often seek efficient and flexible financial solutions to support their ventures, find that CrossFi-based services grant them access to payment gateways for both fiat and crypto transactions. Moreover, these services enable the implementation of tokenized loyalty programs with NFTs, aligning well with the interests of a young and entrepreneurial audience.</p>
<p><strong>Simplicity and convenience</strong>: All services boast a user-friendly interface and seamless integration of various financial services. This ensures a convenient and accessible experience for users. The simplicity of these services plays a critical role in attracting and retaining customers, especially in the highly competitive fintech industry.</p>
<p><strong>Affordability</strong>: CrossFi-based solutions actively promote financial inclusion in Vietnam, addressing the fact that a significant portion of the population remains unbanked or underbanked. By offering a diverse range of financial options, these solutions empower individuals and businesses that have previously been excluded from traditional banking systems.</p>
<p><strong>Innovation</strong>: The distinctive features of CrossFi-based products, such as payment solutions and acquiring capabilities for both fiat and cryptocurrencies, as well as tokenized loyalty programs with NFTs and the seamless transition to traditional banking services, set them apart from conventional financial platforms. These innovations captivate users who are intrigued by the potential of blockchain and NFT technology.</p>
<p><strong>Benefit</strong>: Users of the CrossFi blockchain are rewarded for staking native MPX coins, with an average monthly return of approximately 8% in XFI coins. MPX coins function as a unit of computing power within the CrossFi blockchain, possessing a stable and fixed value. During MPX staking, other native coins of the CrossFi blockchain, namely <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/mineplex-2/">XFI</a>, are generated. XFI serves as a volatile settlement unit that is utilized across all CrossFi services and can be traded on crypto exchanges. MPX stakers receive rewards in XFI tokens, which can be utilized within CrossFi services or exchanged for other cryptocurrencies on crypto exchanges.</p>
<p><strong>Strategic Partnerships</strong>: The CrossFi team actively collaborates with other businesses and financial institutions to expand the capabilities of CrossFi-based solutions, enabling them to reach new customer segments and enhance their offerings.</p>
<p>In the coming months, all CrossFi-based products will be consolidated into a single Finance mobile banking application, streamlining interaction with cryptocurrencies and providing access to financial services for a wide range of users in Vietnam. The application has already obtained a PCI DSS compliance certificate, signifying the high reliability of its software security systems.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-79211 aligncenter" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture122-565x600.png" alt="" width="565" height="600" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture122-565x600.png 565w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture122.png 624w" sizes="(max-width: 565px) 100vw, 565px" /></p>
<p>Vietnam&#8217;s emergence as a digital hub in Southeast Asia stems from the country&#8217;s appeal to blockchain initiatives, providing an opportunity to showcase their full potential. By offering users, including entrepreneurs, a combination of traditional and cryptocurrency financial services with high accessibility and a focus on innovation, Vietnam has positioned itself as an attractive destination in the world of blockchain.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vietnams-crypto-boom-attracting-top-blockchain-projects/">Vietnam&#8217;s Crypto Boom: Attracting Top Blockchain Projects</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blockchain Capital Plunks Money into Eyeball-Scanning Technology</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-capital-plunks-money-into-eyeball-scanning-technology/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 17:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain capital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eyeball scanning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World Coin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78531</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain Capital – a funding company that’s made a name for itself giving several new blockchain startups life – is betting big on a new eyeball-scanning orb. Blockchain Capital Invests in Some Questionable Tech The firm has funded all kinds of crypto companies from Coinbase and Kraken to NFT marketplace Open Sea. In an interview, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-capital-plunks-money-into-eyeball-scanning-technology/">Blockchain Capital Plunks Money into Eyeball-Scanning Technology</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain Capital – a funding company that’s made a name for itself giving several new blockchain startups life – is betting big on a <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/05/26/explaining-blockchain-capitals-big-bet-on-an-eyeball-scanning-orb/">new eyeball-scanning orb</a>.</p>
<h2>Blockchain Capital Invests in Some Questionable Tech</h2>
<p>The firm has funded all kinds of crypto companies from <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/coinbase/">Coinbase</a> and Kraken to NFT marketplace Open Sea. In an interview, general partner Spencer Bogart talked about how much of the company investors currently own. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>It’s not a figure I have in front of me, right now. Generally, companies sell 20 percent of the [equity] in each financing. Granted, things can move down or up from there significantly. I think in this case, the number is going to be meaningfully lower than that across the series A, the series B, and series C.</p></blockquote>
<p>Not long ago, the enterprise invested in a new venture called World Coin. Discussing what led them to take part in this, Bogart explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>The original genesis was… What if I could create a cryptocurrency that I could distribute to everyone in the world, and everyone got an equal share of it? For me, from a venture perspective, that’s certainly interesting, [though] I don’t know that it’s something that we would be super excited to go and underwrite based on the things that our team is typically interested in. [Meanwhile] this requires basically making sure that no one person can accumulate a disproportionate share of [the currency], which requires the ability to identify unique humans. This gets into the part that we’re really excited about, which is World ID. It’s this ability to easily distinguish between machines and humans on the internet [which is crucial as] most of the internet is supported by ad revenue and it costs just as much to serve bot traffic as it does to service human traffic. It’s why various applications and service providers have used CAPTCHAs to distinguish between bots and humans, but that’s no longer viable in a world of advanced automated systems and particularly things powered by AI. It also doesn’t differentiate between unique humans, so I don’t know if the same person is coming to consume a resource excessively.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Lot of People Looking the Same</h2>
<p>Regarding the company’s funding of the eye scanner, he said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The root of what defines humans is biometrics, and my first thought was, ‘Why create this custom hardware to go scan eyeballs?’ Like, billions of people are already walking around with an iPhone. Why don’t we use Face ID, right? The problem is that human facial structures do not have sufficient randomness or entropy to distinguish between unique humans at the scale of tens of millions or hundreds of millions of people… I didn’t think about the fact that once you get past one hundred million people, there are going to be a lot of people that look like Spencer Bogart.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-capital-plunks-money-into-eyeball-scanning-technology/">Blockchain Capital Plunks Money into Eyeball-Scanning Technology</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Where Will Bitcoin Be at the End of 2023? Analysts Weigh In</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/where-will-bitcoin-be-at-the-end-of-2023-analysts-weigh-in/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 15:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tim Shan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78528</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has been on something of a roll in 2023. While things aren’t quite where they could be, many analysts are excited about the fact that this has virtually been the exact opposite of 2022, a year in which bitcoin and its many crypto cousins fell into oblivion, and they’re all wondering where the world’s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/where-will-bitcoin-be-at-the-end-of-2023-analysts-weigh-in/">Where Will Bitcoin Be at the End of 2023? Analysts Weigh In</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has been on something of a roll in 2023. While things aren’t quite where they could be, many analysts are excited about the fact that this has virtually been the exact opposite of 2022, a year in which bitcoin and its many crypto cousins fell into oblivion, and they’re all wondering where the world’s leading digital <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-is-on-a-tear-in-2023-heres-where-4-crypto-pros-see-the-coin-headed-by-the-end-of-the-year/ar-AA1bNtIV">asset will end the year</a>.</p>
<h2>Where Will Bitcoin Be in 6 Months?</h2>
<p>Charmyn Ho – head of crypto insights at digital asset exchange By Bit – said in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>A possible headwind is the potential recession forecast to hit the US, Europe, and other major economies due to a stubbornly inverted yield curve. Couple this with a bunch of other unsavory macro factors, such as inflation, [and] many investors would rather remain on the sidelines. This is contributing to the mostly sideways price action we&#8217;ve been experiencing.</p></blockquote>
<p>Ho also weighed in on next year’s <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/halving/">halving</a>. It’s alleged that this event, as it’s done in the past, will bear a lot of weight on the price of bitcoin in the coming months. Ho said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin halvings are significant because they slash the production of new bitcoins on the network by half. This curtails the supply of freshly minted coins, thus leading to a price increase if the demand persists. Litecoin, which is due [to halve] this year, is up around 90 percent since its lows in Q3, 2022. Therefore, if we take that as a guide, it is possible that we could see a similar 90 percent move from bitcoin&#8217;s Q3, 2023 price, which would give a rough target of about $60,000.</p></blockquote>
<p>Jagdeep Sidhu – president of the Syscoin Foundation – was also quick to comment and said:</p>
<blockquote><p>While we&#8217;ve weathered some storms recently, the resilience of the crypto ecosystem remains evident. From the ashes of FTX, the market has rebounded, demonstrating its inherent capacity to absorb shocks and evolve. As we approach the next bitcoin halving and crypto dominance looks set to peak, we&#8217;re on the cusp of exciting developments in the crypto world.</p></blockquote>
<p>Tim Shan – COO at decentralized exchange Dexalot – mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>My base case is bitcoin will trade in a range between $25,000 and $32,000 for the remainder of 2023, but if we see inflation remain high, I think bitcoin could trade back down to lows of the year. The short to medium term driver is still inflation, and specifically US inflation. I think core inflation has been sticky, but [it] will continue to decline in the US, leading the Fed to pause for the rest of the year.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Investors Remaining Sidelined?</h2>
<p>Last came David Uhryniak, an employee of Tron. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Right now, smart traders are waiting for greater validation as to which way bitcoin and the rest of the market will move next before committing serious money.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/where-will-bitcoin-be-at-the-end-of-2023-analysts-weigh-in/">Where Will Bitcoin Be at the End of 2023? Analysts Weigh In</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
