<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 04:46:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Top Celebs and Investors Still Stand with Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/top-celebs-and-investors-still-stand-with-bitcoin/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/top-celebs-and-investors-still-stand-with-bitcoin/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 17:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[edward snowden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kevin O'Leary]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76247</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin had a rough 2022, but that hasn’t stopped high-ranking celebrities and investors from praising it. They feel that while bitcoin may have had a rough 12 months, things can always return to form, and they’re not turning their backs on the world’s number one digital currency by market cap yet. Bitcoin Is Still the<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/top-celebs-and-investors-still-stand-with-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/top-celebs-and-investors-still-stand-with-bitcoin/">Top Celebs and Investors Still Stand with Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin had a rough 2022, but that hasn’t stopped <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/savingandinvesting/bitcoin-is-still-well-below-20-000-so-why-haven-t-kevin-o-leary-edward-snowden-and-other-celebrity-investors-given-up-on-it/ar-AA15LVeK" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">high-ranking celebrities</a> and investors from praising it. They feel that while bitcoin may have had a rough 12 months, things can always return to form, and they’re not turning their backs on the world’s number one digital currency by market cap yet.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Is Still the Apple of Many Celebrities&#8217; Eyes</h2>
<p>Bitcoin hit a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit in November of 2021. Just a year later, the currency was trading in the high $16,000 range. That’s a valuation dip of more than 70 percent. It’s a sad and ugly sight to see, yet there are still so many individuals out there that have hope that the currency is not dead yet.</p>
<p>One of those people is NSA whistleblower Edward Snowden, who now calls Russia home after fleeing the U.S. In a conference last June, he explained to the viewers about BTC:</p>
<blockquote><p>It’s like a forest fire. When the ground has been cleared, things will grow again.</p></blockquote>
<p>Another person who’s refusing to give up on bitcoin is “Shark Tank” star <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/kevin-oleary/" data-wpel-link="internal">Kevin O’Leary</a>. Always a bitcoin bull, O’Leary explained in an interview last summer that bitcoin has “so much intellectual property” and that it’s a “genius idea.” He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>If you go to any graduating cohort, go engineering, a third of them would want to work in the chain. They don’t want to work in the 11 sectors of the economy. They want something new.</p></blockquote>
<p>Patrick Thompson – host of the blockchain and digital asset podcast “More Than Money” – says while many celebrities continue to support bitcoin, the asset has no doubt experienced heavy value loss over the past several months. There are many reasons for this in his mind, a big one being that there’s heavy talk of a recession.</p>
<p>With so much economic uncertainty in the air, it’s likely many people are getting rid of risky assets and trying to swoop up as much cash as possible. Thompson believes bitcoin was the asset that likely sparked the ongoing selloffs of many risky assets. Discussing crypto, he said:</p>
<blockquote><p>It’s an industry built on an extremely unstable foundation. Many of the biggest companies in the cryptocurrency space had extremely high-risk business models and were over-leveraged… Why would someone want to hold an asset that will most likely decrease in value in the short term? Sometimes, you need to cut off your finger to save your hand, to sell assets now so that your total losses aren’t as detrimental as they could possibly be.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Speculation Isn&#8217;t the Main Problem</h2>
<p>Merav Ozair – a blockchain expert at Rutgers Business School – says speculation isn’t entirely to blame for this crypto winter. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Today, the crypto market is very much correlated and in tune with everything that is happening in the economy and with other asset classes.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/top-celebs-and-investors-still-stand-with-bitcoin/">Top Celebs and Investors Still Stand with Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/top-celebs-and-investors-still-stand-with-bitcoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Report: North Korea Has Made Off with More Than $1 Billion in Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-north-korea-has-stolen-more-than-1-billion-in-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-north-korea-has-stolen-more-than-1-billion-in-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 15:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[North Korea]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76243</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The top spy agency of South Korea stated its neighbor North Korea has stolen an estimated $1.5 trillion won worth of cryptocurrency funds over the past five years. This is equivalent to about $1.2 billion in USD. More than half of that money was stolen in the year 2022 alone. North Korea Is Still Stealing<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-north-korea-has-stolen-more-than-1-billion-in-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-north-korea-has-stolen-more-than-1-billion-in-crypto/">Report: North Korea Has Made Off with More Than $1 Billion in Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The top spy agency of South Korea stated its <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/south-korea-s-top-spy-agency-says-north-korean-hackers-have-stolen-12-billion-in-cryptocurrency-and-other-virtual-assets/ar-AA15CohS" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">neighbor North Korea has</a> stolen an estimated $1.5 trillion won worth of cryptocurrency funds over the past five years. This is equivalent to about $1.2 billion in USD. More than half of that money was stolen in the year 2022 alone.</p>
<h2>North Korea Is Still Stealing Crypto</h2>
<p>North Korea <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/north-korea/" data-wpel-link="internal">has long been in the</a> habit of stealing digital currency and engaging in crypto hacks and related activities to garner the funds it needs to continue building its nuclear arsenal. The country also experienced a weakening economy during the days of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/coronavirus/" data-wpel-link="internal">the COVID pandemic</a> and has also suffered at the hands of the U.S., which has regularly imposed sanctions against the nation. Thus, the country has long been in desperate need of fast cash, and it’s often turned to crypto to make this happen.</p>
<p>But this crypto is usually stolen from other regions of the world including the United States, several parts of Europe, and of course, South Korea. The National Intelligence Service – the main spy agency of the latter region – has said that North Korea’s ability to steal digital currencies has grown exponentially over the years, and they predict the methods it uses are among the best in the world.</p>
<p>Sanctions against North Korea were toughened in the year 2017 by the United Nations given its ongoing nuclear missile tests and its regular focus on cybercrime. Exports from North Korea – such as coal, textiles, and seafood – have all been very limited over the past five or six years, causing the nation to pass several of its foreign workers onto other regions. Even further restrictions came about during the days of the pandemic, and by then, North Korea was allegedly suffering like it never had before.</p>
<p>South Korea is now saying that its neighbor to the north is not done stealing digital assets. In fact, it’s likely only getting started. South Korea fully expects its northern counterpart to conduct additional illegal cyber hacks in the year 2023, and that more crypto is likely to make its way into the hands of Kim Jong-un and his fellow regulators.</p>
<h2>Trying to Keep Itself Alive</h2>
<p>In addition, South Korea says that the northern region will also attempt to make off with specific technology information and confidential data regarding South Korean foreign policy and national security.</p>
<p>In December of last year, several representatives of nations like the U.S., South Korea, and Japan all unanimously agreed to increase their efforts to fight off or at least limit the illegal dealings of North Korea. Just last February, a panel of U.N. representatives claimed that the nation of North Korea was continuing to engage in cyberattacks on various crypto firms and exchanges, and that missile tests go on despite the nation’s ailing economy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-north-korea-has-stolen-more-than-1-billion-in-crypto/">Report: North Korea Has Made Off with More Than $1 Billion in Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-north-korea-has-stolen-more-than-1-billion-in-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Calgary, Canada Refuses to Give Up on Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/calgary-canada-refuses-to-give-up-on-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/calgary-canada-refuses-to-give-up-on-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 13:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Calgary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[canada]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76240</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>2022 was a bad year for crypto. Bitcoin and many leading forms of digital currency have crashed, but that doesn’t mean all the crypto companies out there are turning their backs on their respective industries. Several companies in Calgary, Canada – like Bitvo Inc. – still believe crypto has a fighting chance, and they’re refusing<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/calgary-canada-refuses-to-give-up-on-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/calgary-canada-refuses-to-give-up-on-crypto/">Calgary, Canada Refuses to Give Up on Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>2022 was a bad year for crypto. Bitcoin and many leading forms of digital currency have crashed, but that doesn’t <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-ca/money/topstories/alberta-cryptocurrency-companies-still-say-they-re-optimistic-despite-industry-struggles/ar-AA15MEY8" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">mean all the crypto companies</a> out there are turning their backs on their respective industries. Several companies in Calgary, Canada – like Bitvo Inc. – still believe crypto has a fighting chance, and they’re refusing to give up on this growing financial arena.</p>
<h2>Calgary Has Tried Hard to Incorporate Crypto</h2>
<p>Bitvo is a unique firm <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">in that FTX</a> – the now failed crypto exchange run by Sam Bankman-Fried – was all set to acquire the Calgary-based trading platform in June. Given that FTX has completely crashed and burned, Bitvo has said the entire deal will not go through, now. It has also said it had no direct links to FTX, nor is it part of the company’s ongoing bankruptcy proceedings.</p>
<p>Pamela Draper – president and CEO of Bitvo – said in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>There&#8217;s no impact on Bitvo&#8217;s operations, or the security of our customers&#8217; funds, as a result of the FTX failure.</p></blockquote>
<p>Calgary – which is situated in Alberta, Canada – has long tried to position itself as an industry leader. This is ultimately why the government of the region was so willing to work with FTX at one point. Sam Bankman-Fried and many other employees and staff members of the fallen exchange spent time talking to the regulators of Calgary to see how they could build up the exchange’s presence in the area.</p>
<p>In an interview not too long ago, Bankman-Fried said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We&#8217;ve had some fantastic conversations with the government of Alberta, which has been really constructive, and [we’re] trying to take the lead in Canada and around the world for crypto policy and frameworks.</p></blockquote>
<p>The fall of FTX has certainly led to some ripple effects, and several companies in Canada have felt the heat. Hut 8 – one of the oldest and largest miners in the country – has been hit by the effects of FTX, though it doesn’t feel that the latest bear market is anything to greatly worry about.</p>
<p>Sue Ellis – head of investor relations at Hut 8 – mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>This is not our first bear market. In the last bull market of 2021, we were one of the only guys who were actually setting ourselves up and setting up our balance sheet so that we could weather any sort of storm.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Some Important Factors Are Being Ignored</h2>
<p>Koleya Karringten – executive director of the Canadian Blockchain Consortium – says that while much of the news surrounding crypto has been negative as of late, there are some hardcore developments that have happened that the media is choosing to ignore. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>[The industry is] developing technology that&#8217;s capable of being exported internationally and supporting everything from remittance payments to better transparency and a more secure supply chain for everything from pharmaceuticals to our energy industry to agriculture.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/calgary-canada-refuses-to-give-up-on-crypto/">Calgary, Canada Refuses to Give Up on Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/calgary-canada-refuses-to-give-up-on-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Dips Remain Attractive Near $115</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-dips-remain-attractive-near-115/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-dips-remain-attractive-near-115/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 04:58:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76603</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin cash started a decent increase above the $108 and $112 resistance levels against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above the $115 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $118 on the 4-hours chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-dips-remain-attractive-near-115/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-dips-remain-attractive-near-115/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Dips Remain Attractive Near $115</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin cash started a decent increase above the $108 and $112 resistance levels against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above the $115 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $118 on the 4-hours chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair must clear $125 and $130 to continue higher in the near term.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin cash price is climbing above $115 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-rally-could-extend-above-22k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. BCH/USD could start a fresh surge if it clears the $130 level.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin cash price formed a decent support base above the $110 level. BCH started a recovery wave and was able to clear the $112 resistance zone.</p>
<p>The price climbed above the $120 and $125 resistance levels. The pair is now trading above the $115 zone and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-rally-could-extend-above-125/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. The recent surge was such that the price even traded above the $125 level. A high is formed near $132 before there was a minor decline.</p>
<p>There was a move below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $106 swing low to $132 high. It is now trading above the $115 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $125 level. The next major resistance is near the $132 level, above which the price may perhaps rise towards the $150 level. Any more gains above $150 could set the pace for a move towards the $165 level in the coming days.</p>
<p>An immediate support on the downside is near the $118 level. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $118 on the 4-hours chart of the BCH/USD pair.</p>
<p>The first major support sits near the $115 level. It is near the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $106 swing low to $132 high. The next major support is near $105, below which the bears might aim $100. The next target for them may perhaps be near the $92 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_76604" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Bitcoin-Cash-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76604" class="size-full wp-image-76604" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Bitcoin-Cash-2.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76604" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Cash Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BCHUSD/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">chart</a>, bitcoin cash price is now trading above the $115 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price must clear $125 and $132 to continue higher in the near term.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for BCH/USD is gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BCH/USD is near the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $118 and $115.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $125 and $132.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-dips-remain-attractive-near-115/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Dips Remain Attractive Near $115</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-dips-remain-attractive-near-115/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kabosu, the Dogecoin Shiba Inu Dog, Diagnosed with Serious Illness</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kabosu-the-dogecoin-shiba-inu-dog-diagnosed-with-serious-illness/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kabosu-the-dogecoin-shiba-inu-dog-diagnosed-with-serious-illness/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 17:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Atsuko Sato]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kabosu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76229</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Kabosu – the cute little Shiba Inu dog that inspired the memes of such famous digital currencies as Dogecoin – has been diagnosed with liver disease and leukemia according to her owner Atsuko Sato. Kabosu Is Very Ill The news is indeed sad for both animal lovers and crypto fans alike. Kabosu will likely never<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kabosu-the-dogecoin-shiba-inu-dog-diagnosed-with-serious-illness/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kabosu-the-dogecoin-shiba-inu-dog-diagnosed-with-serious-illness/">Kabosu, the Dogecoin Shiba Inu Dog, Diagnosed with Serious Illness</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Kabosu – the cute little Shiba Inu dog that inspired the memes of such famous digital currencies as Dogecoin – has been <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/other/the-internet-famous-shiba-inu-who-inspired-doge-memes-and-a-joke-cryptocurrency-is-seriously-ill-with-cancer/ar-AA15JVI2" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">diagnosed with liver disease</a> and leukemia according to her owner Atsuko Sato.</p>
<h2>Kabosu Is Very Ill</h2>
<p>The news is indeed sad for both animal lovers and crypto fans alike. Kabosu will likely never know how many people she has inspired with her cute little face, nor will she ever realize that her complexion and furry countenance arguably gave birth to one of the biggest bitcoin rivals to ever exist in Dogecoin.</p>
<p>Her owner made the following announcement on Twitter:</p>
<blockquote><p>Right now, the liver is very bad, and jaundice appears, but antibiotics will definitely improve.</p></blockquote>
<p>Originally a rescue pup, Kabosu voluntarily stopped eating and drinking on or around Christmas time in 2022. However, it has since been reported that she can drink water and that her appetite has come back somewhat, thus suggesting that while her condition is dangerous, hope is not completely lost yet.</p>
<p>Kabosu has already surpassed the life expectancy of her species given that she celebrated her 17th birthday in October of last year. Right now, Shiba Inu dogs are only expected to live between 12 and 15 years, so even if this is the end, one can attest to the fact that Kabosu is indeed a fighter and will go down in crypto history as a true pioneer and powerhouse of the space.</p>
<p>Her image has become synonymous with Dogecoin over the years, a currency that was initially created by computer genius Jackson Palmer. The currency was established as a way of making fun of the crypto space and its users. It was a meme coin, but it wound up becoming a major staple of the industry and has even garnered the attention of hardcore tech and crypto fans such as Elon Musk, who in all fairness, has often been kinder to Doge in the past than he has to bitcoin.</p>
<p>Musk has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-affirms-his-position-on-doge-its-the-peoples-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">referred to Dogecoin</a> as the “people’s crypto.” He has since allowed it to be used for merchandise purchases with many of his companies including <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-permits-tesla-customers-to-use-dogecoin-for-certain-merchandise/" data-wpel-link="internal">Tesla</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-permits-doge-payments-for-spacex-merchandise/" data-wpel-link="internal">SpaceX</a>.</p>
<p>Kabosu first became an <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/shiba-inu-behind-doge-meme-diagnosed-with-leukemia-and-liver-disease-owner-says/ar-AA15JmBp" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">internet sensation in 2010</a>. Her owner Sato posted her photo online and she became a quick hit on Reddit, with one user posting the word “Doge” under her photo, thus birthing the Dogecoin name.</p>
<h2>Let Us All Hope for Her Safety and Potential Recovery</h2>
<p>Three years later, the currency would emerge with her image as its major logo. This startled Sato at first, and she stated in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>When I first found out about the Kabosu memes, I was very surprised. I was terrified at the thought that just one photo I had casually posted on my blog could spread all over the world to places I didn’t know.</p></blockquote>
<p>Let us all join in praying for Kabosu’s safety.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kabosu-the-dogecoin-shiba-inu-dog-diagnosed-with-serious-illness/">Kabosu, the Dogecoin Shiba Inu Dog, Diagnosed with Serious Illness</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kabosu-the-dogecoin-shiba-inu-dog-diagnosed-with-serious-illness/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Argo Blockchain Sells Mining Facility to Galaxy Digital to Stay Afloat</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/argo-blockchain-sells-mining-facility-to-galaxy-digital-to-stay-afloat/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/argo-blockchain-sells-mining-facility-to-galaxy-digital-to-stay-afloat/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 15:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Argo Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celsius Network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Galaxy Digital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76226</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Argo Blockchain – one of the largest and most powerful digital currency mining enterprises in the world – has announced a new plan that will allow it to avoid bankruptcy and become another company that falls victim to the ongoing bear conditions of the crypto arena. Argo Blockchain Won&#8217;t Have to File Bankruptcy Argo has<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/argo-blockchain-sells-mining-facility-to-galaxy-digital-to-stay-afloat/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/argo-blockchain-sells-mining-facility-to-galaxy-digital-to-stay-afloat/">Argo Blockchain Sells Mining Facility to Galaxy Digital to Stay Afloat</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Argo Blockchain – one of the largest and most powerful digital currency mining enterprises in the world – has announced a new plan <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/bitcoin-miner-argo-to-avoid-bankruptcy-with-24100m-deal-from-galaxy-digital/ar-AA15Kx1P" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">that will allow it to avoid</a> bankruptcy and become another company that falls victim to the ongoing bear conditions of the crypto arena.</p>
<h2>Argo Blockchain Won&#8217;t Have to File Bankruptcy</h2>
<p>Argo has agreed to sell its bitcoin mining facility (called Helios) for $65 million to Galaxy Digital, the hedge fund managed by Mike Novogratz, a billionaire investor and big-time fan of bitcoin and other forms of crypto. The wealth management firm will also provide Argo with a $35 million loan to help it restructure its operations. The loan was secured through a collateral package that came in the form of Argo mining equipment.</p>
<p>In a statement, Galaxy Digital explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>The transaction will accelerate the expansion of Galaxy’s bitcoin mining operations and services, provide access to tax-efficient mining infrastructure, and reduce reliance on third-party hosting providers.</p></blockquote>
<p>The crypto space has been extremely bearish over the past 12 months. So much so, that several digital currency companies and mining facilities have entered bankruptcy proceedings as they are unable to keep up with the rising energy prices of Joe Biden’s America. They also cannot contend with the ongoing price dips being experienced by bitcoin and other mainstream forms of digital currency.</p>
<p>Some of the big names that come to mind when discussing crypto bankruptcies include the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/celsius-network-is-next-crypto-company-to-file-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">Celsius Network</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-lender-voyager-digital-files-chapter-11-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">Voyager Digital</a>, and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-hedge-fund-three-arrows-capital-is-now-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">Three Arrows Capital</a>, the latter being a crypto hedge fund. However, it is Celsius that arguably got things going in this direction. It is also one of the largest crypto companies out there and likely received the most attention when it decided to enter court proceedings as a means of shielding itself from angry customers and lenders.</p>
<p>However, it can be argued that the bankruptcies of these companies are nothing compared with the one that is currently underway for FTX, one of the largest digital currency exchanges in the history of the space. FTX first came to fruition in 2019 and rose through the ranks very quickly. It became a top-five crypto exchange by 2021 and it seemed like everything was really going well for the company, though things came crashing down in November of 2022.</p>
<h2>FTX Is the Biggest Bankruptcy Story</h2>
<p>During that month, the company’s chief executive Sam Bankman-Fried <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">announced FTX was enduring</a> a liquidity crunch and needed fast cash. Initially, it looked like the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">larger crypto firm Binance</a> was going to buy FTX out, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">though things didn’t quite</a> turn out that way, and it wasn’t long before FTX became <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">another bankrupt firm</a> and SBF was resigning from his post.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, Argo has debts exceeding $41 million. Peter Wall – CEO of the firm – says he hopes this new deal will allow it to remain functional during the bear market.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/argo-blockchain-sells-mining-facility-to-galaxy-digital-to-stay-afloat/">Argo Blockchain Sells Mining Facility to Galaxy Digital to Stay Afloat</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/argo-blockchain-sells-mining-facility-to-galaxy-digital-to-stay-afloat/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kraken Is Leaving Japan, Laying Off Several Employees</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kraken-is-leaving-japan-laying-off-several-employees/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kraken-is-leaving-japan-laying-off-several-employees/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 13:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Japan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jesse Powell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kraken]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76224</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Popular digital currency exchange Kraken has announced it is closing its Japan branch this month and laying off all its employees in the Land of the Rising Sun. Kraken Is Stepping Away from Japan The Japanese division of Kraken is called Payward Asia. In a recent blog post, the company mentioned that it’s going to<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kraken-is-leaving-japan-laying-off-several-employees/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kraken-is-leaving-japan-laying-off-several-employees/">Kraken Is Leaving Japan, Laying Off Several Employees</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Popular digital currency exchange Kraken has <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/crypto-exchange-kraken-to-shutter-its-japan-operations-after-global-layoffs/ar-AA15JTn8" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced it is closing</a> its Japan branch this month and laying off all its employees in the Land of the Rising Sun.</p>
<h2>Kraken Is Stepping Away from Japan</h2>
<p>The Japanese division of Kraken is called Payward Asia. In a recent blog post, the company mentioned that it’s going to be ceasing all its crypto trading services as of January 31, 2023. This will mark the second time Kraken has left the Japanese market, the first taking place in 2018. Up to that point, the company had been desperately trying to set up operations there for the past four years to no avail.</p>
<p>However, two years later in 2020, it made a successful attempt to establish a presence in the region after it was able to complete the necessary registration process with regulators.</p>
<p>The move is just another chalk on the ever-growing board of crypto casualties over the past several months. 2022 has been a very bad year for the digital currency industry, and while we’re only in the first month of 2023, it doesn’t look like this new era is bringing much recovery just yet. So many companies have fallen to the bearish conditions of the crypto space over the past 12 months, and analysts have no way of predicting what will happen before the year is out.</p>
<p>The news follows a long series of odd reports stemming from the Kraken exchange, a big one arriving in October of last year. It was announced during that time <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kraken-ceo-jesse-powell-is-leaving-his-post/" data-wpel-link="internal">that Kraken’s CEO Jesse Powell</a> was leaving his post following repeated allegations of semi-abusive behavior towards workers. From there, the exchange mentioned that it was going to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-exchange-kraken-is-cutting-off-russian-customers/" data-wpel-link="internal">be ceasing all relations</a> with Russian customers, and that all traders in that region would no longer gain access to the company’s services or products.</p>
<p>This news was shocking given that several months prior, the exchange stated that it would not comply with present sanctions delivered by the present U.S. <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-clarifies-everyday-russians-can-continue-to-use-our-services/" data-wpel-link="internal">administration against Russia</a> and that it would allow the country’s people to maintain their accounts and continue trading.</p>
<p>Kraken is also not the first company to announce layoffs following the start of the crypto bear market. Other big names in the “layoff department” include fellow crypto exchanges Gemini in New York (run by the Winklevoss Twins) and Coinbase in San Francisco, CA.</p>
<h2>So Many Layoffs Over the Past Year</h2>
<p>Gemini <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gemini-exchange-says-major-layoffs-are-coming/" data-wpel-link="internal">wound up releasing</a> as much as ten percent of its staff from employment. The company took flak when it was revealed that many of those who would be out of a job were informed via Zoom calls rather than in-person.</p>
<p>For Coinbase, things were even more <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-says-its-laying-off-several-employees/" data-wpel-link="internal">devastating as the company</a> ended up releasing approximately 18 percent of its staff following the announcement of huge hiring plans.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kraken-is-leaving-japan-laying-off-several-employees/">Kraken Is Leaving Japan, Laying Off Several Employees</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kraken-is-leaving-japan-laying-off-several-employees/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EOS Price Analysis: Risk of More Losses Below $0.95</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-0-95/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-0-95/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 05:38:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EOS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76590</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>EOS price started a fresh decline from the $1.08 resistance zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $1.0 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $1.04 the 4-hours chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-0-95/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-0-95/">EOS Price Analysis: Risk of More Losses Below $0.95</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>EOS price started a fresh decline from the $1.08 resistance zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $1.0 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $1.04 the 4-hours chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to decline if it stays below the $0.98 and $1.00 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>EOS price is struggling below $1.00 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-rally-could-extend-above-22k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. The price might attempt to recover if there is a clear move above $0.98.</em></p>
<h2>EOS Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, EOS price saw a fresh drop from the $1.10 zone against the US Dollar. The price traded below the $1.05 and $1.02 levels to enter a bearish zone.</p>
<p>There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $1.04 the 4-hours chart of the EOS/USD pair. The pair accelerated lower below the $0.98 support zone and settled well below the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-more-gains-possible-above-1/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>.</p>
<p>The bears pushed the price below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.8703 swing low to $1.094 high. On the downside, an immediate support is near the $0.950.</p>
<p>The 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.8703 swing low to $1.094 high is also near the $0.95 zone. The next key support is near the $0.935 level.</p>
<p>If there is a downside break below the $0.935 support, the price could test the $0.88 support in the near term. On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $0.98 level. The first major resistance is near the $1.00 level, above which the price might test the $1.080 level.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $1.08 level could start a steady increase towards the $1.15 level. Any more gains might send the price towards the $1.20 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_76591" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/EOS-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76591" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-76591" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/EOS-1.png" alt="EOS Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76591" class="wp-caption-text">EOS Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/EOSUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, EOS price is now trading below the $0.98 level and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could continue to decline if it stays below the $0.98 and $1.00 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4-hours MACD – The MACD for EOS/USD is gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4-hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $0.95 and $0.935.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $0.980 and $1.00.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-0-95/">EOS Price Analysis: Risk of More Losses Below $0.95</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-0-95/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Could Be Active Near $80</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-could-be-active-near-80/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-could-be-active-near-80/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 03:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76586</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin started a strong increase above $80 against the US Dollar. LTC price is now trading below $80 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $86.50 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair remains supported<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-could-be-active-near-80/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-could-be-active-near-80/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Could Be Active Near $80</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Litecoin started a strong increase above $80 against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>LTC price is now trading below $80 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $86.50 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair remains supported for more gains unless there is a clear move below $80.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Litecoin price is correcting gains from $92 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-rally-could-extend-above-22k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. LTC price could continue to move up if it remains well supported above the $80 level.</em></p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, there was a decent increase in bitcoin, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-rally-pauses-but-not-likely-over/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">ethereum</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-uptrend-in-place-above-0-40/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">ripple</a>, and litecoin against the US Dollar. Earlier, LTC formed a base above the $80 level and started a fresh increase.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above the $85 and $88 resistance levels. The price even climbed above the $90 level and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). However, the bears were active near the $92 zone. A high was formed near $91.14 and the price started a downside correction.</p>
<p>There was a move below the $85 level. The price traded below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $72.45 swing low to $91.14 high. There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $86.50 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>The price is now trading below $80 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). An immediate support is near the $81.80 level. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $72.45 swing low to $91.14 high.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $80 zone. A downside break below the $80 support might start a strong decline. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $84 and $85 levels. A clear move above the $85 level could pump the price towards the $92 level. The next major resistance sits near the $100 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_76587" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Litecoin-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76587" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-76587" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Litecoin-1.png" alt="Litecoin (LTC) Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76587" class="wp-caption-text">Litecoin (LTC) Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, litecoin price is clearly trading below $80 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price remains supported for more gains unless there is a clear move below $80.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LTC/USD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $80 and $75</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $85 and $92.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-could-be-active-near-80/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Could Be Active Near $80</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-could-be-active-near-80/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
