<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 03:10:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>BTC Endures Short-Term Dip Following Federal Reserve Warning</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/btc-endures-short-term-dip-following-federal-reserve-warning/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/btc-endures-short-term-dip-following-federal-reserve-warning/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 15:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[federal reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Janet Yellen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jerome Powell]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78413</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jerome Powell – the man at the head of the table in the Federal Reserve chambers – is getting ready to offer what many analysts call another hawkish speech, and they’re concerned about what his words could do to bitcoin and the rest of the crypto industry. The Federal Reserve is at It Again Over<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/btc-endures-short-term-dip-following-federal-reserve-warning/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/btc-endures-short-term-dip-following-federal-reserve-warning/">BTC Endures Short-Term Dip Following Federal Reserve Warning</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jerome Powell – the man at the head of the table in the Federal Reserve chambers – is getting ready to offer what many <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-in-stasis-below-27k-ahead-of-powell-speech/ar-AA1bpvB8" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">analysts call another hawkish</a> speech, and they’re concerned about what his words could do to bitcoin and the rest of the crypto industry.</p>
<h2>The Federal Reserve is at It Again</h2>
<p>Over the past year or so, every time the Federal Reserve does anything, bitcoin seems to get affected. In 2022, for example, the Federal Reserve regularly <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-fed-bitcoins-worst-enemy-right-now/" data-wpel-link="internal">hiked interest rates</a> as a means of fighting ongoing, record-high inflation in America.</p>
<p>These rate hikes didn’t really do much in terms of lowering the surging prices the nation was seeing. However, they <em>did</em> cause crypto prices to tank like they never had before. Also, with so many working-class people unable to afford the interest, they were instantly cut out of the American dream and could no longer get their hands on cars, homes, or items that would require loans as part of the purchasing process.</p>
<p>Right now, Powell hasn’t even given the speech yet, and already we’re seeing bitcoin take a few dips here and there. Shortly after the event was announced, bitcoin fell into the high $26,000 range. Prior to that, it had been trading for about $27,000 per unit. Marc Chandler – chief market strategist at Bannockburn Global Forex – commented in a recent market update:</p>
<blockquote><p>Hawkish comments from Fed officials and the first decline in continuing unemployment claims below 1.8 million in two months boosted U.S. rates, and the odds of a… rate hike rose to about 37 percent. This represents a near tripling of the probability in the past week.</p></blockquote>
<p>There is also wide speculation that the Federal Reserve will hike rates again if Congress cannot come to an agreement on the present issue surrounding the debt ceiling. Janet Yellen – the current Treasury Secretary – has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-janet-yellen-and-the-debt-ceiling-are-making-btc-look-good/" data-wpel-link="internal">warned that if the debt</a> ceiling isn’t raised, the U.S. is going to run out of money and become a bankrupt nation.</p>
<p>Right now, the nation is facing $31 trillion in debt, and House republicans – led by Speaker Kevin McCarthy – have stated that pushing things higher will result in far too much debt falling onto the shoulders of American taxpayers, and they’re reluctant to do as Yellen asks.</p>
<h2>More Rate Hikes Coming?</h2>
<p>Granted no agreement is made, some – such as Craig Shapiro of La Duc Trading – believe the Fed may step in. Shapiro said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Seems like Powell needs to take the rate hike odds up again today in order to be prepared to go again… if the debt ceiling debacle is tabled for a short-term resolution. Data remains too good right now with the SEP likely to show a lower YE23 U rate and higher PCE, both of which suggest the dots for 24 are way too low.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/btc-endures-short-term-dip-following-federal-reserve-warning/">BTC Endures Short-Term Dip Following Federal Reserve Warning</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/btc-endures-short-term-dip-following-federal-reserve-warning/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mark Shin of Colorado Charged with Massive Crypto Theft</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-shin-of-colorado-charged-with-massive-crypto-theft/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-shin-of-colorado-charged-with-massive-crypto-theft/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 13:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Theft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ICON Nation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mark Shin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78410</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A man in Aurora, Colorado has been accused of stealing roughly $9 million in crypto funds. 31-year-old Mark Shin has been charged with theft, cybercrime, and money laundering at the time of writing for allegedly taking part in a scheme back in April of 2020 through his home computer. Mark Shin: Stealer or Advantage Taker?<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-shin-of-colorado-charged-with-massive-crypto-theft/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-shin-of-colorado-charged-with-massive-crypto-theft/">Mark Shin of Colorado Charged with Massive Crypto Theft</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A man in Aurora, Colorado has been accused of <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/aurora-man-accused-of-9-million-cryptocurrency-theft/ar-AA1ble3a" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stealing roughly $9 million</a> in crypto funds. 31-year-old Mark Shin has been charged with <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/theft/" data-wpel-link="internal">theft</a>, cybercrime, and money laundering at the time of writing for allegedly taking part in a scheme back in April of 2020 through his home computer.</p>
<h2>Mark Shin: Stealer or Advantage Taker?</h2>
<p>Shin is believed to have noticed an “unintended vulnerability in the revision 9 update” of the ICON Nation cryptocurrency. Instead of reporting this to ICON Foundation/Nation, court documents allege that Shin took part in a scheme that ultimately drained the network and made him an instant digital millionaire. The documents state:</p>
<blockquote><p>Shin changed the vote/select delegate function 558 times over an 11-hour period to mint unauthorized ICX. From his personal computer, Shin minted and stole from the ICON Nation approximately 13,924,045 unauthorized ICX, which was roughly the equivalent of approximately $8,988,406.00 U.S. dollars at the time of the attack.</p></blockquote>
<p>Chris Decker, a defense attorney, issued the following statement regarding his feelings on the case:</p>
<blockquote><p>I love this case. I think it’s fascinating.</p></blockquote>
<p>Shin is arguing that he did not engage in thievery, but rather saw a “golden opportunity” and chose to take advantage. Decker said of the matter:</p>
<blockquote><p>Mr. Shin utilized the code that was written by this cryptocurrency to create his own mint or mint his own currency. So, he wasn’t taking property of another. He was creating new currency.</p></blockquote>
<p>George Brachler – legal analyst and former 18th Judicial District attorney – said this case is baffling and nothing like what he’s ever seen in nearly 30 years of serving the law. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I’ve only been doing this (legal work) [for] 28 years. I’ve never seen a case quite like this.</p></blockquote>
<p>He was also quick to say that he doesn’t think Shin’s argument of just trying to mint a new currency is going to be successful. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>I don’t think it will because he acts guilty. I mean, this guy doesn’t act like what he’s doing is above board. He creates a bunch of different accounts. He tries to take the cryptocurrency that he has ‘minted’ and sends it around to other crypto wallets to try to disguise who’s the owner and how much he has.</p></blockquote>
<p>Prosecutors are claiming that Shin used a spinning service called Tornado Cash to move all the money into other wallets to disguise where they originated from. Tornado Cash, at the time of writing, has been used to launder at least $7 billion. Shin said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The fact that I moved the money immediately after that is of no consequence to the fact that I minted it, and I didn’t steal it.</p></blockquote>
<h2>This Argument May Not Work</h2>
<p>Decker finished with:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think that this act undermines a general concern that people don’t quite understand how these programs work.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-shin-of-colorado-charged-with-massive-crypto-theft/">Mark Shin of Colorado Charged with Massive Crypto Theft</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-shin-of-colorado-charged-with-massive-crypto-theft/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Last May, as Bitcoin Fell, Smaller Altcoins Jumped Dramatically</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/last-may-as-bitcoin-fell-smaller-altcoins-jumped-dramatically/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/last-may-as-bitcoin-fell-smaller-altcoins-jumped-dramatically/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 17:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78394</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Something strange happened towards the latter half of May this year. While bitcoin and Ethereum – two of the largest and most mainstream digital currencies – were taking price dips, altcoins – like XRP (Ripple) and Litecoin – were exploding. Altcoins Rose Last May While BTC Suffered During that time, Litecoin and Ripple endured price<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/last-may-as-bitcoin-fell-smaller-altcoins-jumped-dramatically/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/last-may-as-bitcoin-fell-smaller-altcoins-jumped-dramatically/">Last May, as Bitcoin Fell, Smaller Altcoins Jumped Dramatically</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Something strange happened towards the latter half of May this year. While <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a> and Ethereum – two of the largest and most mainstream digital currencies – were taking price dips, altcoins – like XRP (Ripple) and Litecoin – <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/litecoin-xrp-and-other-altcoins-rise-wednesday-as-blue-chip-bitcoin-hits-a-lull/ar-AA1bk5EH" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">were exploding</a>.</p>
<h2>Altcoins Rose Last May While BTC Suffered</h2>
<p>During that time, Litecoin and Ripple endured price hikes of about five percent each, while others – like Sandbox – rose by as much as four percent. Axie also saw its price shoot up by a whopping eight percent. These numbers may not seem like much, but it’s unusual and interesting that this would happen, as these currencies often need to see bitcoin go up before they can follow suit.</p>
<p>The fact that they were able to travel in an entirely different price direction suggests that maybe the correlation between these assets and something larger like their daddy bitcoin are starting to thin out.</p>
<p>Some analysts believe this may have been the start of what they’re calling an “altcoin season.” This is typically when people (traders, investors, etc.) start to shift some of their attention away from larger, mainstream tokens like BTC and focus on smaller assets. As a result, these coins endure certain price hikes on a temporary basis, while some of the larger ones sink deeper into oblivion.</p>
<p>Still, the idea remains amongst many retail traders that bitcoin and Ethereum are “flight-to-safety” tokens, meaning that should things go wrong with the smaller tokens they invest in, they can always sell and allocate more of their wealth and portfolios to the latter two, thus bringing their statuses higher and giving themselves more stability.</p>
<p>One might assume that so long as bitcoin is there for them to enjoy, these investors feel safe enough to try other smaller coins out. Noelle Acheson – author of the “Crypto is Macro Now” newsletter – said that despite all this, volatility remains a problem in the industry at press time. She commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Like macro markets, juggling resilient stock prices with increasingly bleak economic data points, the crypto market is also dealing with duality. There are some signs of frothiness.</p></blockquote>
<p>She also mentioned that despite the traction surrounding the mentioned altcoins, activity remains relatively low for these and other less-known digital currencies, and that in the long term, prices are still down and haven’t quite recovered from the 2022 bear market. She commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>In spite of these hints of froth, activity is low. Prices are down more than ten percent on the month, and volumes are trending lower.</p></blockquote>
<h2>BTC Is Not in the Best Place</h2>
<p>Bitcoin and Ethereum are also largely down despite small price jumps over the past five months.</p>
<p>BTC, for example, was trading in the mid-$16K range at the end of 2022. At the time of writing, the asset has moved into the $27K region, though this doesn’t compare to the $68,000 all-time high it achieved two Novembers ago.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/last-may-as-bitcoin-fell-smaller-altcoins-jumped-dramatically/">Last May, as Bitcoin Fell, Smaller Altcoins Jumped Dramatically</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/last-may-as-bitcoin-fell-smaller-altcoins-jumped-dramatically/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kevin O&#8217;Leary: The U.S. Needs to Change Its Attitude on Crypto Regulation</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kevin-oleary-the-u-s-needs-to-change-its-attitude-on-crypto-regulation/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kevin-oleary-the-u-s-needs-to-change-its-attitude-on-crypto-regulation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kevin O'Leary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78392</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Kevin O’Leary of “Shark Tank” fame is worried about how the U.S. government is dealing with crypto regulation. He says the federal government is less concerned about policy and more concerned with taking fast action, and this is coming back to hurt innovation. Kevin O&#8217;Leary: All the U.S. Needs is Policy Right now, he says<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kevin-oleary-the-u-s-needs-to-change-its-attitude-on-crypto-regulation/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kevin-oleary-the-u-s-needs-to-change-its-attitude-on-crypto-regulation/">Kevin O&#8217;Leary: The U.S. Needs to Change Its Attitude on Crypto Regulation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Kevin O’Leary of “Shark Tank” fame is worried about how the U.S. <a href="https://www.thestreet.com/cryptocurrency/stablecoins/bitcoin-miami-kevin-oleary-are-stablecoins-the-future-of-investment-funds" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">government is dealing with</a> crypto regulation. He says the federal government is less concerned about policy and more concerned with taking fast action, and this is coming back to hurt innovation.</p>
<h2>Kevin O&#8217;Leary: All the U.S. Needs is Policy</h2>
<p>Right now, he says policy is all the U.S. needs when it comes to crypto. He commented that the government doesn’t need to do anything fancy or special. It just needs to implement the right rules to ensure the industry is safe and sound for all. O’Leary stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I&#8217;m not looking for the federal government to provide innovation. I&#8217;m looking for them to provide policy. We don&#8217;t need them to develop anything. What we&#8217;ll do is license multiple stable coins, all backed by the U.S. dollar, and let them compete in the market.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also said he thinks it’s very important that more action be taken to ensure all crypto companies are running on clean energy. This is an attitude he’s held for quite some time, going so far as to say a few years back that he would cease <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-bitcoin-mining-may-require-more-energy-than-180-countries/" data-wpel-link="internal">buying any crypto mined</a> in China given the country’s poor history with renewable energy (this was long before the country <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-crypto-mining-clampdown-in-china-is-not-over/" data-wpel-link="internal">outlawed crypto and</a> mining activity).</p>
<p>O’Leary was adamant that if crypto companies continued to walk the path that they’ve been walking over the past several years, the planet is going to suffer heavily. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>We have to listen to these people and realize we can&#8217;t mine coins using carbon offsets. We&#8217;ve got to go hydro; we&#8217;ve got to go nuclear. I am so glad I had to sell every share I had in a company that uses carbon offsets, because I see the writing on the wall and it&#8217;s not pretty.</p></blockquote>
<p>O’Leary isn’t the only person that has this attitude. Over the years, several reports have been written and published suggesting that crypto mining now utilizes more energy than most third-world or developing countries. In addition, big names like Elon Musk – the billionaire and South African entrepreneur behind companies like SpaceX and Tesla – have chimed in about crypto’s energy usage.</p>
<h2>Musk&#8217;s Attitude Towards Mining</h2>
<p>Not long ago, Musk made it clear he <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-permits-bitcoin-payments-for-tesla-vehicles/" data-wpel-link="internal">wanted Tesla customers to be able</a> to buy vehicles with bitcoin. This caused the price of the asset to shoot up, and everyone thought BTC was going to reach a new level of mainstream legitimacy.</p>
<p>However, it was not to be, as just a few weeks after that, Musk <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-has-taken-a-nasty-stumble-many-are-blaming-elon-musk/" data-wpel-link="internal">rescinded the decision</a>, claiming he was concerned about how much energy was being used to extract BTC from the blockchain and that he would only allow bitcoin-based purchases if miners were more transparent about their sources and used cleaner energy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kevin-oleary-the-u-s-needs-to-change-its-attitude-on-crypto-regulation/">Kevin O&#8217;Leary: The U.S. Needs to Change Its Attitude on Crypto Regulation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kevin-oleary-the-u-s-needs-to-change-its-attitude-on-crypto-regulation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Survey: Bitcoin&#8217;s &#8220;Safe Haven&#8221; Status is Growing</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/survey-bitcoins-safe-haven-status-is-growing/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/survey-bitcoins-safe-haven-status-is-growing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 13:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Safe Haven]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Treasurys]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78389</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A survey suggests that should the United States ever default, the public sees bitcoin as more of a “safe haven” than the U.S. dollar. Bitcoin Is a Bigger Safe Haven Than USD, Survey Says Things aren’t as strong as one would assume considering bitcoin only placed third on the list. The first “safe haven” viewed<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/survey-bitcoins-safe-haven-status-is-growing/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/survey-bitcoins-safe-haven-status-is-growing/">Survey: Bitcoin&#8217;s &#8220;Safe Haven&#8221; Status is Growing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A survey suggests that should the United States ever default, the public <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-would-be-more-trusted-than-the-dollar-as-a-safe-haven-if-the-us-defaults-survey-says/ar-AA1bdA1A" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">sees bitcoin as more</a> of a “safe haven” than the U.S. dollar.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Is a Bigger Safe Haven Than USD, Survey Says</h2>
<p>Things aren’t as strong as one would assume considering bitcoin only placed third on the list. The first “safe haven” viewed by participants was gold, meaning that if the U.S. defaults, most of these people would want to allocate their portfolios and wealth to gold. After that came Treasurys, and bitcoin placed third, meaning it’s still got a way to go in terms of earning general trust.</p>
<p>However, the news is good in that it means many people now feel safer towards bitcoin than they do fiat currency, and the asset has come a long way in a relatively short period. Bitcoin, as we all remember, has only been around since 2009. That’s about 14 years at this stage, so the fact that people can now see it in a stronger light than they do USD is a good sign that the industry is doing something right.</p>
<p>The survey in question was the Markets Live Pulse survey conducted by <em>Bloomberg</em>. The results suggest that about eight percent (or slightly less) see bitcoin as a stronger “safe haven” when compared to USD. This isn’t much, but it’s a step forward.</p>
<p>There are likely many reasons for this, the first one being that banks throughout the U.S. and Europe are crashing and burning like nobody’s business. Right now, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-provide-their-thoughts-on-latest-bitcoin-rally/" data-wpel-link="internal">institutions such as</a> First Republic, Signature, and Silicon Valley have all fallen into heaps of failure and are no longer in operation throughout America. Thus, the institutions that once came off as totally safe, sound, and secure are taking on the shape of unstable firms that can lose your coins or dollar bills the minute something troublesome happens.</p>
<p>The other reason could be that we have so many incapable people running the financial scene in the U.S. People like Janet Yellen, the Treasury Secretary, who <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-fans-may-want-to-wait-on-their-calls-for-regulation/" data-wpel-link="internal">in the past</a>, has commented that she felt inflation was a problem that would resolve itself. Also, there’s Jerome Powell, who despite all the trouble that he’s caused, still only resorts <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-fed-bitcoins-worst-enemy-right-now/" data-wpel-link="internal">to hiking interest rates</a> as a means of combating inflation.</p>
<h2>Treasurys Shouldn&#8217;t Be This High</h2>
<p>The interest rate hikes have done nothing but cause people to be shut out of the American dream. They can no longer afford cars, homes, or other large (yet necessary) items due to their inability to pay high interest. In addition, these interest rate hikes caused crypto prices to crash and burn throughout 2022.</p>
<p>With all this in mind, however, it’s a little shocking (and scary) to think people still trust Treasurys more than they do bitcoin given they placed second on the survey.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/survey-bitcoins-safe-haven-status-is-growing/">Survey: Bitcoin&#8217;s &#8220;Safe Haven&#8221; Status is Growing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/survey-bitcoins-safe-haven-status-is-growing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Rally Gains Pace Above $300</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-rally-gains-pace-above-300/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-rally-gains-pace-above-300/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 03:18:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78999</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin cash started a strong increase above the $225 and $250 levels against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above the $280 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $270.00 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-rally-gains-pace-above-300/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-rally-gains-pace-above-300/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Rally Gains Pace Above $300</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin cash started a strong increase above the $225 and $250 levels against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above the $280 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $270.00 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair must clear $320 and $325 to continue higher in the near term.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin cash price is climbing above $300 against the US Dollar, outperforming <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-bulls-in-control-above-29500/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. BCH/USD could start a fresh surge if it clears the $325 level.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin cash price formed a decent support base above the $180 level. BCH started a decent increase and was able to clear the $225 resistance zone.</p>
<p>The price climbed above the $250 and $280 resistance levels. It even spiked above $300 and traded as high as $326.42. It is now trading above the $280 zone and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-rally-seems-unstoppable-above-130/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. The current price action is positive, suggesting high chances of more gains.</p>
<p>There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $270.00 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $320 level.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $325 level, above which the price may perhaps rise toward the $350 level. Any more gains above $350 could set the pace for a move toward the $400 level.</p>
<p>Immediate support on the downside is near the $300 level or the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $220 swing low to the $326 high. The first major support sits near the $270 level and the trend line region.</p>
<p>The trend line is also near the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $220 swing low to the $326 high. The next support is near the $245 zone, below which the bears might aim for $225. The next target for them may perhaps be near the $200 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_79000" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Bitcoin-Cash-4.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79000" class="size-full wp-image-79000" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Bitcoin-Cash-4.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash Price" width="1835" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-79000" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Cash Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BCHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Bitcoin cash price is now trading above the $280 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price must clear $225 and $250 to continue higher in the near term.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for BCH/USD is gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BCH/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $300 and $272.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $320 and $325.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-rally-gains-pace-above-300/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Rally Gains Pace Above $300</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-rally-gains-pace-above-300/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The United Kingdom Wants Gambling Laws to Apply to Crypto Trading</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-united-kingdom-wants-gambling-laws-to-apply-to-crypto-trading/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-united-kingdom-wants-gambling-laws-to-apply-to-crypto-trading/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto-regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gambling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United Kingdom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78379</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is investing in crypto equivalent to gambling? That’s how the United Kingdom sees it, and leaders are suggesting that crypto be regulated in the same way the U.K. oversees gambling activities. The United Kingdom Sees Crypto Investing as Gambling To an extent, one can argue that investing in crypto is sort of a gamble. Whenever<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-united-kingdom-wants-gambling-laws-to-apply-to-crypto-trading/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-united-kingdom-wants-gambling-laws-to-apply-to-crypto-trading/">The United Kingdom Wants Gambling Laws to Apply to Crypto Trading</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is investing in crypto equivalent to gambling? That’s how the United Kingdom sees it, and leaders are <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2023/may/17/cryptocurrency-trading-in-uk-should-be-regulated-as-form-of-gambling-say-mps?ref=dessenter.ghost.io" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">suggesting that crypto be regulated</a> in the same way the U.K. oversees gambling activities.</p>
<h2>The United Kingdom Sees Crypto Investing as Gambling</h2>
<p>To an extent, one can argue that investing in crypto is sort of a gamble. Whenever you buy bitcoin, Ethereum, or some other digital asset, you’re taking a chance… A chance that it could go down or up. You don’t know where it will be.</p>
<p>The same idea applies to sitting down at a blackjack table. You could win big, or you could lose it all in a matter of minutes. In that sense, crypto and gambling are one and the same, and this is the idea that’s making its way into the financial operations of the United Kingdom.</p>
<p>U.K. authorities believe that like gambling, investing in crypto can be quite addictive, and thus traders won’t always know when to stop. Thus, necessary rules must be put in place to protect people from themselves. Conservative MP and Treasury committee chair Harriett Baldwin explained in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Effective regulation is clearly needed to protect consumers from harm, as well as to support productive innovation in the U.K.’s financial services industry. However, with no intrinsic value, huge price volatility, and no discernible social good, consumer trading of cryptocurrencies like bitcoin more closely resembles gambling than a financial service and should be regulated as such. By betting on these unbacked ‘tokens,’ consumers should be aware that all their money could be lost.</p></blockquote>
<p>Right now, nothing is set in stone, and laws and rules are merely being suggested to the U.K. Parliament. However, should these rules pass, many analysts believe they will eventually influence future crypto regulations in the United Kingdom. Some even believe they will implement themselves <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/european-union-passes-heavy-string-of-new-crypto-regulations/" data-wpel-link="internal">into the MiCA</a> regulations recently passed by the European Union (EU).</p>
<p>Not everyone is happy about what’s going on. For example, a special committee under the Treasury has released a report claiming that crypto and blockchain are part of financial innovations that cannot – and should not – be governed under the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA), which is where crypto regulation would occur in the U.K. The report said:</p>
<blockquote><p>It is not the government’s role to promote particular technological innovations for their own sake.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Some People Have Lost Everything</h2>
<p>Like gambling, there have been many people out that have ultimately gone nuts whenever a bull market has hit. They put all their money into something, expecting and believing with all their might that they will strike it rich within a set period.</p>
<p>However, this isn’t always the case. Crypto is often very volatile, and in years such as 2018 and 2022, there have been many instances of crypto traders losing all they have.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-united-kingdom-wants-gambling-laws-to-apply-to-crypto-trading/">The United Kingdom Wants Gambling Laws to Apply to Crypto Trading</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-united-kingdom-wants-gambling-laws-to-apply-to-crypto-trading/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>France is Trying to Attract American Crypto Companies</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/france-is-trying-to-attract-american-crypto-companies/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/france-is-trying-to-attract-american-crypto-companies/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 15:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto-regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[France]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78377</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Do you run a cryptocurrency company in America and you’re getting tired of the regulatory confusion surrounding your industry? Are you sick of Gary Gensler and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) breathing down the back of your neck? If that’s the case, you may want to give France a try! France Wants American Crypto<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/france-is-trying-to-attract-american-crypto-companies/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/france-is-trying-to-attract-american-crypto-companies/">France is Trying to Attract American Crypto Companies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you run a cryptocurrency company in America and you’re getting tired of the regulatory confusion surrounding your industry? Are you sick of Gary Gensler and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) breathing down the back of your neck? If that’s the case, <a href="https://invezz.com/news/2023/05/17/france-welcomes-cryptocurrency-firms-fleeing-u-s-regulatory-uncertainty/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">you may want to give</a> France a try!</p>
<h2>France Wants American Crypto Firms</h2>
<p>France has commented that it will welcome all companies and enterprises in America devoted to blockchain and crypto as it’s aiming to build up its digital infrastructure and offerings. Regulators are currently working to establish a new framework that will make it so that the U.S. can benefit from its growing crypto environment. The goal is to also appeal to more crypto companies in the United States and appear more inviting – potentially inspiring some of them to move 4,000 miles across the Atlantic and set up stations within the country’s borders.</p>
<p>The United States has long talked about crypto regulation, and these calls for implementing it have only gotten stronger since last November’s <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX collapse</a>. Once one of the top digital currency exchanges, FTX fell into a heaping pile of bankruptcy and fraud, and it really scared American leaders and convinced them that the crypto industry was nothing but a bunch of criminals and fraudsters working together to gain access to the funds of innocent investors.</p>
<p>However, while the U.S. may be all about implementing crypto regulation, its methods for doing so have been questionable. The integration of regulation has fallen primarily on the shoulders of Gary Gensler, the head of the SEC, and it’s become clear he’s not playing fair or clean. In fact, it appears persecution is the only tactic the old geezer is willing to try. Thus far, several big names in crypto – like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">Coinbase</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/" data-wpel-link="internal">Kraken</a> – have fallen victim to his antics, and many analysts are worried about what Gensler is doing to innovation and growth when it comes to crypto in the U.S.</p>
<h2>Trying to Create the Right Rules</h2>
<p>France has clearly taken notice of what’s going on in the land of the free and the home of the brave, and it wants to give entrepreneurs in the blockchain space a little leeway. For the most part, the European Union (EU) appears to be way ahead of the game when it comes to crypto regulation in that it recently implemented the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/european-union-passes-heavy-string-of-new-crypto-regulations/" data-wpel-link="internal">new MiCA rules</a>. France, being part of the EU, stands to gain a lot of traction in the coming weeks when it comes to crypto, though some things remain up in the air.</p>
<p>For example, right now, France is working on the types of crypto influences that can promote crypto business, as specific laws haven’t been set in stone, though this will likely be established firmly before we know it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/france-is-trying-to-attract-american-crypto-companies/">France is Trying to Attract American Crypto Companies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/france-is-trying-to-attract-american-crypto-companies/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blockchain Firm Jia Raises More Than $5 Million in New Funding</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-firm-jia-raises-more-than-5-million-in-new-funding/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-firm-jia-raises-more-than-5-million-in-new-funding/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 13:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zach Marks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78374</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jia is a blockchain-based fintech organization that offers small businesses and emerging markets the loans they need to operate and stay afloat. In recent news, the company announced that it had secured more than $4 million in seed funding, while another $1 million (for a total of $5 million) was delivered to assist its commitment<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-firm-jia-raises-more-than-5-million-in-new-funding/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-firm-jia-raises-more-than-5-million-in-new-funding/">Blockchain Firm Jia Raises More Than $5 Million in New Funding</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jia is a blockchain-based fintech organization <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/jia-blockchain-based-lender-small-090101365.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">that offers small businesses and</a> emerging markets the loans they need to operate and stay afloat. In recent news, the company announced that it had secured more than $4 million in seed funding, while another $1 million (for a total of $5 million) was delivered to assist its commitment to on-chain liquidity.</p>
<h2>What Will Jia Do with the Money?</h2>
<p>The funding round featured the participation of well-known <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/blockchain/" data-wpel-link="internal">blockchain</a> and crypto firms including Block Tower, TCG Crypto, Hashed Emergent, Saison Capital, and Global Coin Research. In addition to the companies, several individual angel investors – including Packy McCormick, the founder of Not Boring, and Anand Lyer of Canonical Crypto – also donated funds to help the company move forward.</p>
<p>Jia says it will use the money to boost its operations in many up-and-coming or third-world nations like Kenya and the Philippines. It will also explore a wide array of new markets in regions such as Asia, Latin America, and West Africa. The idea is that many of these areas have seen their standard financial arenas suffer in recent years, and blockchain can assist them greatly.</p>
<p>The company was founded by Zach Marks, Ivan Orone, Yuting Wang, and Cheng Cheng. All previously worked at a firm called Tala and got to know each other in their previous positions. The company works to garner decentralized finance loans, which are then sent to borrowers.</p>
<p>Granted they repay the loans within certain timeframes they’re rewarded with special token offerings. These tokens can then be redeemed at rates based on Jia’s profits. CEO and co-founder Marks said in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>The idea is to provide affordable financing for micro-businesses, and when they repay, they become owners by getting token rewards… The loans range in size from $200 up to $5,000… They are competitively priced. We charge about a third the interest rate of the typical consumer fintech lender.</p></blockquote>
<h2>How It Gets Customers</h2>
<p>The way Jia finds partners and customers is by utilizing their local apps. Among the many customers the firm currently serves is Ilara Health, a medical inventory company that works with over 2,000 small clinics. Marks said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Ilara’s focus is on helping clinics grow by selling medicine [and] low-cost diagnostic devices. They don&#8217;t want to deal with credit risk[s] on their balance sheet, so we stepped in to finance an inventory financing program for them. We get access to proprietary data on these clinics, which helps us underwrite in a way that banks and other lenders can&#8217;t… What is exciting in what we&#8217;re doing is opening the world&#8217;s capital to MSMEs so they can receive affordable financing. Jia is not just providing financing. We are providing a path to economic resilience and this opportunity to build wealth in a new way that hasn&#8217;t been done before.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-firm-jia-raises-more-than-5-million-in-new-funding/">Blockchain Firm Jia Raises More Than $5 Million in New Funding</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-firm-jia-raises-more-than-5-million-in-new-funding/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=3893 metric#misses=5 metric#hit-ratio=99.9 metric#bytes=6629195 metric#prefetches=400 metric#store-reads=16 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=405 metric#store-misses=0 metric#sql-queries=17 metric#ms-total=231.94 metric#ms-cache=20.89 metric#ms-cache-avg=1.2285 metric#ms-cache-ratio=9.0 -->
