<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 03:20:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/cropped-fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>CFTC Commissioner: We Can&#8217;t Stop All the Crypto Fraud</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cftc-commissioner-we-cant-stop-all-the-crypto-fraud/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 17:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CFTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christy Goldsmith Romero]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto fraud]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78494</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) has warned that while it’s doing all it can to end crypto fraud, it admitted that there’s nothing it can do about all the illicit activity out there, and thus there’s likely to be things here and there that vanish from its radar or go unnoticed. The CFTC Doesn&#8217;t [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cftc-commissioner-we-cant-stop-all-the-crypto-fraud/">CFTC Commissioner: We Can&#8217;t Stop All the Crypto Fraud</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) has <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/no-way-to-police-all-cryptocurrency-fraud-cftc-commissioner-says/ar-AA1bCRU5">warned that while it’s doing</a> all it can to end crypto fraud, it admitted that there’s nothing it can do about all the illicit activity out there, and thus there’s likely to be things here and there that vanish from its radar or go unnoticed.</p>
<h2>The CFTC Doesn&#8217;t Have that Much Power</h2>
<p>Christy Goldsmith Romero – one of five commissioners at the CFTC – announced in a recent interview that crypto cases account for roughly 20 percent (one fifth) of all the fraud cases the organization is overseeing. Among the present items it’s looking at include civil cases against both Binance and FTX, which are (or were) major digital trading platforms. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>There&#8217;s just a lot of fraud in the space. There&#8217;s no way we can police all the fraud, but we&#8217;ve got to do something.</p></blockquote>
<p>She also mentioned that she takes serious issue with the idea that the CFTC is somehow considered lighter or “friendlier” than its rival the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), which is presently run by head Gary Gensler. Over the past several months, the SEC has been more involved in policing crypto activity. Not long ago, the agency went after Kraken and Coinbase.</p>
<p>In the case of the former, the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/">company was forced to end</a> all its staking activities and part with a $30 million penalty fee. With the latter, a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/">Wells notice was sent</a> to executives, informing them that formal charges were likely on their way. The executives took serious issue with these threats because they allegedly met with representatives of the SEC many times over a nine-year period to ensure the company was fully compliant.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, Romero doesn’t want to be seen as the easier of the two agencies. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I don&#8217;t like the idea that somehow the CFTC is light touch. &#8216;Light touch regulator&#8217; would never be written on my tombstone.</p></blockquote>
<p>Right now, the CFTC <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cftc-sues-binance-alleging-financial-violations/">is suing Binance</a> – one of the largest and most popular crypto exchanges in the world – because it allegedly violated the Commodity Exchange Act. CFTC chair Rostin Behnam claimed:</p>
<blockquote><p>For years, Binance knew they were violating CFTC rules, working actively to both keep the money flowing and avoid compliance. This should be a warning to anyone in the digital asset world that the CFTC will not tolerate willful avoidance of U.S. law.</p></blockquote>
<h2>So Many Types of Fraud</h2>
<p>Crypto fraud has taken on many forms in recent years. One of the most common (and more modern) forms has been <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/romance-scams/">romance scams</a>, which usually involve people chasing down others looking for love online.</p>
<p>Once they narrow in on a victim and garner their trust, they get them to invest in a phony crypto platform that’s controlled by their malicious brethren. They then block them from making withdrawals.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cftc-commissioner-we-cant-stop-all-the-crypto-fraud/">CFTC Commissioner: We Can&#8217;t Stop All the Crypto Fraud</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mathew McDermott: Blockchain Is an Unrivaled Technology</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mathew-mcdermott-blockchain-is-an-unrivaled-technology/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 15:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mathew McDermott]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78492</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mathew McDermott – a managing director of Goldman Sachs, one of the biggest financial companies in the world – says he thinks blockchain technology is well on its way to creating a sound new financial system that will never be rivaled or overshadowed. Mathew McDermott on the Future of Blockchain In a recent interview, McDermott [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mathew-mcdermott-blockchain-is-an-unrivaled-technology/">Mathew McDermott: Blockchain Is an Unrivaled Technology</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mathew McDermott – a managing director of Goldman Sachs, one of the biggest financial companies in the world – says he thinks blockchain technology is well <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/savingandinvesting/future-of-finance-goldmans-mcdermott-on-how-blockchain-tech-will-produce-a-profoundly-different-financial-system/ar-AA1bDbpS">on its way to creating</a> a sound new financial system that will never be rivaled or overshadowed.</p>
<h2>Mathew McDermott on the Future of Blockchain</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, McDermott explained his thoughts and feelings towards blockchain and how Goldman plans to integrate the technology into its systems in the coming future. As the head of the company’s digital assets division, McDermott stated that <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/blockchain/">blockchain</a> is likely to really help people do their jobs better. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>We&#8217;ve spent a lot of time recently talking in closed sessions with regulators and central bankers and the like, but I think commercially that sometimes it gets a little lost on people, but there are two real core areas. First, the tokenization and digitizing the lifecycle of different asset classes. It’s about creating efficiencies from inception (from issuance through post-trade), and we see a huge value opportunity there when it manifests itself at scale. The second area… is collateral mobility. A lot of the systems we use are probably as old as me and there are inefficiencies in those. In the movement of collateral from one custodian to another, you can’t be as precise as one would like, in terms of liquidity, which creates inefficiencies. There are certain risk profiles and trades you can totally transform [using] DLT [distributed ledger technology] because of that precision, that settlement finality.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Providing Benefits to Customers</h2>
<p>He also said that there are a multitude of financial companies and banks out there doing all they can to integrate blockchain in some way given that they see the benefits of the technology and what it can do for customers. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>For what [it is] worth, U.S. banks are typically focused on the private blockchains [now]. In client discussions, that tends to be where they want to play because of the control, privacy, security, KYC, all the things you’d expect. I think as people get more familiar with the technology, they’ll see the value that it adds. Web3 is all about empowering the individual, and I genuinely believe one of the biggest beneficiaries of this technology is going to be wealth management clients and family offices because they’re going to get greater access to investment opportunities. There will just be more liquidity in the market because you’re going to start seeing different marketplaces emerge. As public blockchains improve (there’s probably a nicer way to put it, as they <em>mature</em>), and people get more comfortable with them, opportunities will present themselves. I do think it’s probably a few years away, but I think that’s the way it really [must] evolve for regulators and institutions to be completely comfortable with it.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mathew-mcdermott-blockchain-is-an-unrivaled-technology/">Mathew McDermott: Blockchain Is an Unrivaled Technology</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Arguments Against Crypto Mining May Be Based on Untrue Facts</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-arguments-against-crypto-mining-may-be-based-on-untrue-facts/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 13:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Greenidge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[William Hall]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78482</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The crypto mining debate has raged for years, but it appears the fight is taking stronger precedence in recent weeks. Is Crypto Mining a Damaging Enterprise? Maybe Not&#8230; There have been many reports published, over some time, claiming that crypto mining is putting the planet in harm’s way. They say there are several developing nations [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-arguments-against-crypto-mining-may-be-based-on-untrue-facts/">The Arguments Against Crypto Mining May Be Based on Untrue Facts</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto mining debate has raged for years, but it appears the fight is <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/the-bitcoin-mining-debate-is-ignoring-the-people-most-affected-1032346362">taking stronger precedence</a> in recent weeks.</p>
<h2>Is Crypto Mining a Damaging Enterprise? Maybe Not&#8230;</h2>
<p>There have been many reports published, over some time, claiming that crypto mining is putting the planet in harm’s way. They say there are <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-bitcoin-mining-may-require-more-energy-than-180-countries/">several developing nations that</a> do not use the same amount of energy as crypto mining facilities. In addition, there are several arguments that say the pollution caused by these companies is doing a lot of damage to the environment.</p>
<p>New York Assemblywoman Anna Kelles is one of the politicians today that supported her home state’s <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/some-want-the-crypto-moratorium-in-new-york-to-last-longer/">implementation of a crypto moratorium</a>. The law is disallowing all digital currency mining companies from setting up shop in the Empire State granted they do not use renewable energy.</p>
<p>Kelles explained in a recent testimony to Congress the damages that are allegedly caused by crypto mining firms. She has taken issue with the many mining companies that currently call New York home, in particular large ones like Greenidge, and she believes they’re making life difficult for residents. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Facilities like Greenidge also negatively impact aquatic life, killing thousands of fish every year and increasing the risk of harmful algal bloom outbreaks that are toxic for both wildlife and humans.</p></blockquote>
<p>The problem with arguments like these, however, is that they are largely based on information that has either been proven untrue at this stage, or instead stem from things that are not fully verified or even understood.</p>
<p>Steve Griffin – a native of New York’s Yates County and the CEO Of the Finger Lake Economic Development Center – recently stated that many of the arguments being made by individuals like Kelles are completely overblown. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>We know the value and the importance of the lakes&#8217; worth and in our environment or climate. I mean, we&#8217;re a big agricultural community. We know what the value is of the climate. We wouldn&#8217;t want to incentivize anything that was going to clearly negatively impact that.</p></blockquote>
<p>William Hall is the mayor of a town called Dresden, where Greenidge has set up its headquarters. He says that nobody has come out to see the company in action, and thus they cannot say for sure that the company is doing tons of damage to the atmosphere.</p>
<h2>Come and See!</h2>
<p>He also said that he’s tired of the ongoing negative reports that people are creating about crypto mining companies and says he would like to see something positive mentioned occasionally. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Nobody has ever come to talk to us about it. We need people from somewhere to take an interest, to come talk to the people that are benefitting [from Greenidge’s presence], not the anti-[Greenidge] people that don’t even live here.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-arguments-against-crypto-mining-may-be-based-on-untrue-facts/">The Arguments Against Crypto Mining May Be Based on Untrue Facts</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Faces Accusations that It Mixed Customer and Company Funds</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-faces-accusations-that-it-mixed-customer-and-company-funds/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 17:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CFTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78479</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance – the largest and most popular digital currency exchange – is in hot water again after former insiders alleged that the exchange combined funds from customers with those of the company. What Did Binance Do? In what could be argued as taking a page out of the FTX playbook, Binance is accused of not [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-faces-accusations-that-it-mixed-customer-and-company-funds/">Binance Faces Accusations that It Mixed Customer and Company Funds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance – the largest and most popular digital currency exchange – is in <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/23/crypto-giant-binance-commingled-customer-funds-and-company-revenue-former-insiders-say.html">hot water again after former</a> insiders alleged that the exchange combined funds from customers with those of the company.</p>
<h2>What Did Binance Do?</h2>
<p>In what could be argued as taking a page out of the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/">FTX</a> playbook, Binance is accused of not keeping customer and company funds separate. This would be a breach of U.S. financial rules. Binance has denied any wrongdoing.</p>
<p>One of the insiders claims that the total of the commingled money is in the billions, and that this occurred almost daily through accounts the company had with the now <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-provide-their-thoughts-on-latest-bitcoin-rally/">defunct Silvergate Bank</a>. As it stands, various news platforms such as Reuters have conducted analyses of Binance’s financial transactions, yet they cannot find (at least for now) evidence suggesting that what the insiders say is true.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the claims arouse suspicion and concern in digital currency traders given this is exactly what FTX is accused of having done, and for some time, Binance and FTX <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/">were working together</a>. One needs to wonder if perhaps the latter’s bad business protocols didn’t rub off on the former.</p>
<p>In a statement, SEC commissioner Gary Gensler says many crypto exchanges are guilty of offering securities after they failed to register as broker-dealers, thus ensuring that their clients’ money would be protected and separated from all corporate assets and profit funds. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Their business models tend to be built on taking customer funds, commingling it.</p></blockquote>
<p>Binance spokesperson Brad Jaffe came out to say that Binance has not committed any crimes, nor is it guilty of what it’s being accused of. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>These accounts were not used to accept user deposits. They were used to facilitate user purchases. There was no commingling at any time because these are 100 percent corporate funds.</p></blockquote>
<p>Indeed, the situation is very reminiscent of FTX, a crypto exchange that fell into a heaping pile of bankruptcy and fraud last November. Following the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/">announcement of its bankruptcy</a>, the company’s head honcho Sam Bankman-Fried was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftxs-disgraced-founder-has-been-arrested/">arrested in the Bahamas</a> after he was accused of commingling his firm’s money with that of customers. He was also charged with using customer funds to pay off loans with his other firm Alameda Research and to invest in luxury Bahamian real estate.</p>
<p>At the present time, Binance is <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cftc-sues-binance-alleging-financial-violations/">also facing scrutiny from</a> the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), which is suing the exchange for allegedly violating the Commodity Exchange Act.</p>
<h2>Further Legal Issues</h2>
<p>CFTC chair Rostin Behnam said:</p>
<blockquote><p>For years, Binance knew they were violating CFTC rules, working actively to both keep the money flowing and avoid compliance. This should be a warning to anyone in the digital asset world that the CFTC will not tolerate willful avoidance of U.S. law.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-faces-accusations-that-it-mixed-customer-and-company-funds/">Binance Faces Accusations that It Mixed Customer and Company Funds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Michael Saylor Hints at Potential Bull Run for BTC</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-hints-at-potential-bull-run-for-btc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 15:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Saylor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroStrategy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78476</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Saylor – the former CEO of software giant MicroStrategy – is predicting big things for bitcoin. Michael Saylor Is Still a BTC Fan Not long ago, Saylor issued a separate interview that clearly showed him to be a full bitcoin maximalist. He insinuated that he would never live it down, nor would he ever [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-hints-at-potential-bull-run-for-btc/">Michael Saylor Hints at Potential Bull Run for BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Michael Saylor – the former CEO of software giant MicroStrategy – is predicting big <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-has-bottomed-and-the-worlds-biggest-cryptocurrency-is-on-a-new-bull-run-microstrategys-michael-saylor-says/ar-AA1bx3Ui">things for bitcoin</a>.</p>
<h2>Michael Saylor Is Still a BTC Fan</h2>
<p>Not long ago, Saylor issued a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-bitcoin-is-the-future/">separate interview</a> that clearly showed him to be a full bitcoin maximalist. He insinuated that he would never live it down, nor would he ever lose hope that the world’s number one digital currency by market capitalization would amount to something. In this more recent interview, he took his ideas and comments to the next level.</p>
<p>He stated that he thinks a regulatory crackdown on digital markets will ultimately work well for the asset. In addition, he said that the next halving – currently scheduled for 2024 – will help bring BTC to a new level of trading and appreciation. Saylor commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think the crypto tokens and crypto securities are going to be regulated, perhaps out of existence. Bitcoin is the most secure network. It&#8217;s the most secure asset. Everything else has got a black cloud hanging over it. You&#8217;re going to see a consistent flow of capital flowing from the rest of the crypto ecosystem [into] bitcoin.</p></blockquote>
<p>Saylor has had a very long (and up and down) history with crypto. First catching the bitcoin bug in late 2020, he began investing his company’s reserves in the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-microstrategy-bitcoin-bet-is-already-paying-off-big-time/">asset in August of that</a> year. When he first started to make profits, additional investments came, and at first, it looked like everything was going his way.</p>
<p>However, in early 2022, when the market began to crash, Saylor continued to invest in BTC even though losses were beginning to pile up, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-buys-more-btc-despite-ongoing-crash/">and this behavior continued</a> despite what has come to be known as one of the worst bear markets in the history of crypto. Before long, he had put his company into billions of dollars and debt, and the world saw him <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-btc-bull-and-microstrategy-chief-executive-steps-down/">resigning from the CEO</a> post he had held for over 30 years.</p>
<p>Despite all the issues he’s endured, Saylor still believes in BTC. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The FASB initiative to adopt fair value accounting is a very auspicious development.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Working Out the Kinks</h2>
<p>He further commented that while the industry is enduring “growing pains,” here and there, this is to be expected from something that’s still very much in an infant-like state. He mentioned that bitcoin and crypto need to go through these hindrances to be developed into lasting, strong tools that investors can truly benefit from. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Nearly all of the bad leverage has been squeezed out. Everyone in the business of shorting bitcoin, rehypothecating bitcoin, loaning bitcoin, they&#8217;ve all [gone] bankrupt. The remaining exchanges where you can short it are under a massive amount of regulatory pressure. I think bitcoin [has] found the bottom. I think the leverage is out of it. I think we&#8217;re on a bull run.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-hints-at-potential-bull-run-for-btc/">Michael Saylor Hints at Potential Bull Run for BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Powell Announces Potential Pause to Rate Hikes; BTC Slips</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/powell-announces-potential-pause-to-rate-hikes-btc-slips/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 13:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jerome Powell]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78474</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jerome Powell – the head of the Fed – has announced that due to ongoing stress endured by the American banking system, he and his cronies will likely ease their hiking of interest rates. Strangely, the news has not done great things for bitcoin or crypto. In fact, prices took a small and temporary dive [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/powell-announces-potential-pause-to-rate-hikes-btc-slips/">Powell Announces Potential Pause to Rate Hikes; BTC Slips</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jerome Powell – the head of the Fed – has <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-ethereum-dogecoin-drop-after-powells-dovish-comments-trader-predicts-king-crypto-soaring-to-300000/ar-AA1bv0No">announced that due to ongoing</a> stress endured by the American banking system, he and his cronies will likely ease their hiking of interest rates. Strangely, the news has not done great things for bitcoin or crypto. In fact, prices took a small and temporary dive following the announcement.</p>
<h2>Jerome Powell Hints at Potential Curb to Rate Hikes</h2>
<p>This is arguably the attitude Powell should have had a long time ago. When banks are failing left and right, as they’ve been doing over the past few months, one does not seek to put more financial stress on a country and its people. Rather, one steps back, assesses the damage, and tries to ease the problems as best they can.</p>
<p>This, however, is not what Powell has done. Rather, rate hikes have <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-shows-great-resilience-in-face-of-interest-rate-hikes/">continued into 2023</a>, and while the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-provide-their-thoughts-on-latest-bitcoin-rally/">banking crisis</a> has indeed allowed bitcoin and its altcoin cousins to recover somewhat from the dismal days of 2022 and the crypto winter it brought on, things are not quite where they need to be, and there’s still plenty of room to heal for the world’s number one digital asset by market cap.</p>
<p>Edward Moya – senior market analyst at OANDA – commented in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>A month ago, bitcoin was surging, passing the $30,000 level for the first time since the summer of 2022. Regional banking concerns and rising Fed rate cut bets provided a lot of support for cryptos. The bullish catalysts have now faded away, and so has roughly 30 percent of this year&#8217;s rally.  Bitcoin did not get any favor from [the] SEC’s Gensler earlier in the week, just the standard comments on how rules are already in place. The regulatory question remains the key for the crypto verse, and traders will have to remain patient.</p></blockquote>
<p>Crypto trader Tony Vays also threw his two cents in, claiming that while prices may have taken a sudden (albeit small) dip in the short term, he believes the market is turning itself around and bitcoin traders can expect a solid bull run in the coming months. Over the next few years, he’s confident bitcoin will poise itself to reach a price of $300K. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>We continue to consolidate. It’s continued to be frustrating. I&#8217;ve been a bitcoiner, and it&#8217;s very, very clear that bitcoin is choosing the purple path. I have two paths for bitcoin. One was a little more bullish with a lower top ($200,000), and the other was a little more bearish with a higher top ($300,000) a little further down in time.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Inflation Remains a Problem</h2>
<p>The rate hikes discussed above were constant throughout the year 2022 thanks to poor economic policies signed into law by Joe Biden.</p>
<p>These policies resulted in record inflation, and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-fed-bitcoins-worst-enemy-right-now/">the rate hikes became</a> the only tool for fighting this enemy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/powell-announces-potential-pause-to-rate-hikes-btc-slips/">Powell Announces Potential Pause to Rate Hikes; BTC Slips</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Fresh Rally Possible To $330</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-fresh-rally-possible-to-330/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 03:28:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79161</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin cash is eyeing a fresh rally above the $300 resistance against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above the $260 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $289 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-fresh-rally-possible-to-330/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Fresh Rally Possible To $330</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin cash is eyeing a fresh rally above the $300 resistance against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above the $260 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $289 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair must clear $290 and $300 to continue higher in the near term.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin cash price is consolidating gains above $260 against the US Dollar, unlike <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-more-upsides-above-31250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. BCH/USD could start a fresh surge if it clears the $300 level.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin cash price formed a decent support base above the $220 level. BCH started a decent increase and was able to clear the $280 resistance zone.</p>
<p>The price climbed above the $300 and $320 resistance levels. However, the bears appeared near the $328 level. There was a downside correction below the $300 level. The price declined below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $185 swing low to the $328 high.</p>
<p>However, the bulls are active above the $240 level. It is stable above the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $185 swing low to the $328 high.</p>
<p>Bitcoin cash is now trading above the $260 zone and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-rally-gains-pace-above-300/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. It is attempting a fresh rally above the $300 resistance. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $290 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $289 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $300, above which the price may perhaps rise toward the $330 level. Any more gains above $330 could set the pace for a move toward the $350 level.</p>
<p>If not, the price might decline again. Immediate support on the downside is near the $260 level. The first major support sits near the $240 level. The next major support is near $220, below which the bears might aim for $200. The next target for them may perhaps be near the $185 level.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79162" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79162" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash.png"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-79162" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79162" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Cash Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BCHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, Bitcoin Cash’s price is now trading above the $260 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price must clear $290 and $300 to continue higher in the near term.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for BCH/USD is gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BCH/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $260 and $240.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $290 and $300.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-fresh-rally-possible-to-330/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Fresh Rally Possible To $330</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Prices Rise Following Positive Sentiment from Hong Kong</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-prices-rise-following-positive-sentiment-from-hong-kong/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 17:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[china]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hong Kong]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78472</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Towards the end of May, crypto prices rose somewhat following news that Hong Kong would permit retail trading and move in the opposite direction of its mainland countrymen. Hong Kong Says &#8220;Yes&#8221; to Crypto Trading Bitcoin, for example, which had been trading in the mid-$26,000 range for several weeks, eventually shot beyond the $27K mark [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-prices-rise-following-positive-sentiment-from-hong-kong/">Crypto Prices Rise Following Positive Sentiment from Hong Kong</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Towards the end of May, crypto prices rose <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/bitcoin-climbs-back-above-27-000-after-hong-kong-greenlights-some-retail-crypto-trading/ar-AA1bzwAl">somewhat following news that</a> Hong Kong would permit retail trading and move in the opposite direction of its mainland countrymen.</p>
<h2>Hong Kong Says &#8220;Yes&#8221; to Crypto Trading</h2>
<p>Bitcoin, for example, which had been trading in the mid-$26,000 range for several weeks, eventually shot beyond the $27K mark for the first time in a while, while Ethereum – which had fallen into the $1,700 range – shot up to about $1,850.</p>
<p>The jumps arrived after the Securities and Futures Commission in Hong Kong said it would allow all retail traders interested in crypto to trade a certain number of digital assets beginning in June, though they would have to do so through registered platforms. The news is a huge step in an alternate direction given China became highly anti-crypto roughly two years ago.</p>
<p>In 2021, China shocked the world when it decided that per new regulations set forth by Beijing, all crypto and bitcoin mining would be fully illegal, and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-crypto-mining-clampdown-in-china-is-not-over/">all mining facilities</a> would have to be shut down. The move was designed to make the country less polluting and ensure stronger climate regulations were in place.</p>
<p>It was a very surprising statement given that China, at that time, was home to well over 60 percent of the world’s mining facilities. Thus, China was set to lose a lot of money within a short period, but this didn’t seem to bother regulators. In fact, they eventually took things a step further and announced that all crypto trading activities <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-traders-in-china-have-no-exchanges-to-turn-to/">would also be illegal</a>. Nobody could engage in crypto transactions, and if they were caught doing so, they would either pay a fine or go to prison for their actions.</p>
<p>Hong Kong, however, has long sought to decipher itself from the Chinese mainland. The region has worked hard to gain independence, and this is just another stick in the side of China as the area has refused to turn away from crypto the way the mainland has. Noelle Acheson – economist and author of the crypto newsletter “Crypto is Macro Now” – announced in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>This news doesn&#8217;t mean that a flood of retail buying power will enter the market at the beginning… We could see some volume uptick… however.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Trying to Be the Next Big Hub</h2>
<p>Owen Lau – an analyst at Oppenheimer – also threw his two cents into the mix, commenting that Hong Kong is being “pretty aggressive” when it comes to working towards crypto hub status. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>It will continue to capture the attention of the community and attract more firms to set up offices in Hong Kong. It is hard to gauge the exact impact, but it has a long-term effect on capital flow and talent movement.</p></blockquote>
<p>The Securities and Futures Commission has already licensed two digital currency companies.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-prices-rise-following-positive-sentiment-from-hong-kong/">Crypto Prices Rise Following Positive Sentiment from Hong Kong</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Crypto Bill in Texas Would Really Hurt Miners</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-crypto-bill-in-texas-would-really-hurt-miners/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 15:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[china]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Texas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78470</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new bill is making its way to the Texas House of Representatives that might make it hard for crypto mining companies within the state to gain access to the funds and resources they need to stay afloat and function properly. Texas Crypto Bill Is the Wrong Move The bill, for one thing, would ensure [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-crypto-bill-in-texas-would-really-hurt-miners/">New Crypto Bill in Texas Would Really Hurt Miners</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new bill is making its way to the Texas House of Representatives that <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/colinharper/2023/05/23/texas-bitcoin-bill-could-eliminate-key-source-of-funds-for-miners/?sh=5cff32c1dd06">might make it hard for</a> crypto mining companies within the state to gain access to the funds and resources they need to stay afloat and function properly.</p>
<h2>Texas Crypto Bill Is the Wrong Move</h2>
<p>The bill, for one thing, would ensure that power costs for the largest crypto miner in the state will increase by as much as $30 million each year. Also, miners would only be able to provide a limited amount of power to the Electricity Reliability Council of Texas (ERCOT), and bitcoin miners would also not be allowed to access the same property tax breaks currently available to standard industrial power consumers.</p>
<p>The situation is an odd one in that bitcoin mining profits have already shrunk by as much as 60 percent over the last year, largely due to the ongoing crypto winter and the dips many digital asset prices have incurred. Companies like Riot Blockchain – one of the most prominent crypto mining firms in the country – say the power credits that they’re currently privy to make a huge difference in how much they pay and how much they make each year. Representatives for the firm put out the following statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>These credits are recognized in power curtailment credits in the statements of operations, outside of cost of revenues, but significantly reduce the company’s overall cost to mine bitcoin. When netting the power curtailment credits with the costs of revenues, the net costs as a percentage of mining revenue were 39.7 percent and 24.7 percent for the years ended December 31, 2022, and 2021, respectively.</p></blockquote>
<p>The bill has already passed the Senate, though it would need to be signed into law by Texas Governor Greg Abbott, who has shown himself to be a bitcoin and crypto fan in the past. Thus, it’s unlikely, analysts say, that he will react favorably to the bill, though it’s impossible to assume this couldn’t happen for some reason.</p>
<h2>Helping Miners Relocate</h2>
<p>Texas has long been a major bitcoin and crypto mining hub, so it’s odd that such a bill would ever make its way through the state’s political spectrum. The state has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-is-still-a-crypto-mining-king/">highly devoted to mining</a> for about two years now, largely because so many miners have been forced to leave their native China. That country declared crypto mining illegal in 2021, and several made their way to Texas due to the state’s large, vast, and open landscapes and its cheap electricity prices.</p>
<p>While the situation hasn’t been perfect, the sudden influx of miners has given Texas’ economy a major boost. It has also created jobs and opened opportunity windows on all sides of the state, so it seems very strange that such an anti-crypto bill would garner support.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-crypto-bill-in-texas-would-really-hurt-miners/">New Crypto Bill in Texas Would Really Hurt Miners</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
