<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 05:21:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Federal Reserve and Other Agencies Are Warning Banks About Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-federal-reserve-and-other-regulators-are-warning-banks-about-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-federal-reserve-and-other-regulators-are-warning-banks-about-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 17:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[federal reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76323</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>U.S. regulators like the Federal Reserve, the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, and the Office of the Comptroller of the Currency have established a joint statement warning banks all over the world about the alleged risks and problems that come with crypto trading. The Federal Reserve Feels Crypto Is Problematic These agencies say that banks need<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-federal-reserve-and-other-regulators-are-warning-banks-about-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-federal-reserve-and-other-regulators-are-warning-banks-about-crypto/">The Federal Reserve and Other Agencies Are Warning Banks About Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>U.S. regulators like the Federal Reserve, the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, and the Office of the Comptroller of the Currency have <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/personalfinance/us-regulators-warn-banks-over-cryptocurrency-risks/ar-AA15WYvb" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">established a joint statement</a> warning banks all over the world about the alleged risks and problems that come with crypto trading.</p>
<h2>The Federal Reserve Feels Crypto Is Problematic</h2>
<p>These agencies say that banks need to take these risks seriously and implement the necessary security measures to keep themselves and their customers safe. The statement read:</p>
<blockquote><p>The events of the past year have been marked by significant volatility and the exposure of vulnerabilities in the crypto asset sector… It is important that risks related to the crypto asset sector that cannot be mitigated or controlled do not migrate to the banking system.</p></blockquote>
<p>The events of the past year have got plenty of traders, and above all, legislators a little spooked. For one thing, 2022 was marred by some of the worst volatility the crypto arena has ever seen, with assets like bitcoin losing more than 70 percent of their value. BTC hit a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit in November of 2021, though it entered the new year on a down note, and by the time 2022 was over, it had fallen into the mid-$16K range.</p>
<p>Things didn’t stop there, however. The rest of the crypto industry followed in BTC’s footsteps, and the space has lost more than $2 trillion in valuation in under a year. It’s a sad and ugly sight to see.</p>
<p>In addition, 2022 saw several <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">bankruptcies</a> and elements of fraud. While criminal activity has always been a problem in the crypto arena, nothing could have prepared the world for what would happen with FTX, the now fallen crypto exchange that rose to fruition in just three short years.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, the company’s chief executive Sam Bankman-Fried <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-ftx-exec-sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-fraud/" data-wpel-link="internal">has been charged with</a> eight counts of fraud and conspiracy, though he has recently entered a plea of not guilty. It is alleged he used customer funds to purchase lavish Bahamian real estate.</p>
<h2>You Caused a Lot of These Issues!</h2>
<p>At the same time, there is irony in that some of the agencies issuing the statement – such as the Federal Reserve – are responsible for the very crypto problems they’re pointing out. While many contributing factors led to bitcoin’s demise in 2022, one big one was the fact that the Federal Reserve continued to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-slated-to-suffer-in-2022-thanks-to-federal-reserve-rate-hikes/" data-wpel-link="internal">hike rates as a means</a> of dealing with inflation.</p>
<p>The tactic proved relatively useless, as everyday Americans are still witnessing higher prices at grocery stores and they can no longer afford homes. The side effect of these ongoing rate hikes is that bitcoin has ultimately taken a turn for the worse and will need a lot of recovery time if it’s ever to achieve its previous all-time high again.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-federal-reserve-and-other-regulators-are-warning-banks-about-crypto/">The Federal Reserve and Other Agencies Are Warning Banks About Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-federal-reserve-and-other-regulators-are-warning-banks-about-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Some Want the Crypto Moratorium in New York to Last Longer</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/some-want-the-crypto-moratorium-in-new-york-to-last-longer/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/some-want-the-crypto-moratorium-in-new-york-to-last-longer/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 15:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Moratorium]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New York]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76319</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, the state of New York imposed a moratorium on crypto mining, thus barring any firms that did not fully rely on clean energy from entering its borders and setting up shop. Initially, the ban was set to last a total of two years, though now, local legislators are considering extending the ban.<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/some-want-the-crypto-moratorium-in-new-york-to-last-longer/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/some-want-the-crypto-moratorium-in-new-york-to-last-longer/">Some Want the Crypto Moratorium in New York to Last Longer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, the state of New York <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-signs-crypto-moratorium-into-law/" data-wpel-link="internal">imposed a moratorium on</a> crypto mining, thus barring any firms that did not fully rely on clean energy from entering its borders and setting up shop. Initially, the ban was set to last a total of two years, though now, local legislators are <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/massena-town-board-holding-hearing-232100463.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">considering extending the ban</a>.</p>
<h2>The New York Crypto Moratorium Could Be Extended</h2>
<p>A town board meeting has been put on the calendar regarding the moratorium in the region of Massena. Town supervisor Susan J. Bellor explained in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>We have a public hearing scheduled for next Tuesday when we have our organizational meeting. After our installation of both Francis and Debra, we&#8217;ll get right to the public hearing on that.</p></blockquote>
<p>The goal is to keep the moratorium in place until official crypto regulation can be introduced. Bellor and her fellow council members believe local laws need to be established that can fully monitor the crypto space in New York and preside over statewide operations. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>It was good to hear that panel of speakers talking about the pros and cons and how they want to get those regulations done.</p></blockquote>
<p>She has also invited members of the public to address her with their thoughts and concerns, claiming:</p>
<blockquote><p>Some show up, some send me an email, some send me regular mail. Whatever works.</p></blockquote>
<p>Resident David Felton says he’s concerned about all the crypto bankruptcies that have been occurring as of late. He says crypto laws need to be in place to not only protect the companies, but to ensure users or customers of these companies receive their dues should the enterprises decide to close their doors and go bankrupt themselves. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think that is a major problem. You&#8217;re taking the risk where right now there&#8217;s no government regulations. You&#8217;re perpetuating an industry that doesn&#8217;t have any protection. They can go bankrupt very easily. You&#8217;re supporting that. I do not think it&#8217;s a very good idea.</p></blockquote>
<p>Town attorney Eric J. Gustafson also commented that regulations are close to being established, suggesting:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think we&#8217;re just about there. We&#8217;ve got some work to do. They&#8217;re waiting for a draft of cryptocurrency mining operations from me. I have a draft that I think is almost ready for their consideration. I&#8217;m just not quite ready, but we&#8217;re close. I think the January timeframe will give us enough time to finalize the regulations, have the committee review it, and then have it out for public hearing sometime… so that it can be adopted.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A State That&#8217;s Always Been Against Crypto?</h2>
<p>New York is the first state to impose such a ban. The Empire State has long had a strained relationship with crypto beginning with the implementation of its <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitlicense/" data-wpel-link="internal">BitLicense</a> in 2015.</p>
<p>This caused several digital asset firms to pack up and leave the region.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/some-want-the-crypto-moratorium-in-new-york-to-last-longer/">Some Want the Crypto Moratorium in New York to Last Longer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/some-want-the-crypto-moratorium-in-new-york-to-last-longer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former FTX Exec Sam Bankman-Fried Enters Not Guilty Plea</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-ftx-exec-sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-fraud/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-ftx-exec-sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-fraud/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 13:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Wang]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76315</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sam Bankman-Fried – the former head executive of the now fallen crypto exchange FTX – has pleaded not guilty to all counts of fraud. This means his case will potentially be heard by a jury. Sam Bankman-Fried Says He&#8217;s Not Guilty During a recent testimony, Bankman-Fried refused to speak for himself. Instead, it was his<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-ftx-exec-sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-fraud/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-ftx-exec-sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-fraud/">Former FTX Exec Sam Bankman-Fried Enters Not Guilty Plea</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sam Bankman-Fried – the former head executive of the now fallen crypto exchange FTX – has pleaded not guilty to all <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/ftx-crypto-ceo-sam-bankman-fried-expected-to-plead-not-guilty-in-court-tuesday/ar-AA15UZpS" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">counts of fraud</a>. This means his case will potentially be heard by a jury.</p>
<h2>Sam Bankman-Fried Says He&#8217;s Not Guilty</h2>
<p>During a recent testimony, Bankman-Fried refused to speak for himself. Instead, it was his lawyer Mark Cohen who entered the not guilty plea on his behalf. Bankman-Fried’s mother was in attendance and sitting behind her son as the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lewis-kaplan-will-be-the-judge-to-oversee-ftx-court-case/" data-wpel-link="internal">judge who will preside</a> over the former crypto head’s case – Lewis Kaplan – monitored the courtroom.</p>
<p>Sam Bankman-Fried currently faces eight separate charges of fraud and conspiracy. Federal prosecutors say the crypto executive engaged in one of the biggest digital currency fraud schemes in the history of the space.</p>
<p>It is alleged that billions of dollars in customer funds were taken from the exchange and moved to Alameda Research, another company founded by SBF. Both enterprises were supposed to remain separate. By conjoining them through financial procedures, Bankman-Fried is alleged to have taken part in illegal activity.</p>
<p>Furthermore, SBF has also been accused of spending millions of dollars belonging to customers on lavish real estate in the Bahamas and making million-dollar <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-gave-a-lot-of-money-to-democrats-what-will-they-do-with-it/" data-wpel-link="internal">political donations to various</a> democrat candidates in both 2020 and 2022.</p>
<p>Sam Bankman-Fried will likely find no help from his former employees Caroline Ellison and Gary Wang, who served as the CEO of Alameda and the co-founder of FTX, respectively. Both Ellison and Wang have entered guilty pleas, with Ellison facing seven counts and Wang facing four.</p>
<p>In her testimony, Ellison stated the following:</p>
<blockquote><p>We prepared certain quarterly balance sheets that concealed the extent of Alameda&#8217;s borrowing and the billions of dollars in loans that Alameda had made to FTX executives and to related parties. I also understood that FTX had not disclosed to FTX&#8217;s equity investors that Alameda could borrow a potentially unlimited amount from FTX, thereby putting customer assets at risk.</p></blockquote>
<p>FTX is likely to go down in history as one of the biggest crypto embarrassments the space has ever seen. The exchange, barely three years old, rose to fruition in 2019 and quickly became one of the world’s top five digital exchanges. SBF was lauded as a genius, and prior to his company’s fall, his net worth was valued at several billion dollars.</p>
<h2>Two Months of Trouble So Far</h2>
<p>However, trouble began in mid-November of last year when Bankman-Fried complained of a liquidity crunch online and said he needed <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">fast cash to</a> keep the company afloat. He approached his larger rival Binance to see if it’d be interested in buying his enterprise out, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">though the firm backed</a> away, claiming the issues it was facing were too big.</p>
<p>From there, FTX had no <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">choice but to file bankruptcy</a>, and SBF quickly resigned from his post.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-ftx-exec-sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-fraud/">Former FTX Exec Sam Bankman-Fried Enters Not Guilty Plea</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-ftx-exec-sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-fraud/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Rally Could Accelerate Above $0.38</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-rally-could-accelerate-above-0-38/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-rally-could-accelerate-above-0-38/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 06:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76642</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ADA price seems to be forming a support base above the $0.35 level against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above $0.35 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $0.348 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Bitfinex). The price<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-rally-could-accelerate-above-0-38/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-rally-could-accelerate-above-0-38/">Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Rally Could Accelerate Above $0.38</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>ADA price seems to be forming a support base above the $0.35 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $0.35 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $0.348 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Bitfinex).</li>
<li>The price could gain resume its increase if it clears the $0.380 and $0.388 levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Cardano price is showing positive signs above $0.350 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-rally-could-extend-above-22k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. ADA price could extend its increase if it clears the $0.388 resistance.</em></p>
<h2>Cardano Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This week, cardano price started a strong increase above the $0.320 resistance zone against the US Dollar. The ADA/USD pair gained pace for a move above the $0.335 and $0.350 levels.</p>
<p>During the increase, there was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $0.348 on the 4-hours chart. It even broke the $0.372 level and settled well above the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). It traded as high as $0.386 and recently started a downside correction.</p>
<p>There was a move below the $0.382 and $0.380 levels. The price declined slightly below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.3241 swing low to $0.3866 high.</p>
<p>It is now trading above $0.350 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-more-gains-likely-above-0-38/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $0.380 zone. A clear move above the $0.380 resistance might start a strong increase. The next major resistance is near the $0.400 level.</p>
<p>Any more gains above the $0.40 resistance might send the price towards the $0.42 resistance or even $0.432. On the downside, an immediate support is near the $0.370 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $0.355 level. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.3241 swing low to $0.3866 high. A clear move below the $0.350 level might send the price towards the $0.332 level. Any more losses might send the price towards the $0.320 support.</p>
<div id="attachment_76643" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Cardano-Price-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76643" class="size-full wp-image-76643" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Cardano-Price-3.png" alt="Cardano (ADA) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76643" class="wp-caption-text">Cardano (ADA) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ADAUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that ADA price is now trading above $0.350 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $0.380 and $0.388 levels.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ADA/USD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for ADA/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.372 and $0.355.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.388 and $0.400.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-rally-could-accelerate-above-0-38/">Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Rally Could Accelerate Above $0.38</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-rally-could-accelerate-above-0-38/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Analysis: Bulls Aim $1,800 or Higher</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-bulls-aim-1800-or-higher/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-bulls-aim-1800-or-higher/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 04:58:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76639</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum price is gaining pace above the $1,550 level against the US Dollar. ETH price is now trading above $1,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a connecting bullish trend line forming with support near $1,610 on the 4-hours chart (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could climb further if it clears<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-bulls-aim-1800-or-higher/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-bulls-aim-1800-or-higher/">Ethereum Price Analysis: Bulls Aim $1,800 or Higher</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ethereum price is gaining pace above the $1,550 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>ETH price is now trading above $1,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a connecting bullish trend line forming with support near $1,610 on the 4-hours chart (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could climb further if it clears the $1,680 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ethereum price is rising above the $1,550 level against the US Dollar. ETH/USD could rise further if it clears the $1,680 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Ethereum Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, ethereum saw a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-rally-pauses-but-not-likely-over/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">strong increase</a> above the $1,450 level against the US Dollar. ETH price was able to gain pace for a move above the $1,550 level and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</p>
<p>The bulls even cleared the $1,600 resistance zone. The price even spiked above the $1,650 level and formed a high near the $1,680 level. It is now consolidating gains above the $1,600 level. There was a minor decline below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1,500 swing low to $1,680 high.</p>
<p>It is now trading above $1,550 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-upside-break-could-trigger-more-gains/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. An immediate resistance on the upside is near the $1,650 level. The next major resistance is near the $1,680 zone.</p>
<p>Any more gains could even send the price towards the $1,750 resistance zone in the near term. On the downside, an initial support is near the $1,610 level. There is also a connecting bullish trend line forming with support near $1,610 on the 4-hours chart.</p>
<p>The next major support is now near the $1,590 level. The main support is near the $1,580 level or the 50% % Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1,500 swing low to $1,680 high.</p>
<p>A break below the $1,580 support could push the price to $1,520. Any more losses could lead the price towards $1,450 or even $1,320 in the coming days.</p>
<div id="attachment_76640" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Ethereum-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76640" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-76640" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Ethereum-3.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76640" class="wp-caption-text">Ethereum Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Ethereum price is clearly trading above the $1,550 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, ether price could climb further if it clears the $1,680 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $1,610, followed by the $1,580 zone.</p>
<p>Key Resistance$ Levels – $1,650 and $1,680.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-bulls-aim-1800-or-higher/">Ethereum Price Analysis: Bulls Aim $1,800 or Higher</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-bulls-aim-1800-or-higher/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Erik Voorhees Sees a $40K Price for BTC in 5-6 Months</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/erik-voorhees-sees-a-40k-price-for-btc-this-summer/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/erik-voorhees-sees-a-40k-price-for-btc-this-summer/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Erik Voorhees]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tim Draper]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76303</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Erik Voorhees, the CEO and founder of crypto exchange Shape Shift, sees bitcoin – the world’s number one digital currency by market cap – reaching a relatively modest price of about $40,000 at some point this year. Erik Voorhees: BTC Will Be at $40K 2022 was a rough period for bitcoin. The asset fell by<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/erik-voorhees-sees-a-40k-price-for-btc-this-summer/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/erik-voorhees-sees-a-40k-price-for-btc-this-summer/">Erik Voorhees Sees a $40K Price for BTC in 5-6 Months</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Erik Voorhees, the CEO and founder of crypto exchange Shape Shift, sees bitcoin – the world’s number one digital currency by market cap – reaching a <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/stocks/bitcoin-at-40k-by-summer-shapeshift-ceo-thinks-it-s-possible-even-as-tim-draper-sticks-to-bigger-estimate-1031997121" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">relatively modest price</a> of about $40,000 at some point this year.</p>
<h2>Erik Voorhees: BTC Will Be at $40K</h2>
<p>2022 was a rough period for bitcoin. The asset fell by more than 70 percent from its all-time high of $68,000 per unit and dropped into the mid-$16,000 range. Things have been bad for the currency and its altcoin cousins for some time, though there is good news in that we are seeing similar patterns to what was witnessed in the crypto arena around four years ago. If these patterns continue, 2023 could be the year in which a dose of healing is delivered.</p>
<p>As we all remember, for example, 2018 saw the currency fall from a 2017 high of just under $20K to a new low of about $3,500 11 months later. Things weren’t looking great for the asset, though 2019 saw the currency experience a rise into the $15K range by the summer. Things began dipping from there, and bitcoin still ended those 12 months on a relatively low note (around $7,000), though it was far better than where it was a year earlier.</p>
<p>If we’re to assume things will continue in this matter and 2023 is reminiscent of 2019, $40K as proposed by Voorhees is something we can all easily believe in. it’s not quite where it was during its 2021 peak, but it’s still far better than what we witnessed last year.</p>
<p>In an interview, Erik Voorhees mentioned that bitcoin could reach this price as early as summer of 2023, and that he “wouldn’t be surprised” if such action occurred even sooner. This would make sense given that summer of 2019 is also when we witnessed the peak point of post 2018 recovery.</p>
<p>It’s hard to assume what could truly happen, however, given the high number of predictions about what bitcoin will do over the next several months. Many analysts claim to be the experts about where bitcoin will travel in the future, and a consistent problem with their predictions is they all tend to be somewhat over the top.</p>
<h2>So Many People Predicting Where Bitcoin Will Soon Go</h2>
<p>Perhaps the one that most fits this description is Tim Draper’s <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tim-draper-still-predicts-big-things-for-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">notion that bitcoin will</a> somehow hit $250K before 2023’s end. For this to happen, bitcoin would need to see a rise of more than $230,000 in the next 12 months. While we cannot deny that anything is possible in the crypto space, the idea of such high gains in such a short period feels very far fetched.</p>
<p>Other analysts are at <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/the-boldest-bitcoin-calls-for-2023-are-out-and-a-1400-rally-or-a-70-plunge-may-be-on-the-cards/ar-AA15SUkQ" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">the opposite end of the spectrum</a>, with companies like Standard Chartered saying bitcoin could fall another $11K and reach $5,000 per unit before things get better.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/erik-voorhees-sees-a-40k-price-for-btc-this-summer/">Erik Voorhees Sees a $40K Price for BTC in 5-6 Months</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/erik-voorhees-sees-a-40k-price-for-btc-this-summer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Bankruptcy was Big Last Year, but was There a Positive Note to It All?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-bankruptcy-was-big-last-year-but-was-there-a-positive-note-to-it-all/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-bankruptcy-was-big-last-year-but-was-there-a-positive-note-to-it-all/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 15:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bankruptcy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jackie Sawicky]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lee Bratcher]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76300</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>2022 was a year wrought with bankruptcy and the exiting of several crypto companies, but many analysts do not feel this was necessarily a bad thing. Bankruptcy was Big in 2022, but Things Might&#8217;ve Been Better Than We Thought On the surface, one could argue that 2022 was the worst year for crypto since 2018.<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-bankruptcy-was-big-last-year-but-was-there-a-positive-note-to-it-all/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-bankruptcy-was-big-last-year-but-was-there-a-positive-note-to-it-all/">Crypto Bankruptcy was Big Last Year, but was There a Positive Note to It All?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>2022 was a year wrought with bankruptcy and <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/will-2023-bring-more-crypto-bankruptcies-to-weed-out-the-pumps-and-the-frauds/ar-AA15VQp9" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">the exiting of several crypto</a> companies, but many analysts do not feel this was necessarily a bad thing.</p>
<h2>Bankruptcy was Big in 2022, but Things Might&#8217;ve Been Better Than We Thought</h2>
<p>On the surface, one could argue that 2022 was the worst year for crypto since 2018. The price of bitcoin, for example, fell by more than 70 percent after the world’s number one digital currency by market cap hit a new all-time high in the final months of 2021. During that time, BTC rose to a whopping $68,000 per unit, though after that, it endured a series of losses that brought it down into the mid-$16K range.</p>
<p>The whole crypto space followed suit and wound up losing about $2 trillion in valuation. On top of that, many high-ranking crypto firms – from <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-mining-firm-compute-north-files-for-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">Compute North</a> to the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX</a> digital currency exchange – joined a long list of companies that had to endure bankruptcy proceedings either because they couldn’t cope with the ongoing volatility or because they engaged in faulty practices.</p>
<p>But people like Chad Harris are telling fans of crypto that the bankruptcy filings they witnessed last year shouldn’t strike fear in their hearts. Instead, people need to look at them as necessary steps for weeding out all bad actors. He says these bankruptcies have helped to purify the crypto space somewhat, and that the more this happens, the stronger the industry will become.</p>
<p>Chad Harris is a chief commercial officer at Riot Blockchain, arguably one of the most prominent crypto mining enterprises in the world. He stated in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Two years ago, this audience was packed. Today, this is an audience full of passionate people who believe that they can facilitate what they tell the public. I think it’s important because every single time one of us fails in a disastrous way, it affects every one of us in this room.</p></blockquote>
<p>Texas Blockchain Council president Lee Bratcher offered similar sentiment. While he is disappointed in the many collapses that occurred last year, he thinks this will pave the way for better, stronger crypto companies to enter the fray. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The sentiment is we’re disappointed in FTX, but we’re resolved and optimistic about the future of the industry. We’re rolling up our sleeves and moving forward… We are bullish on the future. I think the worst is behind us.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Not Everyone&#8217;s Excited</h2>
<p>Others, however, such as Jackie Sawicky – an environmentalist that’s currently protesting the establishment of a new Riot Blockchain facility in northern Texas – thinks more negativity is going to strike the crypto space in the coming weeks. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>This is not just a bubble. It’s collapsing. It is a dying industry. The problem is a lot of these things can’t be undone. There are real-world consequences for people who invested with these companies.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-bankruptcy-was-big-last-year-but-was-there-a-positive-note-to-it-all/">Crypto Bankruptcy was Big Last Year, but was There a Positive Note to It All?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-bankruptcy-was-big-last-year-but-was-there-a-positive-note-to-it-all/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Valkyrie Investments Seeks More Control of the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/valkyrie-investments-seeks-direct-control-of-the-grayscale-bitcoin-trust/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/valkyrie-investments-seeks-direct-control-of-the-grayscale-bitcoin-trust/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 13:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grayscale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Valkyrie]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76297</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Valkyrie Investments is working to become the new sponsor and manager of the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust, arguably the largest digital currency fund in existence. Valkyrie Investments Wants a Bigger Role in Grayscale&#8217;s Environment Based in Nashville, Tennessee, Valkyrie is tasked with managing $180 million in assets. In late December, the firm announced what’s to be<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/valkyrie-investments-seeks-direct-control-of-the-grayscale-bitcoin-trust/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/valkyrie-investments-seeks-direct-control-of-the-grayscale-bitcoin-trust/">Valkyrie Investments Seeks More Control of the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Valkyrie Investments is working to become the new <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/valkyrie-unveils-proposal-grayscale-troubled-181233698.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">sponsor and manager of</a> the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust, arguably the largest digital currency fund in existence.</p>
<h2>Valkyrie Investments Wants a Bigger Role in Grayscale&#8217;s Environment</h2>
<p>Based in Nashville, Tennessee, Valkyrie is tasked with managing $180 million in assets. In late December, the firm announced what’s to be called the Valkyrie Opportunistic Fund, which will take advantage of discounts being offered through Grayscale Investments. Valkyrie will thus increase its bitcoin holdings in the fund so it can realize the full value of bitcoin. It will also pursue additional bitcoin and digital currency opportunities for the sake of its customers.</p>
<p>In a statement, Steven McClurg – the co-founder and CIO of Valkyrie Investments – mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>We understand that Grayscale has played an important role in the development and growth of the bitcoin ecosystem with the launch of GBTC, and we respect the team and the work that they have done. However, [due to] recent events involving Grayscale and its family of affiliated companies, it is time for a change. Valkyrie is the best company to manage GBTC to ensure its investors are treated fairly.</p></blockquote>
<p>While Valkyrie is all set to obtain more bitcoin through Grayscale, how much control the company will have over future maneuvers is questionable given Grayscale’s current business model. The company has made it clear that no shareholders have sway over management protocols, nor do they have voting rights in the company. In addition, all changes or maneuvers can only be acted upon unless there is a majority decision regarding the shares. This means 50 percent or more.</p>
<p>As it stands, Grayscale shares are trading for around 50 percent less than the price of the bitcoin units held within the company’s grasp. This makes sense in many ways given how low bitcoin has fallen in recent months, and companies that tie themselves so directly to BTC – such as <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/microstrategy-stock-crashes-thanks-to-btc-plunge/" data-wpel-link="internal">MicroStrategy and Coinbase</a> – have not had it easy, as when bitcoin falls, their stocks usually fall along with it.</p>
<p>To say 2022 was a bad year for bitcoin and its many altcoin cousins would be a terrible understatement. BTC fell by more than 70 percent from its all-time high of about $68,000 per unit, which it achieved in November of 2021. From there, the currency experienced a long series of losses that caused it to fall into the mid-$16K range just before the end of 2022.</p>
<h2>A Rough Patch for Both Entities?</h2>
<p>Grayscale worked hard last year to become an exchange-traded fund of sorts based on bitcoin, though this notion (unsurprisingly) was rejected by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Grayscale has since struck up a lawsuit against the agency to give itself a fighting chance.</p>
<p>Valkyrie has been around for roughly two years, first opening its doors for business in January of 2021.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/valkyrie-investments-seeks-direct-control-of-the-grayscale-bitcoin-trust/">Valkyrie Investments Seeks More Control of the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/valkyrie-investments-seeks-direct-control-of-the-grayscale-bitcoin-trust/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Eyes Bullish Break Above $0.10</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-eyes-bullish-break-above-0-10/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-eyes-bullish-break-above-0-10/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 06:28:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar Lumens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76625</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stellar lumen price started a fresh increase above the $0.085 resistance zone against the US Dollar. XLM price is now trading above $0.085 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $0.0875 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-eyes-bullish-break-above-0-10/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-eyes-bullish-break-above-0-10/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Eyes Bullish Break Above $0.10</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Stellar lumen price started a fresh increase above the $0.085 resistance zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>XLM price is now trading above $0.085 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $0.0875 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to rise if it stays above the $0.0870 and $0.0850 support levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Stellar lumen price is trading above $0.0880 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-rally-could-extend-above-22k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. XLM price must stay above the $0.0850 support to rise further.</em></p>
<h2>Stellar Lumen Price Analysis (XLM to USD)</h2>
<p>After forming a base above the $0.080 level, stellar lumen price started a fresh increase against the US Dollar. The XLM/USD pair broke the $0.082 resistance zone to move into a positive zone.</p>
<p>The price even broke the $0.0880 resistance and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-climbs-higher-and-aims-a-move-to-0-10/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $0.0875 on the 4-hours chart. The price is now trading comfortably above the $0.088 level.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $0.0938 level. The next major resistance is near the $0.0950 level.  A clear move above the $0.0950 level might send the price towards the $0.100 level.</p>
<p>Any more gains could lead the price towards the $0.1080 level or even $0.1120 in the coming days. An initial support on the downside is near the $0.0900 level. It is near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.0818 swing high to $0.0937 low.</p>
<p>The next major support sits near the $0.0875 level or the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.0818 swing high to $0.0937 low.</p>
<p>The main support is near the $0.085 zone. Any more losses could lead the price towards the $0.082 level in the near term, below which the price might even retest $0.080.</p>
<div id="attachment_76626" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76626" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-76626" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-3.png" alt="Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76626" class="wp-caption-text">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XLMUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that XLM price is now trading above $0.0880 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could continue to rise if it stays above the $0.0870 and $0.0850 support levels.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XLM/USD is gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for XLM/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.0878 and $0.0850.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.0938, $0.0950 and $0.1000.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-eyes-bullish-break-above-0-10/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Eyes Bullish Break Above $0.10</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-eyes-bullish-break-above-0-10/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
