<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 03:34:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/cropped-fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Finance Professor Disagrees with United Kingdom Sentiment Towards Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/finance-professor-disagrees-with-united-kingdom-sentiment-towards-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gavin Brown]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United Kingdom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78830</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, regulators in the United Kingdom said crypto trading was akin to gambling. In other words, betting on bitcoin was like sitting at a blackjack table. Not exactly the best metaphor, but we get what the country means. Is the United Kingdom Wrong About Crypto? However, there are many that don’t agree with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/finance-professor-disagrees-with-united-kingdom-sentiment-towards-crypto/">Finance Professor Disagrees with United Kingdom Sentiment Towards Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, regulators in the United Kingdom said <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-united-kingdom-wants-gambling-laws-to-apply-to-crypto-trading/">crypto trading was akin</a> to gambling. In other words, betting on bitcoin was like sitting at a blackjack table. Not exactly the best metaphor, but we get what the country means.</p>
<h2>Is the United Kingdom Wrong About Crypto?</h2>
<p>However, there are many <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-au/money/markets/labelling-cryptocurrency-as-gambling-shows-lack-of-understanding-and-misses-the-solution-expert-says/ar-AA1cyjeZ">that don’t agree with</a> this sentiment. In fact, they think it’s downright wrong, and they say it shows a dangerous lack of understanding. Amongst the people that feel this way is Gavin Brown, an associate professor in financial technology at the University of Liverpool.</p>
<p>In a recent interview, Brown criticized lawmakers in the United Kingdom for not bothering to comprehend the ins and outs of blockchain and crypto a bit better. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>[The committee] didn&#8217;t really understand the technology.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also mentioned that the people of the country know much more about crypto than those that have been placed in charge, and he thinks this is going to lead the United Kingdom down a dark path that will eventually put it behind other regions. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I see that all the time. I&#8217;ll get a taxi in London and the taxi driver will know ten times more [about cryptocurrency] than the CEO of a multinational bank I&#8217;m about to visit. We still see that disparity of knowledge, and not just from people on the street, but also from people who are actually making the policies who should know better.</p></blockquote>
<p>He says the time has come for everyday people and politicians to recognize crypto once and for all, and to acknowledge the idea that it’s here to stay. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Western Anglo-Saxon economies are stuck between a rock and a hard place because it&#8217;s not going away, and it&#8217;s a constant threat… The problem we have with things like… bitcoin, is that it&#8217;s not controllable or ban-able in a traditional sense because… [it] doesn&#8217;t have a CEO, a head office, any employees, an email address, doesn&#8217;t file any accounts, doesn&#8217;t have any buildings, has no AGM, [and] has no shareholders. Literally, bitcoin is an idea. It&#8217;s a computer program that&#8217;s being run globally all over the world at the same time… [Cryptocurrency] has been deliberately constructed in a way that is anti-state, and almost naturally beyond the reach of regulators.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Understanding Must Grow</h2>
<p>Natasha Gillezeau – a SXSW Sydney production lead and former Australian journalist – echoed Brown’s sentiment and said:</p>
<blockquote><p>People need to understand how serious [cryptocurrency] is. We [need] to understand how much of a marketing and advertising push that crypto [companies have] done in the last few years… We&#8217;re talking sports stadiums [sponsored by] Crypto.com, we&#8217;re talking outreach to influencers… We&#8217;re in a different point in the cycle of how much the marketing and advertising industry has legitimized it.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/finance-professor-disagrees-with-united-kingdom-sentiment-towards-crypto/">Finance Professor Disagrees with United Kingdom Sentiment Towards Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Opinion: Bitcoin Will Reach $60K Next Year, a New High in 2025, and Drop in 2026</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-bitcoin-will-reach-60k-next-year-a-new-high-in-2025-and-drop-in-2026/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 15:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Opinion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OpEd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin patterns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78826</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin could be back at its $60K high next year (if it doesn’t shoot slightly beyond that). In 2025, the currency will likely reach a new price peak, and in 2026, the currency may drop again. The Repeating Price Patterns of Bitcoin This isn’t just random speculation. Rather, it&#8217;s a complete consideration of all the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-bitcoin-will-reach-60k-next-year-a-new-high-in-2025-and-drop-in-2026/">Opinion: Bitcoin Will Reach $60K Next Year, a New High in 2025, and Drop in 2026</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin could be back at its $60K high next year (if it doesn’t shoot slightly beyond that). In 2025, the currency will likely reach a new price peak, and in 2026, the currency may drop again.</p>
<h2>The Repeating Price Patterns of Bitcoin</h2>
<p>This isn’t just random speculation. Rather, it&#8217;s a complete consideration of all the price routines bitcoin has endured over the past 11 years or so. When one looks at how bitcoin has behaved, it seems to fall onto the same path every four years.</p>
<p>Look at 2012, 2013, and 2014, for example. During that first year, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitcoin/">bitcoin</a> was still new. It was trading for a few nickels or dollars. Nothing special to report. The following year, by the time we reached the final months (November and December), the world’s number one digital currency had <a href="https://www.globaldata.com/data-insights/financial-services/bitcoins-price-history/#:~:text=During%20its%20initial%20years%2C%20bitcoin%20had%20limited%20popularity,attained%20the%20%241%2C127.45%20price%20on%20November%2030%2C%202013.">shot up to about</a> $1,000 per unit. In 2014, the asset <a href="https://www.in2013dollars.com/bitcoin-price-in-2014">sunk into the $400 range</a>, thus experiencing its first major drop.</p>
<p>Now, let’s shift our focus to 2015, 2016, 2017, and 2018. 2015 saw bitcoin struggling, though it eventually began to show more signs of life towards the ending months, rising from the high $100 range to about $300. The next year, during the time of a presidential election, the currency shot up to about $900 or $1,000 again briefly, thus again reaching its 2013 high. After that, BTC rose to almost $20K, thus recording a new price peak for itself before sinking into oblivion and losing about 70 percent of its value in 2018 (the currency fell into the mid-$3,000 range).</p>
<p>Let’s then look at the next four years: 2019, 2020, 2021, and 2022. 2019 was very similar to 2015 in that bitcoin showed small signs of life here and there. It rose a bit towards the end of the year, but nothing that significant occurred. 2020 – the year of another election – arrived, and bitcoin surpassed its previous $20K high. 2021 brought the currency to a new pinnacle, and 2022 removed all the positive price action from the books and is considered the worst year on record for BTC and crypto (the space wound up losing more than $2 trillion in overall valuation).</p>
<h2>Healing Now, Then Everything Else Will Follow Over Three Years</h2>
<p>We are now in 2023, and thus far, it’s looking a lot like 2015 and 2019. There’s a little bit of healing in the mix, but nothing big is happening (yet). We are once again entering into the patterns we saw during the previous four-year roundabouts.</p>
<p>This new cycle encompasses 2023, 2024, 2025, and 2026. With light healing happening now, one can assume that next year (another election year) will bring bitcoin back to the $60K range, its previous high (like we saw in 2016 and 2020). If things continue in the same direction, we’ll see BTC reach a new high in 2025 (as we witnessed in 2017 and 2021), and bitcoin may be in for another major drop in 2026 (like in 2018 and 2022).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-bitcoin-will-reach-60k-next-year-a-new-high-in-2025-and-drop-in-2026/">Opinion: Bitcoin Will Reach $60K Next Year, a New High in 2025, and Drop in 2026</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Experienced Huge Fall in Mid-June Following Fed Announcement</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-experienced-huge-fall-in-mid-june-following-fed-announcement/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 13:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[federal reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Safai]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78824</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin fell below the $25,000 mark for the first time in a while in mid-June of this year after the Federal Reserve threw yet another monkey wrench into America’s economic plans. Major June Dip for Bitcoin During that time, the Federal Reserve announced that while it was not going to be hiking rates again in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-experienced-huge-fall-in-mid-june-following-fed-announcement/">Bitcoin Experienced Huge Fall in Mid-June Following Fed Announcement</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin fell below the $25,000 mark for the <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-drops-below-25000-tethers-stablecoin-falls-under-its-dollar-peg/ar-AA1cAtPV">first time in a while</a> in mid-June of this year after the Federal Reserve threw yet another monkey wrench into America’s economic plans.</p>
<h2>Major June Dip for Bitcoin</h2>
<p>During that time, the Federal Reserve announced that while it was not going to be hiking rates again in the immediate future, citizens of the U.S. could potentially expect to experience the effects of at least two more rate hikes before the end of the year. In other words, two more hikes would occur within the next six months.</p>
<p>Bitcoin didn’t take too kindly to the news and reacted somewhat violently, dropping into the $24K range after it had been trading for about $25,800 for the past 48 hours or so. That’s a drop of about $1,000 in just a few days. It just goes to show traders that bitcoin is still highly sensitive to present macroeconomic conditions being faced by the U.S., and while the crypto winter of last year may be marginally over, things aren’t quite as strong as they could (or should) be.</p>
<p>Michael Safai – managing partner at Dexterity Capital – commented on the bitcoin dip to occur after the Federal Reserve announcement. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>This has little to do with the FOMC and more to do with thinner liquidity and weak sentiment. Given how thin trading volumes are [now], a sizable (but not massive) sell order is enough to set off liquidations. Traders are more inclined to keep their money off the table [amid] this regulatory backlash, especially when it comes to altcoins, so there isn&#8217;t going to be much new capital flowing in to buoy prices so readily.</p></blockquote>
<p>To be fair, a lot has been going on in the last six weeks that bitcoin should have reacted more to, yet for some reason, it didn’t. For example, major lawsuits stemming from the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) against <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sues-binance-alleges-selling-of-illegal-securities/">Binance</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-hit-with-sec-lawsuit-says-it-operated-as-an-exchange-broker/">Coinbase</a> – the two biggest digital currency exchanges in the world – should have ultimately caused bitcoin to tank like no other event has.</p>
<h2>Is Regulation Coming or Not?</h2>
<p>However, bitcoin remained relatively resilient during all that, losing only a few hundred dollars here and there and experiencing marginal bumps after the news made headlines. Safai added:</p>
<blockquote><p>Further confusion about the legality of popular altcoins is keeping capital on the sidelines, and it&#8217;ll take a long run of good news or no news to get traders feeling excited about a recovery. Bitcoin prices will stay relatively rangebound between $25,000 and $27,000 until the next set of regulatory headlines tell us whether we&#8217;re heading towards resolution or even more obfuscation.</p></blockquote>
<p>The issue of regulatory clarity in the crypto space has long been a huge one, and calls have only increased tenfold since the fall of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/">FTX last November</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-experienced-huge-fall-in-mid-june-following-fed-announcement/">Bitcoin Experienced Huge Fall in Mid-June Following Fed Announcement</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Aims Fresh Increase To $0.18</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-aims-fresh-increase-to-0-18/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 05:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar Lumens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79523</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stellar lumen price is attempting a fresh increase from the $0.14 zone against the US Dollar. XLM price is now trading above $0.150 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $0.145 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-aims-fresh-increase-to-0-18/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Aims Fresh Increase To $0.18</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Stellar lumen price is attempting a fresh increase from the $0.14 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>XLM price is now trading above $0.150 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $0.145 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a major increase if there is a clear move above the $0.1650 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Stellar lumen price is trading above $0.150 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. XLM price must clear $0.1650 to start a fresh increase.</em></p>
<h2>Stellar Lumen Price Analysis (XLM to USD)</h2>
<p>After a steady increase, Stellar lumen price saw a downside correction below the $0.180 level against the US Dollar. The XLM/USD pair traded below the $0.165 support and tested the $0.140 zone.</p>
<p>A low is formed near $0.1404 and the price is now attempting a recovery wave. There was a break above the $0.145 resistance zone. Besides, there was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $0.145 on the 4-hour chart.</p>
<p>The price climbed above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.1807 swing high to the $0.1404 low. XLM is now trading above $0.150 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-remains-supported-for-fresh-rally-above-0-18/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $0.165 zone. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.1807 swing high to the $0.1404 low. The next major resistance is near the $0.180 level.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $0.180 level might send the price toward the $0.192 level. Any more gains could lead the price toward the $0.200 level or even $0.2150.</p>
<p>Initial support on the downside is near the $0.1520 level. The main support is near the $0.140 zone. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.1250 level in the near term, below which the price might even retest $0.1120.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79524" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79524" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-4.png"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-79524" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-4.png" alt="Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price" width="1835" height="839" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-4.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-4-600x274.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-4-1100x503.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-4-768x351.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-4-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-4-750x343.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-4-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79524" class="wp-caption-text">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XLMUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a> indicates that XLM price is now trading above $0.150 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start a major increase if there is a clear move above the $0.1650 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XLM/USD is losing momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for XLM/USD is now near the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.1520 and $0.1400.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.165, $0.180, and $0.200.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-aims-fresh-increase-to-0-18/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Aims Fresh Increase To $0.18</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Price Analysis: XRP At Risk of Reversal Below $0.675</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-at-risk-of-reversal-below-0-675/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 03:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79520</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple price started a fresh decline below the $0.785 zone against the US dollar. The price is now trading below $0.725 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $0.715 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Bittrex). [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-at-risk-of-reversal-below-0-675/">Ripple Price Analysis: XRP At Risk of Reversal Below $0.675</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ripple price started a fresh decline below the $0.785 zone against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $0.725 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $0.715 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Bittrex).</li>
<li>The pair could extend losses if it breaks the $0.675 support zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ripple price is struggling below $0.765 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. XRP price could decline further if it settles below the $0.675 support in the near term.</em></p>
<h2>Ripple Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, Ripple price started a fresh decline from well above $0.820 against the US Dollar. The XRP/USD pair gained bearish momentum below the $0.80 level.</p>
<p>The bears were able to push the price below the $0.785 support. It even traded below the 55 simple moving average (4 hours) and spiked below the $0.70 support. A low is formed near $0.6734 and the price is now attempting a recovery wave.</p>
<p>There was a move above the $0.70 level. Besides, there was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $0.715 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair.</p>
<p>XRP is now trading below $0.725 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-protect-uptrend-support-aims-fresh-rally/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near $0.7155, and the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.8525 swing high to the $0.6734 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $0.765 level. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.8525 swing high to the $0.6734 low.</p>
<p>A clear move above $0.765 might start a fresh increase. In the stated case, the price could even surpass the $0.785 resistance. Any more gains might send the price toward the $0.820 resistance. Initial support on the downside is near $0.6750. The next major support is near the $0.650 level. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.620 level, below which the price might even test $0.60.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79521" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79521" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple-4.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-79521" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple-4.png" alt="Ripple Price" width="1835" height="839" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple-4.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple-4-600x274.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple-4-1100x503.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple-4-768x351.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple-4-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple-4-750x343.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple-4-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79521" class="wp-caption-text">Ripple Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/">chart</a>, Ripple’s price is now trading below the $0.725 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could extend losses if it breaks the $0.675 support zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XRP/USD is now losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for XRP/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.700, $0.6750, and $0.650.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.7155 and $0.7650.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-at-risk-of-reversal-below-0-675/">Ripple Price Analysis: XRP At Risk of Reversal Below $0.675</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Fan and Miami Mayor Francis Suarez Enters Presidential Race</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-fan-and-miami-mayor-francis-suarez-enters-presidential-race/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 17:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Francis Suarez]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78822</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As we’ve mentioned in previous articles, it’s likely bitcoin and crypto are going to be huge topics in next year’s presidential election. Recently, another bitcoin-loving candidate threw himself into the race… Republican mayor of Miami Francis Suarez. Francis Suarez is Running for President Suarez has long been a bitcoin advocate, going so far as to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-fan-and-miami-mayor-francis-suarez-enters-presidential-race/">Bitcoin Fan and Miami Mayor Francis Suarez Enters Presidential Race</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As we’ve mentioned in previous articles, it’s likely bitcoin and crypto are <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-bitcoin-could-be-a-big-topic-in-next-years-presidential-election/">going to be huge topics</a> in next year’s presidential election. Recently, another bitcoin-loving <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/new-presidential-contender-bitcoin-mayor-francis-suarez-is-major-crypto-evangelist/ar-AA1cBeuP">candidate threw himself</a> into the race… Republican mayor of Miami Francis Suarez.</p>
<h2>Francis Suarez is Running for President</h2>
<p>Suarez has long been a bitcoin advocate, going so far as <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mayors-eric-adams-and-francis-suarez-are-eager-for-btc-based-salaries/">to announce in 2021 that</a> he would accept his entire mayoral salary in bitcoin (a move shared by New York City mayor Eric Adams). In an interview at the time, he mentioned he wanted to send a message to the world that Miami was going to be one of the most innovative and tech-happy cities on Earth.</p>
<p>He also said he wanted to potentially start a trend and see how many other politicians and government employees would follow suit. He explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>It will be completely optional. We want our employees to have that option, but it certainly is not going to be something we are going to force on them, understanding that a decision like that is a personal decision they [must] make if they want to make it.</p></blockquote>
<p>His bullishness didn’t end there. He also <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/francis-suarez-miami-coin-isnt-going-anywhere/">introduced Miami Coin</a>, a unique token for residents of his town. The idea was that the currency could potentially raise funds for the city’s growth and could also be used amongst citizens to pay utilities and related expenses. When it was launched in early 2022, the currency garnered more than $5 million in disbursements from City Coins (the minting company), which ultimately went towards a city rental assistance program.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, the coin didn’t get very far, only hiking to a price of about five cents per unit. Following the crypto winter of 2022, the asset was soon considered useless, and it was only ever offered on one crypto exchange. That exchange (called OK Coin) has since decided to suspend all trading of the token. In a statement, the company said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Limited liquidity for these coins on our platform has created the possibility of price manipulation and fraudulent activity. As a result, we will suspend trading until we can address these potential risks and protect our customers.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Trying to Get More Companies Involved</h2>
<p>Still, Suarez isn’t allowing this to bring him down. He has worked hard to bring about a Silicon Valley-type air to Miami, only he’s pushing hard for crypto companies to come and set up headquarters there. Among the ones to set up shop in the region were the now defunct crypto exchange FTX and Blockchain.com. Speaking of the latter’s arrival, Suarez said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Blockchain.com’s arrival in Miami perfectly encapsulates what the Miami movement is all about — leveraging Miami&#8217;s talent against the world&#8217;s top companies to build towards our goal of becoming a Miami that lasts forever and a Miami that works for everyone.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-fan-and-miami-mayor-francis-suarez-enters-presidential-race/">Bitcoin Fan and Miami Mayor Francis Suarez Enters Presidential Race</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apple Threatens to Remove Bitcoin Tipping Social App from Its Store</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/apple-threatens-to-remove-bitcoin-tipping-social-app-from-its-store/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Damus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78819</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jack Dorsey and Elon Musk aren’t too happy with the Apple company as of late. Apple Ain&#8217;t No Bitcoin Tipping Fan Not long ago, the technology conglomerate said it was looking into potentially removing the social media app Damus from its store. The reason was because the application offered a bitcoin tipping feature, and Apple [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/apple-threatens-to-remove-bitcoin-tipping-social-app-from-its-store/">Apple Threatens to Remove Bitcoin Tipping Social App from Its Store</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jack Dorsey and Elon Musk aren’t <a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/elon-musk-dorsey-apple-nostr-damus-app-rcna89328">too happy with the</a> Apple company as of late.</p>
<h2>Apple Ain&#8217;t No Bitcoin Tipping Fan</h2>
<p>Not long ago, the technology conglomerate said it was looking into potentially removing the social media app Damus from its store. The reason was because the application offered a bitcoin tipping feature, and Apple doesn’t want anything to do with such services. The company then made it clear to Damus: get rid of the feature, or you will no longer be offered in our store.</p>
<p>It’s not so much bitcoin that’s angering Apple, but rather the reason it’s being used. Damus is giving content creators a chance to earn compensation for material they post when it’s often free on other platforms. The social app says all content creators have a right to garner pay when they create something, and bitcoin is just a way to get them the money they need.</p>
<p>Apple claims Damus is “selling digital content,” which allegedly violates its present terms and conditions, and all gifts connected to receiving such content are required to use the in-app purchase functionality. In any case, Musk and Dorsey are choosing to focus more on the crypto aspects of the situation at hand, and they believe this is more an attempt to get bitcoin out of the picture. In a tweet, Dorsey mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>This is still incorrect @apple. Tipping on posts is not selling digital content. It’s a form of feedback… Why limit people sending bitcoin to each other? This is our one opportunity to build a truly global payment protocol for the internet (which would benefit your company immensely).</p></blockquote>
<p>Musk was also quick to throw his two cents into the mix, tweeting:</p>
<blockquote><p>If Apple competes against the whole world, Apple will have the whole world against it. This is not a winning scenario.</p></blockquote>
<p>Tim Sweeney, the CEO and co-founder of video game developer Epic Games, was also very critical of Apple’s sentiment, claiming:</p>
<blockquote><p>Apple is coming for money transfer and funding apps like Damus, Patreon, Venmo, maybe PayPal and Stripe… If digital goods may be somehow involved in the transfer, now they want 30 percent. If Apple can tax this, they can tax digital banking, payroll, and anything else.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Lot of Crypto Love</h2>
<p>Both Dorsey and Musk have been huge crypto advocates in the past. There was a time that Tesla vehicles, for example, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-permits-bitcoin-payments-for-tesla-vehicles/">were going to be purchasable</a> via bitcoin, though Musk has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-has-taken-a-nasty-stumble-many-are-blaming-elon-musk/">since rescinded this</a> decision. However, he still focuses <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/latest-elon-musk-tweet-sends-dogecoin-soaring/">heavily on Dogecoin</a>.</p>
<p>Dorsey has also been a huge bitcoin <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jack-dorsey-backs-btc-fan-robert-kennedy-jr-for-president/">fanatic and is now pushing</a> Robert F. Kennedy, Jr. – a democratic candidate for president – as the person to consider for the White House given Kennedy is supporting bitcoin use in America and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-hopeful-robert-kennedy-jr-appeared-at-this-years-miami-btc-conference/">recently spoke at this year’s</a> Miami Bitcoin Conference.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/apple-threatens-to-remove-bitcoin-tipping-social-app-from-its-store/">Apple Threatens to Remove Bitcoin Tipping Social App from Its Store</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BLK DNM Fashion Brand Acquired By Leading Blockchain Firm</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blk-dnm-fashion-brand-acquired-by-leading-blockchain-firm/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 13:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BLK DNM]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chroma Way]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78817</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The worlds of fashion and blockchain are coming together as luxury fashion label BLK DNM has been acquired by blockchain firm Chroma Way. The purpose? To embed digital garment IDs (undetectable microchips) into every new piece of clothing that will be issued to potential buyers. BLK DNM Will Have Chips in Its Clothing The chips [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blk-dnm-fashion-brand-acquired-by-leading-blockchain-firm/">BLK DNM Fashion Brand Acquired By Leading Blockchain Firm</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The worlds of fashion and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/blockchain/">blockchain</a> are <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/angelalei/2023/06/15/blk-dnm-to-unveil-fw23-collection-powered-by-blockchain-technology/?sh=3181f36b6ff6">coming together as luxury</a> fashion label BLK DNM has been acquired by blockchain firm Chroma Way. The purpose? To embed digital garment IDs (undetectable microchips) into every new piece of clothing that will be issued to potential buyers.</p>
<h2>BLK DNM Will Have Chips in Its Clothing</h2>
<p>The chips will permit each clothing article to have a unique identity that will be recorded on a distributed ledger. The chips will also monitor the production of the garments from the time they’re first conceived to the moment they arrive on the market. The chips will reward ethical behavior and assure owners’ brand influence.</p>
<p>Toni Collin – CEO of BLK DNM – said in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>BLK DNM’s philosophy is one of community, and our clothing is designed, through both its craftsmanship and timeless aesthetic, to be treasured and passed down through generations — the antithesis of irresponsible fast fashion. Now, with the introduction of BLK DNM Society and the first embedded hardware in our garments, we take those two pillars to a revolutionary new level. By embedding intelligence in every item, we hope we can inspire our industry to join us in using connected fashion to do better.</p></blockquote>
<p>Collin further stated that this is the perfect first step in developing a new fashion community, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>For the first time in fashion, technology is being used to engage that community in the virtual worlds that are increasingly a part of people’s lives, particularly for younger generations.</p></blockquote>
<p>Henrik Hjelte – CEO of and co-founder of Chroma Way – was also quick to throw his two cents into the mix, mentioning:</p>
<blockquote><p>Nothing like this has been attempted in fashion before. This has the potential to transform people’s relationships with the clothes they wear and brands they buy. No longer does the relationship with the customer end at the checkout. Each beautiful garment now becomes its own living, evolving piece of history.</p></blockquote>
<p>Discussing the merging of both fashion and blockchain technology, Collin added:</p>
<blockquote><p>Echoing Henrik, nothing like this has happened before. Blockchain technology offers a unique opportunity to reward responsible behaviors and to create identity and story in individual items&#8230; BLK DNM Society is bridging the gap between offline and online communities in a potentially transformative manner. The industry must begin to address the elephant in the room. The apparel industry generates an extraordinary amount of waste, even more so with the rise of fast fashion. What we’re launching here is the first step towards changing that through next-generation technology.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Rewarding the Right People</h2>
<p>The digital IDs will work to ensure all clothing is authentic while getting rid of anything that’s fake. Responsible behavior (like refurbishing clothing and second-hand purchases) will also garner positive attention and rewards.</p>
<p>BLK DNM believes adding garments to the blockchain will increase their value over time.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blk-dnm-fashion-brand-acquired-by-leading-blockchain-firm/">BLK DNM Fashion Brand Acquired By Leading Blockchain Firm</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Michael Saylor: SEC Lawsuits Are Paving the Way for BTC Dominance</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-sec-lawsuits-are-paving-the-way-to-btc-dominance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 17:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Saylor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroStrategy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78806</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Saylor, the former CEO of MicroStrategy, commented in an interview that the present SEC lawsuits against platforms like Coinbase and Binance will pave the way for bitcoin to become bigger than it’s ever been. Michael Saylor on the Future of BTC He anticipates that the bitcoin dominance in the crypto industry (which currently stands [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-sec-lawsuits-are-paving-the-way-to-btc-dominance/">Michael Saylor: SEC Lawsuits Are Paving the Way for BTC Dominance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Michael Saylor, the former CEO of MicroStrategy, <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/bitcoin-market-share-sec-regulators-cryptocurrencies-binance-microstrategy-michael-saylor-2023-6">commented in an interview</a> that the present SEC lawsuits against platforms like Coinbase and Binance will pave the way for bitcoin to become bigger than it’s ever been.</p>
<h2>Michael Saylor on the Future of BTC</h2>
<p>He anticipates that the bitcoin dominance in the crypto industry (which currently stands between 40 and 48 percent) will shoot up to a whopping 80 percent, leaving only a 20 percent margin for remaining altcoins. He thinks that with so many crypto exchanges afraid of the SEC and delisting altcoins that might be considered securities, bitcoin is going to become the ultimate force in crypto. He commented in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Now I think that the public is beginning to realize that bitcoin is the next bitcoin. The next logical step is for bitcoin to [grow] ten times from here and then ten times again.</p></blockquote>
<p>There are many crypto investors out there that have tried hard to diversify their portfolios. They have invested in multiple coins across a wide spectrum of assets as a means of ensuring that if one coin goes down, they at least have the chance of sustaining their wealth and keeping their stability.</p>
<p>However, with so many exchanges and trading platforms now getting rid of various altcoins, they’ll want to remain in the crypto space and will have no choice but to place all their money into BTC, which could wind up making it the ultimate king of digital assets.</p>
<p>Saylor has always <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-still-believes-btc-has-a-ton-of-power/">been a bitcoin bull</a>, first catching the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-microstrategy-bitcoin-bet-is-already-paying-off-big-time/">bitcoin bug back in late 2020</a> and investing some of his company’s money into the world’s number one digital currency by market cap. While things appeared promising at the start, by 2022, the currency had taken a serious turn for the worse, and Saylor wound up <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/microstrategy-dealt-heavy-blow-following-crypto-crash/">losing a bunch of</a> cash for MicroStrategy that still, largely, has not been recovered. From there, Saylor <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-btc-bull-and-microstrategy-chief-executive-steps-down/">left the CEO position</a> he worked for over 30 years and demoted himself to executive chairman.</p>
<p>Discussing the present mind frame of the SEC, Saylor mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>I mean, their view is [that] crypto exchanges should trade and hold pure digital commodities like bitcoin, and so the entire industry is kind of destined to be rationalized down to a bitcoin-focused industry, with maybe a half a dozen to a dozen other proof of work tokens.</p></blockquote>
<h2>All Exchanges Will Only Focus on BTC</h2>
<p>Eventually, he foresees a time when <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/microstrategy-founder-michael-saylor-says-bitcoin-could-grow-to-80-of-crypto-market-after-sec-suits-against-binance-and-coinbase/ar-AA1cyfwW">all crypto exchanges</a> in the world turn their backs on altcoins entirely and focus purely on bitcoin trading for their customers. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Eventually, I have confidence that the crypto exchanges will come around to realizing that bitcoin really is the dominant asset in this space, and their business models are fine when bitcoin goes up by a factor of ten.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-sec-lawsuits-are-paving-the-way-to-btc-dominance/">Michael Saylor: SEC Lawsuits Are Paving the Way for BTC Dominance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
