<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 12:29:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Woman in South Korea Murdered for Her Crypto Holdings</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/woman-in-south-korea-murdered-for-her-crypto-holdings/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/woman-in-south-korea-murdered-for-her-crypto-holdings/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 17:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Do Kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Murder]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77852</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The recent kidnapping and murder of a woman in Seoul, South Korea (the nation’s capital city) has turned up some new evidence. Police investigating the matter believe the woman may have been involved in various crypto-related disputes, and that her attacker was associated and hired by the opposing party. Why Is There So Much Crypto<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/woman-in-south-korea-murdered-for-her-crypto-holdings/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/woman-in-south-korea-murdered-for-her-crypto-holdings/">Woman in South Korea Murdered for Her Crypto Holdings</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The recent kidnapping and murder of a woman in Seoul, South Korea (the nation’s capital city) has turned up <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/2nd-ld-key-suspect-in-kidnapping-murder-first-proposed-killing-over-cryptocurrency-disputes-police/ar-AA19DSnQ" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">some new evidence</a>. Police investigating the matter believe the woman may have been involved in various crypto-related disputes, and that her attacker was associated and hired by the opposing party.</p>
<h2>Why Is There So Much Crypto Crime in South Korea?</h2>
<p>The pair perpetrating the crime was a husband-and-wife duo named Yoo and Hwang, and they are believed to have paid more than $53,000 to the key suspect in the murder to carry things out. This stems from an official statement from Seoul’s Suseo Police Station. Arrest warrants were later issued for the suspect (who goes by the name Lee) and for Hwang, who is wanted for questioning.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, Lee has confessed to all the charges that are against him, while the married couple say they have nothing to do with what’s going on. Lee has been arrested along with two other accomplices for allegedly carrying out the murder of the 48-year-old woman from the Gangnam district in Seoul, South Korea. The killing is believed to have occurred on March 29 of this year. Lee and his associates then later (crudely) disposed of her remains.</p>
<p>Lee has issued an apology to the victim and her family, saying in recent statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>I&#8217;d like to offer my sincere apology to the victim in this case, and I pray for the repose of her soul. I am also really sorry to her family for the irreparable scars this has caused.</p></blockquote>
<p>South Korea appears to be at the center of heavy digital currency-centered crime as of late. Not long ago, it was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-executive-do-kwon-arrested-in-montenegro/" data-wpel-link="internal">announced that Do Kwon</a> – the creator of Terra Labs – had been arrested in the European nation of Montenegro after he was discovered to be holding phony passports at an airport terminal. Do Kwon was wanted by authorities in connection with the collapse of Terra USD, an algorithmic stable currency that fell apart in the summer of last year, causing investors to lose billions.</p>
<h2>Kwon Making Off with Investments?</h2>
<p>Kwon is believed to have transferred all his Terra <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-case-against-crypto-exec-do-kwon-just-got-a-lot-hairier/" data-wpel-link="internal">holdings into BTC just</a> weeks before the coin’s collapse, suggesting to authorities that Kwon was planning to kill the currency and make off with any remaining profits in a rug pull. For months, Kwon was a fugitive hiding from the law, though he continued to deny this claim on social media, instead mentioning that he <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-exec-do-kwon-says-hes-willing-to-cooperate-following-arrest-warrant/" data-wpel-link="internal">was willing to cooperate</a> with police and that he was busy writing code in his living room.</p>
<p>The victim in this present case was part of a crypto investment scheme that the married couple also took part in. They ultimately discussed stealing her digital currency stash after the murder was to take place.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/woman-in-south-korea-murdered-for-her-crypto-holdings/">Woman in South Korea Murdered for Her Crypto Holdings</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/woman-in-south-korea-murdered-for-her-crypto-holdings/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How strong is the AI quantitative trading bot? speak with data</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-strong-is-the-ai-quantitative-trading-bot-speak-with-data/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-strong-is-the-ai-quantitative-trading-bot-speak-with-data/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 15:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78402</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The picture above is a return test chart of a quantitative strategy. Before the back test week is 2021 to 2023, 25 months, the rate of return is as high as 7869%, which is equivalent to an annualized rate of return of 3779%, which is the annualized rate of return. The rate is close to<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-strong-is-the-ai-quantitative-trading-bot-speak-with-data/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-strong-is-the-ai-quantitative-trading-bot-speak-with-data/">How strong is the AI quantitative trading bot? speak with data</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The picture above is a return test chart of a quantitative strategy. Before the back test week is 2021 to 2023, 25 months, the rate of return is as high as 7869%, which is equivalent to an annualized rate of return of 3779%, which is the annualized rate of return. The rate is close to 40 times. It&#8217;s time to embrace the future with <a href="https://www.atpbot.com?utm_source=livebitcoinnews&amp;utm_medium=sp&amp;utm_campaign=20230512" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>AI trading bots</strong></a>.</p>
<h4>What is Quantitative Trading?</h4>
<p>The quantitative strategy platform is a trading platform based on big data and artificial intelligence technology that develops a series of automated trading strategies by studying historical data and market trends. Through the quantitative strategy platform, you can choose a strategy that suits you, and automatically trade to obtain stable returns. According to incomplete statistics, the proportion of quantitative transactions used by investment banking institutions has exceeded 90%, and it has already determined the future of the speculative world.</p>
<h4>What are the advantages of automated quantitative trading over manual trading?</h4>
<p>Faster speed: Automated trading systems can analyze market data and execute trading operations more quickly, so that transactions can respond faster and capture market opportunities faster.</p>
<p>Better discipline: automated trading systems can adhere to strict trading rules and strategies, and avoid bad trading decisions caused by emotions and subjective judgments. Therefore, automated trading systems are better able to maintain trading discipline and stability.</p>
<p>More Precise: Automated trading systems are able to use sophisticated algorithms and models to analyze market data to more precisely identify and exploit trading opportunities and better manage risk.</p>
<p>Automated execution: The automated trading system can automatically execute trading strategies 24 hours a day, reducing the manpower and time costs required for manual trading, and can also keep trading while sleeping or leaving the computer.</p>
<p>Backtesting and optimization: Automated trading systems can use historical data for backtesting and optimization to improve trading strategies and improve trading performance.</p>
<h4>Why are quantitative trading bots suitable for the crypto market?</h4>
<p>The cryptocurrency market is highly volatile, and market trends are difficult to predict, and many investors have suffered losses as a result. However, trading platforms based on quantitative strategies can use data analysis and machine learning technology to find the laws and trends in the market, improve the success rate of investment, and reduce risks.</p>
<p>How should we carry out quantitative trading? First of all, you have to have a quantitative strategy. If you don&#8217;t have one, then ATPBot is a good choice.</p>
<h4>What is ATPBot?</h4>
<p><a href="https://www.atpbot.com?utm_source=livebitcoinnews&amp;utm_medium=sp&amp;utm_campaign=20230512" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>ATPBot</strong></a> is a platform that focuses on the development and service of quantitative trading strategies, and is committed to providing efficient and stable trading strategies for cryptocurrency investors. Using supercomputers and AI algorithms, combined with data analysis, social network sentiment analysis, fundamental analysis and other methods, a variety of scientific and effective quantitative trading strategies have been developed. All released strategies are back-tested with millisecond-level data, and many of them Quantitative strategies with an annual return of more than 1000% help you easily obtain returns in the market. ATPBot adheres to the consistent concept of integrity, transparency and security, and strives to make quantitative transactions easier, more efficient and more reliable.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-78404 aligncenter" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Picture107-600x424.png" alt="" width="600" height="424" /></p>
<h4>How is ATPBot different from traditional trading bots?</h4>
<p>Compared with other trading bots on the market, ATPBot has unique advantages. Unlike many other trading bot platforms that rely entirely on predetermined parameters set by the trader, ATPBot employs extensively tested and proven trading strategies. By conducting rigorous historical data analysis and market analysis, ATPBot has fine-tuned its strategies to minimize risks and losses while maximizing profits. This is different from other trading bots that cannot control the trading process and often cause traders to lose money.</p>
<p>Additionally, ATPBot eliminates the need for users to spend countless hours manually testing different parameters or gaining expertise in chart and indicator manipulation. With ATPBot, users can rely on a reliable and proven trading bot to professionally manage their investments for an efficient and effective trading experience.</p>
<p>In conclusion, choose ATPBot for an unparalleled trading experience, delivering results through proven trading strategies and professional investment management.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-78405 aligncenter" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Picture108-600x336.png" alt="" width="600" height="336" /></p>
<h4>Why choose ATPBot?</h4>
<p><strong>Technology leadership</strong>: Using the most advanced technology, combining multiple factors, looking for profit methods through complex data types.</p>
<p><strong>Convenient and easy to use</strong>: The platform is easy to use, one-click start strategy, provide professional guidance, suitable for inexperienced traders.</p>
<p><strong>Professional customization</strong>: Personally customize strategies for each customer, and strive to provide each customer with the most suitable quantitative strategy for them.</p>
<p>S<strong>ecurity and transparency</strong>: Customer funds cannot be accessed, all operations are transparent and visible, and we are committed to providing maximum protection for customer transactions.</p>
<p><strong>Monitoring and service</strong>: Provide 24-hour monitoring and one-on-one service to quickly solve customer problems.</p>
<p><strong>Ultra-low management fee</strong>: Provide a one-time payment and permanent operation mode, so that the investment income is greater.</p>
<p>In addition to the functions of the platform itself, ATPBot also has a professional <a href="https://discord.gg/JQnY3pNtkk" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>discord community</strong></a>, which gathers a large number of quantitative trading researchers and practitioners. In the community, you can interact with quantitative trading enthusiasts from all over the world, sharing experiences and ideas. Not only will this improve your trading knowledge and skills, but you can also learn and get inspired by other people&#8217;s trading strategies. At the same time, our community also provides professional guidance, including guidance on market trends, market analysis and trading skills, to help you go further on the road of quantitative trading.</p>
<p>Just <a href="https://www.atpbot.com/signup?utm_source=livebitcoinnews&amp;utm_medium=sp&amp;utm_campaign=20230512" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>register an account</strong></a> at ATPBot, you can open the door of automatic quantitative trading and share the results brought by big data.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-strong-is-the-ai-quantitative-trading-bot-speak-with-data/">How strong is the AI quantitative trading bot? speak with data</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-strong-is-the-ai-quantitative-trading-bot-speak-with-data/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Report Details What Really Led to the FTX Collapse</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-report-details-what-really-led-to-the-ftx-collapse/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-report-details-what-really-led-to-the-ftx-collapse/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 15:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hubris]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77849</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new report has emerged talking about what it was that really led to the destruction and collapse of the FTX digital currency exchange. Why Did FTX Really Fall? Everyone would like to think it was heavy corruption or something similar, but per the words of the report, it was merely “hubris and greed.” Hubris<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-report-details-what-really-led-to-the-ftx-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-report-details-what-really-led-to-the-ftx-collapse/">New Report Details What Really Led to the FTX Collapse</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new report has emerged talking about what it was that <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/hubris-incompetence-and-greed-plagued-failed-cryptocurrency-exchange-ftx/ar-AA19HgzF" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">really led to the destruction</a> and collapse of the FTX digital currency exchange.</p>
<h2>Why Did FTX <em>Really</em> Fall?</h2>
<p>Everyone would like to think it was heavy corruption or something similar, but per the words of the report, it was merely “hubris and greed.” Hubris is described as “arrogance before the gods” (according to games like <em>Far Cry 5</em>). Mere mortals like us should take that like everyone at FTX had tremendous egos. They all thought they were too smart and too capable and thus didn’t take necessary precautions.</p>
<p>In terms of greed, it’s clear that many people involved with the company sought to get their hands on money they didn’t necessarily need. Money that belonged to other people. This is among the many charges that the former head executive of FTX – Sam Bankman-Fried – is now facing. It is said that SBF utilized customer funds to purchase luxury real estate in the Bahamas, where the company was stationed. Naughty, naughty, naughty…</p>
<p>In addition, the debtors’ report also suggests that an incredible lack of competence underlined the many mishaps that occurred behind the FTX walls. For example, the company failed to create key executive roles to ensure specific duties were tackled in due time. Thus, you had an environment where everyone was clearly multi-tasking… Something they weren’t equipped to do. There was also no cybersecurity department to keep customer funds safe should mishaps have occurred (which they obviously did).</p>
<p>Lastly, the company is believed to have lied to third parties about its funds and business dealings, and there were many jokes amongst employees about how quick the company was to lose track of millions of dollars at a time. There was also no controlled framework or oversight of business dealings. In the end, this helped the firm to “collapse as quickly as it had grown,” the report comments.</p>
<p>The fall of FTX is likely to go down as one of the most embarrassing occurrences within the digital currency space. Founded in 2019 (merely four years ago), the company quickly rose through the ranks to become the third largest crypto exchange in the world by the summer of 2021. Everyone thought the company was on top of the world and incapable of collapsing, but they were wrong…</p>
<h2>A History of Bad Behavior</h2>
<p>In November of 2022, Sam Bankman-Fried complained online <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">that his company needed</a> cash fast to continue operating. He <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">approached his competitor</a> Binance about being bought out, but the latter firm took one look at FTX’s issues and quickly said “no.” FTX then had no choice but to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">file bankruptcy</a>.</p>
<p>It wasn’t long before this led to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftxs-disgraced-founder-has-been-arrested/" data-wpel-link="internal">the arrest</a> of Sam Bankman-Fried, who is <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-to-await-trial-at-his-parents-house/" data-wpel-link="internal">now awaiting trial</a> at his parents’ home in Northern California.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-report-details-what-really-led-to-the-ftx-collapse/">New Report Details What Really Led to the FTX Collapse</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-report-details-what-really-led-to-the-ftx-collapse/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Xrp Classic Making Progress in Closed Beta Testing of Forward-Thinking Blockchain Classic Chain!</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/xrp-classic-making-progress-in-closed-beta-testing-of-forward-thinking-blockchain-classic-chain/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/xrp-classic-making-progress-in-closed-beta-testing-of-forward-thinking-blockchain-classic-chain/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Gautham]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 15:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78407</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We are here with exciting news! Working on the blockchain, Xrp Classic is nearing the end of their blockchain, which they call Classic Chain. Classic Chain is configured using the powerful and reliable Proof of Authority protocol. Xrp Classic is proud to share the results of closed beta tests and in this article we will<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/xrp-classic-making-progress-in-closed-beta-testing-of-forward-thinking-blockchain-classic-chain/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/xrp-classic-making-progress-in-closed-beta-testing-of-forward-thinking-blockchain-classic-chain/">Xrp Classic Making Progress in Closed Beta Testing of Forward-Thinking Blockchain Classic Chain!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We are here with exciting news! Working on the blockchain, Xrp Classic is nearing the end of their blockchain, which they call Classic Chain. Classic Chain is configured using the powerful and reliable Proof of Authority protocol. Xrp Classic is proud to share the results of closed beta tests and in this article we will give you some important information.</p>
<h3>What is Proof of Authority?</h3>
<p>Proof of Authority was proposed by Gavin Wood, one of the co-founders of Ethereum. In the Proof of Authority protocol, users who verify transaction blocks on the blockchain use their identities and reputations instead of using and staking cryptocurrency assets to validate transactions. In networks that use the Proof of Authority protocol, individuals with pre-verified identities gain the authority to produce new blocks. The real identities of the validators responsible for the functioning of the network are known, and their authorization comes after a certain review process following the disclosure of their true identity.</p>
<h3>What is the Purpose of Using Proof of Authority Blockchain Networks?</h3>
<p>Proof of Authority was developed as an alternative to commonly used protocols such as Proof of Stake and Proof of Work. It is used in blockchain networks with the aim of providing an alternative to the limitations and issues that need to be addressed in Proof of Stake and Proof of Work. The Proof of Authority protocol allows for a higher number of transactions per second compared to other protocols. The energy consumption in these transactions is significantly lower. In comparison to other protocols, lower transaction fees are incurred.</p>
<h3>Tests on the Classic Chain TestNet Network:</h3>
<h4>Nodes</h4>
<p>The developer team has been conducting closed beta tests on the Classic Chain TestNet network for a long time, today we will share with you some results of these tests. In the closed TestNet network, the number of blocks currently created has exceeded 100,000. This is a testament to the strong and steady progress of the blockchain.</p>
<h4>Fast and Efficient Block Creation and Transfer Time</h4>
<p>The developer team has made and continues to make some updates to the methods of creating nodes as a result of long work to improve the performance of the blockchain. Thanks to these updates, it was possible to reduce the average block generation and transfer time from 6.5 seconds to 5.1 seconds in low-intensity situations. These fast transaction times will enable users to perform transactions on the blockchain faster and more efficiently.</p>
<h3>Transition Plans to Open Beta Tests</h3>
<p>Closed Beta tests of Classic Chain continue unabated, and they stated that they will share other data and achievements they have achieved in the near future. After the Closed Beta tests are fully completed, they announced that they will start open beta tests.</p>
<p>Congratulations to Xrp Classic on their success!</p>
<p>Website: <a href="https://www.xrpclassic.com" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.xrpclassic.com</a><br />
Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/XrpClassic" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/XrpClassic</a><br />
Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/XrpClassicGlobal" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://t.me/XrpClassicGlobal</a><br />
CMC: <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/xrp-classic-token-new/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/xrp-classic-token-new/</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/xrp-classic-making-progress-in-closed-beta-testing-of-forward-thinking-blockchain-classic-chain/">Xrp Classic Making Progress in Closed Beta Testing of Forward-Thinking Blockchain Classic Chain!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/xrp-classic-making-progress-in-closed-beta-testing-of-forward-thinking-blockchain-classic-chain/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Rose to $30K in Mid-April; Analysts Discuss Why</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 13:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Katharine Wooller]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77847</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The price of bitcoin rose to $30,000 in mid-April for the first time since June of last year. The asset is now up roughly $14,000 from where it was at the end of 2022, which was arguably the worst year on record for the world’s number one digital asset by market cap. Bitcoin Just Keeps<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/">Bitcoin Rose to $30K in Mid-April; Analysts Discuss Why</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price of bitcoin rose to $30,000 in mid-April for the first <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/04/11/forget-the-fed-is-this-the-real-reason-behind-cryptos-200-billion-bitcoin-ethereum-bnb-xrp-cardano-dogecoin-polygon-and-solana-price-boom/?sh=76d5c434711d" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">time since June of last year</a>. The asset is now up roughly $14,000 from where it was at the end of 2022, which was arguably the worst year on record for the world’s number one digital asset by market cap.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Just Keeps Shooting Up</h2>
<p>Of course, we’ve now got analysts throughout the digital asset space wondering what could have caused such a massive hike in the currency’s price. Markus Thielen – head of research and strategy at Matrix Port – commented in a recent note:</p>
<blockquote><p>Stable coin tether (USDT) has now reached a market capitalization of $80 billion, an increase of $13.8 billion. The issuance of USDTs on Ethereum accounts for another $35 billion, but the spread between USDTs issued on Tron and Ethereum is now widening significantly. The all-time high in USDT issuance was at $82 billion in May 2022, and tether is now only $2 billion away from it.</p></blockquote>
<p>Rachel Lin – chief executive of crypto trading company Synfutures – was also quick to chime in with her two cents, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>Higher-than-expected U.S. jobless claims suggest the Federal Reserve may soon halt rate hikes, which could benefit risk assets like crypto. Conversely, a higher unemployment rate could signal a looming recession, negatively impacting all assets.</p></blockquote>
<p>Tether is a stable asset that is often widely tied to BTC. In fact, it is often <a href="https://www.engadget.com/2018-06-13-bitcoin-bitfinex-price-manipulation-cryptocurrency.html#:~:text=Researchers%20now%20say%20that%20the%20digital%20currency%20Tether,in%20value%20from%20March%202017%20through%20March%202018." data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">believed that in 2018</a>, when BTC was struggling pricewise, Tether was utilized to purchase more BTC on the side to help push the asset along and tie it further to USD. Thielen commented further that:</p>
<blockquote><p>Circle USDC lost $11.8 billion and Paxos-Binance BUSD lost $9.4 billion. Obviously, those large moves had implications for crypto assets. In addition, the volume of spot vs. derivatives has now declined to just 11 percent. This means that for every $11 traded in spot, $100 dollars are traded in derivatives. This is the lowest ratio since May 2022 and is a sign of &#8216;pure speculation.&#8217;</p></blockquote>
<p>Katharine Wooller – director at Coin Cover – mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin&#8217;s ten-month high should be a confirmation that we’re seeing a return of a crypto bull market. Since the start of 2023, the crypto market has faced regular turmoil in the form of regulatory challenges and the collapse of crypto companies [which are] indicative of wider systemic problems. Yet, despite this, the market continues to perform well against all odds.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Trying to Put the Past Behind It</h2>
<p>Thus far, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a> has shown extraordinary signs of recovery given it’s only been five months since the start of the year. The currency is easily rising through the ranks to put the doldrums of 2022 behind it once and for all.</p>
<p>During the previous 12 months, bitcoin lost more than 70 percent of its value and fell drastically from its all-time high of $68,000 per unit.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/">Bitcoin Rose to $30K in Mid-April; Analysts Discuss Why</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blocktrade is Changing the Game of Crypto Trading &#8211;  A Remarkable First Move with €4.5 Million Worth of BTEX Sold</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blocktrade-is-changing-the-game-of-crypto-trading-a-remarkable-first-move-with-e4-5-million-worth-of-btex-sold/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blocktrade-is-changing-the-game-of-crypto-trading-a-remarkable-first-move-with-e4-5-million-worth-of-btex-sold/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 08:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sponsored]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78399</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrencies are upending the elitist, paper-shuffling world of traditional finance. They’re creating new stores of value and reigniting financial interest amongst a new class of investors. Blocktrade is taking cryptocurrency engagement to a new level through its gamified universe &#8211; a cryptocurrency trading platform that incorporates levels, collectibles, leaderboards and challenges into crypto trading. Making<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blocktrade-is-changing-the-game-of-crypto-trading-a-remarkable-first-move-with-e4-5-million-worth-of-btex-sold/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blocktrade-is-changing-the-game-of-crypto-trading-a-remarkable-first-move-with-e4-5-million-worth-of-btex-sold/">Blocktrade is Changing the Game of Crypto Trading &#8211;  A Remarkable First Move with €4.5 Million Worth of BTEX Sold</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrencies are upending the elitist, paper-shuffling world of traditional finance. They’re creating new stores of value and reigniting financial interest amongst a new class of investors. <a href="https://blocktrade.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Blocktrade</a> is taking cryptocurrency engagement to a new level through its gamified universe &#8211; a cryptocurrency trading platform that incorporates levels, collectibles, leaderboards and challenges into crypto trading.</p>
<p>Making financial knowledge more accessible is a cornerstone of Web3, and Blocktrade is transforming how people engage with and learn about digital assets. The gamification of crypto fills the education gap by applying game design elements to non-gaming contexts, such as trading cryptocurrencies. By making trading exciting, this platform is onboarding the next generation of crypto investors who want an easy, simple way to create wealth.</p>
<p>Powered by the <a href="https://blocktrade.com/btex-token" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">BTEX token</a>, Blocktrade offers a fully gamified universe. As users participate in specific activities and progress through levels on Blocktrade’s platform, they earn BTEX tokens and XP points along the way, unlocking a wide array of benefits and rewards such as trading bonuses and discount fees. Minigames on the platform have already racked up more than 90,000 plays in the first four weeks since beta launch, emphasizing the appetite in the trading community for this new form of engagement.</p>
<p>The wave of NFT popularity that reached new highs in the last years is still only the beginning of investment into digital worlds and personas. Now, crypto investments, digital collectables, and unique, personalizable avatars are all available on a single platform: Blocktrade.</p>
<p>As part of this gamified crypto universe, Blocktrade has just launched a Crypto Greek Gods collection, introducing 50 unique avatars representing Greek Gods for users to immerse themselves in a world where mythological creatures come to life. The collection features five female goddesses: Aphrodite, Artemis, Athena, Hera, and Nemesis, and five male gods: Apollo, Ares, Hades, Poseidon, and Zeus. These limited-edition digital collectible avatars, meticulously designed by a talented NFT artist, serve as a symbol of accomplishment within the rewards program. By intertwining gaming and crypto through a Greek God theme, Blocktrade is creating a captivating connection that bridges the past and future.</p>
<p>The world of cryptocurrency is constantly evolving, pushing the boundaries of what is possible in the digital landscape, and Blocktrade is a crypto platform designed for the future. Gamification is the next step in trading culture and a move that will leave traditional finance further behind. On gamified platforms, routine tasks become exciting challenges, and platforms like Blocktrade deliver an engaging, intuitive experience for investors that want accessible opportunities to make money. This development epitomizes Blocktrade’s goal to democratize investing and bring innovative wealth-creation opportunities to the masses.</p>
<p>Blocktrade&#8217;s vision for gamified cryptocurrency trading is being realized though BTEX, a token that functions as the fuel for Blocktrade’s gamified universe. BTEX has already attracted more than 1400 supporters from all over the world, who bought more than €4,500,000 worth of BTEX in the successful exclusive round of the token sale.</p>
<p>The public round of the token sale is ongoing until June 9th. Anyone with an account on Blocktrade can participate, acquire BTEX at a discounted rate and be a part of the future of cryptocurrency trading. Learn more at <a href="https://blocktrade.com/btex-token" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">blocktrade.com/btex-token</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blocktrade-is-changing-the-game-of-crypto-trading-a-remarkable-first-move-with-e4-5-million-worth-of-btex-sold/">Blocktrade is Changing the Game of Crypto Trading &#8211;  A Remarkable First Move with €4.5 Million Worth of BTEX Sold</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blocktrade-is-changing-the-game-of-crypto-trading-a-remarkable-first-move-with-e4-5-million-worth-of-btex-sold/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Risk of Fresh Drop to $105</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-105/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-105/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 03:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78396</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline below the $120 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below the $118 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support at $116.00 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-105/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-105/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Risk of Fresh Drop to $105</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline below the $120 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below the $118 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support at $116.00 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it stays below the $116 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin cash price is declining below the $118 zone against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-27250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. BCH/USD could extend losses if there is a close below $112.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin cash price struggled to gain pace for a move above the $120 and $122 resistance levels. BCH formed a high near $120.93 and started a fresh decline.</p>
<p>There was a clear move below the $118.00 and $116.00 support levels. The pair even declined below the $116 support. It tested the $112 zone. A low is formed near $112.89 and the price is now consolidating losses. It is now trading above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $120.93 swing high to the $112.89 low.</p>
<p>Besides, it is trading below the $118 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Immediate resistance is near the $116.00 level and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bears-aim-fresh-drop-to-100/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>The 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $120.93 swing high to the $112.89 low is also near $116. The next key resistance is near $118. Any more gains above $116 and $118 could set the pace for a move toward the $120 level.</p>
<p>If there is a move above the $120 resistance, the price could rise toward the $128 zone. If not, the price might continue lower below $112. Immediate support on the downside is near the $110 zone. The next major support is near the $105 level, below which the bears might aim for $100.</p>
<div id="attachment_78397" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Bitcoin-Cash-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78397" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78397" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Bitcoin-Cash-2.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78397" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Cash Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BCHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Bitcoin cash price is now trading below the $118 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $120 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for BCH/USD is losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BCH/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $112 and $110.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $116 and $118.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-105/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Risk of Fresh Drop to $105</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-105/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brazil Village Centers Itself Around Bitcoin Payments</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brazil-village-centers-itself-around-bitcoin-payments/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brazil-village-centers-itself-around-bitcoin-payments/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brazil]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Praia Bitcoin Project]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77835</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A group of business owners have gathered in Brazil to create a new economic center to accept bitcoin as a form of payment. Bitcoin Is Getting Bigger in Brazil Known as the Praia Bitcoin project, the engagement is designed to set a world record for peer-to-peer transactions on the Lightning Network, which as we reported<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brazil-village-centers-itself-around-bitcoin-payments/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brazil-village-centers-itself-around-bitcoin-payments/">Brazil Village Centers Itself Around Bitcoin Payments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A group of business owners have gathered in Brazil to create a <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/04/09/brazils-bitcoin-beach-says-lightning-network-works-better-than-visa/?sh=7a34299e7e7e" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">new economic center</a> to accept bitcoin as a form of payment.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Is Getting Bigger in Brazil</h2>
<p>Known as the Praia Bitcoin project, the engagement is designed to set a world record for peer-to-peer transactions on the Lightning Network, which as we reported earlier today, is <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-to-integrate-the-btc-lightning-network/" data-wpel-link="internal">now being integrated</a> into Coinbase, one of the largest and most prominent digital currency exchanges in the world. In under three and a half minutes, more than 70 separate BTC transactions occurred, thus setting the time for the shortest period in the crypto history books.</p>
<p>The Lightning Network works to take smaller BTC transactions off-chain, thus allowing the network to operate faster and with lesser costs. Praia Bitcoin’s creator Fernando Motolese proudly explained in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>This was only possible because the Lightning Network is ready for the masses. Right now, there is no other option that is as prepared for this kind of market with a functional solution as Lightning. It is superior to Visa.</p></blockquote>
<p>Initially working as a musician, Motolese was used to a time where money was very scarce. This is what ultimately caused him to turn to bitcoin in the first place, and it’s what inspired him to give business dealings and entrepreneurship a try. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>I asked for help from Bitcoin Beach, but that only came a year later. They were just the inspiration at first, but after the release of their Bitcoin Beach whitepaper,<em> </em>they became a role model and an important partner.</p></blockquote>
<p>Initially, the presence of the Lightning Network in the area had to be built up through consumer donations, which Motolese says was a rather hard undertaking. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Getting donations is very difficult. At each stage of our development, we update our crowdfunding campaign with new goals and proof of the work we have done with those donations. I started this by donating 0.02 BTC, which was around $1,000 at the time. Now we have around 2.43 BTC.</p></blockquote>
<h2>The Government Wants to See BTC Thrive</h2>
<p>The Brazilian government, according to Foxbit CEO Ricardo Dantas, is allegedly working to implement new digital currency rules that will help build out the space and ensure a lasting presence for crypto tokens. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>A better understanding of the regulations will light some fire under Brazilian investor demand for bitcoin because today there are a lot of cold feet regarding cryptocurrency… There is a sense that bitcoin technology is relatively complex and has no rules, which gives people the sense that it is totally lawless. We work hard to change that perception even though it’s not something people see, and it’s not something everyone in crypto will follow, but with better rules will come more adoption [and] more investor confidence.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brazil-village-centers-itself-around-bitcoin-payments/">Brazil Village Centers Itself Around Bitcoin Payments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brazil-village-centers-itself-around-bitcoin-payments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase to Integrate the BTC Lightning Network</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-to-integrate-the-btc-lightning-network/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-to-integrate-the-btc-lightning-network/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 15:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lightning Network]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77832</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase – the largest and most popular crypto exchange in the U.S. – has confirmed it’s going to be integrating the bitcoin Lightning Network onto its platform, thus ensuring bitcoin transactions scale and move along at quicker paces. Coinbase and Lightning: The Perfect Match? The Lightning Network has been all the rage in the bitcoin<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-to-integrate-the-btc-lightning-network/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-to-integrate-the-btc-lightning-network/">Coinbase to Integrate the BTC Lightning Network</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase – the largest and most popular crypto exchange in the U.S. – has confirmed it’s going to be integrating <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/04/09/coinbase-ceo-confirms-major-bitcoin-upgrade-as-ethereum-braces-for-24-billion-price-earthquake/?sh=2076f3423eba" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">the bitcoin Lightning Network</a> onto its platform, thus ensuring bitcoin transactions scale and move along at quicker paces.</p>
<h2>Coinbase and Lightning: The Perfect Match?</h2>
<p>The Lightning Network has been all the rage in the bitcoin community for some time. The idea is that it helps move various (smaller) bitcoin transactions off-chain, thus ensuring the network has less baggage to deal with. Removing some of these lesser transactions from the BTC mainframe allows bitcoin to move faster when being transferred between wallets. It also ensures transactions are less costly, which has been a problem with bitcoin in the past.</p>
<p>The news involving the Lightning Network was announced on Twitter by Brian Armstrong, the CEO of Coinbase. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Lightning is great and something we&#8217;ll integrate.</p></blockquote>
<p>The news comes at an interesting time given Coinbase is dealing with quite a bit right now. Not long ago, the trading platform announced it received a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">Wells notice from</a> the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), which has become a major bully on the crypto playground. The agency has made a living out of attacking crypto <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/" data-wpel-link="internal">firms such as Kraken</a>, which was recently forced to part with a $30 million penalty fee and end all its staking services.</p>
<p>A Wells notice doesn’t charge a company with any crime. However, it’s a warning to the company receiving the notice that it’s going to likely be charged in the future. This gives the firm time to prepare and get a good legal team to fight on its behalf.</p>
<p>It’s hard to know if Coinbase has truly done something wrong or if this is just another attempt on the SEC’s part to ensure crypto innovation dies in the U.S., which it appears to have been pursuing for some time. There are several crypto companies out there that have fallen victim to the agency’s drama over the past two years, and very few of them (if any at all) have admitted guilt. It seems the agency is simply looking to garner as much penalty money as it can from digital currency enterprises.</p>
<p>The news surrounding the Lightning Network has got several people excited, with Gabor Gurbacs – a crypto entrepreneur and advisor to Van Eck – saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>Looking forward to seeing Lightning support on Coinbase. Bitfinex has done a great job with Lightning earlier.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Ethereum&#8217;s Also Looking Good</h2>
<p>In the meantime, analysts at K33 Research are commenting on Ethereum, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>1.1 million Ethereum related to partial reward withdrawals could face the market, while Celsius [network] is likely to sell its 158,000 staked balance as part of its bankruptcy process. These two numbers represent nearly 1.3 million Ethereum or approximately $2.4 billion worth of potential sell-side pressure to face the market.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-to-integrate-the-btc-lightning-network/">Coinbase to Integrate the BTC Lightning Network</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-to-integrate-the-btc-lightning-network/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
