<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 02:56:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ripple Price Analysis: Upside Break Looms At $0.485</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-upside-break-looms-at-0-485/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-upside-break-looms-at-0-485/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 03:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78542</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple price is facing resistance near the $0.485 level against the US dollar. The price is now trading above $0.470 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.4640 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Kraken). The pair could<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-upside-break-looms-at-0-485/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-upside-break-looms-at-0-485/">Ripple Price Analysis: Upside Break Looms At $0.485</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ripple price is facing resistance near the $0.485 level against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $0.470 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.4640 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a major increase above the $0.4850 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ripple price is rising above $0.4750 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-another-increase-to-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. XRP price must stay above the $0.4700 support to remain in a bullish zone.</em></p>
<h2>Ripple Price Analysis</h2>
<p>After forming a base above the $0.4120 level, Ripple price started a fresh increase against the US Dollar. The XRP/USD pair broke the $0.432 resistance to move into a positive zone.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above the $0.450 resistance and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). The bulls even pushed the price above the $0.470 resistance. A high is formed near $0.4861 and the price is now consolidating gains.</p>
<p>It is now trading above $0.470 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-more-gains-possible-above-0-47/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near $0.4850. The next major resistance is near the $0.4880 level.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $0.4880 resistance zone might start a strong increase. In the stated case, the price could even surpass the $0.4920 resistance. Any more gains might send the price toward the $0.5120 resistance. Initial support on the downside is near the $0.4760 level or the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.4433 swing low to the $0.4861 high.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $0.4700 level. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.4640 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair.</p>
<p>The trend line is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.4433 swing low to the $0.4861 high. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.4500 level, below which the price might even test $0.4320.</p>
<div id="attachment_78543" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Ripple-4.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78543" class="size-full wp-image-78543" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Ripple-4.png" alt="Ripple Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78543" class="wp-caption-text">Ripple Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">chart</a>, Ripple price is now trading above the $0.47 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start a major increase above the $0.4850 resistance.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XRP/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for XRP/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.476, $0.470, and $0.450.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.4850 and $0.4880.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-upside-break-looms-at-0-485/">Ripple Price Analysis: Upside Break Looms At $0.485</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-upside-break-looms-at-0-485/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Bumps Slow After Bittrex News</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-bumps-stall-after-bittrex-news/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-bumps-stall-after-bittrex-news/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bittrex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77966</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The price of bitcoin has stalled thanks to recent news surrounding Bittrex, a popular digital currency exchange, and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Bitcoin Is Slowing Down a Bit Bitcoin has been on something of a roll since the beginning of the year. In 2022, the world’s number one cryptocurrency by market cap endured<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-bumps-stall-after-bittrex-news/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-bumps-stall-after-bittrex-news/">Bitcoin Price Bumps Slow After Bittrex News</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price of bitcoin has <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-stalls-near-30-000-after-the-token-s-biggest-drop-in-over-a-month/ar-AA19ZzZg" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stalled thanks to recent</a> news surrounding Bittrex, a popular digital currency exchange, and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Is Slowing Down a Bit</h2>
<p>Bitcoin has been on something of a roll since the beginning of the year. In 2022, the world’s number one cryptocurrency by market cap endured one of the harshest beatings it’s ever suffered and lost more than 70 percent of its value after attaining a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit in the prior November. By the end of 2022, the currency had fallen into the mid-$16K range.</p>
<p>In addition, several other digital assets decided to follow in BTC’s footsteps. This caused the entire space to come crashing to the ground and lose more than $2 trillion in valuation over the course of just ten to 12 months.</p>
<p>However, this year has offered something of a turnaround for bitcoin. The asset initially rose to $17K during the early months, and from there, it began expanding its price throughout the $20K range. Recently, it made headlines when it <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">struck the $30K</a> mark for the first time in about ten or 11 months (not since June of last year), causing many analysts to assume that the bulls were back in town and that bitcoin was going to reverse itself for good over the next few months.</p>
<p>While lasting damage arguably hasn’t been done yet, the currency has seen its growth spurt stunted a bit for the time being thanks to the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-continues-its-crypto-wrath-files-suit-against-bittrex/" data-wpel-link="internal">news surrounding Bittrex</a>, which is the latest digital currency victim of the SEC as our latest article suggests. The agency is claiming that the exchange has been breaking financial and securities rules for years, and that it took steps to avoid playing by the rules since it first came to fruition in the year 2014.</p>
<p>To be fair, it’s hard to know if these suggestions are real or not given how the SEC has just been working to crack down on every cryptocurrency company in existence as of late. Not long ago, for example, the agency went after Kraken and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/" data-wpel-link="internal">engaged in a settlement</a> with the exchange that saw the latter forced to give up more than $30 million in penalty fees. It was also required to cease all its staking services.</p>
<h2>Going After All the Companies</h2>
<p>The SEC didn’t stop there. It also recently <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">issued a Wells notice</a> to Coinbase, saying that while the company wasn’t being charged yet, it was being watched and it could expect to face charges in the coming future. The funny thing is that Coinbase claims to have met with representatives of the SEC regularly over the past nine years to ensure it always remained in compliance.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, bitcoin was trading in the low $30K range.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-bumps-stall-after-bittrex-news/">Bitcoin Price Bumps Slow After Bittrex News</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-bumps-stall-after-bittrex-news/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Continues Its Crypto Wrath; Files Suit Against Bittrex</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-continues-its-crypto-wrath-files-suit-against-bittrex/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-continues-its-crypto-wrath-files-suit-against-bittrex/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 15:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bittrex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kraken]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77963</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has laid its nasty hands into another digital currency company. This time, the victim of the agency’s wrath is Bittrex Inc., along with its former chief executive officer William Shihara. The SEC Is At It Again The agency says Bittrex broke its laws for years and that this<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-continues-its-crypto-wrath-files-suit-against-bittrex/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-continues-its-crypto-wrath-files-suit-against-bittrex/">SEC Continues Its Crypto Wrath; Files Suit Against Bittrex</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has laid its <a href="https://siliconangle.com/2023/04/17/sec-charges-cryptocurrency-exchange-bittrex-former-ceo-william-shihara/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">nasty hands into another</a> digital currency company. This time, the victim of the agency’s wrath is Bittrex Inc., along with its former chief executive officer William Shihara.</p>
<h2>The SEC Is At It Again</h2>
<p>The agency says Bittrex broke its laws for years and that this whole time, it operated as an unregistered securities exchange. This appears to be the narrative of the SEC each time it goes after a crypto firm. One wonders if these companies really and truly are engaged in such illicit behavior or if the agency is simply pulling this out of a hat as an excuse to go after whatever digital enterprise it wants.</p>
<p>The complaint was filed by the SEC in the U.S. District Court in Western Washington. The firm mentioned earlier this year that it was of the belief that many crypto companies throughout the country were selling digital currencies that, while popular, could easily be labeled securities. As a result, it said that many of these businesses were out of compliance and thus hadn’t taken part in appropriate registration protocols with the SEC, and now it looks like Bittrex has fallen into that category.</p>
<p>In a statement, SEC head Gary Gensler mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Today’s action, yet again, makes plain that the crypto markets suffer from a lack of regulatory compliance, not a lack of regulatory clarity. As alleged in our complaint, Bittrex and issuers that it worked with knew the rules that applied to them but went to great lengths to evade them by directing issuer-applicants to ‘scrub‘ offering materials of information indicating that certain crypto assets were securities.</p></blockquote>
<p>The SEC has really been going after the world’s leading crypto companies as of late. Not long ago, it engaged in a settlement with digital <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/" data-wpel-link="internal">exchange Kraken that forced</a> the firm to give up $30 million in penalties. It was also required to end all its staking services.</p>
<p>The SEC has also issued a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">Wells notice to Coinbase</a>, meaning that while the latter hasn’t been charged yet, it can likely expect to be charged with something in the coming future. A Wells notice is an indication that you are being watched.</p>
<h2>The Company&#8217;s History</h2>
<p>Bittrex initially launched in 2014 and became one of the world’s 50 largest digital currency exchanges soon after. Per the SEC, the company garnered more than $1 billion in revenue between 2017 and 2022. From its launch until the year 2019, Shihara served as the firm’s CEO.</p>
<p>Prior to today’s ruling, Bittrex had announced that it was looking into potentially shuttering its U.S. division, citing “continued regulatory uncertainty” as the reason why. In October of last year, the company was slapped with a $53 million fine by the U.S. Treasury Department due to its business engagements.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-continues-its-crypto-wrath-files-suit-against-bittrex/">SEC Continues Its Crypto Wrath; Files Suit Against Bittrex</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-continues-its-crypto-wrath-files-suit-against-bittrex/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Star Athlete Shaquille O&#8217;Neal Is Latest Defendant in FTX Suit</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/star-athlete-shaquille-oneal-served-in-ftx-lawsuit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/star-athlete-shaquille-oneal-served-in-ftx-lawsuit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 13:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lawsuit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shaquille O'Neal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77948</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Basketball superstar Shaquille O’Neal is the latest athlete to be served in a class-action lawsuit against the now defunct crypto exchange FTX, which fell apart in a heap of bankruptcy and fraud last November. Shaquille O&#8217;Neal Is the Latest FTX Defendant Adam M. Moskowitz – the attorney leading the lawsuit – made the announcement to<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/star-athlete-shaquille-oneal-served-in-ftx-lawsuit/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/star-athlete-shaquille-oneal-served-in-ftx-lawsuit/">Star Athlete Shaquille O&#8217;Neal Is Latest Defendant in FTX Suit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Basketball superstar Shaquille O’Neal is the latest athlete to be <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nba/shaquille-o-neal-served-in-ftx-lawsuit-lawyers-say/ar-AA19WzUr?OCID=ansmsnnews11" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">served in a class-action lawsuit</a> against the now defunct crypto exchange FTX, which fell apart in a heap of bankruptcy and fraud last November.</p>
<h2>Shaquille O&#8217;Neal Is the Latest FTX Defendant</h2>
<p>Adam M. Moskowitz – the attorney leading the lawsuit – made the announcement to his clients via the following statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>I wanted you to know the good news that we just served Shaquille O&#8217;Neal outside his house in Atlanta. The good news is his home video cameras recorded our service and we have made it very clear he is not to destroy and/or erase any of these security tapes because they must be preserved for our lawsuit.</p></blockquote>
<p>Moskowitz claims that he and his firm have been attempting to serve court documents to O’Neal for the past three months, but that the former Lakers and Miami Heat player has been dodging them repeatedly. Moskowitz also had a judge deny his request that the lawsuit papers be delivered electronically given the basketball legend’s (allegedly) repeated attempts to dodge those of the law firm.</p>
<p>O’Neal is now the final defendant to be served. He – along with several other professional athletes such as football <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tom-brady-named-in-new-ftx-based-lawsuit/" data-wpel-link="internal">quarterback Tom Brady</a> – is being accused of defrauding investors. Moskowitz continued his statement with:</p>
<blockquote><p>Mr. O&#8217;Neal will now be required to appear in federal court and explain to his millions of followers his &#8216;FTX: I Am All In&#8217; false advertising campaign.</p></blockquote>
<p>The NBA champion has denied he had anything to do with the fraudulent dealings of the company, claiming he only possessed a sponsorship deal with the exchange. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>A lot of people think I&#8217;m involved, but I was just a paid spokesperson for a commercial.</p></blockquote>
<p>In a recent email, Moskowitz told news sources that FTX played a false liquidity card and ultimately wound up defrauding more people than Bernie Madoff. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>FTX were geniuses at public relations and marketing and knew that such a massive Ponzi scheme — larger than the Madoff scheme — could only be successful with the help and promotion of the most famous, respected, and beloved celebrities and influencers in the world.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Terrible Occurrence for All</h2>
<p>FTX is likely to go down as one of the worst embarrassments in the history of crypto. What was once one of the world’s top five digital currency exchanges soon became a scam-ridden haven for illicit behavior that ultimately <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-the-damage-caused-by-ftx-was-worse-than-initially-thought/" data-wpel-link="internal">cost the crypto arena more</a> than $200 billion.</p>
<p>It is alleged that Sam Bankman-Fried – the man behind the digital currency trading platform – utilized customer funds to invest in luxury Bahamian real estate. It has also been reported that he used these same monies to pay off loans taken out by his other company Alameda Research, thus combining both business and customer assets (an illegal action).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/star-athlete-shaquille-oneal-served-in-ftx-lawsuit/">Star Athlete Shaquille O&#8217;Neal Is Latest Defendant in FTX Suit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/star-athlete-shaquille-oneal-served-in-ftx-lawsuit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CME Group to Allow Bitcoin Contracts to Expire Every Day of the Week</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cme-group-to-allow-bitcoin-contracts-to-expire-every-day-of-the-week/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cme-group-to-allow-bitcoin-contracts-to-expire-every-day-of-the-week/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin contracts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CME Group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum contracts]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77941</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>CME Group in Chicago, one of the world’s biggest derivatives marketplaces, says it’s going to be expanding its Ethereum and bitcoin-based options across both standard and micro-sized contracts. CME Group to Establish All-Day Bitcoin Contract Trading The news comes right as several other Ethereum and bitcoin-focused contracts are reaching their expirations now in late May.<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cme-group-to-allow-bitcoin-contracts-to-expire-every-day-of-the-week/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cme-group-to-allow-bitcoin-contracts-to-expire-every-day-of-the-week/">CME Group to Allow Bitcoin Contracts to Expire Every Day of the Week</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CME Group in Chicago, one of the world’s biggest derivatives marketplaces, <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cme-group-expand-bitcoin-ether-130000579.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">says it’s going to be</a> expanding its Ethereum and bitcoin-based options across both standard and micro-sized contracts.</p>
<h2>CME Group to Establish All-Day Bitcoin Contract Trading</h2>
<p>The news comes right as several other Ethereum and bitcoin-focused contracts are reaching their expirations now in late May. Through these new contracts, expiries are set to be available every day from Monday through Friday of each week. In a statement, Giovanni Vicioso – the CME Group global head of cryptocurrency products – said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We are pleased to offer these new options contracts to provide market participants with greater precision and versatility in managing short-term bitcoin and ether price risk. Against a backdrop of heightened market volatility in the digital asset sector, we continue to see clients turn to a trusted, regulated venue like CME Group for reliable and efficient cryptocurrency risk management products.</p></blockquote>
<p>Previously, the CME Group only offered contracts that expired on Mondays, Wednesdays, and Fridays. However, these additions will ensure that contracts ending on Tuesdays and Thursdays will also be available to traders, meaning all present contracts will complement each other in the general scope of how the platform works.</p>
<p>Paul Eisma – head of options trading at XBTO – also threw his two cents into the mix, commenting:</p>
<blockquote><p>CME Group continues to innovate and lead in the institutional crypto options on [the] futures market. By completing the short end of the implied volatility surface with the addition of the new Tuesday [and] Thursday micro-options contracts and weekly standard-size contracts, institutional market makers such as XBTO can deliver precise liquidity to market participants of all sizes who trade and hedge cryptocurrency exposures spanning every business day of the upcoming week for the first time.</p></blockquote>
<p>There’s plenty of good news for the CME Group arising as of late. Some of the biggest news circles around the fact that the company has achieved a record daily average national rate of more than $3 billion, suggesting that more and more individuals are seeing bitcoin and Ethereum as valid tools and additions to their portfolios.</p>
<p>In addition, Q1 of 2023 saw more than 11,000 contracts, while open interest averaged more than 24,000 contracts. March 22 also saw a record high in bitcoin contracts traded on the platform (a total of more than 2,300), while open interest reached a high of 14,700 contracts at the end of March.</p>
<h2>Boosting the Crypto Space Like Never Before</h2>
<p>The last major news to emerge regarding CME Group <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cme-group-is-releasing-new-around-the-clock-pricing-info-for-crypto-assets/" data-wpel-link="internal">came about well over</a> a year ago when it was announced the firm was going to be partnering with CF Benchmarks as a means of unveiling approximately 11 new crypto reference rates.</p>
<p>The rates were set to apply not to futures products, but to crypto networks like Litecoin, Cosmos, Polygon, Stellar Lumens, and Solana.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cme-group-to-allow-bitcoin-contracts-to-expire-every-day-of-the-week/">CME Group to Allow Bitcoin Contracts to Expire Every Day of the Week</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cme-group-to-allow-bitcoin-contracts-to-expire-every-day-of-the-week/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jon Blaylock Seeks to Strengthen Churches Through Blockchain</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jon-blaylock-seeks-to-strengthen-churches-through-blockchain/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jon-blaylock-seeks-to-strengthen-churches-through-blockchain/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 15:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[churches]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jon Blaylock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ophir]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philippines]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77938</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jon Blaylock has a rather interesting history behind him. In the past, he was a pastor at a church, though he’s since left the world of religion to focus on technical innovation, eventually beginning a company called 3lock that he’s now the CEO of. Jon Blaylock: A Former Religious Leader with a Vision His most<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jon-blaylock-seeks-to-strengthen-churches-through-blockchain/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jon-blaylock-seeks-to-strengthen-churches-through-blockchain/">Jon Blaylock Seeks to Strengthen Churches Through Blockchain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jon Blaylock has a rather <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-ph/news/others/ex-pastor-launches-cryptocurrency-to-raise-funds-for-philippine-churches/ar-AA19Xmnn" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">interesting history behind</a> him. In the past, he was a pastor at a church, though he’s since left the world of religion to focus on technical innovation, eventually beginning a company called 3lock that he’s now the CEO of.</p>
<h2>Jon Blaylock: A Former Religious Leader with a Vision</h2>
<p>His most recent venture involves establishing Ophir, a decentralized digital currency that will develop the first endowment smart contract on the blockchain (it&#8217;s named after a land mentioned in the Bible). The goal is to raise digital currency funds to help establish further churches throughout the Philippines – his native country – and help present institutions stay afloat.</p>
<p>The donation drive is known as “Project Ophir Crypto.” The goal is to attract crypto donations from all over the world to ensure churches in the country have what they need to keep their services going and their doors open to a God-seeking public. At the time of writing, several digital currencies are accepted through the program including USDT (a popular stable currency), USDC, ETH, SLP, and HEX.</p>
<p>Those who make donations are also set to receive Ophir tokens as rewards for their actions. While at the present time, these tokens possess no monetary value, this is likely to change in the future as Blaylock wants to make Ophir available for general trading on exchanges and similar platforms. In a recent statement, Blaylock mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Opportunities for positive transformation are limitless… By creating a platform that is easy to use and available to all, we hope to empower people to take control of their finances and unlock their true potential, and by accepting a variety of cryptocurrencies, including ETH, USDC, USDT, SLP HEX, and TXN, we can reach a wider audience and make it easier for you to support our project.</p></blockquote>
<p>Continuing his discussion, he commented that if churches can move past technical blockades and adopt blockchain, the impacts will be “remarkable,” and he believes the current state of the church will be transformed for the better.</p>
<h2>Blockchain and Churches Already Have a History</h2>
<p>To an extent, the arenas of both religion and blockchain have <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/several-churches-are-saying-yes-to-btc-donations/" data-wpel-link="internal">already crossed paths</a> multiple times. This largely stems from the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/coronavirus/" data-wpel-link="internal">COVID pandemic</a> of three years ago. During that time, when religious services and institutions were cut off to the public due to stay-at-home orders, many had no means of donating to collection baskets so that their favorite steeples could remain upright.</p>
<p>This, in turn, caused many religious institutions to turn to blockchain and digital currencies. They began posting crypto addresses on their websites to ensure people could send money as necessary. In addition, the maneuver helped a lot of people avoid contact and touching funds that had clearly been handled by multiple hands and people over the years, thus limiting the spread of the disease.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jon-blaylock-seeks-to-strengthen-churches-through-blockchain/">Jon Blaylock Seeks to Strengthen Churches Through Blockchain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jon-blaylock-seeks-to-strengthen-churches-through-blockchain/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vetle Lunde: The Price of BTC Could Soon Hit $45K</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vetle-lunde-the-price-of-btc-could-soon-hit-45k/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vetle-lunde-the-price-of-btc-could-soon-hit-45k/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 13:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vetle Lunde]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77936</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Vetle Lunde – a senior analyst at K33 Research – stated in a recent interview that bitcoin, the world’s number one digital currency by market cap, is following the same patterns it did in 2019, and that the asset could wind up hitting $45K per unit either by the end of this month or next<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vetle-lunde-the-price-of-btc-could-soon-hit-45k/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vetle-lunde-the-price-of-btc-could-soon-hit-45k/">Vetle Lunde: The Price of BTC Could Soon Hit $45K</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Vetle Lunde – a senior analyst at K33 Research – stated in a <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/topstocks/bitcoin-could-peak-at-45k-in-may-analyst-says/ar-AA19Xegv" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">recent interview that</a> bitcoin, the world’s number one digital currency by market cap, is following the same patterns it did in 2019, and that the asset could wind up hitting $45K per unit either by the end of this month or next month.</p>
<h2>The Same Things We Witnessed Roughly Four Years Ago Are Showing Up Again</h2>
<p>It makes sense when he says that bitcoin is following the footsteps it left four years ago. 2019 was an interesting year in many ways given that it followed 2018 (naturally), which up to that point, was one of the worst years on record – if not <em>the</em> worst – for bitcoin. However, nobody could have thought anything could “outclass” it in terms of negativity the way 2022 has.</p>
<p>Last year was easily bitcoin’s worst period, with the asset losing well over 70 percent of its value and dropping into the mid-$16K range during the final weeks (a massive dip from the all-time high of $68,000 per unit it hit in November the previous year). The asset’s crash led the space to lose more than $2 trillion in overall valuation, especially as many other leading digital assets – such as Ethereum – chose to follow BTC’s path.</p>
<p>However, since the beginning of the year, the leading digital currency has experienced a few solid bumps that ultimately saw it jump into <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">the $30K range as</a> recently as a few weeks ago. This marked the first time the coin hit such a mark in about ten or 11 months, and now, according to Lunde, the bull run is going to surge even further given that he thinks $45K is in the asset’s immediate future.</p>
<p>He stated in the discussion:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bottoms in both cycles lasted for approximately 370 days, and the peak-to-trough return after 510 days of both cycles reached 60 percent. In 2018, the bear market rally topped 556 days after the 2017 peak, on June 29, 2019, with a 34 percent drawdown from the peak. While history is far from likely to repeat in a similar fashion if the fractal were to continue, BTC would peak around May 20 at $45,000.</p></blockquote>
<p>During 2018, bitcoin lost more than 80 percent of its value. Prior to the start of that year, it hit its then all-time high of nearly $20K per unit, though by the end of the following year, it was trading in the low and mid-$3,000 ranges, and it took roughly five months for the asset to show any further signs of life.</p>
<h2>How Could a Rally, Which Means Prices Are Going Up, Ever Be &#8220;Hated?&#8221;</h2>
<p>Lunde further noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>The hated rally of 2019 ended with a significant blow-off top before BTC resumed trading at a 40-60 percent drawdown from its 2017 ATH. The early 2023 rally has all the hallmarks of a hated rally.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vetle-lunde-the-price-of-btc-could-soon-hit-45k/">Vetle Lunde: The Price of BTC Could Soon Hit $45K</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vetle-lunde-the-price-of-btc-could-soon-hit-45k/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Has, Thus Far, Recovered More Than $7 Billion in Assets</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-has-thus-far-recovered-more-than-7-billion-in-assets/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-has-thus-far-recovered-more-than-7-billion-in-assets/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 17:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[John Ray III]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77933</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At a recent hearing in Delaware, it was announced the now defunct crypto exchange FTX – which fell apart in November of last year – has recovered more than $7.3 billion in assets at the time of writing. This is an increase of more than $800 million since the month of January. FTX Is Trying<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-has-thus-far-recovered-more-than-7-billion-in-assets/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-has-thus-far-recovered-more-than-7-billion-in-assets/">FTX Has, Thus Far, Recovered More Than $7 Billion in Assets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>At a recent hearing in Delaware, it was <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-in/news/world/bankrupt-cryptocurrency-exchange-ftx-has-recovered-7-3-billion-in-cash-liquid-crypto-assets/ar-AA19MwSv" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced the now</a> defunct crypto exchange FTX – which fell apart in November of last year – has recovered more than $7.3 billion in assets at the time of writing. This is an increase of more than $800 million since the month of January.</p>
<h2>FTX Is Trying to Pick Itself Up</h2>
<p>The company is working to garner as many funds as it can to pay off some of its loans as part of its bankruptcy proceedings, which it first entered roughly six months ago. The company is fully down in the dumps and is considering reopening in the future at some point according to FTX attorney Andy Dietderich. In a recent interview, he stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>The situation has stabilized, and the dumpster fire is out.</p></blockquote>
<p>First coming to fruition in the year 2019, FTX required only three years to come out as one of the world’s top five digital currency trading platforms. The company was overseeing billions in trades, and Sam Bankman-Fried – the main executive behind it – was lauded as a genius by many (his net worth was also in the billions towards the end of 2022).</p>
<p>Sadly, this reputation was short-lived as in mid-November, SBF complained of a liquidity crunch on social media. He said he <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>needed fast cash</strong></a> to keep his business in operation, and he eventually turned to his biggest rival Binance about a possible buyout. While things <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>appeared to be moving</strong></a> in that direction for some time, Binance eventually backed <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>away from the deal</strong></a>, claiming the problems FTX was facing were simply too big for it to handle.</p>
<p>From there, the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>company filed bankruptcy</strong></a> and SBF resigned from his post. Things would have been bad enough if they had stopped there, but the trash meter kept rising. It was later discovered that SBF had utilized customer funds to invest in luxury Bahamian real estate and to pay off loans taken out by his other company Alameda Research. He <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftxs-disgraced-founder-has-been-arrested/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>was eventually arrested</strong></a> and extradited back to the United States. He has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-ftx-exec-sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-fraud/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>entered a not guilty plea</strong></a> and is awaiting trial at his <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-to-await-trial-at-his-parents-house/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>parents’ California home</strong></a>.</p>
<h2>Rising Prices Have Helped</h2>
<p>One of the big things that has helped FTX in the long run is how much crypto prices have come along in just the past few weeks. For example, BTC rose to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">a whopping $30K some</a> time ago, a big improvement from where it was at the end of last year (during that time, it was trading in the mid-$16K range).</p>
<p>Should the company decide to open its doors once again for business, the choice will be left up to the new CEO John Ray III, though Dietderich mentioned that it’s going to be a while before the enterprise can come back in such a way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-has-thus-far-recovered-more-than-7-billion-in-assets/">FTX Has, Thus Far, Recovered More Than $7 Billion in Assets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-has-thus-far-recovered-more-than-7-billion-in-assets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Howard Marks: Bitcoin Is an &#8220;Anti-Bank Play&#8221;</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/howard-marks-bitcoin-is-an-anti-bank-play/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/howard-marks-bitcoin-is-an-anti-bank-play/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 15:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Howard Marks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77931</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Howard Marks, a billionaire investor, is confident bitcoin has a lot to offer. Howard Marks Feels Bitcoin Has a Solid Future Over the past several weeks, Marks said bitcoin is becoming a huge power play for those losing faith in the American banking system, which has been in trouble as of late. At press time,<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/howard-marks-bitcoin-is-an-anti-bank-play/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/howard-marks-bitcoin-is-an-anti-bank-play/">Howard Marks: Bitcoin Is an &#8220;Anti-Bank Play&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Howard Marks, a billionaire investor, is confident <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/howard-marks-says-rock-bottom-rates-are-history-bitcoin-has-its-uses-and-ai-won-t-replace-the-best-investors-here-are-his-8-best-quotes-from-a-new-interview/ar-AA19TEfm" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">bitcoin has a lot</a> to offer.</p>
<h2>Howard Marks Feels Bitcoin Has a Solid Future</h2>
<p>Over the past several weeks, Marks said bitcoin is becoming a huge power play for those losing faith in the American banking system, which has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-provide-their-thoughts-on-latest-bitcoin-rally/" data-wpel-link="internal">been in trouble as</a> of late. At press time, about three banks in the U.S. have completely fallen apart, largely due to the ballooning debt the Fed has taken on.</p>
<p>In a recent interview, Marks commented on bitcoin:</p>
<blockquote><p>There are people who believe that when you have a bank crisis, like we did with Silicon Valley Bank and some of the others, that the weakness of the banks shows the strength of bitcoin. It&#8217;s in many ways an anti-bank play. It does seem that there are good uses for some coins, and bitcoin seems to be the one in the lead so far.</p></blockquote>
<p>He said that up to this point, interest rates have been relatively low, and they’re largely responsible for all the money U.S. investors have made over the past four and a half decades. He also said that while the present rate hikes aren’t likely to last much longer, he does think the days of super-low rates are dead and gone. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>The declining interest rates were responsible for the majority of all the money that&#8217;s been made in the last 45 years… The rates are high today to fight inflation. I don&#8217;t think they&#8217;re going to stay this high, but they&#8217;re through coming down in any major way, and they&#8217;re through being ultra-low.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also stated that the present situation presents opportunities for both investors and the Fed to show some humility, which has been missing from the financial landscape in the U.S. for years. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Humility is a really important thing, especially in the market, which humbles us all. Anybody who doesn&#8217;t allow for humility, in a field where there&#8217;s randomness and uncertainty, and qualitative and subjective things are important, is riding for a fall.</p></blockquote>
<p>In the long run, he doesn’t think the Fed has done a good job in ensuring the cogs of the monetary machine keep running smoothly. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>People used to talk about the factory of the future, which would have one man and one dog, and it was the dog&#8217;s job to keep the man from touching the equipment. It was the man&#8217;s job to feed the dog. I would like to have the Fed keep its hands off the machinery most of the time.</p></blockquote>
<h2>AI Will Present Problems</h2>
<p>In closing, he said advancements in AI could cause problems for a lot of workers in the future, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>AI, just like passive investing and machine learning, even maybe to a greater extent, will knock out everybody who doesn&#8217;t add value.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/howard-marks-bitcoin-is-an-anti-bank-play/">Howard Marks: Bitcoin Is an &#8220;Anti-Bank Play&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/howard-marks-bitcoin-is-an-anti-bank-play/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
