<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 04:15:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Crypto Executive Do Kwon Arrested in Montenegro</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-executive-do-kwon-arrested-in-montenegro/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-executive-do-kwon-arrested-in-montenegro/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 17:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Do Kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Montenegro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra USD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77627</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Do Kwon – the crypto executive behind the Terra USD collapse that occurred in the summer of 2022 – has been arrested and taken into custody. Do Kwon Has Reportedly Been Taken In Kwon has allegedly been a fugitive these past few months. He was apprehended in the European nation of Montenegro, where he was<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-executive-do-kwon-arrested-in-montenegro/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-executive-do-kwon-arrested-in-montenegro/">Crypto Executive Do Kwon Arrested in Montenegro</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do Kwon – the crypto executive behind the Terra USD collapse that occurred in the summer of 2022 – has <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/fugitive-cryptocurrency-king-behind-2022-s-40b-crash-arrested-fleeing-montenegro-with-fake-documents/ar-AA192Gzx" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">been arrested and taken</a> into custody.</p>
<h2>Do Kwon Has Reportedly Been Taken In</h2>
<p>Kwon has allegedly been a fugitive these past few months. He was apprehended in the European nation of Montenegro, where he was found to be holding phony passports and documentation. The country’s interior minister Filip Adzic issued the following statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>Montenegrin police have detained a person suspected of being one of the world&#8217;s most wanted fugitives, South Korean citizen Do Kwon, co-founder and CEO of Singapore-based Terraform Labs. The former &#8216;cryptocurrency king&#8217;, who is behind losses of more than 40 billion dollars, was detained at the Podgorica airport with falsified documents, and South Korea, the USA, and Singapore are demanding [his extradition].</p></blockquote>
<p>The collapse of Terra USD and its alternate Luna token cost crypto investors billions in hard-earned investment funds. In late 2022, the region of South Korea <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/prosecutors-hunt-for-terra-luna-crypto-exec-do-kwon/" data-wpel-link="internal">issued an arrest warrant</a> for Kwon, citing him as the main person of interest behind the collapse given his status as CEO of Terraform Labs, the company responsible for the creation of both assets.</p>
<p>Kwon eventually went into hiding while claiming on Twitter that he was willing to cooperate with the authorities and that he was not running from the law. In fact, he <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-exec-do-kwon-says-hes-willing-to-cooperate-following-arrest-warrant/" data-wpel-link="internal">went so far as to say</a> he was simply coding in his living room.</p>
<p>His presence in Montenegro appears to put these statements in doubt. By February 1 of this year, Kwon had gone silent on social media and he hasn’t tweeted anything since. According to Montenegro authorities, Kwon had allegedly been trying to travel to Dubai using a phony Costa Rican passport. He was also in possession of what has been deemed a fake Belgian passport.</p>
<p>South Korean law enforcement agencies have already confirmed that the fingerprints of the arrested man match those of Kwon’s, suggesting they now have their man.</p>
<p>Terra USD had been classified as a stable coin, so it was shocking to many people not only when the asset lost its peg, but when it went under fully. However, what many traders likely didn’t understand was that it was merely an “algorithmic” stable coin, meaning it wasn’t tied to any serious collateral (i.e., gold or precious metals) or fiat currencies. Rather, its value only stayed consistent when people chose to believe in it.</p>
<h2>Was This All a Scam?</h2>
<p>It has been suggested that the $40 billion collapse of the asset may have <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-case-against-crypto-exec-do-kwon-just-got-a-lot-hairier/" data-wpel-link="internal">been a rug pull</a> of sorts or a similar scam given that just weeks before the crash occurred, Kwon and various executives of the company moved millions of dollars in BTC out of the project.</p>
<p>Kwon’s lawyers have yet to comment on his arrest.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-executive-do-kwon-arrested-in-montenegro/">Crypto Executive Do Kwon Arrested in Montenegro</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-executive-do-kwon-arrested-in-montenegro/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Scared Traders in Late March When It Temporarily Stopped All Trading</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-scared-traders-in-late-march-when-it-temporarily-stopped-all-trading/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-scared-traders-in-late-march-when-it-temporarily-stopped-all-trading/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 15:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[spot trading]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77624</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance – the world’s largest and most popular digital currency exchange per daily market data – gave traders a bit of a scare in late March when it put a temporary halt in place on spot trading, citing system glitches as the reason for doing so. The move only lasted a few hours and trading<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-scared-traders-in-late-march-when-it-temporarily-stopped-all-trading/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-scared-traders-in-late-march-when-it-temporarily-stopped-all-trading/">Binance Scared Traders in Late March When It Temporarily Stopped All Trading</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance – the world’s largest and most popular digital currency exchange per daily market data – gave traders a bit of a scare in <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/binance-pauses-deposits-withdrawals-due-issue-affecting-spot-trading-2023-03-24/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">late March when it put</a> a temporary halt in place on spot trading, citing system glitches as the reason for doing so. The move only lasted a few hours and trading was quickly restored on the platform, but it had a few people shaking in their boots.</p>
<h2>Binance Briefly Stopped Trading Over a Month Ago</h2>
<p>The trading firm issued a statement claiming that there was a “bug on a trailing stop order.” CEO Changpeng Zhao commented in a tweet that temporarily stopping all deposits and withdrawals was standard procedure when such a thing occurred, and that traders could expect to resume activities soon. True to his word, the halt only lasted a few hours.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, there doesn’t appear to be anything further behind the stoppage. This was later confirmed by Ilya Volkov, the CEO of You Hodler. Ilya said that there was merely a technical glitch in play, and that crypto prices weren’t likely to be heavily affected following the pause, though bitcoin appeared to take the new badly and dropped into the high $27K range (about $500 less than where it had been just a day earlier). Volkov commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>These kinds of bugs could happen everywhere, and crypto exchanges are not unique.</p></blockquote>
<p>The main reason, however, why so many people took the stoppage personally or as bigger than it probably was is because this is not the first time Binance has taken such action. In fact, over the past few months, the large digital exchange has made a real name for itself when it comes to halting and stopping specific trades or currencies from being utilized.</p>
<p>For example, in mid-March, the company announced it would be halting all future sterling deposits and withdrawals, and that the currency would no longer be applicable to investment methods or trades through its platform. This followed USD transfers, which ended in February of this year.</p>
<p>Binance has also been subjected to ongoing investigations as of late for what are alleged to be money laundering practices. A top executive of the firm has told news outlets that the company plans to pay penalty fees in the coming future to relieve the charges and end any further investigations.</p>
<h2>The SEC Has Been Relentless</h2>
<p>It’s unclear if Binance really took part in wrongdoing at the time of writing, or if the investigations are just more efforts from agencies such as the SEC to bring down crypto in America and beyond.</p>
<p>The crypto regulatory crackdowns have become extreme in the past few weeks. Agencies such as the SEC have targeted firms <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/" data-wpel-link="internal">such as Kraken</a>, and it recently sent a Wells notice to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">crypto exchange Coinbase</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-scared-traders-in-late-march-when-it-temporarily-stopped-all-trading/">Binance Scared Traders in Late March When It Temporarily Stopped All Trading</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-scared-traders-in-late-march-when-it-temporarily-stopped-all-trading/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Opinion: Biden and the SEC Will Do Everything They Can to Kill Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-biden-and-the-sec-will-do-everything-they-can-to-kill-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-biden-and-the-sec-will-do-everything-they-can-to-kill-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 13:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77621</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Just a day ago, we talked about how Coinbase was served a Wells notice by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The situation is scary given that Coinbase has met with the SEC over 30 times in recent years, and thus the exchange really doesn’t appear to be in a position of any wrongdoing. The<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-biden-and-the-sec-will-do-everything-they-can-to-kill-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-biden-and-the-sec-will-do-everything-they-can-to-kill-crypto/">Opinion: Biden and the SEC Will Do Everything They Can to Kill Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Just a day ago, we talked about how Coinbase was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">served a Wells notice</a> by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The situation is scary given that Coinbase has met with the SEC over 30 times in recent years, and thus the exchange really doesn’t appear to be in a position of any wrongdoing. The situation just comes off as more evidence that Biden and his nation and innovation-hating cronies will do anything to ensure crypto dies in America and that residents cannot enjoy alternative means of finance.</p>
<h2>Biden and the SEC Are Working to Take Crypto Out for Good</h2>
<p>The SEC cannot engage in action without a distinct and clear path from Biden to do so. Everyone in politics today or in federal agencies say they want to regulate digital currency to ensure nothing like what happened with <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX</a> ever occurs again. However, there really aren’t any serious attempts to integrate said regulation or valid laws that would pertain to the space. Rather, all agencies like the SEC are doing are persecuting whatever crypto firms don’t fit with their present narratives.</p>
<p>It’s easy to assume that because this is a new industry, members of the SEC and other financial organizations in the U.S. don’t know what to do when it comes to crypto. That this is what they’ve done before, and thus they’re trying to apply old methodologies to what can only be labeled new sectors and technologies. After all, agencies like the SEC have been seen taking this sort of action before.</p>
<p>Two years ago, for example, SEC head Gary Gensler permitted a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/a-bitcoin-etf-has-made-it-to-the-u-s-but-is-it-what-traders-are-looking-for/" data-wpel-link="internal">company called Pro Shares</a> to unveil a new bitcoin ETF. This should have gotten everyone excited, but the problem was that the ETF was not based on spot trading. Instead, it was based on BTC futures, which many traders said were largely inferior to physical BTC units. The product also fell under a 1940s law that applied primarily to items like mutual funds.</p>
<p>How could such a law ever apply to crypto? The fact is that it cannot, yet the SEC hasn’t done anything to change the statute’s verbiage. When it comes to going after companies it doesn’t like, the SEC is very quick to move forward, yet it’s slower than a turtle when working to officially offer traders new opportunities for investment.</p>
<h2>Attacking Companies Left and Right</h2>
<p>Two months ago, it was announced that Biden was using an Obama-era policy <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-biden-using-an-obama-era-program-to-ban-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">to shut crypto companies</a> out of the financial world altogether. They could not gain access to bank accounts or other tools that would allow them to stay in business (similar to <a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-india-43669730" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">what was seen in India</a> five years prior).</p>
<p>Now, the SEC is going after every crypto firm it can from Coinbase to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/" data-wpel-link="internal">Kraken</a>, and it’s becoming clear the agency is simply a general in what can be called Biden’s anti-crypto army.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-biden-and-the-sec-will-do-everything-they-can-to-kill-crypto/">Opinion: Biden and the SEC Will Do Everything They Can to Kill Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-biden-and-the-sec-will-do-everything-they-can-to-kill-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CoinMarketCap Added Blofin to its Exchange Category</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinmarketcap-added-blofin-to-its-exchange-category/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinmarketcap-added-blofin-to-its-exchange-category/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 12:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78142</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>George Town, Cayman Island (May 1st, 2023) &#8211;  Blofin, the premier perpetual futures exchange, has been added to CoinMarketCap&#8216;s exchange category, the world&#8217;s largest crypto asset tracking website. This move aims at increasing the exchange&#8217;s visibility and adoption. It comes after a remarkable increase in community members and daily trading volume since its launch in<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinmarketcap-added-blofin-to-its-exchange-category/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinmarketcap-added-blofin-to-its-exchange-category/">CoinMarketCap Added Blofin to its Exchange Category</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>George Town, Cayman Island (May 1st, 2023)</strong> &#8211;  <a href="http://www.blofin.com" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Blofin</a>, the premier perpetual futures exchange, has been added to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/exchanges/blofin/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">CoinMarketCap</a>&#8216;s exchange category, the world&#8217;s largest crypto asset tracking website. This move aims at increasing the exchange&#8217;s visibility and adoption. It comes after a remarkable increase in community members and daily trading volume since its launch in January. The exchange&#8217;s 24-hour trading volume currently stands at over 300 million dollars.</p>
<p>Meeting the standards of CoinMarketCap(CMC), Blofin has implemented five different security measures to protect users&#8217; assets. These include partnering with Fireblocks to offer liability insurance coverage, drawing on decentralized Merkle Tree verification to prove users&#8217; funds in the platform&#8217;s reserve, using Wallet as a Service (WaaS) to keep users&#8217; assets in third-party custody, and adopting KYT solution from AnChain for monitoring security, risk, and compliance.</p>
<p>Before listing to the CMC, Blofin has also posted its financial data on <a href="https://portfolio.nansen.ai/dashboard/blofin" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Nansen</a> as part of its Proof of Reserves (PoR) report to ensure transparency and user confidence. As per Nansen&#8217;s data, Blofin&#8217;s net worth has surpassed 5 million US dollars, with USDT representing 30.03% and USDC representing 21.18% of the total. To encapsulate resilience and transparency, Blofin committed to providing monthly updates on the PoR data to offer customers full assurance regarding the company&#8217;s financial stability and the safety of the users&#8217; investments.</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/Blofin_CEO/status/1651923556689920003" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Matt</a>, CEO of Blofin, shared the news on Twitter, stating, &#8220;It&#8217;s our great pleasure to receive confirmation from the best tracking website in the world. Thanks to all the users who like Blofin and their trust in us, we have achieved what we have today. Blofin will continue to pursue our mission and vision, further improve the trading and user experience, and provide the most reliable product to a wider audience. This is just the beginning.&#8221;</p>
<h4>Functions of Blofin &#8211; A Premier Crypto Futures Exchange</h4>
<p>Blofin is a focused crypto futures exchange that prioritizes the smooth operation of its platform. It carefully manages the liquidity on the platform while handling the tedious task of filling out numerous price-feeding sites. By taking care of these details, Blofin ensures that its users can focus on their trading strategies without worrying about technical or administrative issues.</p>
<p>The exchange offers a comprehensive range of functionalities to help investors trade crypto futures with ease and confidence. Specifically, users can:</p>
<p>&#8211; Trade 59 perpetual contracts margined in Tether<br />
&#8211; Track and analyze real-time market prices and contract information with pragmatic features<br />
&#8211; Check the most trending crypto news within the network<br />
&#8211; Securely deposit and withdraw token assets in the wallet for an instant account<br />
&#8211; Copy the operations from the top-notch master traders in the world</p>
<p>To experience the innovative power of Blofin, please go to the Blofin <a href="http://blofin.com" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">website</a> or download the app from the <a href="https://apps.apple.com/tt/app/blofin/id1616804346" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Apple App Store</a> and <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.blofin.android" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Google Play Store</a> to trade easily on the go.</p>
<h4>About Blofin</h4>
<p><a href="https://www.blofin.com?utm_source=NewsBTC&amp;utm_medium=press+release&amp;utm_id=Ukrian+language" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Blofin</a> is a cryptocurrency futures trading exchange where users can get into cryptocurrency futures trading in an exciting and rewarding way. On Jan. 12th, 2023, Blofin launched its futures trading exchange platform packed with pragmatic security measures, including AI-powered algorithms, infrastructure, analysis, and more. Designed to offer all users an equal, transparent, and highly effective trading experience, Blofin is now inviting the best and brightest futures traders to join its pioneering program. Blofin team consists of serial entrepreneurs, executives from the traditional finance industry, professional traders, risk control professionals, and more.</p>
<p><strong>Media Contact</strong></p>
<p>Qi Ai<br />
Content Manager from Blofin<br />
Email: aiqi@blofin.io<br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Blofin_exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/Blofin_exchange</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><em><strong>Disclaimer: This is a paid release. The statements, views and opinions expressed in this column are solely those of the content provider and do not necessarily represent those of Bitcoinist. Bitcoinist does not guarantee the accuracy or timeliness of information available in such content. Do your research and invest at your own risk.</strong></em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinmarketcap-added-blofin-to-its-exchange-category/">CoinMarketCap Added Blofin to its Exchange Category</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinmarketcap-added-blofin-to-its-exchange-category/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Could Recover If It Clears $0.10</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-recover-if-it-clears-0-10/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-recover-if-it-clears-0-10/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 05:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar Lumens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78148</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stellar lumen price is struggling below the $0.100 resistance zone against the US Dollar. XLM price is now trading below $0.0980 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0980 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could start a recovery<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-recover-if-it-clears-0-10/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-recover-if-it-clears-0-10/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Could Recover If It Clears $0.10</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Stellar lumen price is struggling below the $0.100 resistance zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>XLM price is now trading below $0.0980 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0980 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a recovery wave if it clears the $0.100 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Stellar lumen price is trading below $0.100 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-29250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. XLM price could extend losses if it stays below $0.100 for a long time.</em></p>
<h2>Stellar Lumen Price Analysis (XLM to USD)</h2>
<p>After a major decline below $0.100, Stellar Lumen price attempted a recovery wave against the US Dollar. The XLM/USD pair climbed above $0.0950 but it failed to extend gains.</p>
<p>It resumed its decline and traded below the $0.0918 support. A low is formed near $0.0902 and the price is now attempting a fresh recovery wave. It was able to clear the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.1090 swing high to the $0.0902 low.</p>
<p>XLM is still trading below $0.0980 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-takes-hit-0-092-is-the-key/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0980 on the 4-hour chart.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $0.0965 level. The next major resistance is near the $0.0980 zone and the trend line. The first major resistance is near the $0.100 level or the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.1090 swing high to the $0.0902 low.</p>
<p>A clear upside break above the $0.100 zone might send the price toward $0.1080. Any more gains could lead the price toward the $0.1120 level or even $0.1200.</p>
<p>Initial support on the downside is near the $0.0918 level. The main support is near the $0.090 zone. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.0865 level in the near term, below which the price might even retest $0.0850.</p>
<div id="attachment_78149" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Stellar-Lumen-XLM.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78149" class="size-full wp-image-78149" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Stellar-Lumen-XLM.png" alt="Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78149" class="wp-caption-text">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XLMUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that XLM price is now trading below $0.0980 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start a major decline if there is a clear move below the $0.090 support.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XLM/USD is gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for XLM/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.0920 and $0.090.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.0965, $0.0980, and $0.100.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-recover-if-it-clears-0-10/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Could Recover If It Clears $0.10</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-recover-if-it-clears-0-10/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Price Analysis: XRP Could Dive Below $0.44</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-could-dive-below-0-44/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-could-dive-below-0-44/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 03:28:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78145</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple price started a fresh decline from the $0.490 zone against the US dollar. The price is now trading below $0.480 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key rising channel forming with support near $0.4550 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Bittrex). The pair could<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-could-dive-below-0-44/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-could-dive-below-0-44/">Ripple Price Analysis: XRP Could Dive Below $0.44</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ripple price started a fresh decline from the $0.490 zone against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $0.480 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key rising channel forming with support near $0.4550 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Bittrex).</li>
<li>The pair could extend losses if it stays below the $0.490 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ripple price is struggling below $0.490 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-29250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. XRP price could decline heavily if it breaks the $0.440 support in the near term.</em></p>
<h2>Ripple Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, Ripple price attempted an upside break above the $0.500 zone against the US Dollar. The XRP/USD pair failed to gain bullish momentum and formed a high near $0.4868.</p>
<p>The price started a fresh bearish wave and declined below the $0.4750 support. It even traded below the $0.470 level and spiked below the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). It is now testing the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.4322 swing low to the $0.4868 high.</p>
<p>XRP is now trading below $0.480 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-turns-red-below-0-50/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. Besides, there is a key rising channel forming with support near $0.4550 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near $0.470. The next major resistance is near the $0.485 level. A clear move above the $0.4850 and $0.4900 resistance zones might start a fresh increase. In the stated case, the price could even surpass the $0.5000 resistance. Any more gains might send the price toward the $0.520 resistance.</p>
<p>Initial support on the downside is near $0.460. The next major support is near the $0.455 level and the channel trend line. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.4322 swing low to the $0.4868 high. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.440 level, below which the price might even test $0.4000.</p>
<div id="attachment_78146" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Ripple.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78146" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78146" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Ripple.png" alt="Ripple Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78146" class="wp-caption-text">Ripple Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Ripple’s price is now trading below the $0.490 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could extend losses if it stays below the $0.490 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XRP/USD is now gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for XRP/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.4600, $0.4550, and $0.4400.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.4850 and $0.4900.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-could-dive-below-0-44/">Ripple Price Analysis: XRP Could Dive Below $0.44</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-could-dive-below-0-44/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jim Cramer Says BTC Will Shrivel Up and Die Soon</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jim-cramer-says-btc-will-shrivel-up-and-die-soon/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jim-cramer-says-btc-will-shrivel-up-and-die-soon/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 17:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jim Cramer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Silicon Valley Bank]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77618</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jim Cramer – the famed host of “Mad Money” on CNBC – has commented that bitcoin has no real use case, and he thinks the biggest digital currency by market cap will dry up faster than a riverbed. Jim Cramer Thinks BTC Won&#8217;t Last Long Is he right? His words come during a time when<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jim-cramer-says-btc-will-shrivel-up-and-die-soon/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jim-cramer-says-btc-will-shrivel-up-and-die-soon/">Jim Cramer Says BTC Will Shrivel Up and Die Soon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jim Cramer – the famed host of “Mad Money” on CNBC – <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/etf/jim-cramer-predicts-bitcoin-s-imminent-demise-%E2%80%94-will-his-record-for-getting-it-wrong-continue-1032189284" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">has commented</a> that bitcoin has no real use case, and he thinks the biggest digital currency by market cap will dry up faster than a riverbed.</p>
<h2>Jim Cramer Thinks BTC Won&#8217;t Last Long</h2>
<p>Is he right? His words come during a time when bitcoin appears to be picking up steam. The currency was depleted of all its resources and energy during 2022, which is arguably the most bearish year on record for bitcoin. During that time, the asset – which had risen to a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit in November of 2021 – fell to the mid-$16K range roughly 12 months later, meaning the currency lost well over 70 percent of its value.</p>
<p>As a leader of the crypto space, the asset caused many other cryptocurrencies to shrivel up and nearly die along with it. As a result, these assets lost much of their value as well, and the crypto space – which began 2022 at over $3 trillion in value – dropped by more than $2 trillion just one year later. It was a sad and (very) ugly sight to see.</p>
<p>At the same time, it’s not like things like this haven’t happened before. Bitcoin has always been prone to volatility; that’s been its biggest problem. Despite its vulnerability to price swings, however, the currency has always managed to stay in the game. The asset has swung back and forth like a pendulum, always to wind up in a winning circle a few years (or sometimes just a few months) later, and 2023 is no exception.</p>
<p>What we’re seeing right now is probably not something to get hugely excited about. After all, bitcoin is still about 60 percent less than where it was 16 months ago when it first achieved its $60K+ high. However, 2023 is proving to everyone that the currency knows what to do to heal itself.</p>
<p>The asset – which took a major beating, probably more major than anyone could have anticipated – is once again rising through the ranks and is, at press time, trading for just shy of $28,000. This means the currency has nearly doubled where it was at the end of December last year… All within four months.</p>
<h2>This Guy Promoted Silicon Valley Bank, After All</h2>
<p>Cramer has predicted the <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/03/31359732/jim-cramer-predicts-bitcoins-imminent-demise-will-his-record-for-getting-it-wrong-continue" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">death of bitcoin before</a>, but the asset – 15 years after it was initially discussed online – is still alive and trying to do its best for investors and traders around the world. Cramer is also questionable considering he was one of the main advocates for <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-spikes-following-silicon-valley-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">Silicon Valley Bank</a> stock, an institution that recently lost its life during America’s present banking crisis.</p>
<p>So clearly, Cramer isn’t always right, and his words – along with everyone else’s – need to be taken with a strong grain of salt.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jim-cramer-says-btc-will-shrivel-up-and-die-soon/">Jim Cramer Says BTC Will Shrivel Up and Die Soon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jim-cramer-says-btc-will-shrivel-up-and-die-soon/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Most Bitcoin Traders Don&#8217;t Seem Worried About the Banking Crisis</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/most-bitcoin-traders-dont-seem-worried-about-the-banking-crisis/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/most-bitcoin-traders-dont-seem-worried-about-the-banking-crisis/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 15:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[federal reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Janet Yellen]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77616</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin gained traction not too long ago even though the Federal Reserve announced it was hiking rates another 0.25 basis points. Bitcoin Remains Strong This is proof that many people have restored their faith in the world’s number one digital currency by market cap and are shirking both Federal Reserve and banking concerns to the<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/most-bitcoin-traders-dont-seem-worried-about-the-banking-crisis/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/most-bitcoin-traders-dont-seem-worried-about-the-banking-crisis/">Most Bitcoin Traders Don&#8217;t Seem Worried About the Banking Crisis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/first-mover-asia-bitcoin-regains-momentum-as-investors-shrug-off-banking-fed-concerns/ar-AA190seJ" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">gained traction not</a> too long ago even though the Federal Reserve <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-shows-great-resilience-in-face-of-interest-rate-hikes/" data-wpel-link="internal">announced it was hiking rates</a> another 0.25 basis points.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Remains Strong</h2>
<p>This is proof that many people have restored their faith in the world’s number one digital currency by market cap and are shirking both Federal Reserve and banking concerns to the side.</p>
<p>The American economy and the banking crisis the country is enduring at the time of writing would likely cause many standard traders and investors to start shivering in their boots, but with bitcoin suddenly regaining its “digital gold” status, there are many people out there willing to let crypto drive them towards the future.</p>
<p>There are problems rearing their ugly heads, however, a big one being that agencies such as the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) seem to be trying to destroy crypto and bring down all it stands for. Earlier today, we published an article <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">talking about how Coinbase</a> – the western world’s most popular and active digital currency trading platform – had been served a Wells notice saying it was on the verge of facing charges.</p>
<p>Benoit Bosc – global head of product at crypto trading firm GSR Markets – commented on the situation and said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The crypto ecosystem is under attack. You&#8217;re seeing all those regulation-by-enforcement attempts, but also the banking crisis that has spread to banks (that) serve the crypto community. As a result, you have this flight to quality to the majors. Bitcoin has benefited the most, and it&#8217;s rallied significantly ever since those events have started. This [has] been the case with the action of the Fed yesterday in their refusal to really consider any cuts, but even refusal to pause in the cycle of hikes.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also took issue with Janet Yellen, the current Treasury Secretary. He said that her unwillingness to expand FDIC insurance coverage to deposits and amounts greater than $250K is a huge mistake, especially when the banking world has become so unpredictable. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>The first reaction is one that&#8217;s correlated to all risk assets. It&#8217;s a little leg down, but then after that, you do become, you know, you have that store of value, digital gold feature of bitcoin, which is that you still have inflation. They&#8217;re fighting it, but it still exists. Bitcoin has a limited supply, and so that&#8217;s a better alternative. You also have issues with stable coins. So, bitcoin suddenly seems more stable and safer than those at the moment.</p></blockquote>
<h2>The Future&#8217;s Bright</h2>
<p>Still, he’s confident about where bitcoin and crypto will go. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>A couple of months ago, it was no one thought we would be there. Those events a couple of years ago would have decimated the market. It&#8217;s very interesting to see how strong the market is… I don&#8217;t see it as a risk on rally.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/most-bitcoin-traders-dont-seem-worried-about-the-banking-crisis/">Most Bitcoin Traders Don&#8217;t Seem Worried About the Banking Crisis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/most-bitcoin-traders-dont-seem-worried-about-the-banking-crisis/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Receives Wells Notice from the SEC</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 13:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kraken]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77609</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase just can’t seem to catch a break. Not long ago, the company was the subject of a lawsuit that’s now being examined by the U.S. Supreme Court, and the trading platform is also the receiver of a Wells notice sent by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), proving once again that the agency has<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/">Coinbase Receives Wells Notice from the SEC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase just can’t seem to catch a break. Not long ago, the company <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/suit-against-coinbase-is-headed-for-the-supreme-court/" data-wpel-link="internal">was the subject of</a> a lawsuit that’s now being examined by the U.S. Supreme Court, and the trading platform is also the receiver of a <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/stocks/is-coinbase-part-of-unhealthy-regulatory-climate-3-analysts-react-to-sec-notice-see-upside-downside-risks-increasing-substantially-1032188433" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Wells notice sent by</a> the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), proving once again that the agency has just become a complete bully to all digital currency firms.</p>
<h2>Will the SEC Go After Coinbase?</h2>
<p>To be clear, Coinbase has not been charged with anything at the time of writing, though a Wells notice usually implies that charges are coming at some point in the not-so-distant future. The SEC has made it clear how it feels about staking and securities in the past, and now, the agency is alleging that Coinbase may have broken securities laws.</p>
<p>Analysts at Key Banc have mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>No charges/enforcement action were presented against Coinbase connected to the Wells notice as of March 22, 2023, though such notices generally precede future charges/enforcement action per our understanding. We can’t assess the model impact with high confidence at this juncture given the apparent lack of detail from the SEC and obvious lack of explicit charges/enforcement action, though [we] do recognize the materiality of certain products/services mentioned in the company’s announcement as it relates to revenue/adjusted EBITDA contribution.</p></blockquote>
<p>They also commented that should regulatory action in the United States against the crypto space continue (and it likely will), Coinbase won’t be the only company that suffers. They stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Following the Wells notice from the SEC and the recent economic report of the President criticizing the digital asset industry, we are downgrading COIN from outperform to perform. We raised concerns about blockchain development in the U.S. after the demise of three banks… Under this unhealthy regulatory climate, we are increasingly worried about the fairness of the enforcement actions, and the ability for the ecosystem to grow with seemingly limited and shrinking support from the banking system in the U.S.</p></blockquote>
<p>Shares in Coinbase fell by more than 16 percent following news of the notice. The analysts finished with:</p>
<blockquote><p>Recent strength in bitcoin indicates that people have called for alternative financial systems, but it could also become the victim of its success. While we downgrade Coinbase shares, we believe both upside opportunities and downside risk have increased substantially, and we may find an attractive risk/reward entry point in the future.</p></blockquote>
<h2>There Have Been Other Victims</h2>
<p>It seems the SEC has been on a role to persecute any crypto firms that go against its narrative. One of the most recent victims of the SEC’s digital <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/" data-wpel-link="internal">wrath was trading</a> firm Kraken, which per a settlement, was forced to part with about $30 million in penalty fees.</p>
<p>In addition, the company was made to end all its staking activities and services.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/">Coinbase Receives Wells Notice from the SEC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
