<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 10:50:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Crypto.com Sends Lots of Money to the Wrong Place</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-com-sends-lots-of-money-to-the-wrong-place/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-com-sends-lots-of-money-to-the-wrong-place/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto.com]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kris Marszalek]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75522</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Popular digital currency exchange Crypto.com is in hot water after it allegedly sent a lot of digital money to the wrong account. Crypto.com Sent Money to the Wrong Area At the time of writing, Crypto.com is purported to have sent as much as $400 million in Ethereum funds to a wallet stationed on the platform<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-com-sends-lots-of-money-to-the-wrong-place/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-com-sends-lots-of-money-to-the-wrong-place/">Crypto.com Sends Lots of Money to the Wrong Place</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Popular digital currency exchange Crypto.com is in hot water <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/esports/crypto-com-accidentally-sent-400-million-to-a-competitor/ar-AA146oKn" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">after it allegedly sent</a> a lot of digital money to the wrong account.</p>
<h2>Crypto.com Sent Money to the Wrong Area</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Crypto.com is purported to have sent as much as $400 million in Ethereum funds to a wallet stationed on the platform of its competitor and rival Gate.io. CEO Kris Marszalek took to social media to express his remorse over the situation and explain things to potential investors. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>It was supposed to be a move to a new cold storage address but was sent to a whitelisted external exchange address. We worked with [the] Gate team and the funds were subsequently returned to our cold storage.</p></blockquote>
<p>The maneuver resulted in some negative attention for the exchange, and Cronos – the native token of Crypto.com – is presently down roughly 40 percent over the course of the last few weeks. In addition, the company’s daily trading volumes – which at one point exceeded $4 billion – are now down to about $284 at press time. It’s a sad and embarrassing scenario, and probably one that could have been easily avoided with a little double checking.</p>
<p>The event is also <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/some-fear-crypto-com-could-become-the-next-ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">hiking speculation around</a> Crypto.com, with many analysts wondering if it has what it takes to remain afloat in a world that seems to be on its last legs.</p>
<p>2022 has been a very bad year for crypto. Not only have prices taken harsh beatings, but several digital currency companies have up and vanished, the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">most recent being FTX</a>.</p>
<p>Long considered the poster company for crypto and financial autonomy, FTX experienced a huge liquidity crunch in mid-November and approached Binance for help through a possible merger. Within 24 hours, the larger company declined the offer, claiming that the problems the firm was facing were too big to handle. Since then, FTX has entered bankruptcy proceedings and its main executive, Sam Bankman-Fried, has resigned from his post.</p>
<p>Crypto.com has put out a statement claiming that it is not in a position similar with that of FTX. The company says it has enough reserves onboard to stay operational, and that investors don’t have anything to worry about. This sentiment was supported by Owen Rapaport, co-founder and CEO of Argus, who in a recent interview said:</p>
<blockquote><p>To its credit, Crypto.com continues to have the funds to meet these withdrawals, lending further credence to its CEO’s claims that their assets are backed 1:1.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Getting Its Money Back</h2>
<p>At one stage, Crypto.com was heavily tied into FTX’s finances, something that has garnered criticism in recent days. However, Crypto.com immediately responded to the flak it was taking by saying much of the funds stored on the FTX exchange have been recovered. In a YouTube video, Marszalek explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>We recovered $990 million from FTX.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-com-sends-lots-of-money-to-the-wrong-place/">Crypto.com Sends Lots of Money to the Wrong Place</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-com-sends-lots-of-money-to-the-wrong-place/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Iran Hacks U.S. Servers So It Can Mine Cryptocurrency</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/iran-hacks-u-s-servers-so-it-can-mine-cryptocurrency/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/iran-hacks-u-s-servers-so-it-can-mine-cryptocurrency/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 15:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Iran]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lazarus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[North Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75520</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hackers from the sanctioned nation of Iran have allegedly hacked several servers of the United States government as a means of installing software to mine digital currencies. These hackers also allegedly sought to steal various network passwords and compromise the nation’s systems. Iran May Have Compromised the U.S. It is believed that hacking attempts by<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/iran-hacks-u-s-servers-so-it-can-mine-cryptocurrency/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/iran-hacks-u-s-servers-so-it-can-mine-cryptocurrency/">Iran Hacks U.S. Servers So It Can Mine Cryptocurrency</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hackers from the sanctioned nation of Iran <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/iranian-hackers-compromise-us-government-network-in-cryptocurrency-generating-scheme-officials-say/ar-AA14bpr7" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">have allegedly hacked several</a> servers of the United States government as a means of installing software to mine digital currencies. These hackers also allegedly sought to steal various network passwords and compromise the nation’s systems.</p>
<h2>Iran May Have Compromised the U.S.</h2>
<p>It is believed that hacking attempts by Iran may have started back in February of this year. This means that U.S. networks have been in danger for ten months, and regulators only seem to be aware of the situation <em>now</em>. It is alleged that the hackers exploited vulnerabilities the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) began warning about several months ago. Either nobody listened or the information fell on deaf ears.</p>
<p>It is alleged that hackers from Iran are sponsored by members of the region’s government. This shouldn’t come as a surprise given that Iran and the U.S. have never been on the best terms. Situations like this have occurred with other U.S. enemies in the past, a perfect example being the Lazarus hacking group in North Korea.</p>
<p>Lazarus has been <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/hackers-in-north-korea-blamed-for-harmony-attack/" data-wpel-link="internal">caught stealing cryptocurrencies</a> on multiple occasions as a means of funding the nuclear arms program of its home nation of North Korea, another region that has not always been friendly with or to the United States. Both Iran and North Korea are presently dealing with various sanctions enforced by the U.S., which has prevented them from gaining access to standard or traditional financial outlets.</p>
<p>As a result, it appears both have turned to cryptocurrencies to get what they want. In the case of North Korea, Lazarus has been utilized to hack exchanges and digital accounts in multiple countries, one of which was the United States, to garner digital funds so the nation could continue to build and test nuclear arms. It is estimated that the amount of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/north-korea-has-upped-its-attempts-to-garner-crypto-since-2017/" data-wpel-link="internal">money stolen by Lazarus</a> at press time is in the billions.</p>
<p>It has also been suggested that various digital currency companies have either helped these nations avoid U.S. sanctions or engage in cryptocurrency transactions regardless of whether they were lawful. Recently, crypto exchange Binance faced criticism after it was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/did-binance-help-iran-avoid-financial-sanctions/" data-wpel-link="internal">alleged the company</a> helped the nation of Iran take part in roughly $8 billion worth of crypto transactions.</p>
<h2>Governments Use Hackers Against Their Enemies</h2>
<p>Binance later defended its actions, claiming it enforces a top vetting process for all parties engaging in trades and that it didn’t notice anything that would arouse suspicion.</p>
<p>Governments of these countries along with others like China will often hire hackers as contractors. This gives top-standing individuals in those chains of government plausible deniability, meaning they can say they knew nothing of what was going on, nor did they have any control. On several occasions, Iran has denied illegally accessing U.S. data systems.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/iran-hacks-u-s-servers-so-it-can-mine-cryptocurrency/">Iran Hacks U.S. Servers So It Can Mine Cryptocurrency</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/iran-hacks-u-s-servers-so-it-can-mine-cryptocurrency/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Crypto Firm Block Fi Next in Line to File Bankruptcy?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-crypto-firm-block-fi-next-in-line-to-file-bankruptcy/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-crypto-firm-block-fi-next-in-line-to-file-bankruptcy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 13:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bankruptcy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Block Fi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75516</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>2022 has been an atrocious year for cryptocurrency. Many digital asset companies have been forced into dark places and filed for bankruptcy, and it looks like leading blockchain firm Block Fi might be next. Things Aren&#8217;t Looking Good for Block Fi Throughout 2022, the crypto space has been hit harder than it ever has in<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-crypto-firm-block-fi-next-in-line-to-file-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-crypto-firm-block-fi-next-in-line-to-file-bankruptcy/">Is Crypto Firm Block Fi Next in Line to File Bankruptcy?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>2022 has been an atrocious year for cryptocurrency. Many digital asset companies have been forced into dark places and filed for bankruptcy, and it looks like <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/billybambrough/2022/11/16/new-crypto-warning-bankruptcy-fears-suddenly-spread-after-ftx-collapse-wipes-billions-from-the-price-of-bitcoin-ethereum-and-crypto/?sh=4936814e26bd" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">leading blockchain firm</a> Block Fi might be next.</p>
<h2>Things Aren&#8217;t Looking Good for Block Fi</h2>
<p>Throughout 2022, the crypto space has been hit harder than it ever has in its short, 14-year history. Bitcoin, for example, has dropped from its all-time high of about $68,000 per unit – which it achieved in November of last year – and has fallen into the mid-$16K range at the time of writing. The world’s number one digital asset has lost more than 70 percent of its value, and overall, the digital currency space has shed more than $2 trillion in valuation.</p>
<p>Many digital currency companies have also up and vanished because they can no longer deal with ongoing speculation and volatility. Several firms – including the Celsius Network, Voyager Digital, Three Arrows Capital, and recently top <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">exchange FTX</a> – <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-in-the-age-of-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">have all entered bankruptcy</a> proceedings. It’s a sad and ugly sight to see, and one that’s instilling fear in traders’ hearts.</p>
<p>Now, it has been insinuated that Block Fi could be the next to disappear, and investors are not happy. Not long ago, the company hinted in a statement that it was dealing with financial issues and that it was looking for ways to work around them. The company mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>There are a number of scenarios that may be available to us, and we are doing the work now to determine the best path forward.</p></blockquote>
<p>The notice came after it had suspended withdrawals, which <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/another-mega-bitcoin-crash-is-in-the-books/" data-wpel-link="internal">appears to be the token</a> mark of a company that’s about to go under. Dan Ashmore, a crypto analyst, says everyone is on pins and needles following the dreadful collapse of FTX, which was considered one of the strongest and most stable enterprises in the crypto space. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The FTX insolvency is devastating for the entire cryptocurrency industry. Bankruptcy proceedings are long, drawn out, and will likely only end with customers getting pennies on the dollar.</p></blockquote>
<p>In a recent blog post, Block Fi appeared to contradict the idea that it was somehow running out of money, writing:</p>
<blockquote><p>Block Fi has the necessary liquidity to explore all options, and we have engaged expert outside advisors that are helping us navigate Block Fi’s next steps.</p></blockquote>
<h2>People Will Panic</h2>
<p>According to Cory Kippstein, however, this isn’t going to be enough to stop people from panicking. The chief executive of the bitcoin-buying app Swan Bitcoin said in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>All of these centralized businesses with large piles of altcoins on their balance sheets are literally confidence games. They are inherently fragile, susceptible to a Lehman-like collapse at any time, and the only hope once under pressure is that another player will bail them out.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-crypto-firm-block-fi-next-in-line-to-file-bankruptcy/">Is Crypto Firm Block Fi Next in Line to File Bankruptcy?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-crypto-firm-block-fi-next-in-line-to-file-bankruptcy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brazilian Footballer David Luiz is Now the Brand Ambassador for BC.GAME</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brazilian-footballer-david-luiz-is-now-the-brand-ambassador-for-bc-game/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brazilian-footballer-david-luiz-is-now-the-brand-ambassador-for-bc-game/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 10:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76137</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BC.GAME has announced that David Luiz, a Brazilian professional football player of the Flamengo team, has become its official brand ambassador. As the crypto casino’s brand ambassador, Luiz will consistently collaborate with BC.GAME to help promote the casino platform and engage with its community through social media and live-streaming platforms. David Luiz as a Brand<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brazilian-footballer-david-luiz-is-now-the-brand-ambassador-for-bc-game/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brazilian-footballer-david-luiz-is-now-the-brand-ambassador-for-bc-game/">Brazilian Footballer David Luiz is Now the Brand Ambassador for BC.GAME</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://bc.game/i-8wa14xt6-n" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">BC.GAME</a> has announced that David Luiz, a Brazilian professional football player of the Flamengo team, has become its official brand ambassador. As the crypto casino’s brand ambassador, Luiz will consistently collaborate with BC.GAME to help promote the casino platform and engage with its community through social media and live-streaming platforms.</p>
<p><strong>David Luiz as a Brand Ambassador for BC.GAME</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/Cmb8VwPOO23/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">David Luiz</a>’s association with BC.GAME will not only help the crypto casino gain more exposure. As a BC.GAME ambassador and one of Brazil’s most prominent football players, he can connect the Brazilian football community with the crypto casino platform and grow the brand’s player base in Brazil.</p>
<p>David will primarily engage and connect with the crypto casino community through social media activities. He will also be connecting with many players and fans through Twitch, an interactive streaming platform made for gaming and entertainment.</p>
<p>David shared,<em> “I’m very very happy to be partnering with BC.GAME and very excited for the collaboration coming soon.” </em></p>
<p><strong>BC.GAME’s Opportunity For Growth</strong></p>
<p>Brazil has seen a rise in the number of players participating in online casinos, with many opting to play at crypto casinos for their excellent accessibility and offered security. BC.GAME has also recently included sports betting in its gaming portfolio, which also happens to be one of the most popular forms of gambling games in Brazil.</p>
<p>The partnership is an excellent opportunity for BC.GAME to penetrate the Brazilian market and reach more audiences as it expands. With BC.GAME’s entry into the Brazilian casino and sports betting scene, Brazilian football fans and sports betting enthusiasts will have more opportunities to participate in virtual sports and casino events. This includes welcoming grander sports betting opportunities for highly-anticipated sports events like the 2022 FIFA World Cup.</p>
<p>Coco, the emblem of BC.GAME, said, <em>“Brazil has dominated 2022 in regards to tech innovation and regulatory framework for cryptocurrencies and iGaming. BC.GAME has proudly contributed to this since the doors first opened. We are very pleased to be moving into 2023 with this announcement of our partnership with David Luiz. Our combined efforts will help to maintain this trend, with Brazil at the focal point for tech advancements and crypto mass adoption. The world is watching.”</em></p>
<p><strong>About David Luiz</strong></p>
<p>David Luiz Marinho, also known professionally as David Luiz, is a professional football player from Diadema, Brazil. He is part of the Flamengo Rowing Club, a Brazilian sports club headquartered in Rio de Janeiro. Although Luiz mainly plays as a center-back, he’s also known for taking on other roles, such as a defensive midfielder or full-back.</p>
<p>In the 2009 – 2010 season, David was named the LPFP Primeira Liga Player of the Year. He was hailed as the FIFA Club World Cup Silver Ball winner in 2012. He has also earned two FA cups (2011 – 2012 and 2017 – 2018) and holds one FIFA Confederations cup title.</p>
<p><strong>About BC.GAME</strong></p>
<p>BC.GAME is a licensed online crypto casino platform that offers a wide variety of casino games, live casinos, and sports betting events. Besides integrating cryptocurrency and blockchain technology in its platforms, the crypto casino is also one of the first casinos to support lightning networks, Binance Smart Chain, Arbitrum, and other Layer 2 solutions,  further revolutionizing the casino industry and the world of blockchain.</p>
<p>This year, BC.GAME has received the “Crypto Casino Of The Year” title from the 2022 Sigma Awards. It also formed partnerships with the <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/bcgame-is-now-argentine-football-associations-global-crypto-casino-sponsor-301620425.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Argentine Football Association (AFA)</a> and <a href="https://cloud9.gg/latest/cloud9-welcomes-a-new-crypto-casino-partner-bc-game/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Cloud9</a>.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brazilian-footballer-david-luiz-is-now-the-brand-ambassador-for-bc-game/">Brazilian Footballer David Luiz is Now the Brand Ambassador for BC.GAME</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brazilian-footballer-david-luiz-is-now-the-brand-ambassador-for-bc-game/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Recovery Could Fade Near $102</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-recovery-could-fade-near-102/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-recovery-could-fade-near-102/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 04:58:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76134</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline from the $112 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below the $105 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $103 on the 4-hours chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-recovery-could-fade-near-102/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-recovery-could-fade-near-102/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Recovery Could Fade Near $102</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline from the $112 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below the $105 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $103 on the 4-hours chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it breaks the $98 and $95 support levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin cash price is declining from the $112 zone against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-at-risk-of-another-crash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. BCH/USD could decline heavily if there is a move below $95.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin cash price struggled to gain pace for a move above the $111 and $112 resistance levels. BCH formed a high near $111.38 and started a fresh decline.</p>
<p>There was a clear move below the $110 and $105 support levels. The bears even pushed the price below the $100 support and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bears-in-action-can-they-clear-the-100-support/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. It traded as low as $97.52 before there was an upside correction.</p>
<p>The price climbed above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward wave from the $111.38 swing high to $97.52 low. However, the price is struggling to rise above the $102 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</p>
<p>There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $103 on the 4-hours chart of the BCH/USD pair. The trend line is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward wave from the $111.38 swing high to $97.52 low.</p>
<p>The main resistance sits near the $105 level.  Any more gains above $103 and $105 could set the pace for a move towards the $112 level. If there is a move above the $112 resistance, the price could rise towards the $120 zone.</p>
<p>An immediate support on the downside is near the $98 zone. The next major support is near the $95 level, below which the bears might aim $88. The next target for them may perhaps be near the $80 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_76135" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Bitcoin-Cash-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76135" class="size-full wp-image-76135" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Bitcoin-Cash-3.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76135" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Cash Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BCHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, bitcoin cash price is now trading below the $105 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it breaks the $98 and $95 support levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for BCH/USD is losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BCH/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $98 and $95.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $102 and $105.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-recovery-could-fade-near-102/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Recovery Could Fade Near $102</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-recovery-could-fade-near-102/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Anthony Scaramucci on the Fall of FTX</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/anthony-scaramucci-on-the-fall-of-ftx/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/anthony-scaramucci-on-the-fall-of-ftx/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 17:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthony Scaramucci]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75514</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Anthony Scaramucci – the founder of Sky Bridge Capital and the former communications director for President Donald Trump – has given his thoughts on the FTX debacle and the fall of what was labeled one of the biggest and most prominent crypto exchanges in the space. Anthony Scaramucci Gives His Thoughts on FTX FTX took<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/anthony-scaramucci-on-the-fall-of-ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/anthony-scaramucci-on-the-fall-of-ftx/">Anthony Scaramucci on the Fall of FTX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Anthony Scaramucci – the founder of Sky Bridge Capital and the former communications director for President Donald Trump – has <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/11/11/scaramucci-on-ftx-sam-bankman-fried-and-the-worst-week-in-cryptocurrency-history.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">given his thoughts on</a> the FTX debacle and the fall of what was labeled one of the biggest and most prominent crypto exchanges in the space.</p>
<h2>Anthony Scaramucci Gives His Thoughts on FTX</h2>
<p>FTX took a 30 percent stake in Sky Bridge last September. At the time of writing, the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">company has filed</a> bankruptcy and the executive behind it all, Sam Bankman-Fried, has resigned from his post. The company began experiencing trouble in mid-November after it attempted to be bought out by Binance following what online posts described as a “liquidity crunch.”</p>
<p>From there, it looked <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">like there was going</a> to be a merger between Binance and FTX, though this was later cancelled given Binance felt the problems FTX was dealing with would be too big to handle. This is what led the firm into further demise and eventual bankruptcy.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, Bankman-Fried is getting a lot of flak for his role in the enterprise’s fall. Some are claiming that he played around with investors’ money and took too many chances. Others are stating that his greed and malicious nature led to FTX’s collapse. Scaramucci is dismissing all these claims for now, and he’s reluctant to say that there was any fraud contributing to what occurred.</p>
<p>In an interview, he commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>I don’t want to call it fraud at this moment because that’s a legal term. I would implore Sam and his family to tell the truth to their investors. Get to the bottom of it.</p></blockquote>
<p>Scaramucci feels that more than likely what happened is Bankman-Fried made mistakes while coping with the bear market, which he thinks can be said for many companies including Voyager Digital and even the Celsius Network, two firms <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-in-the-age-of-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">that eventually went</a> on to file bankruptcy earlier in the year. He doesn’t necessarily think these companies are bad or did anything malicious.</p>
<p>Rather, he wonders if they simply “lost their cool” as a means of dealing with the bearish conditions 2022 has brought on, and that they weren’t thinking clearly during this time. He further stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>When Three Arrows went down, it could be possible that Sam had difficulty then, and then he made some decisions that turned out to be disastrous for him and both sides of this business.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Maybe Nothing Nasty Was Happening</h2>
<p>Scaramucci then went on to say that he had spent time personally looking into what might have happened, and his research leads him to conclude that there was no illegal activity involved. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Duped I guess is the right word, but I am very disappointed because I do like Sam. I don’t know what happened because I was not an insider at FTX.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/anthony-scaramucci-on-the-fall-of-ftx/">Anthony Scaramucci on the Fall of FTX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/anthony-scaramucci-on-the-fall-of-ftx/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tom Brady Named in New FTX-Based Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tom-brady-named-in-new-ftx-based-lawsuit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tom-brady-named-in-new-ftx-based-lawsuit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tom Brady]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75510</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new lawsuit centering around failed exchange FTX has named legendary sports stars like Tom Brady and David Ortiz as potential defendants. Many of these individuals have long been associated with FTX and promoted what is now considered a fraudulent and twisted exchange. Tom Brady and Others Are Being Sued The lawsuit was filed in<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tom-brady-named-in-new-ftx-based-lawsuit/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tom-brady-named-in-new-ftx-based-lawsuit/">Tom Brady Named in New FTX-Based Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new lawsuit centering around failed exchange FTX has named legendary sports stars like Tom Brady and David Ortiz as potential defendants. Many of <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/ortiz-brady-named-among-defendants-in-lawsuit-over-ftx-collapse/ar-AA14bFG8" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">these individuals have long</a> been associated with FTX and promoted what is now considered a fraudulent and twisted exchange.</p>
<h2>Tom Brady and Others Are Being Sued</h2>
<p>The lawsuit was filed in the U.S. District Court of Miami, Florida. Not long ago, FTX had purchased the naming rights of the home arena for the Miami Heat.</p>
<p>The lawsuit states:</p>
<blockquote><p>Part of the scheme employed by the FTX entities involved utilizing some of the biggest names in sports and entertainment, like these defendants, to raise funds and drive American consumers to invest in the (yield-bearing accounts), which were offered and sold largely from the FTX entities’ domestic base of operations here in Miami, Florida, pouring billions of dollars into the deceptive FTX platform to keep the whole scheme afloat.</p></blockquote>
<p>Figures like Brady and Ortiz have <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sports-stars-stephen-curry-and-tom-brady-join-the-ftx-exchange-family-as-ambassadors/" data-wpel-link="internal">operated as brand ambassadors</a> for FTX in the past. According to the suit, this makes them liable for any losses or damages incurred by traders. Brady’s now ex-wife Giselle Bundchen has also been named in the lawsuit due to her taking part in the firm’s promotion.</p>
<p>Brady has also appeared <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tom-brady-featured-in-new-ftx-crypto-commercial/" data-wpel-link="internal">in several commercials</a> for FTX, the most recent of which poked fun at the bitcoin mining process. Brady was seen with a flamethrower in hand and burning away at a huge block of ice. Once the ice melted, a large bitcoin was revealed.</p>
<p>The lawsuit continued with:</p>
<blockquote><p>The FTX entities and defendants made numerous misrepresentations and omissions to plaintiff and class members about the deceptive FTX platform in order to induce confidence and to drive consumers to invest in what was ultimately a Ponzi scheme, misleading customers and prospective customers with the false impression that any cryptocurrency assets held on the deceptive FTX platform were safe and were not being invested in unregistered securities.</p></blockquote>
<p>The FTX exchange will go down as one of the biggest embarrassments of the crypto world. Once considered a top exchange, the enterprise came to a sudden halt in mid-November when it was announced that Sam Bankman-Fried – the man behind the platform – was approaching Binance as a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">means of garnering additional</a> funds to keep the business in play. At the time, FTX was allegedly enduring a liquidity crunch.</p>
<h2>A Major Disappointment</h2>
<p>While Binance initially took <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">on the idea of the</a> merger, the notion was later rejected given that the exchange felt FTX’s problems were too big for it to handle. Since then, FTX <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">has filed bankruptcy</a> and Sam Bankman-Fried has resigned from his position as head executive of the company.</p>
<p>Another top name included in the lawsuit was Kevin O’Leary, a known crypto bull and star of the reality series “Shark Tank.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tom-brady-named-in-new-ftx-based-lawsuit/">Tom Brady Named in New FTX-Based Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tom-brady-named-in-new-ftx-based-lawsuit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>California Establishes New Site Discussing Digital Currency Dangers</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/california-establishes-new-site-discussing-digital-currency-dangers/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/california-establishes-new-site-discussing-digital-currency-dangers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 13:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[california]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rob Bonta]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75508</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The California Attorney General’s office is launching a new website warning people of the risks that come with digital currencies. California Is Warning Traders About Crypto&#8217;s Dangers California says there are simply too many crypto scams out there that people have fallen for. Regulators in the Golden State suggest that between the Ponzi schemes, the<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/california-establishes-new-site-discussing-digital-currency-dangers/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/california-establishes-new-site-discussing-digital-currency-dangers/">California Establishes New Site Discussing Digital Currency Dangers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The California Attorney General’s office is <a href="https://fox5sandiego.com/news/california-wire/california-launches-cryptocurrency-information-website/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">launching a new website</a> warning people of the risks that come with digital currencies.</p>
<h2>California Is Warning Traders About Crypto&#8217;s Dangers</h2>
<p>California says there are simply too many crypto scams out there that people have fallen for. Regulators in the Golden State suggest that between the Ponzi schemes, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/romance-scam/" data-wpel-link="internal">the romance scams</a>, and all the other digital dangers out there, crypto has given way to a world of criminality that cannot be controlled unless people have the right knowledge.</p>
<p>California attorney general Rob Bonta explained in a recent news release:</p>
<blockquote><p>From celebrities to your next-door neighbor, it seems like everyone these days is investing in cryptocurrency based on the promise of fast and easy money. Don’t fall for a fantasy. Cryptocurrency, like all investments, carries significant risks, and there’s no guarantee that you’ll see large – or any – returns.</p></blockquote>
<p>The website will feature information about what to avoid while also providing tips for those seeking to engage in legitimate crypto trades. Some of the data will discuss purchasing non-fungible tokens (NFTs), for example. It will also answer questions regarding the sale and transfer of digital assets.</p>
<p>Bonta was adamant that anyone looking to engage in crypto trading needs to do their due diligence and check out the legitimacy of every exchange or company they do business with. He says traders need to be aware of the problems stemming from the space and that they should ensure they’re always spending money wisely.</p>
<p>He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>You should only invest money you are willing to lose, and you should be on the lookout for red flags and potential scams.</p></blockquote>
<p>Among the tips the website gives are to avoid any promotions that involve celebrity faces or endorsements. Bonta and his team said that many of these promotions are not real, and that several of these celebrities have not given permission for their likenesses to be utilized. Thus, traders are likely entering phony trading schemes that could see their money vanish for good.</p>
<p>He also said that any coins bearing names similar with mainstream currencies should be avoided at all costs. A prime example is Ethereum Max, which of course, stems from the Ethereum digital currency, presently the second largest cryptocurrency in the world.</p>
<h2>What to Steer Clear Of</h2>
<p>Not long ago, reality star Kim Kardashian was hit with a $1 million+ <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kim-kardashian-settles-with-the-sec-over-ethereum-max-promotion/" data-wpel-link="internal">financial penalty by the SEC for unlawfully</a> promoting the asset.</p>
<p>Lastly, Bonta says that no legitimate cryptocurrency firm will bombard you with phone calls or other forms of contact. You should not respond to phone calls, nor should you give in if any of these firms require heavy payments. He also said that no company can guarantee large returns, and thus statements revolving around what you’ll get back should not be believed.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/california-establishes-new-site-discussing-digital-currency-dangers/">California Establishes New Site Discussing Digital Currency Dangers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/california-establishes-new-site-discussing-digital-currency-dangers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Win Crypto With the Biggest American Leagues at 1xBit</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/win-crypto-with-the-biggest-american-leagues-at-1xbit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/win-crypto-with-the-biggest-american-leagues-at-1xbit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 07:12:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76125</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Have you been looking for chances to win big from sports? 1xBit is launching a tournament designed for the biggest American leagues &#8211; NHL, NFL, and NBA. This tournament will offer plenty of chances to take your betting journey to the next level and optimize for more. With a 250 mBTC prize fund spread across<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/win-crypto-with-the-biggest-american-leagues-at-1xbit/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/win-crypto-with-the-biggest-american-leagues-at-1xbit/">Win Crypto With the Biggest American Leagues at 1xBit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Have you been looking for chances to win big from sports? 1xBit is launching a tournament designed for the biggest American leagues &#8211; NHL, NFL, and NBA. This tournament will offer plenty of chances to take your betting journey to the next level and optimize for more.</p>
<p>With a 250 mBTC prize fund spread across 15 places, this tournament has a wide winning chance. All you have to do is to follow the instructions, create a betting strategy, and choose your teams. You can bet on NHL, NFL, and NBA matches to win prizes for the longest streak.</p>
<p>You&#8217;ll want to study the leagues and games to win big in this tournament. The best bettors work with strategies to deliver huge wins. <a href="https://refpa4903566.top/L?tag=d_967525m_1732c_pr_big_leag&amp;site=967525&amp;ad=1732&amp;r=promotions/big-leagues-streak" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Big Leagues Streak</a> offers you an avenue to bring your best strategies to the fore and cash out on the American leagues.</p>
<p>The tournament will span between December 20, 2022 &#8211; January 10, 2023, offering you sufficient time to play your bets and develop your strategies. Your goal is to have the longest win streak in the NHL, NFL &amp; NBA. Therefore, prepare yourself by familiarizing yourself with the games and know how to place your bets.</p>
<p>Do you have what it takes to join the tournament? Take your chances with the Big Leagues Streak and show what you have.</p>
<h4><strong>Why 1xBit is the Right Place for You</strong></h4>
<p><a href="https://refpa4903566.top/L?tag=d_967525m_1732c_pr_big_leag&amp;site=967525&amp;ad=1732" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">1xBit</a> leads innovation and trends in the sportsbook industry because of its high regard for user experience. Thinking about a platform that prioritizes rewarding bettors? Think about 1xBit. The sportsbook optimizes features that make the betting experience rewarding and satisfactory. Let’s consider a few.</p>
<p>On 1xBit, you gain access to a list of sporting events. Even when the World Cup ends, you still have a long list of sports to bet on. While doing this, you can access live betting, allowing you to follow your favorite matches without losing out on any part.</p>
<p>You can experience a sportsbook with big titles and promotions at all times. The beautiful thing about these promotions and tournaments is that 1xBit offers huge rewards. Here’s Big Leagues Streak with a 250 mBTC prize fund. Some other tournaments can go as high as 3 BTC.</p>
<p>Additionally, the sportsbook supports more than 40 cryptocurrencies. This allows you to retain your asset in your favorite cryptos and still make your bets. What more? The platform is constantly adding new tokens to its list.</p>
<p>Register today and become eligible for a Welcome Bonus up to 7 BTC as a newcomer following your first four deposits. Registration is seamless, as you can get started anonymously. Once you sign up, you’ll enjoy fast payouts and seamless withdrawals with zero fees. What else are you waiting for?</p>
<h4><strong>Final Thoughts</strong></h4>
<p>If you want to win big, your chance awaits you at this new tournament. Be one of the winners at 1xBit’s <a href="https://refpa4903566.top/L?tag=d_967525m_1732c_pr_big_leag&amp;site=967525&amp;ad=1732&amp;r=promotions/big-leagues-streak" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Big Leagues Streak</a>!</p>
<p>Find 1xBit on Social Media:</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/1x_bit" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a> | <a href="https://www.instagram.com/1xbit/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a> | <a href="https://t.me/sportsbook_1xBit" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram </a>| <a href="https://t.me/Promo_1xBit" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram Contest Channel </a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/win-crypto-with-the-biggest-american-leagues-at-1xbit/">Win Crypto With the Biggest American Leagues at 1xBit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/win-crypto-with-the-biggest-american-leagues-at-1xbit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
