<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 17:37:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Keep Calm, Fly High with HyperWallet Token (HWT) on PancakeSwap</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/keep-calm-fly-high-with-hyperwallet-token-hwt-on-pancakeswap/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/keep-calm-fly-high-with-hyperwallet-token-hwt-on-pancakeswap/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 17:37:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76472</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Following an acute rise of 30% in liquidity mining, HyperWallet Token (HWT) has finally broken the resistance stronghold. It soared to a new height of $0.047, which is 470% of robust appreciation from its official listing on PancakeSwap in less than 2 months. Started from $0.01, it is truly defying the laws of gravity in<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/keep-calm-fly-high-with-hyperwallet-token-hwt-on-pancakeswap/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/keep-calm-fly-high-with-hyperwallet-token-hwt-on-pancakeswap/">Keep Calm, Fly High with HyperWallet Token (HWT) on PancakeSwap</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Following an acute rise of 30% in liquidity mining, HyperWallet Token (HWT) has finally broken the resistance stronghold. It soared to a new height of $0.047, which is 470% of robust appreciation from its official listing on PancakeSwap in less than 2 months. Started from $0.01, it is truly defying the laws of gravity in the awfully cold and brazen “crypto winter” now.</p>
<p><strong>Currently hovering above 0.040 at the time of writing, HWT remains bullish, with active trading volume continuing to surge more than USD$148.82k worth of transactions for the past 24 hours and still counting.</strong></p>
<p>According to sources at GeckoTerminal, HWT has a combined liquidity of more than $2.05 million afloat on top of a fully diluted valuation worth $9.08 million.</p>
<p><strong>So, what makes HWT so strong and so stable?</strong></p>
<p>Behind HWT is <strong>an established financial ecosystem designed to be a self-sustaining ecosystem within a DeFi aggregator platform for universal interoperability</strong>. The HyperWallet Token will be presented as a multi-facet utility system as The HyperNation rolls out a series of new products to reward all loyal hodlers of HWT. If you felt that 440% rise is staggering or surprising enough, well, we aren’t sitting in the back-seat yet. Please take note that this is merely just the initial push, as the much-awaited bull run is just about to return. A streamline of confidence and trust will be given back to all those who have faith in HWT. And soon, you’ll know why.</p>
<p><strong>HWT Welfare to Reward Subscribers</strong></p>
<p>First on the list to reward HWT hodlers will be a new welfare that allows those who have recruited at least one direct downline to subscribe at a lower price. Thereafter, to maximize gain, subscribers are allowed to participate in Hyper Yield Aggregator and receive more HWT rewards. In return, HWT hodlers get to leverage their assets simply by hodling HWT and participating in the welfare campaign that lasts from 13 to 18 January 2023.</p>
<p><strong>Take Your Advantage of HyperWallet Token Welfare</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Limited 500 welfare subscriptions only</li>
<li>Lower entry, higher gain</li>
<li>Participate in Hyper Yield Aggregator for more rewards</li>
<li>Take a grip on the impeccably uprising coin and HODL</li>
<li>The 440% appreciation is only the beginning</li>
<li>Get x4 Rewards with a Daily Release Rate of up to 0.7%</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Seize Your Opportunity and Lock in Your Gains</strong></p>
<p>HWT will be a testament to The HyperNation’s holistic financial ecosystem. Soon, this first virtual nation will thrive vivaciously in the Metaverse as the development is in full swing. GameFi, blockchain-enabled store, and loan system are among the ambitious plans in the pipeline. Hence, the prospects of HWT continue to stay bullish. And every Citizen who holds this belief will be rewarded.</p>
<p><strong>The Power of Belief in Cryptocurrency</strong></p>
<p>To believe something is a persevering process that cuts a raw ore into a sparkling gem. The beginning is always modest, just like how Bitcoin started. People doubted the idea of digital currencies when Bitcoin was initially minted based on the never-before-heard blockchain technology. Quite the contrary, the successes that evolved from this cryptocurrency scene cannot be attributed to the technology itself only. It was the synergy of all determining factors, with the most influential being the people who hold their beliefs from the initiators to the community, including the end users.</p>
<p>Unlike Bitcoin and many of the earliest cryptocurrencies, HyperWallet Token solves all pressing matters in our real-life society. It breaks all boundaries in a genuine Metaverse empowered by blockchain technologies. It all started small and has expanded enormously since the collective consensus proliferated by leaps and bounds.</p>
<p><strong>The Inequality of Wealth Share throughout the World</strong></p>
<p>Let us make a simple comparison with some public information. First, take a step back and look at the total money circulation worldwide. This amount easily exceeds $90.4 trillion USD as we conclude from M0 – the end consumers, to M3 – the institutional money market funds for the world population of 7.837 billion. That is how much money, in comparison, across the globe that sustains the current value of USD for the world’s topmost superpower consisting of 331.9 million of population.</p>
<p>[World Market = $90,400,000,000,000]</p>
<p>[World Population = 7,837,000,000]</p>
<p>[Average Share of Money = $11,535]</p>
<p>Put the ratio in simple words. A world citizen should hold a share of $11,535 in real life. However, the cruel reality refrains from this equal share of wealth. While $3.828 trillion USD should be the total market cap of the United States, the superpower actually amassed more than $23 trillion USD as of the year 2021. That is a whopping 6 times the equal value being accumulated.</p>
<p>[US Market = $23,000,000,000,000]</p>
<p>[US Population = 331,900,000]</p>
<p>[6 Times the Average Share of Money Per Capita]</p>
<p><strong>The Legitimated Currency of the First Virtual Nation</strong></p>
<p>Now, things can be very different in The HyperNation – the first virtual nation truly decentralized and fully liberated from conventional authority.</p>
<p>While the global crypto market worth stands at $322.48 billion USD, there are approximately 320 million crypto users worldwide, who account for 4.2% of the world population, according to TripleA’s estimation. Now, we know that each crypto user possesses around $1,007 USD worth of crypto.</p>
<p>[$320,480,000,000 / 320,000,000 world users = $1,007]</p>
<p>Likewise, The HyperNation will emerge as a superpower, and the market size of this first virtual nation in the Metaverse is aimed to take up a quarter of the total crypto market worldwide. Hence, each of the current 200k citizens of The HyperNation will stand a chance to have a fair share of up to $400,600 USD worth of HWT. Potentially, that is more than 6 times the projected revenue.</p>
<p>[$320,480,000,000 x 0.25 / 200,000 population = $400,600]</p>
<p><strong>Incubating a Wholistic Financial Ecosystem</strong></p>
<p>Still in the early stage, primed to bypass banks, brokers, and exchanges, HWT is on the right path applying a wide range of blockchain technologies that unleash growth potential.</p>
<p>Soon, the wallet function will bring on a revolutionary experience enabling you to regain authority over your financial capability. Users can make transactions within a few taps via the upcoming dApp. This is also where your digital assets are kept safe and ready for you to browse anytime, anywhere.</p>
<p>On top of that, the upcoming public chain allows you to develop your own blockchain products and enable sale and purchase, instantly. Imagine in the near future, you can develop your interactive 3D games in the Metaverse and sell interactive movie tickets to audiences for them to experience and admire your fascinating works on the blockchain. And best of all, the movie ticket serves as the NFT in your crypto wallet for its sentimental value.</p>
<p><strong>Financial Assistance within Thumbs’ Reach</strong></p>
<p>Also planned in the diligent development includes a financing facility that provides monetary support based on your blockchain credibility, in which The HyperNation will unleash your financial capability in no time, and you need not liquidize your HWT holdings. You can even go for a termed pawn to get higher monetary support.</p>
<p>This dApp wallet will eventually evolve to become the portable bank that follows you everywhere you go. And this wallet will make up the final last mile for you to obtain loans whenever you need them through a patented KYC process. Rest assured, it is fully secured and totally hassle-free.</p>
<p>Indeed, there is a sustainable future destined for HWT. The HyperNation has so much to share with you in the coming days, weeks, months and years! If there is a cryptocurrency token that you must not miss out on in the year 2023, this is it! Fly high in anti-gravity rocket ship mode and get ready for unstoppable growth of up to x1000.</p>
<p>Check the $HWT listing @ <a href="https://pancakeswap.finance/swap?outputCurrency=0xe9e7CEA3DedcA5984780Bafc599bD69ADd087D56&amp;inputCurrency=0x8266Fa3adb0E15c8A3e45C63f7CEa051b03a1620&amp;chainId=56" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">PANCAKE</a> now.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/keep-calm-fly-high-with-hyperwallet-token-hwt-on-pancakeswap/">Keep Calm, Fly High with HyperWallet Token (HWT) on PancakeSwap</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/keep-calm-fly-high-with-hyperwallet-token-hwt-on-pancakeswap/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Katie Stockton: BTC Could Fall to About $13,900</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/katie-stockton-btc-could-fall-to-about-13900/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/katie-stockton-btc-could-fall-to-about-13900/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 17:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Katie Stockton]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76110</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There is good news and bad news surrounding bitcoin. The good news is that its next major rally is believed to be about six months away according to analyst Katie Stockton. The bad news is that the world’s number one digital currency by market cap is likely to endure a few more hectic drops before<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/katie-stockton-btc-could-fall-to-about-13900/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/katie-stockton-btc-could-fall-to-about-13900/">Katie Stockton: BTC Could Fall to About $13,900</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There is good news and bad news surrounding bitcoin. The good news is that its next major rally is believed to be <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/bitcoins-next-major-rally-least-202051738.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">about six months away</a> according to analyst Katie Stockton. The bad news is that the world’s number one digital currency by market cap is likely to endure a few more hectic drops before this rally occurs. In fact, she is confident that at one point, bitcoin will fall below the $14K mark.</p>
<h2>Katie Stockton on the Fate of Bitcoin</h2>
<p>We are now in the early stages of 2023, and many traders are wondering if this year will present the healing and rallying that they expected but didn’t get in the final months of 2022. The latter year was arguably the worst on record for both bitcoin and crypto in general. BTC fell by more than 70 percent from its all-time high of about $68,000 per unit, which was achieved in November of 2021.</p>
<p>Exactly one year after that, the currency was trapped in the mid-$16,000 range, thus bringing everyone’s hopes that the world’s primary form of crypto was somehow a hedge designed to fight inflation. The Fed <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-fed-bitcoins-worst-enemy-right-now/" data-wpel-link="internal">invoked several rate hikes</a> as a means of fighting inflation, and bitcoin – each time without fail – sunk even further into oblivion whenever a new push occurred.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, bitcoin is in the high $16,000 range. It was believed that the currency would remain in the high $17,000 range during the final days of 2022, but this has been a struggle for the asset, and Stockton believes things could get worse before they get better. In a recent interview, she stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Short-term momentum has shifted negative, which supports a bearish near-term bias. We expect a retest of the November lows, near $15,600, in the coming weeks.</p></blockquote>
<p>From there, she believes the currency could fall even more. She predicts a price of $13,900 during the second half of 2023, which would mean that bitcoin would have to fall another 18 percent from where it is now. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>With long-term momentum still strongly negative, we ultimately expect bitcoin to make a lower low, increasing risk to long-term support near $13,900, which is defined by the 2019 peak.</p></blockquote>
<p>To reach her present numbers, Stockton says she’s focusing primarily on price trends rather than the fundamentals of bitcoin. She commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>For indications of a major low, we like to consult the De Mark Indicators, which are at least seven months away from logging a counter-trend signal on the monthly chart.</p></blockquote>
<h2>There&#8217;s Still a Fighting Chance</h2>
<p>Despite all the gloom and doom, Stockton assures that there’s always a chance bitcoin will defy her negative expectations.</p>
<p>If this happens, she’ll be keeping her eye on various resistance levels to see whether a rally has true strength behind it or if it’s a fluke.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/katie-stockton-btc-could-fall-to-about-13900/">Katie Stockton: BTC Could Fall to About $13,900</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/katie-stockton-btc-could-fall-to-about-13900/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sherrod Brown Suggests a Ban on BTC in the U.S.</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sherrod-brown-suggests-a-ban-on-btc-in-the-u-s/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sherrod-brown-suggests-a-ban-on-btc-in-the-u-s/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 15:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sherrod Brown]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76108</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Senator Sherrod Brown – an Ohio democrat – says he thinks agencies such as the Fed need to examine bitcoin following the collapse of the FTX exchange and possibly ban it to make sure that what happened with the trading platform never happens again. Senator Sherrod Brown Thinks We Should Do Away with BTC As<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sherrod-brown-suggests-a-ban-on-btc-in-the-u-s/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sherrod-brown-suggests-a-ban-on-btc-in-the-u-s/">Sherrod Brown Suggests a Ban on BTC in the U.S.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Senator Sherrod Brown – an Ohio democrat – says <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/senate-banking-chairman-says-maybe-163938610.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">he thinks agencies such</a> as the Fed need to examine bitcoin following the collapse of the FTX exchange and possibly ban it to make sure that what happened with the trading platform never happens again.</p>
<h2>Senator Sherrod Brown Thinks We Should Do Away with BTC</h2>
<p>As the chairman of the Senate Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs Committee, Brown said the Treasury and all other financial agencies in the U.S. need to work together to ensure bitcoin is kept in its place and possibly invoke legal action to ensure no more pain and suffering is caused. He said in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Maybe banning it, although banning it is very difficult because it will go offshore, and who knows how that will work.</p></blockquote>
<p>There are several problems with what Brown is saying, the first one being that banning bitcoin does not solve the problem that arose from FTX. What happened with the exchange happened not with an individual currency because of bitcoin. This was a case where someone in charge chose to behave in a criminal manner and thus take advantage of the security clearance they’d been given.</p>
<p>Sam Bankman-Fried has admitted to playing around with users’ funds and utilizing coins that weren’t his to purchase items such as luxury condominiums. Whether bitcoin was in the picture or not has nothing to do with what happened. A person chose to behave criminally and utilized the advantages he held as the owner of a crypto exchange – not a single currency – to cause pain to others.</p>
<p>Second, as a democrat, what Brown should probably be talking about more is what his party plans to do with <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-gave-a-lot-of-money-to-democrats-what-will-they-do-with-it/" data-wpel-link="internal">all the money they received</a> from Sam Bankman-Fried. As more time goes by and more information about what happened gets revealed to the public, it’s likely the funds they received for both their 2022 and 2022 election campaigns was dirty money taken from users without their permission or knowledge.</p>
<p>To this day, these democrats have received mountains of money from Sam Bankman-Fried, and they have spoken very little about whether they are looking to give it back. One must wonder if Brown is not really concerned about bitcoin but is instead trying to distract from the idea that his party is wallowing in filth.</p>
<h2>How Does One Do This?</h2>
<p>Brown further commented that the digital currency arena is largely unregulated and that this needs to change. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>So, we’ve got to do this right. I’ve spent much of the last eight years and a half in this job as chair of the Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs Committee educating my colleagues and trying to educate the public about crypto and the dangers that it presents to our security as a nation and the consumers that get hoodwinked by them.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sherrod-brown-suggests-a-ban-on-btc-in-the-u-s/">Sherrod Brown Suggests a Ban on BTC in the U.S.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sherrod-brown-suggests-a-ban-on-btc-in-the-u-s/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chess Master Garry Kasparov Is a Big BTC Fan</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/chess-master-garry-kasparov-is-a-big-btc-fan/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/chess-master-garry-kasparov-is-a-big-btc-fan/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 13:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[china]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Garry Kasparov]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76105</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Renowned chess master Garry Kasparov has always been a big supporter of and believer in bitcoin despite its price having fallen so much. Garry Kasparov Gives His Thoughts on BTC In a recent interview, Kasparov talked about how he believed that the fusion of charitable acts and current technology could potentially help bring about new<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/chess-master-garry-kasparov-is-a-big-btc-fan/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/chess-master-garry-kasparov-is-a-big-btc-fan/">Chess Master Garry Kasparov Is a Big BTC Fan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Renowned chess master Garry Kasparov has always been a big supporter of and believer in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a> despite its price having fallen so much.</p>
<h2>Garry Kasparov Gives His Thoughts on BTC</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, Kasparov talked about <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/rogerhuang/2022/12/21/garry-kasparov-on-bitcoin-cryptocurrency-human-rights-and-ukraine/?sh=56a5dcc86c86" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">how he believed that the</a> fusion of charitable acts and current technology could potentially help bring about new policies for delivering human rights to victimized parties and for helping the fight for freedom. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>You know, I don&#8217;t pretend to be an expert in tech, but I&#8217;m more you know, just on the philosophy side — why I believe it is necessary. Because technology is a tool. Technology is agnostic. It&#8217;s how we use it. So, I think we’ve reached the point where we [need] to embrace every technology that empowers individuals. Even if we have negative elements of technology, because oh, like bitcoin and all the cryptos they can be used for bad guys for money laundering. Money laundering has existed since when money was invented. I feel like it [”crypto”] is a part of the global fight for empowered individuals and we&#8217;re not only talking about the terrorist agenda of dictators and terrorists and all sorts of authoritarians.</p></blockquote>
<p>He stated that one of the reasons so many politicians and agencies like the Fed have nothing but angry, negative things to say about bitcoin is because they realize it’s taking away their power. Their goal is to consistently control our pockets and remain ahead of macroeconomics. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>They print more money, and you know, our savings are devalued. [Suddenly], there is something that is based in math, something that is based on technology that offers equal opportunity to you and to me and Warren Buffett.</p></blockquote>
<h2>What About Bank-Issued Digital Currencies?</h2>
<p>Kasparov was also asked about digital currencies issued by centralized banks, such as the digital yuan. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Digital currency, you know, must be decentralized. Otherwise, it&#8217;s not a digital currency the way we understand it. There will be attempts, not only from China to take it to put it under control, but that they go against the tide… Yes, China is powerful, the Chinese are powerful, but they are fighting the world… My daughter will be 16 in three months. So, you know, let&#8217;s say five years from now she&#8217;ll be 21. My son will be 12, and I mean to them, crypto will be even more natural than that. What is the dollar? I mean, it&#8217;s disappearing cash. So, you&#8217;re talking about online payments, payments made by credit cards. So, we are already moving in this direction. So, the idea of the dollar, this becomes more and more vague. So, they understand that payments are digital, and I think for them the transition from dollar into crypto will be very natural.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/chess-master-garry-kasparov-is-a-big-btc-fan/">Chess Master Garry Kasparov Is a Big BTC Fan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/chess-master-garry-kasparov-is-a-big-btc-fan/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LBank Exchange Will List Jencoin (JEN) on January 11, 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-jencoin-jen-on-january-11-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-jencoin-jen-on-january-11-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 08:33:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76469</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Jan 6, 2023 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list Jencoin (JEN) on January 11, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the JEN/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading at 12:00 UTC on January 11, 2023. Built on BSC, Jencoin (JEN) aims to create a<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-jencoin-jen-on-january-11-2023/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-jencoin-jen-on-january-11-2023/">LBank Exchange Will List Jencoin (JEN) on January 11, 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Jan 6, 2023 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list Jencoin (JEN) on January 11, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the JEN/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading at 12:00 UTC on January 11, 2023.</p>
<p>Built on BSC, <a href="https://bscscan.com/token/0xf513203f0ad2077e4baa8a3c02d2fb91709e052b" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Jencoin</a> (JEN) aims to create a decentralized platform where users can transfer money using its currency. Its native token JEN will be listed on LBank Exchange at 12:00 UTC on January 11, 2023, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision.</p>
<p><strong>Introducing </strong><strong>Jencoin</strong></p>
<p>Built on the BSC, Jencoin is here to create a crypto platform that focuses on decentralization, privacy and anonymity of the trader. Its working protocol BSC P2P has assisted the team in developing a network of widely used payment channels as options for users’ P2P transactions, allowing its users to transfer money around the world quickly and without fear of disruptions, reimbursements, or processing issues.</p>
<p>The transfer of control and decision-making from a centralized entity (individual, organization, or group thereof) to a distributed network is referred to as decentralization, which allows the transactions taken place to be untraceable. As a platform that allows PoS Mining, payment gateways for internet enterprises, and multiplatform wallets for local merchants, Jencoin is completely decentralized. Decentralized cryptocurrencies have proven to be an invaluable lifeline for those who were previously denied access to traditional financial systems.</p>
<p>The transactions at Jencoin are fully transparent and anonymous. They are under the control of the dealer, there is no limit to the amount of currency, and the dealer can keep the confidentiality of its transaction. In addition, with Jencoin’s encrypted VPN, users are offered optional anonymity, decentralization, and security. Jencoin allows a completely anonymous cryptocurrency exchange. Although the wallets, address and history of the transactions is available publicly but the owners are not documented and are kept anonymous. This adds to the safety and security of the platform, allowing users to buy and sell with full confidence and trust.</p>
<p>Furthermore, being aware of the high trading fee charged by other cryptocurrency networks, Jencoin created a cryptocurrency that can operate on low fee. It charges as low as $0.001, which will not hurt user’s wallet. Jencoin is concerned about its wallet owners and hope they benefit from each and every transaction, rather than paying more trading fee. It wants to provide everyone with an independently run financial system so that the world can create banking software that allows users to be their own independent bank. The mission of Jencoin is to provide simple yet strong banking for everyone to support their finances with easy access from anywhere in the world.</p>
<p><strong>About JEN Token</strong></p>
<p>Jencoin’s native token JEN is a type of cryptocurrency which is supported by an encrypted VPN. It uses the Zerocoin protocol that allows it to have lightning fast transactions with low fee, and secures the blockchain network using the proof-of-stake (PoS) script method while paying a 40% APR on coins held. JEN will be used for JEN Online Shopping Store, JEN VPN Technology, JEN Lottery, FASTBIT, and JEN Games.</p>
<p>Based on BEP-20, JEN has a total supply of 21 million (i.e., 21,000,000) tokens. It will be listed on LBank Exchange at 12:00 UTC on January 11, 2023, investors who are interested in the Jencoin investment can easily buy and sell JEN token on LBank Exchange by then. The listing of JEN token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p>
<p><strong>Learn More about</strong><strong> JEN Token:</strong></p>
<p>Official Website: <a href="http://www.jencoin.net" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.jencoin.net</a><br />
Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/jencoin0" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://t.me/jencoin0</a><br />
Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/Thejencoin" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/Thejencoin</a><br />
Facebook: <a href="https://www.facebook.com/JENCOIN100" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://www.facebook.com/JENCOIN100</a></p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media: </strong></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Facebook</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong></p>
<p>LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
LBank Exchange<br />
<a href="mailto:marketing@lbank.info">marketing@lbank.info</a><br />
<a href="mailto:business@lbank.info">business@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-jencoin-jen-on-january-11-2023/">LBank Exchange Will List Jencoin (JEN) on January 11, 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-jencoin-jen-on-january-11-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EOS Price Analysis: More Gains Possible Above $1</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-more-gains-possible-above-1/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-more-gains-possible-above-1/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 05:58:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EOS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76466</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>EOS price started a fresh increase above the $0.92 resistance against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above $0.92 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There was a break above a key rising channel with resistance near $0.955 on the 4-hours chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-more-gains-possible-above-1/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-more-gains-possible-above-1/">EOS Price Analysis: More Gains Possible Above $1</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>EOS price started a fresh increase above the $0.92 resistance against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $0.92 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a key rising channel with resistance near $0.955 on the 4-hours chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move up if it clears the $0.99 and $1.00 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>EOS price is rising above $0.92 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-climbs-and-aims-steady-increase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. The price could resume its increase if it clears the $0.99 and $1.00 resistance levels.</em></p>
<h2>EOS Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This week, EOS price started a fresh increase from the $0.88 zone against the US Dollar. The price gained pace and was able to clear the $0.92 resistance zone.</p>
<p>The price broke the $0.95 resistance zone and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-0-83/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. The bulls even pushed the price above the $0.98 level. However, the bears appeared near the $1.00 zone. Besides, there was a break above a key rising channel with resistance near $0.955 on the 4-hours chart of the EOS/USD pair.</p>
<p>A high is formed near $0.9951 and the price is now consolidating gains. On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $0.995 level. The first major resistance is near the $1.00 level, above which the price could rise steadily.</p>
<p>In the stated case, it could rise towards the $1.10 level. Any more gains might send the price towards the $1.12 level. On the downside, an immediate support is near the $0.958. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.9225 swing low to $0.9951 high.</p>
<p>The next key support is near the $0.950. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.9225 swing low to $0.9951 high. If there is a downside break below the $0.95 support, the price could revisit the $0.92 support.</p>
<div id="attachment_76467" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/EOS.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76467" class="size-full wp-image-76467" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/EOS.png" alt="EOS Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76467" class="wp-caption-text">EOS Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/EOSUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, EOS price is now trading above the $0.92 level and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could continue to move up if it clears the $0.99 and $1.00 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4-hours MACD – The MACD for EOS/USD is gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4-hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $0.958 and $0.950.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $1.00 and $1.10.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-more-gains-possible-above-1/">EOS Price Analysis: More Gains Possible Above $1</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-more-gains-possible-above-1/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Can The Bulls Finally Aim $100</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-can-the-bulls-finally-aim-100/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-can-the-bulls-finally-aim-100/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 03:38:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76463</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin started a strong increase above $70 against the US Dollar. LTC price is now trading above $80 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $82.00 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair remains supported for more<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-can-the-bulls-finally-aim-100/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-can-the-bulls-finally-aim-100/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Can The Bulls Finally Aim $100</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Litecoin started a strong increase above $70 against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>LTC price is now trading above $80 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $82.00 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair remains supported for more gains unless there is a clear move below $78.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Litecoin price is rising steadily above $75 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-climbs-and-aims-steady-increase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. LTC price could continue to move up if it remains well supported above the $78 level.</em></p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few sessions, there was a decent increase in bitcoin, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-upside-break-could-trigger-more-gains/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">ethereum</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-aim-higher-above-0-37/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">ripple</a>, and litecoin against the US Dollar. Earlier, LTC formed a base above the $72 level and started a fresh increase.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above the $75 and $78 resistance levels. The price even climbed above the $80 level and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). However, the bears were active near the $88 zone. A high was formed near $87.88 and the price started a downside correction.</p>
<p>There was a move below the $86 level. The price tested the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $72.45 swing low to $87.88 high.</p>
<p>The price is now trading above $80 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $82.00 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair. The first major support is near the $83 level and the trend line.</p>
<p>If there is a downside break below the $82 support, the price could accelerate lower towards the $80 level in the near term. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $72.45 swing low to $87.88 high.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $85 and $87 levels. A clear move above the $87 level could pump the price towards the $92 level. The next major resistance sits near the $100 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_76464" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Litecoin.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76464" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-76464" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Litecoin.png" alt="Litecoin (LTC) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76464" class="wp-caption-text">Litecoin (LTC) Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, litecoin price is clearly trading above $80 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price remains supported for more gains unless there is a clear move below $78.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LTC/USD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $82 and $80</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $87 and $92.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-can-the-bulls-finally-aim-100/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Can The Bulls Finally Aim $100</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-can-the-bulls-finally-aim-100/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlackRock: Assets That Fell with BTC Won&#8217;t Recover This Year</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blackrock-assets-that-fell-with-btc-wont-recover-this-year/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blackrock-assets-that-fell-with-btc-wont-recover-this-year/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 17:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76078</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin, Ethereum, and other digital currencies hit rock bottom in 2022. Many of them crashed and experienced dips of 70 percent or more. Now, BlackRock – a famed investing firm – has stated that many assets and businesses that have moved in tandem with bitcoin and crypto are not likely to heal in the coming<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blackrock-assets-that-fell-with-btc-wont-recover-this-year/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blackrock-assets-that-fell-with-btc-wont-recover-this-year/">BlackRock: Assets That Fell with BTC Won&#8217;t Recover This Year</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin, Ethereum, and other digital currencies hit rock bottom in 2022. Many of them crashed and experienced dips of 70 percent or more. Now, BlackRock – a famed investing firm – has stated that many assets and businesses that have moved in tandem with bitcoin and crypto are not <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/billybambrough/2022/12/18/8-trillion-fund-issues-stark-2023-fed-warning-after-huge-bitcoin-ethereum-and-crypto-price-crash/?sh=598964234588" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">likely to heal in the coming</a> months, and that the Federal Reserve will not come to the rescue like they have with rate hikes.</p>
<h2>BlackRock Predicts Gloom and Doom for 2023</h2>
<p>With talk of recession lingering in the clouds, many are wondering if America’s economy is about to experience a whole new world of hurt that no analyst could have predicted. Strategists at BlackRock – which currently manages more than $8 trillion in overall assets – explained in a recent report:</p>
<blockquote><p>Recession is foretold as central banks race to try to tame inflation. It&#8217;s the opposite of past recessions. Central bankers won&#8217;t ride to the rescue when growth slows in this new regime, contrary to what investors have come to expect. Equity valuations don&#8217;t yet reflect the damage ahead.</p></blockquote>
<p>In 2022, inflation reached an all-time high. The prices of consumer goods, food, and even gasoline struck new points on the price meter, and many struggled to make ends meet. There has long been hope that 2023 would offer the healing many standard citizens were hoping for, though BlackRock questions if this will happen. The document states:</p>
<blockquote><p>We don&#8217;t think equities are fully priced for recession. Corporate earnings expectations have yet to fully reflect even a modest recession. This keeps us tactically underweight developed market equities.</p></blockquote>
<p>BlackRock also took note of the lack of progress the country has seen given the high number of hikes on rates the Fed has initiated. <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-fed-bitcoins-worst-enemy-right-now/" data-wpel-link="internal">There have been numerous</a> .75 and .50 jumps recorded throughout 2022, but they ultimately did no good. Inflation remained high, and crypto prices became lower and lower in the process.</p>
<p>The report by BlackRock mentioned that these rate hikes do not work the way they used to, and agencies such as the Fed will need to find new ways of fighting economic disaster if people are to stay steady and afloat in the months to come. The strategists said:</p>
<blockquote><p>What worked in the past won&#8217;t work now. The old playbook of simply &#8216;buying the dip&#8217; doesn&#8217;t apply in this regime of sharper trade-offs and greater macro volatility. We don&#8217;t see a return to conditions that will sustain a joint bull market in stocks and bonds of the kind we experienced in the prior decade.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Where Does Bitcoin Stand in All This?</h2>
<p>Some analysts – such as Alex Kuptsikevich of FX Pro – have also stated that the bitcoin price has stalled somewhat. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>From a tech analysis perspective, bitcoin has failed to latch on to levels above the 50-day moving average, causing it to now face speculative pressure.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blackrock-assets-that-fell-with-btc-wont-recover-this-year/">BlackRock: Assets That Fell with BTC Won&#8217;t Recover This Year</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blackrock-assets-that-fell-with-btc-wont-recover-this-year/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Xmile (XML) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/xmile-xml-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/xmile-xml-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 17:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76448</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Jan. 11, 2023 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed Xmile (XML) on January 11, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the XML/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading. Creating innovation that goes beyond the limits of current mileage industry, Xmile (XML) utilizes blockchain technology<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/xmile-xml-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/xmile-xml-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">Xmile (XML) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Jan. 11, 2023 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed Xmile (XML) on January 11, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the XML/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading.</p>
<p>Creating innovation that goes beyond the limits of current mileage industry, <a href="https://etherscan.io/token/0xadfafbf05d3d74af537bdec348ce4e536d99fb95" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Xmile</a> (XML) utilizes blockchain technology to promote an easier and more accessible mileage system with seamless asset management. Its native token XML has been listed on LBank Exchange at 6:00 UTC on January 11, 2023, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision.</p>
<p><strong>Introducing </strong><strong>Xmile</strong></p>
<p>Mileage is a type of reward for customers in airlines, transportation, e-commerce, and other industries. The mileage system is quite common across the world and even in carbon credit and other public sectors. There are many forms of rewards such as cashback, discounts, or a variety of free goods depending on the mileage tier.</p>
<p>However, problems such as restrictions and limitations of using mileage points and the expiration policy of the mileage system, difficulties in asset management and marketing still exist. To address all these issues with mileage, Xmile will promote an easier and more accessible mileage system with seamless asset management.</p>
<p>Xmile is a fully integrated platform for mileage systems that are designed to mutually benefit corporations and customers in the transportation and aviation industry and aims to establish a mileage ecosystem for broader usage. Customers can exchange or integrate mileage and points of Xmile’s partners through the Xmile platform and can use discount benefits and pay at affiliated stores.</p>
<p>The mileage integration and exchange function are key services that can track lost mileage most effectively by minimizing the possibility of a dropout according to each company&#8217;s mileage expiration and use policy. Mileage is treated as equivalent to real goods, and usage history is stored in the blockchain, while errors are minimized through cross-validation through mutual sharing between customers, companies, and Xmile. After the initial mileage service launch, Xmile intends to present a business model through rapid function expansion, including advertisement, wallet, DApp alliance, and exchange.</p>
<p>Xmile&#8217;s partners can be all companies that issue mileage and points. Many of these companies are closely related to real life and e-commerce that targets MZ generation. Xmile will continue to expand the usage for customer convenience with its partners, while considering expanding the number of affiliated brands to about 100.</p>
<p><strong>About XML Token</strong></p>
<p>XML is the native token of Xmile ecosystem. It is a token in the form of mileage used in the Xmile ecosystem and it’s an abbreviation of X Important Mileage. After exchanging mileage or points of each partner company for XML, customers can conveniently make payments at affiliated stores, etc. at any time.</p>
<p>Based on ERC-20, XML has a total supply of 2 billion (i.e., 2,000,000,000) tokens. It has been listed on LBank Exchange at 6:00 UTC on January 11, 2023, investors who are interested in Xmile investment can easily buy and sell XML token on LBank Exchange right now. The listing of XML token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.<strong> </strong></p>
<p><strong>Learn More about</strong> <strong>XML Token:</strong></p>
<p>Official Website: <a href="https://www.xmile.io" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.xmile.io</a></p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media: </strong></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Facebook</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong><br />
LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
LBank Exchange<br />
<a href="mailto:marketing@lbank.info">marketing@lbank.info</a><br />
<a href="mailto:business@lbank.info">business@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/xmile-xml-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">Xmile (XML) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/xmile-xml-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
