<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 17:03:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>BlackRock: Assets That Fell with BTC Won&#8217;t Recover This Year</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blackrock-assets-that-fell-with-btc-wont-recover-this-year/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blackrock-assets-that-fell-with-btc-wont-recover-this-year/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 17:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76078</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin, Ethereum, and other digital currencies hit rock bottom in 2022. Many of them crashed and experienced dips of 70 percent or more. Now, BlackRock – a famed investing firm – has stated that many assets and businesses that have moved in tandem with bitcoin and crypto are not likely to heal in the coming<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blackrock-assets-that-fell-with-btc-wont-recover-this-year/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blackrock-assets-that-fell-with-btc-wont-recover-this-year/">BlackRock: Assets That Fell with BTC Won&#8217;t Recover This Year</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin, Ethereum, and other digital currencies hit rock bottom in 2022. Many of them crashed and experienced dips of 70 percent or more. Now, BlackRock – a famed investing firm – has stated that many assets and businesses that have moved in tandem with bitcoin and crypto are not <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/billybambrough/2022/12/18/8-trillion-fund-issues-stark-2023-fed-warning-after-huge-bitcoin-ethereum-and-crypto-price-crash/?sh=598964234588" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">likely to heal in the coming</a> months, and that the Federal Reserve will not come to the rescue like they have with rate hikes.</p>
<h2>BlackRock Predicts Gloom and Doom for 2023</h2>
<p>With talk of recession lingering in the clouds, many are wondering if America’s economy is about to experience a whole new world of hurt that no analyst could have predicted. Strategists at BlackRock – which currently manages more than $8 trillion in overall assets – explained in a recent report:</p>
<blockquote><p>Recession is foretold as central banks race to try to tame inflation. It&#8217;s the opposite of past recessions. Central bankers won&#8217;t ride to the rescue when growth slows in this new regime, contrary to what investors have come to expect. Equity valuations don&#8217;t yet reflect the damage ahead.</p></blockquote>
<p>In 2022, inflation reached an all-time high. The prices of consumer goods, food, and even gasoline struck new points on the price meter, and many struggled to make ends meet. There has long been hope that 2023 would offer the healing many standard citizens were hoping for, though BlackRock questions if this will happen. The document states:</p>
<blockquote><p>We don&#8217;t think equities are fully priced for recession. Corporate earnings expectations have yet to fully reflect even a modest recession. This keeps us tactically underweight developed market equities.</p></blockquote>
<p>BlackRock also took note of the lack of progress the country has seen given the high number of hikes on rates the Fed has initiated. <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-fed-bitcoins-worst-enemy-right-now/" data-wpel-link="internal">There have been numerous</a> .75 and .50 jumps recorded throughout 2022, but they ultimately did no good. Inflation remained high, and crypto prices became lower and lower in the process.</p>
<p>The report by BlackRock mentioned that these rate hikes do not work the way they used to, and agencies such as the Fed will need to find new ways of fighting economic disaster if people are to stay steady and afloat in the months to come. The strategists said:</p>
<blockquote><p>What worked in the past won&#8217;t work now. The old playbook of simply &#8216;buying the dip&#8217; doesn&#8217;t apply in this regime of sharper trade-offs and greater macro volatility. We don&#8217;t see a return to conditions that will sustain a joint bull market in stocks and bonds of the kind we experienced in the prior decade.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Where Does Bitcoin Stand in All This?</h2>
<p>Some analysts – such as Alex Kuptsikevich of FX Pro – have also stated that the bitcoin price has stalled somewhat. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>From a tech analysis perspective, bitcoin has failed to latch on to levels above the 50-day moving average, causing it to now face speculative pressure.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blackrock-assets-that-fell-with-btc-wont-recover-this-year/">BlackRock: Assets That Fell with BTC Won&#8217;t Recover This Year</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blackrock-assets-that-fell-with-btc-wont-recover-this-year/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Xmile (XML) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/xmile-xml-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/xmile-xml-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 17:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76448</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Jan. 11, 2023 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed Xmile (XML) on January 11, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the XML/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading. Creating innovation that goes beyond the limits of current mileage industry, Xmile (XML) utilizes blockchain technology<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/xmile-xml-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/xmile-xml-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">Xmile (XML) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Jan. 11, 2023 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed Xmile (XML) on January 11, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the XML/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading.</p>
<p>Creating innovation that goes beyond the limits of current mileage industry, <a href="https://etherscan.io/token/0xadfafbf05d3d74af537bdec348ce4e536d99fb95" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Xmile</a> (XML) utilizes blockchain technology to promote an easier and more accessible mileage system with seamless asset management. Its native token XML has been listed on LBank Exchange at 6:00 UTC on January 11, 2023, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision.</p>
<p><strong>Introducing </strong><strong>Xmile</strong></p>
<p>Mileage is a type of reward for customers in airlines, transportation, e-commerce, and other industries. The mileage system is quite common across the world and even in carbon credit and other public sectors. There are many forms of rewards such as cashback, discounts, or a variety of free goods depending on the mileage tier.</p>
<p>However, problems such as restrictions and limitations of using mileage points and the expiration policy of the mileage system, difficulties in asset management and marketing still exist. To address all these issues with mileage, Xmile will promote an easier and more accessible mileage system with seamless asset management.</p>
<p>Xmile is a fully integrated platform for mileage systems that are designed to mutually benefit corporations and customers in the transportation and aviation industry and aims to establish a mileage ecosystem for broader usage. Customers can exchange or integrate mileage and points of Xmile’s partners through the Xmile platform and can use discount benefits and pay at affiliated stores.</p>
<p>The mileage integration and exchange function are key services that can track lost mileage most effectively by minimizing the possibility of a dropout according to each company&#8217;s mileage expiration and use policy. Mileage is treated as equivalent to real goods, and usage history is stored in the blockchain, while errors are minimized through cross-validation through mutual sharing between customers, companies, and Xmile. After the initial mileage service launch, Xmile intends to present a business model through rapid function expansion, including advertisement, wallet, DApp alliance, and exchange.</p>
<p>Xmile&#8217;s partners can be all companies that issue mileage and points. Many of these companies are closely related to real life and e-commerce that targets MZ generation. Xmile will continue to expand the usage for customer convenience with its partners, while considering expanding the number of affiliated brands to about 100.</p>
<p><strong>About XML Token</strong></p>
<p>XML is the native token of Xmile ecosystem. It is a token in the form of mileage used in the Xmile ecosystem and it’s an abbreviation of X Important Mileage. After exchanging mileage or points of each partner company for XML, customers can conveniently make payments at affiliated stores, etc. at any time.</p>
<p>Based on ERC-20, XML has a total supply of 2 billion (i.e., 2,000,000,000) tokens. It has been listed on LBank Exchange at 6:00 UTC on January 11, 2023, investors who are interested in Xmile investment can easily buy and sell XML token on LBank Exchange right now. The listing of XML token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.<strong> </strong></p>
<p><strong>Learn More about</strong> <strong>XML Token:</strong></p>
<p>Official Website: <a href="https://www.xmile.io" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.xmile.io</a></p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media: </strong></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Facebook</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong><br />
LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
LBank Exchange<br />
<a href="mailto:marketing@lbank.info">marketing@lbank.info</a><br />
<a href="mailto:business@lbank.info">business@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/xmile-xml-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">Xmile (XML) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/xmile-xml-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tim Draper Still Thinks Big Things Will Happen for BTC</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tim-draper-still-predicts-big-things-for-btc/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tim-draper-still-predicts-big-things-for-btc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 15:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tim Draper]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76075</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin had an extremely rough year in 2022. The price crashed, and the asset lost more than 70 percent of its value. Nothing could have prepared us for such a dramatic decline in the standing of the world’s largest and most popular digital currency, and yet there are some – such as venture capitalist Tim<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tim-draper-still-predicts-big-things-for-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tim-draper-still-predicts-big-things-for-btc/">Tim Draper Still Thinks Big Things Will Happen for BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin had an extremely rough year in 2022. The price crashed, and the asset lost more than 70 percent of its value. Nothing could have prepared us for such a dramatic decline in the standing of the world’s largest and most popular digital currency, and yet there are some – such as venture capitalist Tim Draper – <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/12/05/tim-draper-predicts-bitcoin-will-reach-250000-despite-ftx-collapse.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">that refuse to give up</a> on it.</p>
<h2>Tim Draper Still Loves BTC</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, Draper stated that 2023 will be the year in which bitcoin reaches a whopping price of $250,000. He believes this number could also materialize as early as June. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I have extended my prediction by six months. $250K is still my number.</p></blockquote>
<p>The reason he is pushing the price back to the summer is because he believes the drama <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">surrounding FTX and</a> its now disgraced founder Sam Bankman-Fried has caused the currency to be seen in a negative light by many people, whether they be new to the industry or experienced traders. However, he’s confident those involved in BTC will eventually be able to look past the problems surrounding the exchange and rev up their belief in the asset enough that it reaches his set price.</p>
<p>Draper also said that he expects bitcoin to be the only cryptocurrency that lasts. He thinks many copycats and altcoins are going to sink into oblivion, though he’s confident bitcoin is going to stand the test of time and become the strongest asset out there. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>I expect a flight to quality and decentralized crypto like bitcoin and for some of the weaker coins to become relics.</p></blockquote>
<p>This would all be fine and dandy except for two things. The first is the price that bitcoin is experiencing right now. The currency is presently trading in the high $16K range, which means that within the next few months, BTC would have to add more than $230,000 to its price to strike the chord Draper has predicted for it. Is this possible? While crypto has often proven unpredictable – sometimes pleasantly so – it’s hard to imagine such a huge jump in such a short period.</p>
<h2>Is Such a Prediction Believable?</h2>
<p>Second, this is not the first time Draper has predicted $250,000 for BTC. He did so back in 2018 and <a href="https://www.thestreet.com/investing/bitcoin/billionaire-tim-draper-super-bullish-on-bitcoin-14603011" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">claimed that 2022 of</a> all years would be the time in which the asset hit that number. Not only did this not happen, but 2022 will likely go down as the worst year for bitcoin or any form of cryptocurrency, so one has no choice but to take Draper’s words with a grain of salt.</p>
<p>Either way, the venture capitalist remains assured that bitcoin will prove a dominant currency in the future and that we will all be paying for our groceries and daily needs with the asset.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tim-draper-still-predicts-big-things-for-btc/">Tim Draper Still Thinks Big Things Will Happen for BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tim-draper-still-predicts-big-things-for-btc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sam Bankman-Fried, FTX&#8217;s Disgraced Founder, Has Been Arrested</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftxs-disgraced-founder-has-been-arrested/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftxs-disgraced-founder-has-been-arrested/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 13:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bahamas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76073</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sam Bankman-Fried – the man behind now failed digital currency exchange FTX – has been arrested while stationed in the Bahamas and is being extradited to the United States, where he will face criminal charges after they were filed in a New York court. Sam Bankman-Fried Is Heading to an American Jail The criminal charges<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftxs-disgraced-founder-has-been-arrested/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftxs-disgraced-founder-has-been-arrested/">Sam Bankman-Fried, FTX&#8217;s Disgraced Founder, Has Been Arrested</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sam Bankman-Fried – the man behind now failed digital currency exchange FTX – has been arrested while stationed in the Bahamas and is <a href="https://www.usatoday.com/videos/news/2022/12/20/cryptocurrency-exchange-founder-agrees-extradition-u-s/10931188002/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">being extradited to</a> the United States, where he will face criminal charges after they were filed in a New York court.</p>
<h2>Sam Bankman-Fried Is Heading to an American Jail</h2>
<p>The criminal charges come by way of the Department of Justice (DOJ), though now the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is filing its <a href="https://www.thestreet.com/video/sbf-arrested-in-bahamas-after-orchestrating-years-long-fraud" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">own civil suit against</a> the disgraced crypto mogul. The agency says Sam Bankman-Fried orchestrated what it called “years-long fraud” in a statement, and they are using him to set an example to any other would-be crypto criminals that view the space as an area to commit crimes and take advantage of investors.</p>
<p>The SEC says Sam Bankman-Fried used the funds of others for “his own personal benefit and to help grow his crypto empire.”</p>
<p>Former U.S. prosecutor Renato Mariotti says Bankman-Fried <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/us-government-wants-send-message-194635575.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">has undoubtedly soured</a> the crypto space permanently for some. In an interview, he commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>From the DOJ’s perspective, SBF was spreading misinformation and was creating a lack of confidence in the regulators to police the market.</p></blockquote>
<p>He further stated that there was a lot of concern that Bankman-Fried was somehow going to get away with everything he’d done given his ties to political authorities. It is estimated that he donated more than $40 million to various <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-gave-a-lot-of-money-to-democrats-what-will-they-do-with-it/" data-wpel-link="internal">democrat politicians alone</a>. He is also classified as the second largest donor to Joe Biden. Many have questioned democrats about whether they plan to give this money back and revoke their ties to the criminally charged crypto executive.</p>
<p>Mariotti says Biden and his cronies largely view the crypto space through a biased lens. They see the industry as unregulated and dangerous, and they will likely use this incident to their advantage and monitor activity with eagle eyes. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The [Biden] administration believes that the digital asset space is unregulated and thinks that [crypto firms] can get away with anything.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Real Damper in the Crypto Agenda</h2>
<p>FTX will likely go down as one of the biggest embarrassments of the digital currency space. Beginning in the year 2019, FTX was only three years old, yet it somehow rose through the ranks and became one of the five largest crypto trading platforms in the world. Sam Bankman-Fried was lauded as a genius by many, and his net worth prior to the company’s collapse was estimated to be more than $16 billion.</p>
<p>However, it is alleged that Bankman-Fried utilized customer funds to purchase luxury condominiums for himself and assorted executives and employees of FTX in the Bahamas, the country where the exchange was based. The company was initially going to be <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">bought out by Binance</a> after it experienced a liquidity crunch, though this <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">never came to be</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftxs-disgraced-founder-has-been-arrested/">Sam Bankman-Fried, FTX&#8217;s Disgraced Founder, Has Been Arrested</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftxs-disgraced-founder-has-been-arrested/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: More Gains Possible Above $0.055</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-more-gains-possible-above-0-055/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-more-gains-possible-above-0-055/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 07:28:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76445</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tron price started a fresh increase above the $0.0535 level against the US Dollar. TRX price is now trading above $0.0542 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $0.0525 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could continue to<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-more-gains-possible-above-0-055/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-more-gains-possible-above-0-055/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: More Gains Possible Above $0.055</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Tron price started a fresh increase above the $0.0535 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>TRX price is now trading above $0.0542 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $0.0525 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move up if it breaks the $0.0560 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>TRON price started a fresh increase above $0.0542 against the US Dollar, similar <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-climbs-and-aims-steady-increase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. TRX price could rise further if it clears the $0.056 resistance.</em></p>
<h2>Tron Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, tron price retested the key $0.050 support zone against the US Dollar. TRX price remained well bid and started a decent increase from the $0.052 zone.</p>
<p>It traded above the $0.0525 and $0.0530 resistance levels to move into a positive zone. During the increase, there was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $0.0525 on the 4-hours chart. The price traded as high as $0.0567 and is currently correcting lower.</p>
<p>There was a move below the $0.0555 level. The price declined below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.0497 swing low to $0.0567 high.</p>
<p>It is now trading above $0.0542 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bulls-aim-upside-break-above-0-055/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. On the upside, TRX is facing resistance near the $0.0556 level.</p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $0.0560 level. A close above $0.0560 is must for a fresh increase. In the stated case, the price could rise towards the $0.0588 resistance in the near term.</p>
<p>Any more gains might send trx price towards $0.065. On the downside, an initial support is near the $0.0540 level or the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). The next major support is now forming near $0.0532. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.0497 swing low to $0.0567 high.</p>
<p>If there is a downside break below the $0.0532 support, the price might revisit the $0.0500 support. Any more losses might call for a move towards the $0.0450 zone in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_76446" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/TRON-TRX-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76446" class="size-full wp-image-76446" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/TRON-TRX-1.png" alt="Tron (TRX) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76446" class="wp-caption-text">Tron (TRX) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/TRXUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that TRX price is now trading above $0.0542 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could continue to move up if it breaks the $0.0560 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for TRX/USD is slowly gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for TRX/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.0540 and $0.0532.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.0555, $0.056 and $0.062.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-more-gains-possible-above-0-055/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: More Gains Possible Above $0.055</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-more-gains-possible-above-0-055/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Climbs And Aims Steady Increase</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-climbs-and-aims-steady-increase/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-climbs-and-aims-steady-increase/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 05:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76442</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price started a fresh increase from the $16,650 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above $17,000 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $17,050 on the 4-hours chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-climbs-and-aims-steady-increase/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-climbs-and-aims-steady-increase/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Climbs And Aims Steady Increase</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin price started a fresh increase from the $16,650 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $17,000 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $17,050 on the 4-hours chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move up if it stays above the $17,000 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin price is rising above $17,000 against the US Dollar. BTC might extend gains if there is a clear move above the $17,500 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price started a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-steady-increase-to-18k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">fresh increase</a> from the $16,650 support zone. A base was formed and the price climbed higher above the $16,880 resistance zone.</p>
<p>The bulls pushed the price above the $17,000 resistance and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). The upward move was such that the price climbed towards the $17,500 resistance zone. A high is formed near $17,494 and the price is now consolidating gains.</p>
<p>It is now trading above $17,000 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-drop-to-new-2022-lows/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $17,050 on the 4-hours chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>An immediate resistance on the upside is near the $17,500 level. The next major resistance might near the $17,850 zone. The first major resistance is near the $18,000 level. A clear move above the $18,000 level might send the price towards $19,000, above which the price might rise towards the $20,000 level.</p>
<p>Any more gains might push the price towards the $21,200 zone. If there is no upside break, the price might decline below the $17,400 level. The first major support is near $17,300 or the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $16,670 swing low to $17,494 high.</p>
<p>The next key support is near the $17,050 level or the trend line. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $16,670 swing low to $17,494 high, below which the price might accelerate lower.</p>
<p>In the stated case, the price could decline towards the $16,650 level. Any more losses might send the price towards the $16,000 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_76443" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Bitcoin-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76443" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-76443" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Bitcoin-1.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76443" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XBTUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, bitcoin price is clearly trading above $17,000 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could continue to move up if it stays above the $17,000 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $17,300 and $17,050.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $17,500, $18,000 and $19,200.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-climbs-and-aims-steady-increase/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Climbs And Aims Steady Increase</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-climbs-and-aims-steady-increase/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mark Mobius Says Bitcoin Could Fall to $10K</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-mobius-calls-btc-dangerous-and-says-it-could-fall-to-10k/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-mobius-calls-btc-dangerous-and-says-it-could-fall-to-10k/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 17:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mark Mobius]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75861</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The price of bitcoin has taken several hard hits over the past 14 months, but according to legendary investor Mark Mobius, he thinks things are going to get a lot worse before they get better. In fact, he sees the world’s number one digital currency by market cap falling to a new low of $10K<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-mobius-calls-btc-dangerous-and-says-it-could-fall-to-10k/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-mobius-calls-btc-dangerous-and-says-it-could-fall-to-10k/">Mark Mobius Says Bitcoin Could Fall to $10K</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price of bitcoin has taken several hard hits over the past 14 months, but according to legendary investor Mark Mobius, he thinks things are <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/mark-mobius-sees-bitcoin-down-at-2410000-in-e2-80-98dangerous-e2-80-99-crypto-market/ar-AA14DirI" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">going to get a lot</a> worse before they get better. In fact, he sees the world’s number one digital currency by market cap falling to a new low of $10K before it begins its rebound.</p>
<h2>Mark Mobius Isn&#8217;t Crazy About Bitcoin</h2>
<p>Mobius has never been a bitcoin fan. At times, he’s referred to it in rather derogatory ways, even calling it a “psycho” currency in the year 2019. <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-mobius-calls-bitcoin-a-psycho-currency/" data-wpel-link="internal">During that era</a>, he expressed his thoughts on BTC, claiming he didn’t trust it as its price spikes weren’t based on anything except hardcore speculation. He said the only thing keeping BTC up was the belief it had from average investors, and he hinted that should that ever die down (like it is now), BTC would soon find itself in the can.</p>
<p>He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I call them psycho currencies because it’s a matter of faith whether you believe in bitcoin or any of the other cybercurrencies… I think with the rise of [bitcoin], there’s going to be a demand for real, hard assets, and that includes gold.</p></blockquote>
<p>Now, over three years later, his sentiment hasn’t changed much, though he <em>did</em> mention that even with the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">recent fall of FTX</a> and the ongoing bearish trends witnessed in today’s crypto market, he doesn’t feel bitcoin is going to disappear completely. Rather, while he believes it may continue to go down in price, he thinks it’s held up rather well given all it’s been through in the last year.</p>
<p>He claimed in a more recent appearance:</p>
<blockquote><p>But crypto is here to stay as there are several investors who still have faith in it. It’s amazing how bitcoin prices have held up.</p></blockquote>
<p>Despite this little note of positivity, he was quick to mention that he would never invest any money of his own into BTC or other cryptocurrencies, citing them as “too dangerous.”</p>
<h2>The Worst Year for Crypto?</h2>
<p>2022 will likely go down as one of the worst years – if not <em>the worst year</em> – for bitcoin. In November 2021, the currency reached a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit. It felt like the currency was on a ladder that could never topple, but these thoughts were proven wrong as soon as the new year came into play.</p>
<p>From there, the asset endured a long series of price dips that eventually saw it lose more than 70 percent of its overall value. The currency dropped into the mid-$16K range, and while a few small rallies occurred here and there, many traders and analysts tried to warn others that getting too excited early was a big mistake. Overall, crypto space lost more than $2 trillion in valuation in 2022.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-mobius-calls-btc-dangerous-and-says-it-could-fall-to-10k/">Mark Mobius Says Bitcoin Could Fall to $10K</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-mobius-calls-btc-dangerous-and-says-it-could-fall-to-10k/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>All in Web3? Where will BTC go in 2023? FAMEEX united 9 projects hosted a popular Twitter Space with users.</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/all-in-web3-where-will-btc-go-in-2023-fameex-united-9-projects-hosted-a-popular-twitter-space-with-users/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/all-in-web3-where-will-btc-go-in-2023-fameex-united-9-projects-hosted-a-popular-twitter-space-with-users/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 16:51:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76420</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>After the crypto market crash in 2022, BTC supporters and crypto investors are left wondering where the market will go in 2023 and while enduring the massive loss. Will Web3 drive a resurgence in the crypto industry? Will DAO become the preferred form of alternative corporate organization? On January 9, 2023, FAMEEX held a popular<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/all-in-web3-where-will-btc-go-in-2023-fameex-united-9-projects-hosted-a-popular-twitter-space-with-users/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/all-in-web3-where-will-btc-go-in-2023-fameex-united-9-projects-hosted-a-popular-twitter-space-with-users/">All in Web3? Where will BTC go in 2023? FAMEEX united 9 projects hosted a popular Twitter Space with users.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After the crypto market crash in 2022, BTC supporters and crypto investors are left wondering where the market will go in 2023 and while enduring the massive loss. Will Web3 drive a resurgence in the crypto industry? Will DAO become the preferred form of alternative corporate organization? On January 9, 2023, FAMEEX held a popular Twitter space with several projects to discuss the future of Web3. Nearly 500 users participated in the discussion, including Cybermartians, Damn It, Randverse, Reitio, EtherPOAP, Flappy Moonbird, Freename, 3WW3, and other major projects. The discussion resulted in the identification of potential opportunities for growth in Web3 in the areas of GameFi, DAO, and SocialFi in 2023.</p>
<p>“Actually 2022 is a hard year for crypto, NFT and BTC sharp rise brought numerous new users to the industry but now they are suffering the pain of crypto crash. From the series of major events triggered by the Luna crashed to the collapse of FTX exchange, the industry will definitely go to a healthier and more compliant future. The bear market is still not over, but the bull market will definitely come back, and the next bull cycle will probably start at the end of 2023,” FAMEEX India Market Manager EthAn said.</p>
<p><strong>About FAMEEX Exchange</strong></p>
<p>FAMEEX has established itself over the past 2 years in the crypto derivatives market and is consistently operating in the futures trading broker sector. Always Following the philosophy of &#8220;Secure global crypto exchange with quantitative trading&#8221;, FAMEEX aims to offer its users comprehensive and secure trading solutions, integrating decentralized finance (DeFi) with centralized finance (CeFi) in the futures roadmap.</p>
<p>One key difference between FAMEEX and other exchanges is that FAMEEX focuses on providing opportunities and benefits to new users. This includes campaigns and activities that can help users earn without taking on any risk.</p>
<p>One example of how FAMEEX sets itself apart from other exchanges is by offering opportunities for users to become our ambassadors and receive top rebate commissions,more than 500USDT/M. To apply, users can direct message the FAMEEX marketing team on Telegram (@MKT_FAMEEX). FAMEEX also provides funding for new users to experience the platform without having to invest their own money, and offers opportunities for marketing professionals to become our local agents and connect with influencers, communities, and YouTubers. These privileges and opportunities provide unique benefits for FAMEEX users and help the exchange stand out in a crowded market.</p>
<p>Additionally, all users can participate in the campaigns and activities designed by FAMEEX, which can help them experience without taking on any risk. This focus on providing opportunities and benefits to users sets FAMEEX apart from other exchanges and allows it to compete effectively in a crowded market.</p>
<p>Currently, FAMEEX has users in over 50 countries and is undergoing rapid expansion of the userbase. FAMEEX co-founder explained, &#8220;Despite the recent macro downturn, the market is still rife with growth opportunity. Our strategy for the future incorporates numerous developments in tokenomics and we foresee a key role for enabling web3 in the next transformation of FAMEEX.&#8221;</p>
<p>FAMEEX is a reliable crypto exchange broker which operates under a policy of transparency and fairness. Moreover, the trading platform offers a high level of sophistication, with plenty of engaging trade choices to help traders accomplish their goals.</p>
<p><strong>Find Out More about FAMEEX</strong></p>
<p>Launched in 2020. FAMEEX is a global cryptocurrency exchange that currently provides fiat-crypto, crypto-crypto, grid trading, futures, margin, spot and a hugely popular referral and affiliate program. With more than 200,000 users across 50 countries and regions we provide a secure, stable and efficient 24/7 trading platform.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/all-in-web3-where-will-btc-go-in-2023-fameex-united-9-projects-hosted-a-popular-twitter-space-with-users/">All in Web3? Where will BTC go in 2023? FAMEEX united 9 projects hosted a popular Twitter Space with users.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/all-in-web3-where-will-btc-go-in-2023-fameex-united-9-projects-hosted-a-popular-twitter-space-with-users/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sam Bankman-Fried Makes Rare Appearance Following FTX Collapse</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-makes-rare-appearance-following-ftx-collapse/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-makes-rare-appearance-following-ftx-collapse/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 15:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75858</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sam Bankman-Fried – the disgraced founder of fallen digital currency exchange FTX – made a rare appearance at the Deal Book Summit in New York on the last day of November last year. Sam Bankman-Fried Does First Interview Following Company&#8217;s Demise While he did not arrive in person, Bankman-Fried was featured prominently on a screen<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-makes-rare-appearance-following-ftx-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-makes-rare-appearance-following-ftx-collapse/">Sam Bankman-Fried Makes Rare Appearance Following FTX Collapse</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sam Bankman-Fried – the disgraced founder of fallen digital currency exchange FTX – made a rare appearance at the Deal Book Summit in New York <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/sam-bankman-fried-former-ceo-of-ftx-says-we-messed-up-big/ar-AA14KURn" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">on the last day of November</a> last year.</p>
<h2>Sam Bankman-Fried Does First Interview Following Company&#8217;s Demise</h2>
<p>While he did not arrive in person, Bankman-Fried was featured prominently on a screen from an undisclosed location in the Bahamas, where he still claims to live.</p>
<p>In the interview, Bankman-Fried attempted to explain what happened with his exchange in his own words. It is believed that much of the money stationed in FTX and his other company Alameda Research was commingled or mixed, and that this ultimately helped contribute to the downfall. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I didn’t knowingly commingle funds… I wasn’t running Alameda. I didn’t know what was going on. A lot of the things were things I learned over the last month.</p></blockquote>
<p>At times, Sam Bankman-Fried appeared to express remorse about everything that happened. He mentioned casually to the audience:</p>
<blockquote><p>Look, I screwed up. I was the CEO of FTX. I say this again and again. That means I had a responsibility. We messed up big.</p></blockquote>
<p>At the same time, there were several other moments throughout the event where he seemed to deny he was responsible for anything. He also appeared to suggest that he shouldn’t face any direct repercussions for what occurred. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think I was scared. I was nervous because of the conflict of interest.</p></blockquote>
<p>He further said that while his lawyers believed doing any interviews would be a mistake, he felt it was the right move to make and stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I have a duty to explain what happened, and I have a duty to try to help [customers].</p></blockquote>
<p>He also clarified where he got much of the money that eventually went to the many democrat <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-billionaire-sam-bankman-fried-spends-big-in-the-name-of-politics/" data-wpel-link="internal">politicians that he funded</a> in both 2020 and 2022. He claimed in the interview that all the funds came directly from the company’s profits.</p>
<p>There are still many unanswered questions surrounding FTX, but one thing is for sure. There are several people that have suffered because of the company’s collapse, and the problems at hand probably aren’t quite over.</p>
<h2>The Drama of FTX</h2>
<p>Trouble for FTX first appeared in mid-November of last year. The company reported on social media that it was experiencing a “<a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">liquidity crunch</a>” and needed cash fast. From there, Bankman-Fried approached Binance – his larger rival – about a possible bailout, but this failed from the get-go, with the larger exchange claiming FTX’s <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">issues were too big</a> for it to handle.</p>
<p>From there, FTX <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">was forced to file bankruptcy</a> and Sam Bankman-Fried resigned from his post. The company’s collapse has sent waves throughout the space and has caused many other firms – such as <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block-fi-is-the-latest-crypto-company-to-go-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">lending platform Block Fi</a> – to follow in its footsteps.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-makes-rare-appearance-following-ftx-collapse/">Sam Bankman-Fried Makes Rare Appearance Following FTX Collapse</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-makes-rare-appearance-following-ftx-collapse/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
