<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 03:08:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Turns Red Below $29K</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-29k/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-29k/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 03:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78255</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price started a fresh decline below the $29,000 pivot level against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $28,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support at $28,400 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-29k/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-29k/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Turns Red Below $29K</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin price started a fresh decline below the $29,000 pivot level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $28,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support at $28,400 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could extend its decline toward the $27,000 and $26,200 levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin price is declining below $28,500 against the US Dollar. BTC might extend losses if it stays below the $28,500 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price started a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-extend-losses-below-27000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">fresh decline</a> below the $29,000 zone. A high was formed near $29,850 before the price started a steady decline. There was a clear move below the $29,000 and $28,500 support levels.</p>
<p>The bears even pushed the price below the $28,000 support zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). The price traded as low as $27,279 and is currently correcting losses. There was a correction toward the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward wave from the $29,850 swing high to the $27,279 low.</p>
<p>However, it is still trading below $29,500 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-29250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. Immediate resistance on the upside is near the $27,900 level. The next major resistance might be near the $28,150 zone.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $28,150 level might send the price toward $28,500 or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward wave from the $29,850 swing high to the $27,279 low, above which the price might rise toward the $29,200 level. Any more gains might push the price toward the $30,000 zone.</p>
<p>If there is no upside break, the price might decline below the $27,250 level. The first major support is near $27,000. The next key support is near the $26,200 level, below which the price might accelerate lower. In the stated case, the price could decline toward the $25,500 level. Any more losses might send the price toward the $25,000 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_78256" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Bitcoin-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78256" class="size-full wp-image-78256" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Bitcoin-1.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78256" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XBTUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Bitcoin price is clearly trading below $28,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could extend its decline toward the $27,000 and $26,200 levels.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD is now losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $27,250 and $27,000.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $28,000, $28,500, and $29,200.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-29k/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Turns Red Below $29K</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-29k/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jake Paul Settles Crypto-Related Charges with the SEC</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jake-paul-settles-crypto-related-charges-with-the-sec/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jake-paul-settles-crypto-related-charges-with-the-sec/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 17:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jake Paul]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lindsay Lohan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77732</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Social media star and boxer Jake Paul has recently settled crypto-related charges with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Paul had initially been hired by blockchain network Tron to promote a new digital currency, though he had allegedly failed to reveal he was being paid to engage in the promotion. Jake Paul and the SEC<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jake-paul-settles-crypto-related-charges-with-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jake-paul-settles-crypto-related-charges-with-the-sec/">Jake Paul Settles Crypto-Related Charges with the SEC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Social media star and boxer Jake Paul has recently settled <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/jake-paul-26-reaches-settlement-following-crazy-cryptocurrency-controversy/ar-AA19hmkP" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">crypto-related charges with</a> the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Paul had initially been hired by <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-targets-tron-in-latest-crypto-case/" data-wpel-link="internal">blockchain network Tron to promote</a> a new digital currency, though he had allegedly failed to reveal he was being paid to engage in the promotion.</p>
<h2>Jake Paul and the SEC Settle Their &#8220;Differences&#8221;</h2>
<p>The SEC says that this goes against present securities laws. If you are granted payment for taking part in a crypto or token-based promotion, you must reveal this data to your fans and followers. Discussing the present case against Tron and the numerous celebrities it paid to endorse its product(s), SEC head Gary Gensler explained in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>This case demonstrates again the high-risk investors face when crypto asset securities are offered and sold without proper disclosure. As alleged, Sun and his companies not only targeted U.S. investors in their unregistered offers and sales, generating millions in illegal proceeds at the expense of investors, but they also coordinated wash trading on an unregistered trading platform to create the misleading appearance of active trading in TRX. Sun further induced investors to purchase TRX and BTT by orchestrating a promotional campaign in which he and his celebrity promoters hid the fact that the celebrities were paid for their tweets.</p></blockquote>
<p>Paul is not the only celebrity being targeted by the federal financial agency. Among the others is Lindsay Lohan, who also took part in Tron’s online promotion. It’s alleged in lawsuit documents that the actress and former child star was paid roughly $10K to promote Tronix tokens on Twitter, though she failed to let her social media followers know she had received compensation. A spokesperson for Lohan said that she was unaware that she was required to disclose this information and that she’s agreed to pay a fine to resolve the matter.</p>
<p>It’s estimated that the fines Paul paid exceeded $400K. In other news, Paul is claiming to have at one time taken a hallucinogen with football star Aaron Rodgers. In an interview with FOX News, Paul said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Aaron and I were together when we did the ayahuasca. He&#8217;s more publicly known for speaking about it, but I was actually there with him when we did it. We spent the week there doing it. [We] share that similarity in terms of spirituality and reflecting and going into the deepest parts of the mind.</p></blockquote>
<h2>The Agency Is Going After Every Crypto Company, It Seems</h2>
<p>It’s unclear if the present SEC case against Tron is valid or if it’s just another attempt (in a long string of attempts) to bring the crypto space down.</p>
<p>Not long ago, the SEC forced Kraken to part with a $30 million fine and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/" data-wpel-link="internal">end its staking activities and services</a>. It <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">also sent a Wells notice</a> to Coinbase letting it know it could likely face charges.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jake-paul-settles-crypto-related-charges-with-the-sec/">Jake Paul Settles Crypto-Related Charges with the SEC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jake-paul-settles-crypto-related-charges-with-the-sec/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Event TAB Conf Will Soon Take Place in Atlanta</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-event-tab-conf-will-soon-take-place-in-atlanta/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-event-tab-conf-will-soon-take-place-in-atlanta/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 15:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brandon Iglesias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TAB Conf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77729</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Two crypto developers are establishing a new bitcoin-centered conference in Atlanta, Georgia. This will be a reimagining of the TAB Conf gathering that’s occurred every year for the last five years within the capital city. TAB Conf Is Almost Here TAB Conf is still set to occur at the end of 2023. The event allows<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-event-tab-conf-will-soon-take-place-in-atlanta/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-event-tab-conf-will-soon-take-place-in-atlanta/">Bitcoin Event TAB Conf Will Soon Take Place in Atlanta</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Two crypto developers are <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/planners-bitcoin-conference-atlanta-move-160405191.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">establishing a new bitcoin-centered</a> conference in Atlanta, Georgia. This will be a reimagining of the TAB Conf gathering that’s occurred every year for the last five years within the capital city.</p>
<h2>TAB Conf Is Almost Here</h2>
<p>TAB Conf is still set to occur at the end of 2023. The event allows members of the public to recommend specific crypto-related topics that they would like to discuss and hear about. This new conference will be more open-source and feature subjects relating to the open-source nature of bitcoin, which the developers seem to think has been dying out over time.</p>
<p>Co-founder of TAB Conf LLC Brandon Iglesias gave his initial ideas regarding the event in an interview. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Anyone can open an issue, and the issues are not selected based on whether a sponsor decides to give us money or whether a person has a certain status in the community. The issues are solely chosen based on merit.</p></blockquote>
<p>Both he and his fellow co-founder Michael Tidwell developed TAB Conf in 2018. The event was established through a long meetup series they initially organized to get more people interested in the growing crypto space. Iglesias also serves as the director of product at decentralized storage firm Storj, while Tidwell is the director of infrastructure at the bitcoin gaming and payments firm Zebedee (which has recently put out a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/zebedee-gaming-platform-unveils-bitcoin-chess/" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin-centered version of chess</a>).</p>
<p>Iglesias continued his statement with:</p>
<blockquote><p>What we&#8217;re doing is we&#8217;re having people go on to a GitHub repository and submit ideas for workshops and panels and talks that they want to either see at the conference or give at the conference. This is all public and transparent… The level of detail and time potential speakers put into their issues will show and help us decide what issues will bring the most value to the TAB Conf 2023 attendees. If we don&#8217;t select an issue with a lot of conversation or emojis compared to the rest, the attendees at least have transparency and can hold us accountable.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Strong, Five-Year History</h2>
<p>When TAB Conf first debuted, it attracted more than 500 attendees and featured several dozen speakers. Among them were bitcoin core developers Andrew Chow, Gloria Zhao, and Murch and Pieter Wuille. Jeremy Rubin, a developer, also discussed the growing world of bitcoin smart contracts. At that stage, said contracts were predominantly associated with Ethereum.</p>
<p>Before now, the job of coming up with the agenda to be featured in each conference lied on the shoulders of the event’s organizers, though now, both Iglesias and Tidwell are letting the public have more of a hand in deciding how and where the event should operate and the directions it should move in. This, they say, brings the democratic nature of bitcoin more front and center.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-event-tab-conf-will-soon-take-place-in-atlanta/">Bitcoin Event TAB Conf Will Soon Take Place in Atlanta</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-event-tab-conf-will-soon-take-place-in-atlanta/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Fraud Victim in Canada Gets a Lot of Money Back</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-fraud-victim-in-canada-gets-a-lot-of-money-back/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-fraud-victim-in-canada-gets-a-lot-of-money-back/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 13:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[canada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scam]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77250</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A fraud victim in Winnipeg, Canada has lost more than $168,000 to a digital currency scam. The clincher? At the time of writing, much of the money has been gotten back, which is an odd outcome in situations like these. Canada Victim Gets a Lot of Money Returned Everyone knows that most of the time,<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-fraud-victim-in-canada-gets-a-lot-of-money-back/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-fraud-victim-in-canada-gets-a-lot-of-money-back/">Crypto Fraud Victim in Canada Gets a Lot of Money Back</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A fraud victim in Winnipeg, Canada has lost <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-ca/news/canada/winnipeg-police-recover-155k-of-168k-taken-in-cryptocurrency-investment-scam/ar-AA186yZX" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">more than $168,000 to a</a> digital currency scam. The clincher? At the time of writing, much of the money has been gotten back, which is an odd outcome in situations like these.</p>
<h2>Canada Victim Gets a Lot of Money Returned</h2>
<p>Everyone knows that most of the time, once crypto is stolen, it’s gone for good. This is one of the major problems with the crypto scene. Since it’s unregulated, there are no federal offerings such as FDIC or anything similar in the mix designed to protect crypto traders from becoming potential fraud victims. Nine times out of ten, if someone loses their money or has it taken from them, they can usually kiss it goodbye.</p>
<p>The loss occurred sometime last October. The person in question wound up losing more than 5.8 units of bitcoin to a crypto investment scam after being directed to purchase crypto for well over three months. Without this person’s knowledge, the money they invested wound up getting transferred overseas and converted into Tether, a popular stable asset.</p>
<p>Police discovered this and were able to interfere with future activity and thus return about $155,000 of the stolen funds to the original owner. Constable Dani McKinnon from the public information office in Winnipeg explained in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>Police utilize certain techniques to trace crypto assets as they are moved. In some cases, the timely tracking of crypto assets can identify opportunities for law enforcement intervention.</p></blockquote>
<p>Canada is eager to end all crypto fraud <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/canada-does-all-it-can-to-prevent-another-ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">and implement strict</a> regulatory tactics following the collapse of FTX, arguably the biggest embarrassment to ever hit the digital currency arena. Once one of the world’s top digital currency trading enterprises, FTX hit a real snag last November when its founder and chief executive Sam Bankman-Fried said the company was suddenly in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">need of fast cash</a> and that a liquidity crunch was being experienced.</p>
<p>While he initially sought the aid of his rival Binance and tried to instigate a buyout, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">this never occurred</a>, and it wasn’t long before his <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">firm entered bankruptcy</a> and he resigned from his post. <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-to-await-trial-at-his-parents-house/" data-wpel-link="internal">He’s now awaiting</a> trial, however, after it was discovered that he allegedly misused customer funds to purchase real estate and pay off loans for his other company Alameda Research.</p>
<h2>A Lot of Problems It&#8217;s Trying to Avoid</h2>
<p>Canada was also the central hub of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/quadriga-cx/" data-wpel-link="internal">Quadriga CX</a>, which many believe was another scam opportunity for those in charge. The trading platform’s owner passed away close to five years ago, and he was the only one (purportedly) with knowledge of the private keys needed to access all the funds locked away within the company.</p>
<p>This meant that none of the customers could gain access to their funds after his death, and a huge class-action lawsuit has emerged in the meantime.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-fraud-victim-in-canada-gets-a-lot-of-money-back/">Crypto Fraud Victim in Canada Gets a Lot of Money Back</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-fraud-victim-in-canada-gets-a-lot-of-money-back/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Bears In Control Below $0.4</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-bears-in-control-below-0-4/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-bears-in-control-below-0-4/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 05:08:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78243</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ADA price is showing bearish signs below the $0.40 support zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $0.40 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.375 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Coinbase). The price could continue to<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-bears-in-control-below-0-4/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-bears-in-control-below-0-4/">Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Bears In Control Below $0.4</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>ADA price is showing bearish signs below the $0.40 support zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $0.40 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.375 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Coinbase).</li>
<li>The price could continue to move down if it stays below the $0.38 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Cardano price is struggling below $0.40 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-extend-losses-below-27000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. ADA price could start a fresh increase if it clears the $0.375 and $0.38 resistance levels.</em></p>
<h2>Cardano Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, Cardano price saw a fresh decline from the $0.400 zone against the US Dollar. The ADA/USD pair declined below the $0.380 and $0.375 support levels.</p>
<p>The price even declined below the $0.365 support and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-upsides-capped-near-0-40/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. It revisited the $0.355 support zone. A low is formed near $0.3539 and the price is consolidating losses. It is now trading below $0.38 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>Besides, there is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.375 on the 4-hour chart. On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $0.375 zone, the trend line, and the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent drop from the $0.3971 swing high to the $0.3539 low.</p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $0.380 level. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent drop from the $0.3971 swing high to the $0.3539 low.</p>
<p>A clear upside break above the $0.380 level might send the price toward the $0.40 resistance. Any more gains could start a steady increase toward the $0.425 level. On the downside, immediate support is near the $0.355 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $0.332 level, below which the price may perhaps decline toward the $0.320 support level. Any more losses might call for a test of the $0.300 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_78244" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Cardano-Price-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78244" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78244" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Cardano-Price-1.png" alt="Cardano (ADA) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78244" class="wp-caption-text">Cardano (ADA) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ADAUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that ADA price is now trading below $0.380 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $0.380 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ADA/USD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for ADA/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.355 and $0.335.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.375 and $0.380.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-bears-in-control-below-0-4/">Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Bears In Control Below $0.4</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-bears-in-control-below-0-4/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH At Risk of Downside Break</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-at-risk-of-downside-break/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-at-risk-of-downside-break/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 03:38:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78240</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum price is gaining bearish momentum below the $1,885 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH price is now trading below $1,885 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support at $1,885 on the 4-hour chart (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could recover,<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-at-risk-of-downside-break/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-at-risk-of-downside-break/">Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH At Risk of Downside Break</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ethereum price is gaining bearish momentum below the $1,885 resistance against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>ETH price is now trading below $1,885 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support at $1,885 on the 4-hour chart (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could recover, but it is likely to face sellers near the $1,885 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ethereum price is declining below $1,885 against the US Dollar. ETH/USD remains at a risk of more downsides below the $1,800 support zone.</em></p>
<h2>Ethereum Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, Ethereum struggled to clear the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-faces-increase-in-bearish-pressure/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">$2,020 resistance zone</a> against the US Dollar. ETH price struggled to gain pace above the $2,000 level and reacted to the downside.</p>
<p>The recent high was formed near $2,020 and the price started a fresh decline. There was a drop below the $1,920 and $1,885 support levels. The pair even spiked below the $1,820 support. A low is formed near $1,810 and the price is now consolidating losses.</p>
<p>It is now trading below $1,885 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-revisits-key-support-but-struggles/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. On the upside, the price is now facing resistance near the $1,860 level. It is near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $2,020 swing high to the $1,810 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $1,885 level, above which it could test the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $2,020 swing high to the $1,810 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $1,970 zone. A clear move above the $1,970 and $1,980 resistance levels might call for a fresh move to $2,020. Any more gains could even send the price toward the $2,120 resistance zone or even $2,200 in the near term.</p>
<p>On the downside, initial support is near the $1,800 level. The next major support is now near the $1,775 level. A break below the $1,775 support could push the price to $1,720. If the bulls fail to protect the $1,720 support, the price might decline toward $1,650.</p>
<div id="attachment_78241" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Ethereum-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78241" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78241" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Ethereum-1.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78241" class="wp-caption-text">Ethereum Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Ethereum price is trading below $1,885 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, Ether’s price could recover, but it is likely to face sellers near the $1,885 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for ETH/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $1,800, followed by the $1,775 zone.</p>
<p>Key Resistance$ Levels – $1,885 and $1,915.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-at-risk-of-downside-break/">Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH At Risk of Downside Break</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-at-risk-of-downside-break/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Not Everyone Is Convinced Bitcoin Is Moving in the Right Direction</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/not-everyone-is-convinced-bitcoin-is-moving-in-the-right-direction/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/not-everyone-is-convinced-bitcoin-is-moving-in-the-right-direction/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 17:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ed Moya]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77719</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has soared following the bank crisis that occurred earlier in the year, but many analysts – despite clear evidence that the world’s number one digital currency has risen exponentially – don’t think the asset is moving in the right direction or think it’s doing as well as so many of their peers believe. Some<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/not-everyone-is-convinced-bitcoin-is-moving-in-the-right-direction/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/not-everyone-is-convinced-bitcoin-is-moving-in-the-right-direction/">Not Everyone Is Convinced Bitcoin Is Moving in the Right Direction</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has soared following the bank crisis that occurred earlier in the year, but many analysts – despite clear evidence that the world’s number one digital currency has risen exponentially – don’t think the asset is <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/03/31/technology/bitcoin-banks-crisis.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">moving in the right direction</a> or think it’s doing as well as so many of their peers believe.</p>
<h2>Some Don&#8217;t Think Bitcoin Is Doing That Well</h2>
<p>At the time of this article’s writing, the price of bitcoin is at about $28,000 per unit. This occurred after the world’s number one cryptocurrency lost more than 70 percent of its value. It was trading at a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit in November of 2021, though 12 short months later, it dropped into the mid-$16K range. 2022 was, arguably, the worst year on record for crypto.</p>
<p>However, now the currency is rising back up again, and this appears to be due, in part, to the banking <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-more-banks-fell-bitcoin-rose-beyond-28k/" data-wpel-link="internal">problems occurring in regions</a> like the U.S. and Europe. Silvergate, Silicon Valley Bank, and Signature Bank have all crashed and burned over the past two months, and things are still very much up in the air regarding the world of centralized finance.</p>
<p>Thus, many have turned to bitcoin and similar assets to keep their portfolios “intact.” Who would have thought that such speculative and once volatile assets would now be the answers so many individuals are turning to?</p>
<p>Still, things allegedly aren’t happening as fast as some analysts think they should be. Ed Moya, a crypto analyst at the trading firm OANDA, said in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Is there widespread interest in and growth coming into the space? Is it a lot of new money? It doesn’t really seem like that’s happening.</p></blockquote>
<p>Conor Ryder – research analyst for Kaiko – also threw his two cents into the mix, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>It doesn’t mean that because there’s a big price move one way that this is a whole new wave of institutional money or anything like that. It’s more so a liquidity issue.</p></blockquote>
<p>Initially, bitcoin was introduced in whitepaper form in 2008 on Halloween. The asset was designed to be an answer, of sorts, to the financial crisis and Great Recession that were occurring that year, but things haven’t really taken off the way they were supposed to. Moya continued his statement with:</p>
<blockquote><p>You’re seeing some flows just go out of stablecoins into bitcoin.</p></blockquote>
<p>Molly White – a known crypto critic – was also quick to suggest that the banking issues haven’t led to as many people as originally anticipated jumping into the BTC space. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>If the spike was fear-driven, I would have expected it to have started during the SVB bank run.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Others Feel the Asset Is in a Great Spot</h2>
<p>Cory Klippsten – chief executive at Swan Bitcoin – disagrees, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>They’re believers that this will be the global reserve currency. This is the best moment for bitcoin marketing and bitcoin adoption in its history.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/not-everyone-is-convinced-bitcoin-is-moving-in-the-right-direction/">Not Everyone Is Convinced Bitcoin Is Moving in the Right Direction</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/not-everyone-is-convinced-bitcoin-is-moving-in-the-right-direction/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Q1 of 2023 Was the Best Quarter for Bitcoin in 2 Years</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/q1-of-2023-was-the-best-quarter-for-bitcoin-in-2-years/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/q1-of-2023-was-the-best-quarter-for-bitcoin-in-2-years/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 15:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Callie Cox]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77717</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For bitcoin, 2023 has been a year of vast turnaround. A report was issued in late March showing that the world’s number one digital currency enjoyed three straight months of solid gains, and the asset doesn’t appear to be showing serious signs of slowing down. Bitcoin Has Had a Great Year Thus Far This is<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/q1-of-2023-was-the-best-quarter-for-bitcoin-in-2-years/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/q1-of-2023-was-the-best-quarter-for-bitcoin-in-2-years/">Q1 of 2023 Was the Best Quarter for Bitcoin in 2 Years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For bitcoin, 2023 has been a year of vast turnaround. A <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-heads-for-its-third-positive-month-in-a-row-after-fighting-off-us-banking-crisis-and-regulatory-crackdown/ar-AA19keX0" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report was issued</a> in late March showing that the world’s number one digital currency enjoyed three straight months of solid gains, and the asset doesn’t appear to be showing serious signs of slowing down.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Has Had a Great Year Thus Far</h2>
<p>This is a huge reversal of what was witnessed in 2022, obviously the worst year on record for crypto. The space wound up losing more than $2 trillion in valuation after assets like bitcoin lost 70 percent or more from their previous November 2021 all-time highs. During that period, bitcoin was trading at a whopping $68,000 per unit, though just 12 short months later, the currency dropped into the mid-$16K range. It was a sad sight to see.</p>
<p>But not long ago, the digital asset <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-more-banks-fell-bitcoin-rose-beyond-28k/" data-wpel-link="internal">enjoyed a nine-month high</a>, and March saw bitcoin extend its rally and price by more than 20 percent. This brings its overall jump since the beginning of the year to over 70 percent. This also marks the best quarter on record for bitcoin since early 2021, the beginning of a major bull run. Jeff Cantwell – an equity analyst at Wells Fargo – explained in a recent statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>The rally has continued in March even after recent bank closures. While the rebound has more than one underlying reason, our conversations with investors have centered on three: crypto as a &#8216;flight to safety&#8217; given banking turbulence; positioning (short covering); and a shift &#8216;at the margin&#8217; by investors to &#8216;risk on&#8217; as prospects of a Fed pivot have increased.</p></blockquote>
<p>It appears the banking crisis Cantwell is speaking of has done wonders for bitcoin. There’s so much distrust, suddenly, surrounding the world of standard finance that many have turned to more speculative (and riskier) assets like BTC as a means of keeping their financials safe. There’s no guarantee that the bank they work with is going to remain afloat, and thus bitcoin and various digital currencies suddenly seem like safer bets.</p>
<p>Callie Cox, an analyst at investment firm e-Toro, commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin still seems to be in a favorable light, but only if growth stays healthy as well. A recession could still pressure crypto prices considering it&#8217;s still such a retail-dominated asset, and high rates are still an obstacle… The banking news narrows the gap for a soft landing and increases the chance of seeing an extreme scenario in either direction.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Don&#8217;t Just Jump Back in Yet&#8230;</h2>
<p>She added:</p>
<blockquote><p>For now, it&#8217;s anybody&#8217;s guess how crypto weathers either extreme scenario – a recession or persistently high inflation. We&#8217;re seeing signs of some buying exhaustion, too – flows out of crypto exchange-traded products, bad reactions to good news. Crypto investors should still tread carefully. Bitcoin&#8217;s strong streak this year isn&#8217;t necessarily a green light to pile back in.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/q1-of-2023-was-the-best-quarter-for-bitcoin-in-2-years/">Q1 of 2023 Was the Best Quarter for Bitcoin in 2 Years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/q1-of-2023-was-the-best-quarter-for-bitcoin-in-2-years/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Report: Singapore Remains a Huge Crypto Haven Despite Trust Dips</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-singapore-remains-a-huge-crypto-haven-despite-trust-dips/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-singapore-remains-a-huge-crypto-haven-despite-trust-dips/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 13:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Singapore]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77714</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Independent Reserve Cryptocurrency Index claimed in a recent report that the digital currency world, despite taking several hits in the trust department, is still enjoying active trading among people in Singapore, who appear to be as steady in their investing as ever. Singapore Still Loves Crypto Crypto interest in Singapore once stood beyond the<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-singapore-remains-a-huge-crypto-haven-despite-trust-dips/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-singapore-remains-a-huge-crypto-haven-despite-trust-dips/">Report: Singapore Remains a Huge Crypto Haven Despite Trust Dips</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Independent Reserve Cryptocurrency Index claimed in a <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/pressreleases/23/03/n31570327/2023-independent-reserve-cryptocurrency-index-shows-singaporeans-are-still-actively-investing-in-c" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">recent report that</a> the digital currency world, despite taking several hits in the trust department, is still enjoying active trading among people in Singapore, who appear to be as steady in their investing as ever.</p>
<h2>Singapore Still Loves Crypto</h2>
<p>Crypto interest in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/singapore/" data-wpel-link="internal">Singapore</a> once stood beyond the 60 point mark, thus meaning digital currency was very popular within the nation and there were several individuals that trusted it and loved it as though it were on the same level as standard, fiat currency. Now, it appears that the mark has fallen to the 55 level. Thus, trust has dropped a little, but not enough to end the trading hype that’s clearly still occurring in the nation.</p>
<p>It’s estimated that about 44 percent of residents in Singapore – just shy of half the population – hold digital currency as part of their investment portfolios, while as many as 46 percent invest in crypto monthly. Lasanka Perera – chief executive officer of Independent Reserve Singapore – explained in a recent statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>2022 was a challenging time for the cryptocurrency industry due to several macroeconomic factors. The collapse of Terra-Luna and the FTX fallout has understandably led to a loss of confidence and trust in the industry. As recent global financial events continue to unfold, many may also re-evaluate their dependence on traditional financial institutions to safeguard their money and turn to alternative assets such as bitcoin to hedge against bank defaults and currency debasement. It is encouraging to see that optimism towards the long-term benefits of cryptocurrency remains strong in Singapore, and that investors who adopt a long-term view are reaping rewards… Singapore has one of the clearest and robust regulations for cryptocurrencies, which gives investors an added assurance of dealing with trusted players. As Singapore continues to remain open to innovation in digital assets, education remains crucial as awareness and adoption of cryptocurrencies among residents grow.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Awareness Is Going Up, Up, Up</h2>
<p>This year alone, the level of awareness surrounding crypto grew by more than one percent, suggesting that while most residents were previously obsessed with bitcoin, many have turned their attention to neighboring altcoins as a means of diversifying a bit more. Right now, people between the ages of 26 and 35 are the most aware of digital currency. Perera said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The rising popularity of altcoins shows that more Singaporeans are beginning to gain more awareness about other cryptocurrencies apart from bitcoin. This is a promising sign for the industry as more investors gain exposure to various types of blockchains and projects that have innovative utility and potential to be adopted more widely for real-world applications and use cases.</p></blockquote>
<p>Despite being a very bearish year, crypto adoption in Singapore rose three percent in 2022 from 40 to 43 percent.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-singapore-remains-a-huge-crypto-haven-despite-trust-dips/">Report: Singapore Remains a Huge Crypto Haven Despite Trust Dips</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-singapore-remains-a-huge-crypto-haven-despite-trust-dips/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
