<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 17:03:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Opinion: 2023 Is Already Looking Like Another 2019 for Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-2023-is-already-looking-like-another-2019-for-bitcoin/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-2023-is-already-looking-like-another-2019-for-bitcoin/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 17:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OpEd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76412</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At Live Bitcoin News, we’ve talked about how 2022 was reminiscent of 2018, which at one stage, was considered the worst year for bitcoin and crypto. We also mentioned that given the patterns and the similarities we were witnessing, it was possible (and even likely) that 2023 was going to be somewhat of a copy<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-2023-is-already-looking-like-another-2019-for-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-2023-is-already-looking-like-another-2019-for-bitcoin/">Opinion: 2023 Is Already Looking Like Another 2019 for Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>At <em>Live Bitcoin News</em>, we’ve talked <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-2022-is-2018-all-over-again-for-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">about how 2022</a> was reminiscent of 2018, which at one stage, was considered the worst year for bitcoin and crypto. We also mentioned that given the patterns and the similarities we were witnessing, it was possible (and even likely) that 2023 was going to be somewhat of a copy of 2019, which led to a touch of healing for most crypto fans.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Looks Like It&#8217;s Beginning to Heal</h2>
<p>While we’re only a few weeks in, we’re thus far being proven right as 2023 has given us a small surge in the BTC price that some traders are getting excited over.</p>
<p>The price of <a href="https://www.fxstreet.com/cryptocurrencies/news/btc-price-analysis-bitcoin-price-sees-bulls-taking-baby-steps-toward-19-000-202301091332" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">bitcoin shot up to about</a> $17,200 during the second week of January. This is not a huge deal when one considers BTC was trading for $68,000 per unit (its highest price ever) just over a year ago. At the same time, given what a disastrous run bitcoin has experienced over the past 12 months, this little jump to $17K is something that some of us can at least breathe a sigh of relief over. At this stage, all we can do is keep our fingers crossed and hope things continue along this path.</p>
<p>2022 was by far the worst period for crypto. Bitcoin, the world’s number one digital currency, began the year by enduring a series of dips from its previous $68,000 price and falling deeper into the doldrums. By January of that year, the currency had fallen by about $20,000 and was in the $40K range. Just a few months later, it was trading for $30K, and by the summer, the currency (quite scarily) fell below $18K albeit briefly. From there, it began to ascend the ladder to $20,000 again.</p>
<p>However, traders hadn’t seen the worst of bitcoin’s debacle as by the end of the year, the golden boy of the crypto space <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX would collapse</a> into a heap of bankruptcy and fraud, and bitcoin would take another Earth-shattering hit and fall into the $16K range, where it would end the year.</p>
<h2>Don&#8217;t Be Excited; Be Aware</h2>
<p>This small jump is nothing to be terribly enthused by, and traders are warned not to thrust themselves into the “bitcoin is recovering” mindset right away. However, they should keep an eye on the currency and be aware of the current patterns, as bitcoin already appears to be entering 2019 territory, as there were small snippets of correction that occurred throughout the first several months of that year.</p>
<p>If these trends continue, it’s likely bitcoin may end 2023 in the $30K range or something similar. We can’t forget that 2019 wasn’t necessarily the year of huge price runs, but rather a doorway to a year (2020) that delivered huge price runs, so while 2023 may be bitcoin’s wound-licking phase, we could see it hit the top again come 2024.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-2023-is-already-looking-like-another-2019-for-bitcoin/">Opinion: 2023 Is Already Looking Like Another 2019 for Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-2023-is-already-looking-like-another-2019-for-bitcoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gary Harmon, Larry Harmon&#8217;s Brother, Pleads Guilty to Crypto Theft</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gary-harmon-larry-harmons-brother-pleads-guilty-to-crypto-theft/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gary-harmon-larry-harmons-brother-pleads-guilty-to-crypto-theft/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 15:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Harmon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IRS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Larry Harmon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76410</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An Ohio native allegedly stole millions of dollars in bitcoin from the Internal Revenue Service (IRS). 31-year-old Gary Harmon has recently pled guilty to one count of wire fraud and a separate count of obstruction of justice after allegedly stealing more than 700 individual bitcoin units from the agency. Gary Harmon Pleads Guilty to Crypto<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gary-harmon-larry-harmons-brother-pleads-guilty-to-crypto-theft/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gary-harmon-larry-harmons-brother-pleads-guilty-to-crypto-theft/">Gary Harmon, Larry Harmon&#8217;s Brother, Pleads Guilty to Crypto Theft</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An Ohio native <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/brother-criminal-bitcoin-mixing-ceo-190220608.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">allegedly stole millions of dollars</a> in bitcoin from the Internal Revenue Service (IRS). 31-year-old Gary Harmon has recently pled guilty to one count of wire fraud and a separate count of obstruction of justice after allegedly stealing more than 700 individual bitcoin units from the agency.</p>
<h2>Gary Harmon Pleads Guilty to Crypto Theft and Wire Fraud</h2>
<p>The bitcoins in question were taken by law enforcement agents from Gary’s brother <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/larry-harmon/" data-wpel-link="internal">Larry Harmon</a>, who ran a darknet crypto mixing service called Helix. Larry was arrested in 2020 and his money was confiscated soon after.</p>
<p>In 2021, Larry Harmon pleaded guilty to one count of conspiracy to launder money. He was ordered to pay more than $60 million in penalties to the Financial Crimes Enforcement Network (FinCEN). He also entered a plea deal that required him to forfeit all the gains he’d earned and to serve as an active informant for government agencies. It’s unknown if his plea deal includes a prison sentence.</p>
<p>It seems that while Larry was working with the government to try and rid the world of future crime lords, his brother sought to take Larry’s place in the dark underworld of crypto fraud and take back all the digital units that had been confiscated. Gary was initially employed by Coin Ninja, one of Larry’s companies, and had been stealing digital assets from his brother’s wallets.</p>
<p>It is estimated that he took money from these wallets on at least eight separate occasions in April of 2020. These individual Trezor wallets which held the money that was later stolen were stored in a locker run by the IRS. The money was transferred to his own wallets and amounted to 712 bitcoins, which would be worth just shy of $5.5 million units at the time of writing.</p>
<p>Prosecutors said that Gary held the innocence card for a long time, claiming that he had never taken money from Larry’s wallets even when they presented him with evidence clearly showing that they knew of his activities. They also say that prior to taking all the money, Gary lived a very limited lifestyle and was collecting unemployment checks after his brother was arrested and he had been laid off from Coin Ninja.</p>
<h2>Living on the Dole to Living It Up</h2>
<p>To help with Larry’s trial, Gary said he had to set up a GoFundMe account to cover the family’s legal expenses and attorney fees. The page has since been taken down.</p>
<p>Once he had garnered the money from his brother’s accounts, he used roughly $1.2 million to purchase a new luxury condo in the city of Cleveland in his native Ohio. He also spent loads on private jet flights and on strip clubs. He has agreed to forfeit roughly $12 million in crypto but still faces 40 years in prison.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gary-harmon-larry-harmons-brother-pleads-guilty-to-crypto-theft/">Gary Harmon, Larry Harmon&#8217;s Brother, Pleads Guilty to Crypto Theft</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gary-harmon-larry-harmons-brother-pleads-guilty-to-crypto-theft/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nicholas Taleb Still Ain&#8217;t Crazy About Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nicholas-taleb-still-aint-crazy-about-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nicholas-taleb-still-aint-crazy-about-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 13:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nicholas Taleb]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76408</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin spent the early parts of January and the new year rising through the ranks and jumping beyond the $17K mark again. Everyone began to get a little excited about the currency’s prospects, but for hardcore critics like Nicholas Taleb – the author of the bestselling book The Black Swan – bitcoin is still a<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nicholas-taleb-still-aint-crazy-about-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nicholas-taleb-still-aint-crazy-about-crypto/">Nicholas Taleb Still Ain&#8217;t Crazy About Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin spent the early parts of January and the new year rising through the ranks and jumping beyond the $17K mark again. Everyone began to get a little excited about the currency’s prospects, but for hardcore critics like Nicholas Taleb – the author of the bestselling book <em>The Black Swan</em> – bitcoin is still a low-end trading tool that should be <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/gold-or-bitcoin-beware-the-malignant-tumor-says-black-swan-guru-nassim-nicholas-taleb/ar-AA166uB9" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">ignored and avoided</a> at all costs.</p>
<h2>Nicholas Taleb Still Hates BTC</h2>
<p>While bitcoin may be doing somewhat better at press time, it is still down more than 60 percent from its all-time high of $68,000 per unit, which it achieved in November of 2021. According to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nassim-nicholas-taleb-bitcoin-is-way-too-fragile/" data-wpel-link="internal">Taleb</a>, there are several problems with bitcoin, a big one being the following as he stated in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>We are not sure of the interests, mentalities, and preferences of future generations. Technology comes and goes, gold stays, at least physically. Once neglected for a brief period, bitcoin would necessarily collapse… It cannot be expected that an entry on a register that requires active maintenance by interested and motivated people – this is how bitcoin works – will retain its physical properties, a condition for monetary value, for any period.</p></blockquote>
<p>When questioned about what began the crypto craze in the first place, Taleb hinted that it’s likely the crypto industry comes from the very low interest rates Americans once enjoyed in the past. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Lowering rates creates asset bubbles without necessarily helping the economy. Capital no longer costs anything, risk-free returns on investment become too low, even negative, pushing people into speculation. We lose our sense of what a long-term investment is. It is the end of real finance.</p></blockquote>
<p>He mentioned that years of financial irresponsibility amongst former or past members of the Federal Reserve ultimately gave rise to bitcoin. He is critical, for example, of Ben Bernanke, who led the Fed during the time of the Great Recession, and he says that Bernanke failed to see the many red flags that were forming. When he did, he was too slow to react.</p>
<p>Taleb explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>Instead of correcting debt and mitigating hidden risks, he covered them with a monetary policy that was only supposed to be transitory. I wrongly thought bitcoin would be a bulwark against the distortions of this monetary policy.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Growing Haven for Scammers?</h2>
<p>Another big problem with crypto, in his mind, is that it has allegedly become a major haven for criminals and fraudulent activity. This is something that’s becoming harder to argue against given the collapse of FTX, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">which occurred at the</a> end of 2022.</p>
<p>Long considered the golden boy of the crypto space, it came to light that the company’s head executive Sam Bankman-Fried had purportedly utilized customer funds to engage in luxury Bahamian real estate purchases for himself and several other employees of the exchange.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nicholas-taleb-still-aint-crazy-about-crypto/">Nicholas Taleb Still Ain&#8217;t Crazy About Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nicholas-taleb-still-aint-crazy-about-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto and Blockchain Gaming sites and their Impact on Next Generation</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-and-blockchain-gaming-sites-and-their-impact-on-next-generation/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-and-blockchain-gaming-sites-and-their-impact-on-next-generation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 17:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76714</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The gaming industry is undergoing a rapid transformation as technology continues to advance at a rapid pace. This has led to an increase in the popularity and accessibility of digital gaming for players from all backgrounds. Amongst the digital gaming sectors that have seen a surge in popularity worldwide is that of crypto gambling sites.<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-and-blockchain-gaming-sites-and-their-impact-on-next-generation/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-and-blockchain-gaming-sites-and-their-impact-on-next-generation/">Crypto and Blockchain Gaming sites and their Impact on Next Generation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The gaming industry is undergoing a rapid transformation as technology continues to advance at a rapid pace. This has led to an increase in the popularity and accessibility of digital gaming for players from all backgrounds. Amongst the digital gaming sectors that have seen a surge in popularity worldwide is that of crypto gambling sites. These are online casinos and bookmakers that enable players to engage in gambling activities using cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin. This article delves into the ways in which crypto gambling sites are shaping the future of gaming and the opportunities they present for players across the globe. Cryptocurrency gambling sites like 1XBit, BitCasino, BC.Game, Betway, BitStarz, Stake and others are also known as online casinos, use cryptocurrencies as a mode of payment. This new form of gambling is built on blockchain technology, which provides several benefits over traditional online casinos. Crypto gambling sites are anonymous, secure, fast and offer lower fees and higher limits than traditional casinos. Additionally, they are also highly transparent as they are based on blockchain technology.</p>
<p><strong>Blockchain Technology and its Impact</strong></p>
<p>The different ways in which blockchain technology is impacting the gambling industry:</p>
<p>First, blockchain technology is providing a new method for individuals to engage in online gambling. Various online casinos now accept crypto as a form of payment / <a href="https://smartbettingguide.com/crypto-sports-betting/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Crypto Betting</a>, allowing players to gamble anonymously without the involvement of a third party.</p>
<p>Secondly, the way in which jackpots are distributed is also being transformed by blockchain technology. In the past, jackpots were typically paid out in fiat currency, however, with the integration of blockchain technology, jackpots can now be paid out in cryptocurrency. This allows for increased anonymity for the winners and eliminates the need for a middleman to hold and distribute the winnings.</p>
<p>Thirdly, blockchain technology is being utilized to develop new types of games. For instance, blockchain-based games now enable players to wager on the outcome of real-world events. This is made possible due to the secure and tamper-proof nature of blockchain technology, which allows for accurate tracking of bets and payouts.</p>
<p>In conclusion, it is evident that blockchain technology is having a significant impact on the gambling industry. It offers new methods for online gambling, revolutionizes the way jackpots are paid out, and creates new types of games.</p>
<p>It is evident that blockchain technology is having a significant impact on the gambling industry. This revolutionary technology is providing new opportunities for players to engage in online gambling, transforming the way in which jackpots are paid out, and enabling the creation of novel types of games. Blockchain technology is introducing new possibilities in the gambling industry and is changing the way people gamble online. It is providing players with new ways to gamble anonymously, new ways to claim and receive their winnings and also new types of games to play that were not possible before. Overall, blockchain technology is bringing a major shift in the gambling industry and is shaping the future of online gambling.</p>
<p><strong>The Rise in Cryptocurrency Based Games<br />
</strong><br />
The demand for games that utilize cryptocurrencies as a form of payment is on the rise. These cryptocurrency-based games offer several benefits over traditional games, making them increasingly popular among players. Firstly, they can be played from any location in the world, as they do not require a bank account or credit card. Additionally, these games are often more secure as they utilize blockchain technology to safeguard player data. Finally, they often have lower fees compared to traditional games, making them more financially accessible to players. Overall, the popularity of <a href="https://www.btcwires.com/c-buzz/will-cryptocurrency-replace-traditional-currency-in-gambling/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">cryptocurrency-based games</a> is increasing as they provide players with more flexibility, security and cost-effectiveness.</p>
<p><strong>Enhanced Gaming Experience<br />
</strong><br />
The top crypto gambling sites are offering an unparalleled player experience by utilizing the latest technology. They provide a wide range of features that traditional online casinos cannot match, making the gaming experience more immersive and engaging. One of the most noteworthy examples is the integration of 3D graphics, which provides a much more realistic gaming experience. Additionally, the use of virtual reality (VR) technology, which is still in its early stages, has the potential to further enhance the gaming experience. Another area where crypto gambling sites excel is in customer service, by offering live chat and 24/7 support, they ensure that players have access to assistance at all times for any issues or queries they may have. Overall, crypto gambling sites are setting the standard for player experience by utilizing the latest technology and providing superior customer service.</p>
<p><strong>Innovating Players Incentivisation<br />
</strong><br />
Online crypto gambling sites are revolutionizing the way players are incentivized, by introducing new and innovative rewards and loyalty programs. While traditional online casinos primarily rely on bonuses and promotions to attract new players and retain existing ones, crypto gambling sites are taking it to a whole new level. They are using rewards and loyalty programs to incentivize players by offering rewards for playing, making deposits, and referring friends. The more a player engages in these activities, the more points they earn, which can be redeemed for cash, prizes, or bonuses. This creates a mutually beneficial situation for both the players and the casinos, as players receive more value for their money and casinos gain more loyal and active customers. This is one of the many ways that crypto gambling sites are innovating the online gambling industry.</p>
<p><strong>Overall Gaming Experience </strong></p>
<p>The emergence of crypto gambling sites has had a significant impact on the gaming industry. Traditional online casinos are facing pressure to adapt or risk losing relevance. Many are beginning to accept cryptocurrency as a payment method, and some are even launching their own crypto gambling sites. The influence of crypto gambling sites is being felt across the entire gaming industry, from game developers to platform providers. And this trend is expected to continue to grow in popularity in the future.</p>
<p><strong>To Summarize</strong></p>
<p>Crypto gambling sites are considered to be the future of online gambling. They provide numerous benefits over traditional online casinos, and their popularity is expected to continue to increase. If you are seeking the ultimate online gambling experience, then it is recommended to explore the options provided by a crypto gambling site</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-and-blockchain-gaming-sites-and-their-impact-on-next-generation/">Crypto and Blockchain Gaming sites and their Impact on Next Generation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-and-blockchain-gaming-sites-and-their-impact-on-next-generation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Police Seize Nearly $2 Million in Crypto from New Zealand Drug Dealers</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/police-seize-nearly-2-million-in-crypto-from-new-zealand-drug-dealers/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/police-seize-nearly-2-million-in-crypto-from-new-zealand-drug-dealers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 17:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New Zealand]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76382</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto crime was a big deal in 2022, and while we’re only a few weeks into 2023, it looks like the trend is continuing after a criminal gang crackdown that resulted in close to $2 million in assets – some of which were crypto units – being seized by law enforcement officials. Crypto Crime Takes<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/police-seize-nearly-2-million-in-crypto-from-new-zealand-drug-dealers/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/police-seize-nearly-2-million-in-crypto-from-new-zealand-drug-dealers/">Police Seize Nearly $2 Million in Crypto from New Zealand Drug Dealers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto crime was a big deal in 2022, and while we’re only a few weeks into 2023, it looks like the trend is continuing after a criminal gang crackdown that resulted in close to $2 million in assets – some of which were crypto units – <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-nz/news/national/cryptocurrency-nfts-among-almost-dollar2m-worth-of-assets-seized-in-huge-gang-bust/ar-AA15WNwk" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">being seized by law enforcement</a> officials.</p>
<h2>Crypto Crime Takes on a New Form</h2>
<p>Two men have allegedly been arrested in New Zealand for taking part in various drug dealings. Police came barging into the home they were both living in and seized roughly $1.9 million in various assets. Among them were, according to arrest statements, digital currencies and NFTs.</p>
<p>The pair – both aged 28 – were part of a group of six men that were all taken into custody for assorted drug offenses. They now face a series of charges including participating in organized crime and selling and supplying class A and B drugs.</p>
<p>Waikato/Bay of Plenty Asset Recovery Unit Detective Senior Sergeant Keith Kay explained in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Police secured restraining orders for these assets pursuant to the Criminal Proceeds (Recovery) Act [of] 2009. Methamphetamine and other illicit drugs cause immense harm across our communities and are the drivers of crime, creating victims and distress throughout society. The Criminal Proceeds (Recovery) Act enables police to not only recover criminal proceeds, but [it] also prevents criminals from reinvesting the proceeds of their crime to cause more harm.</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition to the money and crypto that was taken, the Hamilton High Court has ordered that the men’s home – which is presently valued at close to $700K – be restrained. Police also confiscated several vehicles including a Harley Davidson motorcycle worth approximately $47,000 at press time.</p>
<p>While situations like these are not necessarily uncommon, crypto crime has – over the past few years – taken on different forms. For example, there have been many examples <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/romance-scam/" data-wpel-link="internal">of romance scams</a> in recent months, where fraudsters take on the form of individuals looking for love online. They snag victims and over time, convince them to begin engaging in crypto trades and investing on digital asset exchanges they control.</p>
<p>From there, the victims see their investments growing and they get excited, but when they try to make withdrawals, they can’t unless they’re willing to put more money into the platforms. Often, they never see their money again.</p>
<h2>FTX Has Set the New Precedent</h2>
<p>One of the biggest examples of crypto crime in recent history came in the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">shape of FTX</a>, the fallen crypto exchange run by now former executive Sam Bankman-Fried. Coming to fruition in 2019, the exchange is <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-ftx-exec-sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-fraud/" data-wpel-link="internal">believed to have been a haven</a> for fraud as SBF is accused of utilizing customer funds to pay off loans accepted by his other company Alameda Research.</p>
<p>In addition, he is alleged to have purchased luxury Bahamian real estate with users’ money.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/police-seize-nearly-2-million-in-crypto-from-new-zealand-drug-dealers/">Police Seize Nearly $2 Million in Crypto from New Zealand Drug Dealers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/police-seize-nearly-2-million-in-crypto-from-new-zealand-drug-dealers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Abhinav R. Soomaney Has Written a New Crypto Taxation Book</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/abhinav-r-soomaney-has-written-a-new-crypto-taxation-book/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/abhinav-r-soomaney-has-written-a-new-crypto-taxation-book/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 15:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abhinav R. Soomaney]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Andrew Yang]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto-taxation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76380</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Author and crypto expert Abhinav R. Soomaney has a new book out called “Cryptocurrency in a Nutshell.” In the composition, Soomaney discusses a big topic in the crypto space: taxation. A New Crypto Tax Book By Abhinav R. Soomaney Taxation in crypto has often been talked about amongst even the most knowledgeable analysts given tax<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/abhinav-r-soomaney-has-written-a-new-crypto-taxation-book/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/abhinav-r-soomaney-has-written-a-new-crypto-taxation-book/">Abhinav R. Soomaney Has Written a New Crypto Taxation Book</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Author and crypto expert Abhinav R. Soomaney has a <a href="https://www.laweekly.com/author-abhinav-r-soomaney-examines-cryptocurrency-industry-and-tax-saving-tips-in-amazon-best-selling-new-book/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">new book out called</a> “Cryptocurrency in a Nutshell.” In the composition, Soomaney discusses a big topic in the crypto space: taxation.</p>
<h2>A New Crypto Tax Book By Abhinav R. Soomaney</h2>
<p>Taxation in crypto has often been talked about amongst even the most knowledgeable analysts given tax protocols within the arena’s borders can be quite complicated. In fact, during the 2020 election, there were two democrat candidates – <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/michael-bloomberg/" data-wpel-link="internal">Michael Bloomberg</a>, the former New York City mayor, and entrepreneur <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/andrew-yang-the-crypto-president/" data-wpel-link="internal">Andrew Yang</a> – that claimed they would make the crypto taxation laws in America easier to understand. This was one of the big staples of their campaigns. That’s how difficult crypto taxation laws can be.</p>
<p>Neither of these candidates were able to get very far given at the time, crypto was still not a major topic amongst the public or politicians like it is today. However, if Soomaney can publish an entire book on the subject, you know things are getting real, and crypto taxation is becoming something that many more people are now curious about.</p>
<p>In the book, Soomaney says one of the big things that often increase tax obligations is when traders shift from long term to short-term trading. While this can ultimately minimize capital gains, it can make things far more noticeable to agencies like the IRS. He writes:</p>
<blockquote><p>Minimize capital gains by using the highest-in-first-out tax calculation method that allows you to use the highest cost basis pool against the first sale until that inventory pool is completely exhausted. Maintaining accurate records for tokens transferred from one platform to another will help to determine whether the capital gain is short-term capital gain or long-term capital gain and accurately report taxes.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also advises crypto investors to look at several money-saving strategies and not just get stuck on one. He writes:</p>
<blockquote><p>Do not store all tokens in one wallet. Split [them] between multiple exchanges and wallets to avoid complete loss, especially when exchanges like FTX/Celsius crash or liquidate.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Trying to Help as Best He Can</h2>
<p>In an interview, he stated that one of the big problems with the way crypto is taxed in the United States is that very few regulations and guidelines exist to help people fully understand what they’re getting into before they begin trading or purchasing assets. He ultimately wrote the book to explain blockchain technology further and help newbie investors as best he could. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>With very limited government guidelines, every step of the crypto tax space can be looked at as a challenge, but we as crypto tax experts try our best to find a solution for all clients tailored to their needs.</p></blockquote>
<p>The book also contains special references to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/satoshi-nakamoto/" data-wpel-link="internal">Satoshi Nakamoto</a>, the man purportedly behind the creation of the world’s number one digital currency by market cap.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/abhinav-r-soomaney-has-written-a-new-crypto-taxation-book/">Abhinav R. Soomaney Has Written a New Crypto Taxation Book</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/abhinav-r-soomaney-has-written-a-new-crypto-taxation-book/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Litecoin Could Make a Serious Comeback in 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/why-litecoin-could-make-a-serious-comeback-in-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/why-litecoin-could-make-a-serious-comeback-in-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 13:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76378</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>2022 was a crazy year for bitcoin and cryptocurrency. With all the talk regarding the fall of bitcoin’s price and value, it became easy to forget about some of the more obscure coins. Now, many of those assets are coming back into the fray, including Litecoin, which many analysts think is about to make a<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/why-litecoin-could-make-a-serious-comeback-in-2023/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/why-litecoin-could-make-a-serious-comeback-in-2023/">Why Litecoin Could Make a Serious Comeback in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>2022 was a crazy year for bitcoin and cryptocurrency. With all the talk regarding the fall of bitcoin’s price and value, it became easy to forget about some of the more obscure coins. Now, many of those assets are coming back into the fray, including Litecoin, which many analysts think is about to make a major comeback and become one of the biggest, <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-in/money/topstories/the-lit-cryptocurrency-why-litecoin-is-the-next-big-thing-in-the-making/ar-AA15ZpGO" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">most talked about assets</a> of the new year.</p>
<h2>Litecoin Is Back, Baby!</h2>
<p>One of the reasons <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/litecoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">Litecoin</a> is returning to everyone’s attention at this time is because it appears to be one of the few digital currencies that hasn’t been affected by the fall of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">crypto exchange FTX</a>. In fact, not long after the platform crashed and burned, the mysterious altcoin rose by more than 35 percent and hit a peak of about $81. This is huge considering most other altcoins and bitcoin itself were falling into the doldrums.</p>
<p>Prashant Kumar – the founder and CEO of We Trade, a cryptocurrency platform – said in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>LTC is a peer-to-peer cryptocurrency and open-source platform that has been created from the BTC blockchain. While it may have similarities with BTC, LTC has a different algorithm and maximum supply. The altcoin has seen some volatility in 2022 and would hope for [a] breakthrough in pricing this year.</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition, it appears Litecoin is being adopted like crazy by merchants far more than they are even adopting bitcoin. NerdWallet shows that more than 42 million Litecoin-based transactions occurred in 2021 alone as it is labeled a stronger medium of exchange when compared to its daddy BTC.</p>
<p>Amanjot Malhotra – the head of the Indian crypto exchange Bitay – said in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>In terms of importance in [the] cryptocurrency industry, I believe LTC has played a role in helping to popularize the use of cryptocurrency and has served as a testbed for new features that have later been implemented in other cryptocurrencies. For example, LTC was the first cryptocurrency to implement Segregated Witness (Seg Wit), which is a protocol that improves the scalability and security of the blockchain.</p></blockquote>
<p>Several other exchanges – including big names like Coinbase, Kraken, and Binance – have also permitted Litecoin transactions and trades since the beginning. This has led to a product called Liteverse, which is believed to be the first Litecoin centered non-fungible token (NFT) on the market.</p>
<h2>Will More Businesses Seek to Use the Coin?</h2>
<p>Sathvik Vishwanath – co-founder and CEO of crypto exchange Uno Coin – said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Global sectors that could potentially benefit from LTC include e-commerce, cross-border payments, and [the] financial industry. LTC could benefit the decentralized finance (defi) landscape by providing an alternative to Ethereum, which is currently the dominant platform for defi applications.</p></blockquote>
<p>At the time of writing, it’s believed that more businesses are going to demand Litecoin usage in 2023.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/why-litecoin-could-make-a-serious-comeback-in-2023/">Why Litecoin Could Make a Serious Comeback in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/why-litecoin-could-make-a-serious-comeback-in-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Opinion: Congress Should Not Be Permitted to Engage in Crypto Trading</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-congress-should-not-be-permitted-to-engage-in-crypto-trading/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-congress-should-not-be-permitted-to-engage-in-crypto-trading/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 17:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Congress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76376</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With January having arrived, the new Congress has convened. While at the time of writing, the House of Representatives is still struggling to elect or even nominate a republican speaker, we can rest assured that things are going to go quite well for crypto in the coming months and that the country is now well<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-congress-should-not-be-permitted-to-engage-in-crypto-trading/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-congress-should-not-be-permitted-to-engage-in-crypto-trading/">Opinion: Congress Should Not Be Permitted to Engage in Crypto Trading</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With January having arrived, the new Congress has convened. While at the time of writing, the House of Representatives is still struggling to elect or even <a href="https://www.dailysignal.com/2023/01/04/round-four-still-no-speaker-house/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">nominate a republican speaker</a>, we can rest assured that things are going to go quite well for crypto in the coming months and that the country is now well on its way towards garnering a small bit of healing from all the trouble it’s been through since Biden entered the fray.</p>
<h2>Congress Needs to Stay Out of Crypto</h2>
<p>One of the big things this new Congress is expected to vote on is <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-in/money/markets/united-states-lawmakers-expected-to-prohibit-stock-and-crypto-trading-in-upcoming-congress-session/ar-AA15Uzkw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">crypto and stock trading</a> amongst lawmakers. Congress has long been talking about such a maneuver, but it’s failed to really act on it, likely because one of the main reasons that members of Congress even get <a href="https://www.rt.com/op-ed/545848-us-politicians-trading-stocks-bill/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">rich is because they are</a> privy to stock information prior to members of the public.</p>
<p>With this knowledge, they can sell or buy before anyone else and add hefty sums to their portfolios. In many ways, this is insider trading, and if any everyday citizen was to take part in such activity, they would likely be arrested and jailed. Insider trading has always been a crime, and this serves as another clear example of the hypocrisy and jaded rules that cloud Washington.</p>
<p>But this time, there is genuine hope the new Congress will do the right thing and ensure that no regulator – whether they be a senator or a member of the House – be permitted to engage in either crypto or stock trades while they sit in office. They can trade items all they want, but they need to vacate their seats if they are going to take part in such activity.</p>
<h2>Too Many Opportunities for Criminality</h2>
<p>In 2022, the world of crypto came crashing down when it was announced that the space’s golden boy FTX was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">filing bankruptcy</a> and that Sam Bankman-Fried <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-ftx-exec-sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-fraud/" data-wpel-link="internal">was going to face trial</a> for fraud. One of the scary points of this story is that SBF is alleged to have given <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-gave-a-lot-of-money-to-democrats-what-will-they-do-with-it/" data-wpel-link="internal">donations to many politicians</a> (primarily democrats) in the form of user funds. As it turns out, even after the arrest of SBF, many of these politicians have refused to say if they are going to give the money back.</p>
<p>This situation alone should be enough to convince incoming lawmakers that politics and crypto don’t go together. There is no way all these politicians – given their close ties to FTX and SBF – didn’t see what was going on with the exchange. This was clearly a mark of criminality in both the crypto space and in the U.S. government, and if lawmakers are to remain in power, they must focus less on using their power to get rich and more on assisting the people they were hired to serve.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-congress-should-not-be-permitted-to-engage-in-crypto-trading/">Opinion: Congress Should Not Be Permitted to Engage in Crypto Trading</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-congress-should-not-be-permitted-to-engage-in-crypto-trading/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Andy Greenberg Is Publishing a New Book on BTC&#8217;s Traceability</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/andy-greenberg-is-publishing-a-new-book-on-btcs-traceability/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/andy-greenberg-is-publishing-a-new-book-on-btcs-traceability/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 15:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Andy Greenberg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[traceability]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76374</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Andy Greenberg – a technology journalist – has a new book coming out called “Tracers in the Dark: The Global Hunt for the Crime Lords of Cryptocurrency.” Andy Greenberg Has a New BTC Book Coming Out The book details the early 2021 incident in which the Colonial Pipeline was hacked by cyberthieves who demanded bitcoin<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/andy-greenberg-is-publishing-a-new-book-on-btcs-traceability/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/andy-greenberg-is-publishing-a-new-book-on-btcs-traceability/">Andy Greenberg Is Publishing a New Book on BTC&#8217;s Traceability</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Andy Greenberg – a technology journalist – <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/criminals-thought-crypto-was-untraceable-they-were-wrong/ar-AA15M9ve" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">has a new book coming</a> out called “Tracers in the Dark: The Global Hunt for the Crime Lords of Cryptocurrency.”</p>
<h2>Andy Greenberg Has a New BTC Book Coming Out</h2>
<p>The book details the early 2021 incident in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fbi-halts-bitcoin-ransomware-attack-on-colonial-pipeline/" data-wpel-link="internal">which the Colonial Pipeline</a> was hacked by cyberthieves who demanded bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies in exchange for its release. The Department of Justice (DOJ) was able to recover half of the payment that was sent and take the funds back, thus resulting in the thieves receiving a lot less money than they had anticipated.</p>
<p>The book is a testament to the traceability of crypto, which is often labeled as anonymous and immune to prying eyes. Greenberg claims this is not true and discusses the matter in detail in the book.</p>
<p>He explained that the way the traceability happens is when agencies collapse bitcoin addresses into single identities. He says there are certain patterns that occur on the blockchain, even when transactors utilize multiple addresses to send or receive crypto funds, and that organizations such as the DOJ are now able to read those patterns with greater ease and discover who the money is going to and who it’s coming from. They can then intercede if necessary.</p>
<p>In the book, Greenberg writes:</p>
<blockquote><p>In bitcoin, for good and for ill, everyone was witness to every payment… [which] offered an enormous collection of data to analyze. Who could say what sorts of patterns might give away users who thought they were cleverer than those watching them?</p></blockquote>
<p>One of the big “characters” in the book is a woman named Sarah Meiklejohn, who studied at the University of California at San Diego in 2011. Working to get her PhD, Sarah heard about bitcoin while focusing on privacy research, and she became intrigued by the technology behind it.</p>
<h2>Finding the Patterns</h2>
<p>In taking a broader look at the blockchain, she was able to decipher many of the patterns that the book discusses and that agencies like the Department of Justice are now able to utilize when studying criminal activity. Greenberg writes:</p>
<blockquote><p>She scanned her blockchain database for every multi-input transaction, linking all those double, triple, or even hundredfold inputs to single identities. The result immediately reduced the number of potential bitcoin users from twelve million to date to around five million, slicing away more than half of the problem… Many bitcoin wallets only allowed spenders to pay the entire [number] of coins sitting at a certain address. Each address was like a piggy bank that [must] be smashed open to spend the coin inside. Spend less than the whole amount in that piggy bank and the leftovers [must] be stored in a newly created piggy bank.</p></blockquote>
<p>Crypto crime has become a much larger subject following the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">fall of FTX</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/andy-greenberg-is-publishing-a-new-book-on-btcs-traceability/">Andy Greenberg Is Publishing a New Book on BTC&#8217;s Traceability</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/andy-greenberg-is-publishing-a-new-book-on-btcs-traceability/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
