<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 16:51:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Mark Mobius Says Bitcoin Could Fall to $10K</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-mobius-calls-btc-dangerous-and-says-it-could-fall-to-10k/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-mobius-calls-btc-dangerous-and-says-it-could-fall-to-10k/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 17:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mark Mobius]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75861</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The price of bitcoin has taken several hard hits over the past 14 months, but according to legendary investor Mark Mobius, he thinks things are going to get a lot worse before they get better. In fact, he sees the world’s number one digital currency by market cap falling to a new low of $10K<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-mobius-calls-btc-dangerous-and-says-it-could-fall-to-10k/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-mobius-calls-btc-dangerous-and-says-it-could-fall-to-10k/">Mark Mobius Says Bitcoin Could Fall to $10K</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price of bitcoin has taken several hard hits over the past 14 months, but according to legendary investor Mark Mobius, he thinks things are <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/mark-mobius-sees-bitcoin-down-at-2410000-in-e2-80-98dangerous-e2-80-99-crypto-market/ar-AA14DirI" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">going to get a lot</a> worse before they get better. In fact, he sees the world’s number one digital currency by market cap falling to a new low of $10K before it begins its rebound.</p>
<h2>Mark Mobius Isn&#8217;t Crazy About Bitcoin</h2>
<p>Mobius has never been a bitcoin fan. At times, he’s referred to it in rather derogatory ways, even calling it a “psycho” currency in the year 2019. <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-mobius-calls-bitcoin-a-psycho-currency/" data-wpel-link="internal">During that era</a>, he expressed his thoughts on BTC, claiming he didn’t trust it as its price spikes weren’t based on anything except hardcore speculation. He said the only thing keeping BTC up was the belief it had from average investors, and he hinted that should that ever die down (like it is now), BTC would soon find itself in the can.</p>
<p>He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I call them psycho currencies because it’s a matter of faith whether you believe in bitcoin or any of the other cybercurrencies… I think with the rise of [bitcoin], there’s going to be a demand for real, hard assets, and that includes gold.</p></blockquote>
<p>Now, over three years later, his sentiment hasn’t changed much, though he <em>did</em> mention that even with the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">recent fall of FTX</a> and the ongoing bearish trends witnessed in today’s crypto market, he doesn’t feel bitcoin is going to disappear completely. Rather, while he believes it may continue to go down in price, he thinks it’s held up rather well given all it’s been through in the last year.</p>
<p>He claimed in a more recent appearance:</p>
<blockquote><p>But crypto is here to stay as there are several investors who still have faith in it. It’s amazing how bitcoin prices have held up.</p></blockquote>
<p>Despite this little note of positivity, he was quick to mention that he would never invest any money of his own into BTC or other cryptocurrencies, citing them as “too dangerous.”</p>
<h2>The Worst Year for Crypto?</h2>
<p>2022 will likely go down as one of the worst years – if not <em>the worst year</em> – for bitcoin. In November 2021, the currency reached a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit. It felt like the currency was on a ladder that could never topple, but these thoughts were proven wrong as soon as the new year came into play.</p>
<p>From there, the asset endured a long series of price dips that eventually saw it lose more than 70 percent of its overall value. The currency dropped into the mid-$16K range, and while a few small rallies occurred here and there, many traders and analysts tried to warn others that getting too excited early was a big mistake. Overall, crypto space lost more than $2 trillion in valuation in 2022.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-mobius-calls-btc-dangerous-and-says-it-could-fall-to-10k/">Mark Mobius Says Bitcoin Could Fall to $10K</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-mobius-calls-btc-dangerous-and-says-it-could-fall-to-10k/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>All in Web3? Where will BTC go in 2023? FAMEEX united 9 projects hosted a popular Twitter Space with users.</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/all-in-web3-where-will-btc-go-in-2023-fameex-united-9-projects-hosted-a-popular-twitter-space-with-users/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/all-in-web3-where-will-btc-go-in-2023-fameex-united-9-projects-hosted-a-popular-twitter-space-with-users/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 16:51:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76420</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>After the crypto market crash in 2022, BTC supporters and crypto investors are left wondering where the market will go in 2023 and while enduring the massive loss. Will Web3 drive a resurgence in the crypto industry? Will DAO become the preferred form of alternative corporate organization? On January 9, 2023, FAMEEX held a popular<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/all-in-web3-where-will-btc-go-in-2023-fameex-united-9-projects-hosted-a-popular-twitter-space-with-users/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/all-in-web3-where-will-btc-go-in-2023-fameex-united-9-projects-hosted-a-popular-twitter-space-with-users/">All in Web3? Where will BTC go in 2023? FAMEEX united 9 projects hosted a popular Twitter Space with users.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After the crypto market crash in 2022, BTC supporters and crypto investors are left wondering where the market will go in 2023 and while enduring the massive loss. Will Web3 drive a resurgence in the crypto industry? Will DAO become the preferred form of alternative corporate organization? On January 9, 2023, FAMEEX held a popular Twitter space with several projects to discuss the future of Web3. Nearly 500 users participated in the discussion, including Cybermartians, Damn It, Randverse, Reitio, EtherPOAP, Flappy Moonbird, Freename, 3WW3, and other major projects. The discussion resulted in the identification of potential opportunities for growth in Web3 in the areas of GameFi, DAO, and SocialFi in 2023.</p>
<p>“Actually 2022 is a hard year for crypto, NFT and BTC sharp rise brought numerous new users to the industry but now they are suffering the pain of crypto crash. From the series of major events triggered by the Luna crashed to the collapse of FTX exchange, the industry will definitely go to a healthier and more compliant future. The bear market is still not over, but the bull market will definitely come back, and the next bull cycle will probably start at the end of 2023,” FAMEEX India Market Manager EthAn said.</p>
<p><strong>About FAMEEX Exchange</strong></p>
<p>FAMEEX has established itself over the past 2 years in the crypto derivatives market and is consistently operating in the futures trading broker sector. Always Following the philosophy of &#8220;Secure global crypto exchange with quantitative trading&#8221;, FAMEEX aims to offer its users comprehensive and secure trading solutions, integrating decentralized finance (DeFi) with centralized finance (CeFi) in the futures roadmap.</p>
<p>One key difference between FAMEEX and other exchanges is that FAMEEX focuses on providing opportunities and benefits to new users. This includes campaigns and activities that can help users earn without taking on any risk.</p>
<p>One example of how FAMEEX sets itself apart from other exchanges is by offering opportunities for users to become our ambassadors and receive top rebate commissions,more than 500USDT/M. To apply, users can direct message the FAMEEX marketing team on Telegram (@MKT_FAMEEX). FAMEEX also provides funding for new users to experience the platform without having to invest their own money, and offers opportunities for marketing professionals to become our local agents and connect with influencers, communities, and YouTubers. These privileges and opportunities provide unique benefits for FAMEEX users and help the exchange stand out in a crowded market.</p>
<p>Additionally, all users can participate in the campaigns and activities designed by FAMEEX, which can help them experience without taking on any risk. This focus on providing opportunities and benefits to users sets FAMEEX apart from other exchanges and allows it to compete effectively in a crowded market.</p>
<p>Currently, FAMEEX has users in over 50 countries and is undergoing rapid expansion of the userbase. FAMEEX co-founder explained, &#8220;Despite the recent macro downturn, the market is still rife with growth opportunity. Our strategy for the future incorporates numerous developments in tokenomics and we foresee a key role for enabling web3 in the next transformation of FAMEEX.&#8221;</p>
<p>FAMEEX is a reliable crypto exchange broker which operates under a policy of transparency and fairness. Moreover, the trading platform offers a high level of sophistication, with plenty of engaging trade choices to help traders accomplish their goals.</p>
<p><strong>Find Out More about FAMEEX</strong></p>
<p>Launched in 2020. FAMEEX is a global cryptocurrency exchange that currently provides fiat-crypto, crypto-crypto, grid trading, futures, margin, spot and a hugely popular referral and affiliate program. With more than 200,000 users across 50 countries and regions we provide a secure, stable and efficient 24/7 trading platform.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/all-in-web3-where-will-btc-go-in-2023-fameex-united-9-projects-hosted-a-popular-twitter-space-with-users/">All in Web3? Where will BTC go in 2023? FAMEEX united 9 projects hosted a popular Twitter Space with users.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/all-in-web3-where-will-btc-go-in-2023-fameex-united-9-projects-hosted-a-popular-twitter-space-with-users/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sam Bankman-Fried Makes Rare Appearance Following FTX Collapse</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-makes-rare-appearance-following-ftx-collapse/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-makes-rare-appearance-following-ftx-collapse/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 15:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75858</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sam Bankman-Fried – the disgraced founder of fallen digital currency exchange FTX – made a rare appearance at the Deal Book Summit in New York on the last day of November last year. Sam Bankman-Fried Does First Interview Following Company&#8217;s Demise While he did not arrive in person, Bankman-Fried was featured prominently on a screen<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-makes-rare-appearance-following-ftx-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-makes-rare-appearance-following-ftx-collapse/">Sam Bankman-Fried Makes Rare Appearance Following FTX Collapse</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sam Bankman-Fried – the disgraced founder of fallen digital currency exchange FTX – made a rare appearance at the Deal Book Summit in New York <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/sam-bankman-fried-former-ceo-of-ftx-says-we-messed-up-big/ar-AA14KURn" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">on the last day of November</a> last year.</p>
<h2>Sam Bankman-Fried Does First Interview Following Company&#8217;s Demise</h2>
<p>While he did not arrive in person, Bankman-Fried was featured prominently on a screen from an undisclosed location in the Bahamas, where he still claims to live.</p>
<p>In the interview, Bankman-Fried attempted to explain what happened with his exchange in his own words. It is believed that much of the money stationed in FTX and his other company Alameda Research was commingled or mixed, and that this ultimately helped contribute to the downfall. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I didn’t knowingly commingle funds… I wasn’t running Alameda. I didn’t know what was going on. A lot of the things were things I learned over the last month.</p></blockquote>
<p>At times, Sam Bankman-Fried appeared to express remorse about everything that happened. He mentioned casually to the audience:</p>
<blockquote><p>Look, I screwed up. I was the CEO of FTX. I say this again and again. That means I had a responsibility. We messed up big.</p></blockquote>
<p>At the same time, there were several other moments throughout the event where he seemed to deny he was responsible for anything. He also appeared to suggest that he shouldn’t face any direct repercussions for what occurred. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think I was scared. I was nervous because of the conflict of interest.</p></blockquote>
<p>He further said that while his lawyers believed doing any interviews would be a mistake, he felt it was the right move to make and stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I have a duty to explain what happened, and I have a duty to try to help [customers].</p></blockquote>
<p>He also clarified where he got much of the money that eventually went to the many democrat <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-billionaire-sam-bankman-fried-spends-big-in-the-name-of-politics/" data-wpel-link="internal">politicians that he funded</a> in both 2020 and 2022. He claimed in the interview that all the funds came directly from the company’s profits.</p>
<p>There are still many unanswered questions surrounding FTX, but one thing is for sure. There are several people that have suffered because of the company’s collapse, and the problems at hand probably aren’t quite over.</p>
<h2>The Drama of FTX</h2>
<p>Trouble for FTX first appeared in mid-November of last year. The company reported on social media that it was experiencing a “<a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">liquidity crunch</a>” and needed cash fast. From there, Bankman-Fried approached Binance – his larger rival – about a possible bailout, but this failed from the get-go, with the larger exchange claiming FTX’s <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">issues were too big</a> for it to handle.</p>
<p>From there, FTX <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">was forced to file bankruptcy</a> and Sam Bankman-Fried resigned from his post. The company’s collapse has sent waves throughout the space and has caused many other firms – such as <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block-fi-is-the-latest-crypto-company-to-go-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">lending platform Block Fi</a> – to follow in its footsteps.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-makes-rare-appearance-following-ftx-collapse/">Sam Bankman-Fried Makes Rare Appearance Following FTX Collapse</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-makes-rare-appearance-following-ftx-collapse/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Opinion: Has the FTX Crash Exposed a Government Conspiracy?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-did-the-ftx-fall-expose-a-government-conspiracy/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-did-the-ftx-fall-expose-a-government-conspiracy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 13:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75853</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FTX is likely to go down as one of the biggest embarrassments in the history of crypto. More than that, as additional layers get stripped away to reveal what happened, one can’t help but put a few pieces of the puzzle together and be horrified by the final image. Was the FTX Collapse Part of<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-did-the-ftx-fall-expose-a-government-conspiracy/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-did-the-ftx-fall-expose-a-government-conspiracy/">Opinion: Has the FTX Crash Exposed a Government Conspiracy?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesstaff/article/the-fall-of-ftx/?sh=67ef4aca7d0c" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">FTX</a> is likely to go down as one of the biggest embarrassments in the history of crypto. More than that, as additional layers get stripped away to reveal what happened, one can’t help but put a few pieces of the puzzle together and be horrified by the final image.</p>
<h2>Was the FTX Collapse Part of Something Bigger?</h2>
<p>This may sound like something of a conspiracy theory, yet when one really considers everything and puts multiple ideas in place, one can find a thread of common sense. Consider the following:</p>
<p>Crypto was built to keep all government regulators, third parties, and financial middlemen out. Those who used crypto were supposed to enjoy autonomy and independence with their money. They would not see their funds dabbled with by institutions, nor would these players have any say in what users did with their funds. The choices were theirs and theirs alone.</p>
<p>Enter FTX. Within three years, it becomes the golden child of the digital currency arena. Its founder Sam Bankman-Fried is lauded as a genius, and it rises to the top of the exchange ladder, becoming one of the biggest and most popular digital currency trading platforms around. Then, by <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">the end of 2022</a>, it all comes crashing down, sending negative ripples throughout the space and eliminating companies like Block Fi from the playing field.</p>
<p>This is where things get tricky. Over the past several weeks, political figures <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/biden-voices-support-for-crypto-regulation/" data-wpel-link="internal">like Joe Biden</a> and Treasury Secretary <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/janet-yellen-following-ftx-we-must-regulate-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">Janet Yellen</a> have cited FTX as the reason why crypto regulation needs to take precedence in Washington. They’re allegedly concerned about customer safety, and they don’t want anything like this to happen again. Thus, government monitoring of the space may be the best solution.</p>
<p>This would all be fine except for one thing… Many <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-billionaire-sam-bankman-fried-spends-big-in-the-name-of-politics/" data-wpel-link="internal">politicians and government</a> players have <em>accepted</em> money from FTX and Sam Bankman-Fried. These politicians were elected to office by people who believed they understood national law. Are we <em>really</em> expected to assume they didn’t see any sort of corruption or negativity occurring with the exchange when they were so directly connected to it? SBF said he gave money to both democrats <em>and</em> <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-allegedly-gave-just-as-much-money-to-republicans-as-it-did-to-democrats/" data-wpel-link="internal">republicans</a>, meaning both sides of the political spectrum had exposure to the company’s dealings and operations, and nobody saw <em>anything</em> unusual?</p>
<p>It&#8217;s possible the close relationship between FTX and Washington’s elite exposed something it wasn’t supposed to, and it’s plausible to assume that at least some government players knew what was going on and chose to ignore it.</p>
<h2>Your Autonomy Goes Out the Window</h2>
<p>Why? Well, if FTX – a major crypto exchange – crashes and burns, Washington now has the ultimate excuse to completely step in, take over, and regulate the space like the standard financial system, thus eliminating your freedoms entirely. What was built as an uncontrollable space will now be <em>completely</em> controlled by the very people who helped ruin it.</p>
<p>Was the FTX collapse <em>really</em> the result of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/john-ray-iii-ftx-is-the-most-mismanaged-company-ive-ever-seen/" data-wpel-link="internal">bad accounting procedures</a> like we’ve been told? Or was this whole thing part of a larger, more sinister plan?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-did-the-ftx-fall-expose-a-government-conspiracy/">Opinion: Has the FTX Crash Exposed a Government Conspiracy?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-did-the-ftx-fall-expose-a-government-conspiracy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Bulls Are Back, Push to $0.40 Possible</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-bulls-are-back-push-to-0-40-possible/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-bulls-are-back-push-to-0-40-possible/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 06:28:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76417</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ADA price seems to be forming a support base above the $0.30 level against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above $0.32 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.302 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Bitfinex). The price could gain<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-bulls-are-back-push-to-0-40-possible/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-bulls-are-back-push-to-0-40-possible/">Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Bulls Are Back, Push to $0.40 Possible</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>ADA price seems to be forming a support base above the $0.30 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $0.32 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.302 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Bitfinex).</li>
<li>The price could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $0.340 and $0.350 levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Cardano price is showing positive signs above $0.300 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-steady-increase-to-18k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. ADA price could extend its increase if it clears the $0.350 resistance.</em></p>
<h2>Cardano Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This week, cardano price started a steady increase above the $0.270 resistance zone against the US Dollar. The ADA/USD pair gained pace for a move above the $0.280 and $0.285 levels.</p>
<p>It even broke the $0.30 level and settled well above the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). It traded as high as $0.3453 and recently started a downside correction. There was a move below the $0.340 and $0.332 levels. The price declined below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.2391 swing low to $0.3453 high.</p>
<p>It is now trading above $0.30 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-bulls-aim-fresh-increase-above-0-28/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.302 on the 4-hours chart.</p>
<p>On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $0.320 zone. A clear move above the $0.320 resistance might start a strong increase. The next major resistance is near the $0.350 level. A clear upside break above the $0.350 level might send the price towards the $0.38 resistance or even $0.40.</p>
<p>On the downside, an immediate support is near the $0.300 level and the trend line. The next major support is near the $0.292 level. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.2391 swing low to $0.3453 high.</p>
<p>A clear move below the $0.292 level might send the price towards the $0.270 level. Any more losses might send the price towards the $0.250 support.</p>
<div id="attachment_76418" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Cardano-Price-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76418" class="size-full wp-image-76418" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Cardano-Price-1.png" alt="Cardano (ADA) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76418" class="wp-caption-text">Cardano (ADA) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ADAUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that ADA price is now trading above $0.300 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $0.340 and $0.350 levels.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ADA/USD is now losing pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for ADA/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.302 and $0.292.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.320 and $0.350.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-bulls-are-back-push-to-0-40-possible/">Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Bulls Are Back, Push to $0.40 Possible</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-bulls-are-back-push-to-0-40-possible/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Analysis: Upside Break Could Trigger More Gains</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-upside-break-could-trigger-more-gains/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-upside-break-could-trigger-more-gains/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 04:28:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76414</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum price is gaining pace above the $1,250 level against the US Dollar. ETH price is now trading above $1,250 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $1,300 on the 4-hours chart (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could climb further if it clears<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-upside-break-could-trigger-more-gains/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-upside-break-could-trigger-more-gains/">Ethereum Price Analysis: Upside Break Could Trigger More Gains</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ethereum price is gaining pace above the $1,250 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>ETH price is now trading above $1,250 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $1,300 on the 4-hours chart (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could climb further if it clears the $1,350 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ethereum price is rising above the $1,250 level against the US Dollar. ETH/USD could rise further if it clears the $1,350 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Ethereum Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, ethereum saw a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-gain-pace-above-1250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">decent increase</a> above the $1,220 level against the US Dollar. ETH price was able to gain pace for a move above the $1,250 level and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</p>
<p>The bulls even cleared the $1,300 resistance zone. The price even spiked above the $1,320 level and formed a high near the $1,345 level. ETH is now consolidating gains above the $1,300 level. It is consolidating near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1,234 swing low to $1,345 high.</p>
<p>It is now trading above $1,250 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-attempt-fresh-increase-above-1240/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. An immediate resistance on the upside is near the $1,340 level. The next major resistance is near the $1,350 zone.</p>
<p>Any more gains could even send the price towards the $1,350 resistance zone in the near term. On the downside, an initial support is near the $1,310 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is now near the $1,300 level. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $1,300 on the 4-hours chart. The main support is near the $1,290 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1,234 swing low to $1,345 high.</p>
<p>A break below the $1,290 support could push the price to $1,250. Any more losses could lead the price towards $1,210 or even $1,200 in the coming days.</p>
<div id="attachment_76415" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Ethereum-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76415" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-76415" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Ethereum-1.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76415" class="wp-caption-text">Ethereum Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">chart</a>, Ethereum price is clearly trading above the $1,250 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, ether price could climb further if it clears the $1,350 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $1,300, followed by the $1,290 zone.</p>
<p>Key Resistance$ Levels – $1,340 and $1,350.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-upside-break-could-trigger-more-gains/">Ethereum Price Analysis: Upside Break Could Trigger More Gains</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-upside-break-could-trigger-more-gains/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Didi Taihuttu Is Moving All His BTC to Defi Platforms</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/didi-taihuttu-is-moving-all-his-btc-to-decentralized-exchanges/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/didi-taihuttu-is-moving-all-his-btc-to-decentralized-exchanges/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Decentralized exchanges]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Didi Taihuttu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75850</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Didi Taihuttu and his family – often dubbed the “bitcoin family” due to their devotion to the world’s number one digital currency – are still confident in bitcoin and aren’t letting last year’s price flops and the collapse of FTX get to them. However, things have changed enough that they’re moving their bitcoin over and<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/didi-taihuttu-is-moving-all-his-btc-to-decentralized-exchanges/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/didi-taihuttu-is-moving-all-his-btc-to-decentralized-exchanges/">Didi Taihuttu Is Moving All His BTC to Defi Platforms</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Didi Taihuttu and his family – often dubbed the “bitcoin family” due to their devotion to the world’s number one digital currency – are still confident <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/bitcoin-family-is-moving-more-than-1-million-into-decentralized-exchanges-after-sam-bankman-fried-s-ftx-disaster/ar-AA14KAAc" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">in bitcoin and aren’t</a> letting last year’s price flops and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">collapse of FTX</a> get to them. However, things have changed enough that they’re moving their bitcoin over and finding new ways of securing it.</p>
<h2>Didi Taihuttu Feels Strongly About Defi</h2>
<p>Many years ago, Taihuttu, his wife, and their three daughters <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/didi-taihuttu-and-his-family-are-putting-everything-they-have-into-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">sold everything they owned</a> and exchanged it for bitcoin. Since then, they have begun a life on the road. Last year, they settled in a coastal city in Portugal, where Taihuttu <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/didi-taihuttu-opens-bitcoin-bar-in-portugal/" data-wpel-link="internal">opened what’s known</a> as the “bitcoin bar.”</p>
<p>Up to this point, he’s stored all his crypto assets in exchanges, both centralized and decentralized. Since so many crypto companies are now in the process of filing for bankruptcy, he’s putting all his faith only in decentralized exchanges. He’s moving more than $1 million in crypto assets to said platforms, as they cannot prevent a person from accessing their funds should they decide to go dark.</p>
<p>He commented in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>For me, bitcoin is still about freedom, and decentralized currency should be able to be used by everyone in the world without needing to do KYC or any other regulatory stuff.</p></blockquote>
<p>He is concerned because many centralized exchanges do not give traders private keys. These individuals are fully reliant on the exchanges for buying, selling, and trading their digital assets. Thus, their ownership of the assets is always in question.</p>
<p>Taihuttu isn’t crazy about this. He wants to be able to access his money at any point during an emergency, and he’s now putting all his time, hope, and energy into the world of defi. No KYC protocols, no blockades, just traders and quick access to their money.</p>
<p>He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>You never send your bitcoin to an exchange. Your bitcoin stays in your own wallet, meaning you have complete custody of your coins. You connect to a DEX, and by making that connection, you trade out of your own wallet. If the DEX collapses, it doesn&#8217;t matter because the bitcoin [is] always in your own wallet.</p></blockquote>
<p>Taihuttu and his family are presently living on .3 bitcoin a month. This amounts to roughly $5,000 USD at the time of writing. They are also buying back all the BTC they sold last year. At that time, the BTC price was around $55,000 per unit. They now have a chance to get all their funds back at only a fraction of the cost.</p>
<h2>Never Trusting of FTX?</h2>
<p>He further stated he’s always had a bad feeling about FTX, and he’s not surprised by its sudden fall. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Too many influencers were paid too much money to promote that one.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/didi-taihuttu-is-moving-all-his-btc-to-decentralized-exchanges/">Didi Taihuttu Is Moving All His BTC to Defi Platforms</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/didi-taihuttu-is-moving-all-his-btc-to-decentralized-exchanges/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Allegedly Gave Just as Much Money to Republicans as It Did to Democrats</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-allegedly-gave-just-as-much-money-to-republicans-as-it-did-to-democrats/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-allegedly-gave-just-as-much-money-to-republicans-as-it-did-to-democrats/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[democrats]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[republicans]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75848</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The drama surrounding FTX is getting a lot worse. Initially, it was believed that Sam Bankman-Fried – the man behind the now failed digital currency exchange – gave a lot of money to democrat politicians, and he did. However, it’s now being alleged by him that equal money was given to republicans, only those donations<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-allegedly-gave-just-as-much-money-to-republicans-as-it-did-to-democrats/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-allegedly-gave-just-as-much-money-to-republicans-as-it-did-to-democrats/">FTX Allegedly Gave Just as Much Money to Republicans as It Did to Democrats</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The drama surrounding FTX is getting a lot worse. Initially, it <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-billionaire-sam-bankman-fried-spends-big-in-the-name-of-politics/" data-wpel-link="internal">was believed that</a> Sam Bankman-Fried – the man behind the now failed digital currency exchange – gave a lot of money to democrat politicians, and he did. However, it’s now being alleged by him that equal money was given to republicans, only those donations <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2022/nov/30/ftx-billionaire-sam-bankman-fried-dark-money-republicans" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">were more secret</a>.</p>
<h2>FTX Also Allegedly Delivered Funds to Republicans</h2>
<p>FTX collapsed in mid-November of last year following what SBF referred to as a “<a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">liquidity crunch</a>” on social media. He initially sought the aid of Binance and approached the company about being bought out. However, Binance said that the problems the firm was dealing with were too big to handle, and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">thus the buyout did not</a> occur.</p>
<p>From there, FTX had no choice <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">but to file bankruptcy</a>, and its founder resigned from his post. The company has caused ripples throughout the space, and many other enterprises – <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block-fi-is-the-latest-crypto-company-to-go-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">such as Block Fi</a> – have been forced into similar bankruptcy proceedings as a result.</p>
<p>Last year, it was reported that Bankman-Fried was the second largest donor to the democrat party. When this knowledge was made public, many right-leaning politicians – such as Texas Senator Ted Cruz – jumped on it and took to social media to attack members of the left. On Twitter, Cruz wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>Will Joe Biden and democrats who cashed Bankman-Fried’s checks give that money to the people SBF screwed?</p></blockquote>
<p>Now, however, Bankman-Fried has come out to say he gave just as much to republicans as he did to democrats, though many of those donations occurred on a more secretive level. He said in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>I donated to both parties. I donated about the same amount to both parties. All my republican donations were dark. The reason was not for regulatory reasons. It’s because reporters freak the f*ck out if you donate to republicans. They’re all super liberal, and I didn’t want to have that fight.</p></blockquote>
<p>It is alleged that much of the money for republicans was delivered via FTX US per data from Open Secrets. However, much of the money that SBF himself donated to politicians largely went to leftwingers. Open Secrets shows that Bankman-Fried donated nearly $1 million to specific democrat candidates in the last election cycle, while nearly $40 million went to democrat-centered groups.</p>
<p>By contrast, it appears he gave less than $250K of his money to republican candidates, so clearly bias exists.</p>
<h2>Scary for Many Reasons</h2>
<p>The situation raises several questions. It’s not exactly easy to take SBF’s word on anything, anymore. The allegation that his company utilized customer funds to purchase luxury condos in the Bahamas suggests he doesn’t have a penchant for the truth.</p>
<p>At the same time, if what he’s saying is real, this is far more frightening given many members of the U.S. government either couldn’t recognize corruption when they saw it, or worse – they’re part of the corruption themselves.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-allegedly-gave-just-as-much-money-to-republicans-as-it-did-to-democrats/">FTX Allegedly Gave Just as Much Money to Republicans as It Did to Democrats</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-allegedly-gave-just-as-much-money-to-republicans-as-it-did-to-democrats/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Exchange Kraken Lays Off Over 1,000 Employees</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kraken-to-lay-off-30-of-its-staff/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kraken-to-lay-off-30-of-its-staff/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 13:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kraken]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Layoffs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75844</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Kraken – a popular digital currency trading platform based in northern California – is laying off more than 1,000 employees as it attempts to deal with the ongoing crypto winter. Kraken Says Bye to a Lot of Workers The crypto exchange says that the maneuver has nothing to do with the fall of FTX, which<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kraken-to-lay-off-30-of-its-staff/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kraken-to-lay-off-30-of-its-staff/">Crypto Exchange Kraken Lays Off Over 1,000 Employees</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Kraken – a popular digital currency trading platform based in northern California – is laying off more than 1,000 employees as it attempts <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/kraken-layoffs-crypto-exchange-ftx-winter-jesse-powell-2022-11" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">to deal with the ongoing</a> crypto winter.</p>
<h2>Kraken Says Bye to a Lot of Workers</h2>
<p>The crypto exchange says that the maneuver has nothing to do with <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">the fall of FTX</a>, which has caused a serious firestorm in the digital currency world. The exchange collapsed in mid-November and has sent ripples throughout the space, making several other firms – <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block-fi-is-the-latest-crypto-company-to-go-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">such as Block Fi</a> – follow in its footsteps and file for bankruptcy.</p>
<p>However, Kraken wants it made clear that this has nothing to do with FTX. Rather, the crypto winter has not subsided, and the company is working to ensure it can stay afloat while the market repairs itself. A spokesperson for the firm said:</p>
<blockquote><p>No. Kraken was already reviewing its business and workforce needs when news of [the] FTX bankruptcy was made public. Kraken had no material exposure to FTX.</p></blockquote>
<p>Kraken is specifically pointing the finger at “macro-economic and geopolitical factors” as the reasons behind its new string of layoffs. With more than 1,000 people saying goodbye to their jobs with the exchange, the company is losing approximately 30 percent of its workforce. In a statement, Kraken said:</p>
<blockquote><p>This resulted in significantly lower trading volumes and fewer client sign-ups. We responded by slowing hiring efforts and avoiding large marketing commitments. Unfortunately, negative influences on the financial markets have continued, and we have exhausted preferable options for bringing costs in line with demand.</p></blockquote>
<p>Employees who are being let go are not leaving empty handed. They are being offered 16 weeks of pay, which amounts to roughly four months of additional money as they spend time looking for employment elsewhere. They will also receive an extension of benefits including health coverage and counseling services. They are also being given access to stock options, while employees on visas are being given immigration support.</p>
<p>Jesse Powell – the CEO of Kraken – continued the initial statement with:</p>
<blockquote><p>I&#8217;m confident the steps we are taking today will ensure we can continue to deliver on our mission which the world needs now more than ever before. I remain extremely bullish on crypto and Kraken.</p></blockquote>
<h2>The Drama of the Space Continues</h2>
<p>To say it’s been a rough time for crypto and bitcoin would be a huge understatement. Many crypto companies – such as <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gemini-exchange-says-major-layoffs-are-coming/" data-wpel-link="internal">Gemini</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-says-its-laying-off-several-employees/" data-wpel-link="internal">Coinbase</a> – have been forced to let go of staff members as they endure the growing effects of the weakening industry. Many mainstream tokens like bitcoin have also fallen drastically from the all-time highs they achieved in November of 2021.</p>
<p>During that time, BTC was trading at a whopping $68,000 per unit. Now, the asset has fallen into the low $17K range. Here’s to hoping that 2023 will be kinder to this young financial arena.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kraken-to-lay-off-30-of-its-staff/">Crypto Exchange Kraken Lays Off Over 1,000 Employees</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kraken-to-lay-off-30-of-its-staff/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
