<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:18:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/cropped-fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The UK&#8217;s James Wharton Thrashed Over Alleged Crypto Ties</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/uk-politician-james-wharton-thrashed-over-alleged-crypto-ties/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 17:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[James Wharton]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United Kingdom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78849</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>James Wharton – a former campaign manager to Boris Johnson that’s now leading an education quango – is being questioned over his alleged ties to a crypto lobbying firm. James Wharton Criticized for Ties to Crypto Wharton presently leads an organization known as the Office for Students (OFS). However, he’s also launched a new public [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/uk-politician-james-wharton-thrashed-over-alleged-crypto-ties/">The UK&#8217;s James Wharton Thrashed Over Alleged Crypto Ties</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>James Wharton – a former campaign manager to Boris Johnson that’s now leading an education quango – is being <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2023/jun/18/tory-peer-james-wharton-working-for-crypto-lobbying-firm-northpoint-strategy">questioned over his alleged</a> ties to a crypto lobbying firm.</p>
<h2>James Wharton Criticized for Ties to Crypto</h2>
<p>Wharton presently leads an organization known as the Office for Students (OFS). However, he’s also launched a new public affairs company designed to help clients “navigate the complexities” of Westminster. He also provides legal counseling on regulated sectors.</p>
<p>That company – known as North Point Strategy – is managing a group called the UK Crypto Asset Business Council (UKCBC). It emerged a few years back and began working in the lobbying sector while trying to build connections within the UK Parliament. The main goal of the UKCBC is to establish the United Kingdom as a leading crypto hub.</p>
<p>Among the tactics it’s undertaken to create this future have been writing to both civil servants and ministers and meeting with Treasury officials. Wharton was appointed to the organization about two years ago in 2021, but his attachment to the group is now being criticized by the UK Labor Party, which says Wharton is placing his own interests above those involved in education (people he’s purportedly trying to help through the quango mentioned above).</p>
<p>Matt Western – the shadow minister for higher education with the Labor Party – explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>This is the latest in a long line of examples of the chair of the Office for Students putting his political interests above the interests of students. Students rightly expect swift action from the independent regulator on matters that affect them the most. It is less than clear how Lord Wharton’s additional commitment helps further those interests.</p></blockquote>
<p>Over the past several months, crypto has taken a new lead on regulators’ priorities lists in the UK. Not long ago, it was believed that crypto trading should fall under the same <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-united-kingdom-wants-gambling-laws-to-apply-to-crypto-trading/">rules and guidelines</a> that apply to gambling. In other words, buying bitcoin, in lawmakers’ eyes, was a lot like sitting down and betting one’s money at a blackjack table, a metaphor that <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/finance-professor-disagrees-with-united-kingdom-sentiment-towards-crypto/">has been criticized</a> by many.</p>
<p>The main idea behind the gambling comparison, however, stems from regulators’ blatant feelings that crypto assets like bitcoin have no intrinsic value and are very risky endeavors.</p>
<h2>The UK Is Leading the Way to Crypto Regulation</h2>
<p>After the UKCBC’s work with the Treasury came to public attention, a Treasury spokesperson emerged and issued the following statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>Government officials have consulted with well over 50 crypto organizations, including one meeting with UKCBC, to ensure our new crypto asset regulatory regime achieves robust, transparent, and fair standards.</p></blockquote>
<p>Following the disastrous <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/">fall of FTX</a> last November, the United Kingdom <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-united-kingdom-announces-plans-for-new-crypto-regulations/">became one of the first</a> regions in the world to get serious about crypto regulation and impose strict new laws designed to regulate trading and keep investors protected.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/uk-politician-james-wharton-thrashed-over-alleged-crypto-ties/">The UK&#8217;s James Wharton Thrashed Over Alleged Crypto Ties</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ben Zhang: Everyone Should Invest in Crypto for the Long Run</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ben-zhang-everyone-should-invest-in-crypto-for-the-long-run/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ben Zhang]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78847</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dr. Ben Zhang – a former banker at JPMorgan and the co-founder of Node Real – believes blockchain and crypto are long-term investments, and he thinks entrepreneurs and startups alike need to get involved now before things really explode. Ben Zhang on How Crypto Should Be Viewed Over the last year or so, the crypto [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ben-zhang-everyone-should-invest-in-crypto-for-the-long-run/">Ben Zhang: Everyone Should Invest in Crypto for the Long Run</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dr. Ben Zhang – a former banker at JPMorgan and the co-founder of Node Real – believes blockchain and crypto are <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/06/32905479/ex-jp-morgan-banker-says-cryptocurrency-is-a-long-term-investment-opportunity">long-term investments</a>, and he thinks entrepreneurs and startups alike need to get involved now before things really explode.</p>
<h2>Ben Zhang on How Crypto Should Be Viewed</h2>
<p>Over the last year or so, the crypto market has been subjected to haphazard conditions that have really caused prices to sink. Bitcoin, for example, was trading 70 percent less at the end of last year from where it was at the end of 2021. The crypto industry’s overall valuation dropped by more than $2 trillion during a 12-month period, and things really took ugly (and unexpected) turns.</p>
<p>However, while it’s easy to blame <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/inflation/">inflation</a> and all these other economic factors, Zhang is confident the industry fell the way it did due to a lack of innovation. In an interview, he said:</p>
<blockquote><p>So far, I think business innovation for some specific areas is very good, but there are a lot of areas which lack innovation. I think crypto or web3 or blockchain is still in the very early stages. It&#8217;s the perfect time to start your journey as a startup, entrepreneur, or developer in crypto. You can learn some of blockchain&#8217;s fundamental technology and some of MetaMask’s wallet management.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also said that the crypto space needs to be looked at as a long-term investment opportunity. One of the big issues, in his opinion, is that everyone wants to rush in, make a little money, and then sell their stashes as soon as they see some gains. This is the wrong idea, Zhang commented. People need to be in it for the long run. Otherwise, the arena is not going to succeed. He says:</p>
<blockquote><p>We should put more money in the crypto market and look for long-term investment. Crypto and blockchain are still getting a lot of attention. Now we have so many different regulatory frameworks, and it helps improve the downturn movement of crypto. I don&#8217;t think too many regulations cause a downturn. The downturn is caused by many factors including the macro economy&#8217;s instability worldwide, but there are so many regulatory frameworks, and [they’re] very difficult to follow.</p></blockquote>
<h2>The Growth of Web3</h2>
<p>Discussing the implantation of web3, Zhang said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Web3 marks the next significant advancement in the evolution of the internet. Building upon the foundations of web1 and web2, which introduced user interaction[s] and social media, web3 represents a transformative leap forward. Powered by blockchain technology, NFTs, and cryptocurrencies, web3 is set to revolutionize the online landscape. Web3 environments are revolutionizing the gaming industry by enabling the creation of video games that utilize blockchain technology. Through these games, players can leverage the power of non-fungible tokens and token rewards within the game to earn profits.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ben-zhang-everyone-should-invest-in-crypto-for-the-long-run/">Ben Zhang: Everyone Should Invest in Crypto for the Long Run</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Winklevoss Twins Aren&#8217;t Giving Up on Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-winklevoss-twins-arent-giving-up-on-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 13:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Saylor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Winklevoss]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78845</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has been in a bit of a slump over the last month and a half or so, but according to Michael Saylor – the former CEO of MicroStrategy – and the Winklevoss Twins, this slump could soon be coming to an end, and the world’s number one digital currency by market cap is going [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-winklevoss-twins-arent-giving-up-on-bitcoin/">The Winklevoss Twins Aren&#8217;t Giving Up on Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has been in a bit of a slump over the last month and a half or so, but according to Michael Saylor – the former CEO of MicroStrategy – and the Winklevoss Twins, this slump could soon be coming to an end, and the world’s number one digital currency by market cap <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/06/17/it-could-happen-very-quickly-crypto-bulls-issue-huge-10x-price-prediction-amid-wild-bitcoin-and-ethereum-price-swings/?sh=5fd9a4fc6a35">is going to reach</a> new levels of bullishness.</p>
<h2>The Winklevoss Twins Have High Hopes for BTC</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, Saylor mentioned that the bitcoin price could hit a new height “very quickly,” and the weakened behavior we’ve been so accustomed to over the last six or seven weeks may be ending sooner than we think. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>I have confidence that the crypto exchanges will come around to realizing that bitcoin really is the dominant asset in this space, and their business models are fine when bitcoin goes up by a factor of ten.</p></blockquote>
<p>Right now, bitcoin’s dominance in the crypto market stands at about 50 percent. However, he’s confident that this dominance could soon hit the 80 percent mark, meaning roughly 80 percent of the market will be entirely composed of bitcoin. He is also confident that this will happen at around the time that the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-sec-lawsuits-are-paving-the-way-to-btc-dominance/">lawsuits from the</a> SEC against leading digital currency exchanges Binance and Coinbase reach their pinnacles in the coming months. Saylor said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The entire industry is kind of destined to be rationalized down to a bitcoin-focused industry, with maybe a half a dozen to a dozen other proof of work tokens.</p></blockquote>
<p>He’s not the only one who feels this way. This sentiment is shared by both Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss, the bitcoin billionaires that run the Gemini exchange in New York. They are firm believers that bitcoin is going to “disrupt” the gold market, and that the world’s primary form of crypto will eventually hit a price of about $500K per unit. This would give it a market cap of about $10 trillion.</p>
<p>Cameron Winklevoss chimed in with:</p>
<blockquote><p>If you look at the value increases in bitcoin, it is this punctuated equilibrium where it is steady, steady, steady, and then boom! It reaches a new price level. That is the new normal. So, it could happen very quickly.</p></blockquote>
<p>2022 was badly marred by a harsh crypto winter. Things really fell into the depths, with some coins – like BTC – losing approximately 70 percent of their overall value, and the valuation of the general crypto market wound up shedding about $2 trillion over the course of a year.</p>
<h2>Forget About the Crypto Winter!</h2>
<p>However, the brothers were quick to toss this over their shoulders, with Cameron saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>It is still going to be the best investment of this decade. Bitcoin is [like] a honey badger. Whatever does not kill it makes it stronger, and it has been through a lot.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-winklevoss-twins-arent-giving-up-on-bitcoin/">The Winklevoss Twins Aren&#8217;t Giving Up on Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coin Ex Settles Suit in New York, Vows to Leave the U.S.</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coin-ex-settles-suit-in-new-york-vows-to-leave-the-u-s/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 17:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coin Ex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Leticia James]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New York]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78840</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coin Ex is a digital currency exchange based in Hong Kong. Not long ago, the company was faced with a lawsuit from New York Attorney General Leticia James, who said the firm had violated various financial laws and put traders and investors in danger. Coin Ex Settles, Set to Exit America Now, it looks like [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coin-ex-settles-suit-in-new-york-vows-to-leave-the-u-s/">Coin Ex Settles Suit in New York, Vows to Leave the U.S.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coin Ex is a digital currency exchange based in Hong Kong. Not long ago, the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leticia-james-sues-coin-ex-alleging-crypto-fraud/">company was faced</a> with a lawsuit from New York Attorney General Leticia James, who said the firm had violated various financial laws and put traders and investors in danger.</p>
<h2>Coin Ex Settles, Set to Exit America</h2>
<p>Now, it looks like Coin Ex has <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/coinex-settles-for-17-million-ceases-new-york-operations/ar-AA1cCyIJ">agreed to settle with James</a> for nearly $2 million to get the suit off its back. In addition, the company is also ceasing all its U.S. operations, and the American branch of the exchange is facing imminent shutdown.</p>
<p>The lawsuit against Coin Ex was filed in February of this year. Allegations came about that the company had violated what’s known as the Martin Act, which was enacted in 1921 (over 100 years ago). The law disallows the selling and offering of any securities by companies that haven’t registered as dealers, brokers, or salesmen within specific regions or states (in this case, New York).</p>
<p>By allegedly failing to register either with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) or the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), the company was in violation of the Act and therefore subject to penalties. Leticia James issued a statement regarding the matter that read:</p>
<blockquote><p>Today’s agreement should serve as a warning to crypto companies that there are hefty consequences for ignoring New York’s laws. My office will continue to crack down on crypto companies that brazenly disregard the law, mislead investors, and put New Yorkers at risk… Rampant fraud and dysfunction have become the hallmarks of cryptocurrency, and it is time to bring law and order to the multi-billion-dollar industry.</p></blockquote>
<p>Coin Ex has also mentioned that while the lawsuit ultimately contributed to the decision to leave the U.S., the regulatory atmosphere in America has become too convoluted and confusing for it to handle anymore. Thus, the country will no longer be privy to the exchange’s services or product offerings.</p>
<h2>So Many Crypto Companies Victimized</h2>
<p>This sentiment is shared by several digital asset enterprises at the time of writing. For the past several months, agencies like the SEC have employed harsh methods of enforcing regulation. For example, the SEC has filed major lawsuits against large crypto companies like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-hit-with-sec-lawsuit-says-it-operated-as-an-exchange-broker/">Coinbase</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sues-binance-alleges-selling-of-illegal-securities/">Binance</a>, and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/">Kraken</a>. Not long ago, Coinbase even opened an <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-is-now-active-in-bermuda/">office in Bermuda</a> and said it would be focusing more on international crypto trading and activities until the U.S. can get its rules and priorities in place.</p>
<p>Also, Leticia James can act like she’s concerned for investors’ safety all she wants, but the fact remains that, like the SEC, she’s simply made a habit of going after crypto every chance she can. Several firms – including <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-yorks-leticia-james-sues-crypto-firm-nexo/">Nexo</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-attorney-generals-office-now-suing-ku-coin-exchange/">Ku Coin</a> – have fallen victim to her wrath and been subjected to heavy financial penalties or other punishments.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coin-ex-settles-suit-in-new-york-vows-to-leave-the-u-s/">Coin Ex Settles Suit in New York, Vows to Leave the U.S.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Panel: NFTs Need to Have Real-World Value if They&#8217;re to Succeed</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/panel-nfts-need-to-have-real-world-value-if-theyre-to-succeed/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 15:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jordan Fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rob Nelson]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78838</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Where will non-fungible tokens (NFTs) be in the next few years? NFTs&#8230; Where Will the Future Take Them? NFTs were, at one point, the big rage of the crypto industry. They saw a lot of action and activity, and within two or three years, the arena was worth billions of dollars and was all the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/panel-nfts-need-to-have-real-world-value-if-theyre-to-succeed/">Panel: NFTs Need to Have Real-World Value if They&#8217;re to Succeed</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Where will non-fungible tokens (NFTs) <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/nfts-beyond-the-hype-the-future-of-blockchain-identity/ar-AA1cDeXW">be in the next few</a> years?</p>
<h2>NFTs&#8230; Where Will the Future Take Them?</h2>
<p>NFTs were, at one point, the big rage of the crypto industry. They saw a lot of action and activity, and within two or three years, the arena was worth billions of dollars and was all the rage of crypto fanatics. However, since then, NFTs have <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-ordinals-nfts-are-bringing-the-space-back-from-disaster/">taken a serious dive</a>, and we’re not seeing that many people engaged with them anymore.</p>
<p>In a recent roundtable that saw the participation of several NFT creators and experts, the topic of where these pixelated art tokens are going to be in the next five to ten years raised a lot of questions and delivered a few answers. Each of the participants gave their thoughts and ideas on where these tokens will arrive and what traders can potentially expect.</p>
<p>One of them was Jordan Fried, who introduced the idea of a “soul bound token.” This item would be an NFT that is permanently tied to a single person. It cannot be transferred, sold, or disposed of through conventional means. He commented to the moderator of the panel Rob Nelson:</p>
<blockquote><p>It would be the Rob Nelson coin. It&#8217;d be you. It&#8217;d be the roundtable coin for the brand, but it can&#8217;t be transferred. It&#8217;s non-transferrable. Its soul bound. It&#8217;s bound to this account forever, and that&#8217;s likely what will capture identity as it&#8217;s a version of a non-fungible token, but it&#8217;s a non-transferable, non-fungible token… The greatest problem in the NFT space right now is that there&#8217;s no one sitting anywhere in the world saying, ‘If I just had an NFT, that would be the solution to my problem.&#8217;</p></blockquote>
<p>The idea of having a token permanently tied to you is a little scary, but Jordan clarified his thoughts a tad more by commenting that these tokens would also be built to resolve various problems being faced by the individual or by the public. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>To have a crypto punk meant something about you, but for the technology to actually live up to its promise, you&#8217;re going to have to have NFTs that solve real problems. NFTs that actually have real-world value.</p></blockquote>
<h2>No Real-World Value</h2>
<p>Right now, most non-fungible tokens are simply seen as collectibles. While some have sold for hundreds of thousands of dollars, the “collectible” nature of most NFTs is what Jordan thinks has led to the demise of the space. He commented that they need to be able to tackle certain issues. They must have real-world use if they’re going to carve out a legitimate space for themselves. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>We&#8217;ve got to tokenize actual value as NFTs. Otherwise, the whole purpose of buying an NFT, it&#8217;s just not going to be there for most people.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/panel-nfts-need-to-have-real-world-value-if-theyre-to-succeed/">Panel: NFTs Need to Have Real-World Value if They&#8217;re to Succeed</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is the U.S. Government Hiding a Big BTC Stash Somewhere?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-u-s-government-hiding-a-big-btc-stash-somewhere/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Morgan Creek]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[U.S. government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78836</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. government appears to be very anti crypto as of late. Everywhere you look, regulators in the Biden administration are doing what appears to be all they can to ensure bitcoin and crypto don’t have futures in America. The U.S. Government and Bitcoin&#8230; It&#8217;s Complicated! The SEC, for example, is suing or criminally charging [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-u-s-government-hiding-a-big-btc-stash-somewhere/">Is the U.S. Government Hiding a Big BTC Stash Somewhere?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. government appears to be very anti crypto as of late. Everywhere you look, regulators in the Biden administration are doing what appears to be all they can to ensure bitcoin and crypto don’t have futures in America.</p>
<h2>The U.S. Government and Bitcoin&#8230; It&#8217;s Complicated!</h2>
<p>The SEC, for example, is suing or criminally charging every <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-hit-with-sec-lawsuit-says-it-operated-as-an-exchange-broker/">single digital currency</a> company it can, while Biden is looking to initiate an Obama-era policy that will <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-biden-using-an-obama-era-program-to-ban-btc/">potentially shut all crypto</a> firms out of the traditional finance fray. Thus, it seems like the U.S. government wouldn’t hold much bitcoin and it wouldn’t be <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/us-government-owns-way-more-bitcoin-than-any-other-country-so-why-aren-t-they-selling-it/ar-AA1cDjZk">keeping a private bitcoin</a> stash somewhere… Right?</p>
<p>Wrong. As it turns out, the U.S. government has more than $5 billion in bitcoin secretly hocked away. It’s all illicit bitcoin that representatives have gathered following various seizures over the years, and for one reason or another, they’ve been reluctant to get rid of it or sell it. Why?</p>
<p>Perhaps one reason is because they know <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/inflation/">inflation</a> (which they’re responsible for) is a major issue in the country. They know the dollar is flailing, and they want to have bitcoin as a “backup plan” of sorts because they’re worried about what the prospects of traditional finance are. In many ways, the U.S. government has likely come to see bitcoin as the “safe haven” so many others view it as.</p>
<p>Right now, it’s estimated the U.S. Treasury has more than 207,000 individual bitcoin units stored away somewhere. The money has been garnered over the course of several years through several events, a big one being a Justice Department seizure of more than $1 billion in BTC in 2020. A doctoral thesis written by Sachin Jaitly, a general partner at investment advisory firm Morgan Creek Capital, states the following:</p>
<blockquote><p>By matching publicly available information through the media and blockchain, Elementus is able to map out the universe of sovereign digital wallets and maintain this map over time.</p></blockquote>
<p>Elementus is the blockchain startup Morgan Creek is working with to track the history of the U.S.’s bitcoin collecting habits. CEO Max Galka was also quick to throw his two cents in. He commented that the company has, thus far, recorded at least 11 world governments that are holding bitcoin. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>All of that bitcoin is held by those government agencies, but that does not mean that that is the only bitcoin that is held by those governments, nor that other governments are not using bitcoin.</p></blockquote>
<h2>What Other Entities Hold BTC?</h2>
<p>Jaitly concluded with:</p>
<blockquote><p>As money supply was increasing, and as fear of inflation was increasing, bitcoin adoption on a sovereign level was also increasing, and so there was a relationship that was statistically significant.</p></blockquote>
<p>They have also worked to gather information for North Korea, but that data has proven largely unobtainable.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-u-s-government-hiding-a-big-btc-stash-somewhere/">Is the U.S. Government Hiding a Big BTC Stash Somewhere?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FUN Token Pioneers Blockchain Evolution with 20 Million FUN Seed Fund Initiative</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fun-token-pioneers-blockchain-evolution-with-20-million-fun-seed-fund-initiative/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Gautham]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 12:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79545</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FUNToken is delighted to announce the launch of the FUN Token Seed Fund, an innovative program designed to accelerate the integration of FUN Token into the rapidly expanding blockchain industry. The company set aside a 20 million FUN Tokens reserve and will award 40 dapps with 500,000 FUNToken each. The goal is to inspire these [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fun-token-pioneers-blockchain-evolution-with-20-million-fun-seed-fund-initiative/">FUN Token Pioneers Blockchain Evolution with 20 Million FUN Seed Fund Initiative</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FUNToken is delighted to announce the launch of the <a href="https://bit.ly/459euCA">FUN Token Seed Fund</a>, an innovative program designed to accelerate the integration of FUN Token into the rapidly expanding blockchain industry.</p>
<p>The company set aside a 20 million FUN Tokens reserve and will award 40 dapps with 500,000 FUNToken each. The goal is to inspire these projects to develop creative applications, services, or products incorporating FUN Token, thereby boosting its value and usefulness.</p>
<p>As another advantage to applying for the seed fund, qualified dapps would also gain access to 50 million crypto users by Freebitco.in, further extending their reach and potential impact.</p>
<p>The 500,000 FUN Tokens will be a game-changer for the selected projects, empowering them to improve various aspects of their business, including development, marketing, and operations. The aim is to help them grow quickly and establish a strong market presence.</p>
<p>This initiative will benefit dapps and promote the visibility and adoption of FUN Token. As more platforms adopt FUN, demand for the token will increase, leading to a potential surge in value. The selected projects will also gain recognition and credibility within the crypto industry, attracting more investment and partnerships.</p>
<p>If you&#8217;re eager to participate in this transformational journey, we encourage you to apply by completing the<a href="https://forms.gle/1CTPRzPNUrPFWjDV6"> FUN Token Seed Fund Application Form</a>. The FUN Token Seed Fund is a catalyst for innovation and growth, aligning the future of blockchain with the present through <a href="https://bit.ly/3YdJ77G">FUNToken</a>. We welcome everyone to join us on this journey. With FUN, the future of blockchain integration is brighter and more promising than ever!</p>
<h4>About FUN Token</h4>
<p>FUN Token&#8217;s mission is to leverage the power of blockchain technology to create &#8220;trustless&#8221; gaming ecosystems that users can trust, and operators can implement effortlessly. Supported by industry veteran FreeBitco.in, FUN Token strives to make non-custodial gaming the new industry standard.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fun-token-pioneers-blockchain-evolution-with-20-million-fun-seed-fund-initiative/">FUN Token Pioneers Blockchain Evolution with 20 Million FUN Seed Fund Initiative</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>GAMMA 4, Powered by Bluzelle, Launches Private Beta: Invites Testers to Play and Reshape Crypto Sci-Fi Gaming!</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gamma-4-powered-by-bluzelle-launches-private-beta-invites-testers-to-play-and-reshape-crypto-sci-fi-gaming/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 12:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79526</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>GAMMA 4, the Crypto Sci-Fi Epic, is now available for select players who can also earn early rewards for helping shape the game, powered by Bluzelle ~ Bringing GameFi on Cosmos! Singapore, August 01, 2023 &#8211; Bluzelle, a pioneering blockchain for GameFi, proudly announces the highly-anticipated launch of GAMMA 4 Private Beta, an enthralling sci-fi [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gamma-4-powered-by-bluzelle-launches-private-beta-invites-testers-to-play-and-reshape-crypto-sci-fi-gaming/">GAMMA 4, Powered by Bluzelle, Launches Private Beta: Invites Testers to Play and Reshape Crypto Sci-Fi Gaming!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>GAMMA 4, the Crypto Sci-Fi Epic, is now available for select players who can also earn early rewards for helping shape the game, powered by Bluzelle ~ Bringing GameFi on Cosmos!</em></p>
<p><strong><em>Singapore, August 01, 2023</em></strong> &#8211; Bluzelle, a pioneering blockchain for GameFi, proudly announces the highly-anticipated launch of <a href="http://gamma4.com/">GAMMA 4 Private Beta</a>, an enthralling sci-fi RPG for the Cosmos ecosystem. After 18 months of relentless development by a world-class team, GAMMA 4 is now ready to take players on an extraordinary journey through a galaxy filled with powerful races, NFTs, and thrilling battles.</p>
<h4>Innovations in Web3 Gaming</h4>
<p>GAMMA 4 introduces groundbreaking innovations in Web3 gaming, including card strategy, character breeding, and the captivating use of NFTs. Players will find themselves immersed in a universe where a newly discovered energy source, Elementi, binds with various species  across the galaxy, unleashing formidable abilities. As a cataclysmic event sparks a planetary battle, players must choose sides and embark on a quest of strategic brilliance and epic encounters.</p>
<p>The game&#8217;s features include card deck building, genetic breeding of characters, team selection, exhilarating battles, and NFT character collecting, providing players with a vast array of options and immersive gameplay.</p>
<p>Commenting on the game, <a href="https://bluzelle.com/">Bluzelle</a> CEO and GAMMA 4 Executive Producer Pavel Bains added, &#8220;<em>We&#8217;re excited to announce that GAMMA 4’s private beta will have two full chapters, each consisting of eight levels, totaling 16 levels, and this includes exhilarating Boss Battles. The gameplay is designed to offer an immersive and enjoyable experience, allowing players to explore and provide us with valuable feedback. Our goal is to create a game that not only captivates players but also incorporates their insights to make it truly exceptional.</em>&#8221;</p>
<p>He further commented, &#8220;<em>It&#8217;s a feature complete game but running two levels, and then we&#8217;ll have more. The goal is to put all these good features in, get all the feedback from everybody, and then us and the team keep building more levels.</em>&#8221;</p>
<h4>Exclusive Opportunity for 50 Players</h4>
<p>The GAMMA 4 Private Beta is limited to just 50 players, offering an exclusive opportunity for enthusiastic gamers to join and actively shape the game. Pavel also expressed his excitement, &#8220;<em>We&#8217;re thrilled to offer this opportunity to a select group of 50 players. Their valuable feedback will be instrumental in helping us refine and enhance the gaming experience. It&#8217;s a unique chance to be a part of GAMMA 4&#8217;s development journey from the start.</em>&#8221;</p>
<h4>Rewards for Building a Better Game</h4>
<p>To reward the dedication of the selected players in shaping the game, Bluzelle will offer three exclusive NFT character cards as players progress through the campaigns. Players&#8217; feedback will be helpful in building and enhancing the game, and they will receive three unique NFT character entities as a token of appreciation. These rare NFTs will become cherished collector&#8217;s items, symbolizing their role in GAMMA 4&#8217;s legacy.</p>
<p>With the GAMMA 4 Private Beta release, Bluzelle aims to gather valuable feedback from the community and build a dynamic and captivating gaming experience that will push the boundaries of GameFi entertainment.</p>
<p>The GAMMA 4 Private Beta is LIVE now. Complete the Quests on Zealy and be among the first 50 players to access and play the game now.</p>
<p>To Complete the Quests on Zealy, visit : <a href="https://zealy.io/c/gamma4/questboard">https://zealy.io/c/gamma4/questboard</a></p>
<p>Watch the GAMMA 4 Private Beta World Premiere to learn more: <a href="https://bit.ly/3PX3ZxO">https://bit.ly/3PX3ZxO</a></p>
<p>For more information, visit <a href="http://gamma4.com">http://gamma4.com</a>.</p>
<p><strong>Follow GAMMA 4 ~The Crypto Sci-Fi Epic</strong></p>
<p><a href="http://www.gamma4.com/">Website</a> | <a href="https://twitter.com/gamma_four?s=21">Twitter</a> | <a href="http://capella.bluzelle.com/">Capella</a> | <a href="https://t.co/MQIgGclevf">Discord</a></p>
<p><strong>About Bluzelle</strong></p>
<p>Bluzelle is an advanced L1 blockchain with 10K TPS, set to transform the Web3 gaming landscape with high-quality games. Upgraded to the latest Stargate V9, Bluzelle is <em>bringing GameFi on Cosmos </em>with codebase enhancements, IBC compatibility, Osmosis integration, fast &amp; affordable cross-chain transfers, and more.</p>
<p>Bluzelle R2, a decentralized storage layer, uses a multi-node backup mechanism to ensure enhanced security of users’ assets in the Bluzelle ecosystem on GAMMA 4 and Capella, the first NFT Marketplace on Bluzelle.</p>
<p>Keep an eye out on Bluzelle’s official social channels to learn more.</p>
<p><a href="https://bluzelle.com/">Website</a> | <a href="https://twitter.com/bluzellehq?s=21">Twitter</a> | <a href="https://t.me/bluzelle">Telegram</a> | <a href="https://discord.com/invite/af7byz6">Discord</a> | <a href="https://blog.bluzelle.com/">Medium</a> | <a href="https://www.binance.com/en-IN/feed/profile/35193718">Binance Feed</a></p>
<p><strong> </strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gamma-4-powered-by-bluzelle-launches-private-beta-invites-testers-to-play-and-reshape-crypto-sci-fi-gaming/">GAMMA 4, Powered by Bluzelle, Launches Private Beta: Invites Testers to Play and Reshape Crypto Sci-Fi Gaming!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Finance Professor Disagrees with United Kingdom Sentiment Towards Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/finance-professor-disagrees-with-united-kingdom-sentiment-towards-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gavin Brown]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United Kingdom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78830</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, regulators in the United Kingdom said crypto trading was akin to gambling. In other words, betting on bitcoin was like sitting at a blackjack table. Not exactly the best metaphor, but we get what the country means. Is the United Kingdom Wrong About Crypto? However, there are many that don’t agree with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/finance-professor-disagrees-with-united-kingdom-sentiment-towards-crypto/">Finance Professor Disagrees with United Kingdom Sentiment Towards Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, regulators in the United Kingdom said <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-united-kingdom-wants-gambling-laws-to-apply-to-crypto-trading/">crypto trading was akin</a> to gambling. In other words, betting on bitcoin was like sitting at a blackjack table. Not exactly the best metaphor, but we get what the country means.</p>
<h2>Is the United Kingdom Wrong About Crypto?</h2>
<p>However, there are many <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-au/money/markets/labelling-cryptocurrency-as-gambling-shows-lack-of-understanding-and-misses-the-solution-expert-says/ar-AA1cyjeZ">that don’t agree with</a> this sentiment. In fact, they think it’s downright wrong, and they say it shows a dangerous lack of understanding. Amongst the people that feel this way is Gavin Brown, an associate professor in financial technology at the University of Liverpool.</p>
<p>In a recent interview, Brown criticized lawmakers in the United Kingdom for not bothering to comprehend the ins and outs of blockchain and crypto a bit better. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>[The committee] didn&#8217;t really understand the technology.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also mentioned that the people of the country know much more about crypto than those that have been placed in charge, and he thinks this is going to lead the United Kingdom down a dark path that will eventually put it behind other regions. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I see that all the time. I&#8217;ll get a taxi in London and the taxi driver will know ten times more [about cryptocurrency] than the CEO of a multinational bank I&#8217;m about to visit. We still see that disparity of knowledge, and not just from people on the street, but also from people who are actually making the policies who should know better.</p></blockquote>
<p>He says the time has come for everyday people and politicians to recognize crypto once and for all, and to acknowledge the idea that it’s here to stay. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Western Anglo-Saxon economies are stuck between a rock and a hard place because it&#8217;s not going away, and it&#8217;s a constant threat… The problem we have with things like… bitcoin, is that it&#8217;s not controllable or ban-able in a traditional sense because… [it] doesn&#8217;t have a CEO, a head office, any employees, an email address, doesn&#8217;t file any accounts, doesn&#8217;t have any buildings, has no AGM, [and] has no shareholders. Literally, bitcoin is an idea. It&#8217;s a computer program that&#8217;s being run globally all over the world at the same time… [Cryptocurrency] has been deliberately constructed in a way that is anti-state, and almost naturally beyond the reach of regulators.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Understanding Must Grow</h2>
<p>Natasha Gillezeau – a SXSW Sydney production lead and former Australian journalist – echoed Brown’s sentiment and said:</p>
<blockquote><p>People need to understand how serious [cryptocurrency] is. We [need] to understand how much of a marketing and advertising push that crypto [companies have] done in the last few years… We&#8217;re talking sports stadiums [sponsored by] Crypto.com, we&#8217;re talking outreach to influencers… We&#8217;re in a different point in the cycle of how much the marketing and advertising industry has legitimized it.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/finance-professor-disagrees-with-united-kingdom-sentiment-towards-crypto/">Finance Professor Disagrees with United Kingdom Sentiment Towards Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
