<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 06:22:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>New York Continues to Not Care About Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-continues-to-not-care-about-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-continues-to-not-care-about-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 17:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BitLicense]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kathy Hochul]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New York]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75398</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York really doesn’t care about cryptocurrency, and the re-election of Governor Kathy Hochul is proof of this. New York Just Doesn&#8217;t Get It During this year’s midterm elections, Hochul ran against Lee Zeldin, who arguably had one of the most competitive republican campaigns in the Empire State in years. Right now, New York is facing a<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-continues-to-not-care-about-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-continues-to-not-care-about-crypto/">New York Continues to Not Care About Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York really doesn’t care about cryptocurrency, and <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/the-fate-of-crypto-mining-is-back-on-the-table-in-new-york/ar-AA13VEDA" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/the-fate-of-crypto-mining-is-back-on-the-table-in-new-york/ar-AA13VEDA&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537717630000&amp;usg=AOvVaw2_mmA_Pj2tidgQjZe9z1DE" data-wpel-link="external">the re-election of</a> Governor Kathy Hochul is proof of this.</p>
<h2>New York Just Doesn&#8217;t Get It</h2>
<p>During this year’s midterm elections, Hochul ran against Lee Zeldin, who arguably had one of the most competitive republican campaigns in the Empire State in years. Right now, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-governor-hochul-facing-real-pressure-to-sign-crypto-moratorium/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-governor-hochul-facing-real-pressure-to-sign-crypto-moratorium/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537717630000&amp;usg=AOvVaw0uV_wYwq8AzATCp-4JowqA" data-wpel-link="internal">New York is facing a bill</a> that’s been passed by the state legislature. The bill would enforce a moratorium on the crypto mining space and prevent all new digital currency mining companies from setting up shop within the region’s borders.</p>
<p>Zeldin has mentioned numerous times he would end the bill and prevent its passage if he were elected governor. In his campaign against Hochul, he clearly addressed many issues New York was facing. He discussed crime and inflation, items that Hochul – in the past – has refused to acknowledge. He also clearly won the one and only debate between himself and the democrat incumbent, and it appeared he was on a solid track to make native New Yorkers view the conservative party differently.</p>
<p>Sadly, this was not meant to be. Despite being a clear winner in many areas and having some solid ideas in place for the state, New York – as usual – chose to go blue and voted Hochul in for a second term despite her clear lack of attention to the well-being of those living in her state. Now, the crypto moratorium is back on the table, and Hochul has until the end of the year to decide if she’s going to sign it into law. Clearly, the people of New York don’t care about crypto enough to get rid of her.</p>
<p>New York has developed a reputation for being a very anti-crypto state. A big contributor to this is the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitlicense/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitlicense/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537717630000&amp;usg=AOvVaw2oI0R66233KwSXukvFUFB4" data-wpel-link="internal">BitLicense</a>, which was enacted in the year 2015. Many crypto companies left New York completely or were forced to end all their services there due to the harsh regulatory tactics enforced by the BitLicense. Acquiring one also came with monster-sized fees and given that the crypto space was still very much in its infancy at that time, several of these firms couldn’t afford to hawk up the required funds.</p>
<h2>The Bill Is Damaging</h2>
<p>John Olsen – the New York state lead for the Blockchain Association – explained that the moratorium would arguably make a lot of miners leave the state. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think you would see a swift exodus. Should the governor sign the bill, I think you would see a swift exodus of any miners that aren’t almost solely reliant on renewable energy. It’s a difficult time for the industry. New York probably wouldn’t be worth it if it doesn’t have [a] strong signal to the industry that it’s welcome here&#8230; That starts with a veto of that bill.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-continues-to-not-care-about-crypto/">New York Continues to Not Care About Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-continues-to-not-care-about-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>It Appears Michael Saylor Will Never Reject BTC</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/it-appears-michael-saylor-will-never-reject-btc/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/it-appears-michael-saylor-will-never-reject-btc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 15:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Saylor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroStrategy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75396</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Despite the recent crash of the crypto space, despite everything bitcoin has cost him, Michael Saylor – the former head executive of MicroStrategy, a one-time software giant that has since transformed into one of the biggest bitcoin bulls out there – says bitcoin is going to be a winning asset in the end. Michael Saylor Will Never<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/it-appears-michael-saylor-will-never-reject-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/it-appears-michael-saylor-will-never-reject-btc/">It Appears Michael Saylor Will Never Reject BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite the recent crash of the crypto space, despite everything bitcoin has cost him, Michael Saylor – the former head executive of MicroStrategy, a one-time software giant that has since transformed into one of the biggest bitcoin bulls out there – says <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/bitcoin-will-be-the-winner-because-bitcoin-is-a-digital-commodity-and-it-s-the-least-controversial-of-everything-said-microstrategy-s-michael-saylor/ar-AA13YdF2" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/bitcoin-will-be-the-winner-because-bitcoin-is-a-digital-commodity-and-it-s-the-least-controversial-of-everything-said-microstrategy-s-michael-saylor/ar-AA13YdF2&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537717369000&amp;usg=AOvVaw2kWpmknVD2L0hrzLsUsHPc" data-wpel-link="external">bitcoin is going to</a> be a winning asset in the end.</p>
<h2>Michael Saylor Will Never Give Up on BTC</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, he commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Speaking for all bitcoiners, we feel we’re trapped in a dysfunctional relationship with crypto and we want out. Bitcoin will be the winner because bitcoin is a digital commodity and it’s the least controversial of everything.</p></blockquote>
<p>Michael Saylor first began adding bitcoin to the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-microstrategy-bitcoin-bet-is-already-paying-off-big-time/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-microstrategy-bitcoin-bet-is-already-paying-off-big-time/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537717369000&amp;usg=AOvVaw3AG2iG7mBenyTfr1ujQmvv" data-wpel-link="internal">MicroStrategy balance sheet</a> in August of 2020. At that time, the world’s number one digital currency by market cap was trading in the $11K range, which was small compared to what the price would be just 12 months later. However, at the time, the price was considered a milestone for the currency, and apparently MicroStrategy wanted in.</p>
<p>During that month, the company purchased close to $400 million in BTC. This would be the first in a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/microstrategy-just-bought-a-whole-lot-more-btc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/microstrategy-just-bought-a-whole-lot-more-btc/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537717369000&amp;usg=AOvVaw1AwNz2_6wHWQ5TVfIE8mlZ" data-wpel-link="internal">string of purchases</a> that would ultimately reach beyond the billion-dollar mark. Bitcoin, in many ways, was still considered a very risky investment given how volatile it was. Its vulnerability to price swings was often labeled as the main reason as to why so many institutions refused to get involved in crypto investing, and MicroStrategy appeared to be a risk taker in this department.</p>
<p>At first, it appeared things were paying off. Throughout 2021, bitcoin’s price reached mega highs, and MicroStrategy was indeed experiencing huge growth as a result. Unfortunately, bitcoin took a serious beating this year, and instead of backing off like it probably should have, MicroStrategy – by way of Saylor’s incessant fanaticism – chose to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-just-bought-more-btc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-just-bought-more-btc/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537717369000&amp;usg=AOvVaw1MJxnz-uv-GII1awo1yTk9" data-wpel-link="internal">continue investing</a> in the digital asset.</p>
<p>MicroStrategy is now billions of dollars in the hole, and Saylor was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-btc-bull-and-microstrategy-chief-executive-steps-down/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-btc-bull-and-microstrategy-chief-executive-steps-down/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537717369000&amp;usg=AOvVaw3_Kg0l5aLqWFI5yhoXwfR7" data-wpel-link="internal">recently pressured to relieve</a> himself of his chief executive duties, instead reverting to the lesser position of executive chairman. The company that had been run under his careful eye for more than 30 years is no longer in his hands.</p>
<h2>More Players Will Enter</h2>
<p>To say Saylor’s constant admiration of bitcoin is likely overwrought would be an understatement. Nevertheless, he continues to push the BTC agenda and claims it has properties that cannot be ignored. Continuing his interview, Saylor said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We’re moving from the entrepreneurial stage… to an institutional digital asset stage where big players… are going to enter this space and we’re all just going to grow up and the world is going to benefit from that.</p></blockquote>
<p>At the time of writing, the price of bitcoin is at its lowest point since June of this year. It is presently trading in the high $17K range, which is a slight improvement over the recent $16K it struck.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/it-appears-michael-saylor-will-never-reject-btc/">It Appears Michael Saylor Will Never Reject BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/it-appears-michael-saylor-will-never-reject-btc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ahmad Abu Daher Is a Young (and Wealthy) Crypto Miner</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ahmad-abu-daher-is-a-young-and-wealthy-crypto-miner/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ahmad-abu-daher-is-a-young-and-wealthy-crypto-miner/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 13:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ahmad Abu Daher]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lebanon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75394</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ahmad Abu Daher is only 22 years old, yet he’s already making a handsome living as a bitcoin miner in his home country of Lebanon. Ahmad Abu Daher Is Doing Well as a Miner Daher runs a whole team and has been doing so ever since he graduated from university. He entered a world that was wrought with financial<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ahmad-abu-daher-is-a-young-and-wealthy-crypto-miner/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ahmad-abu-daher-is-a-young-and-wealthy-crypto-miner/">Ahmad Abu Daher Is a Young (and Wealthy) Crypto Miner</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ahmad Abu Daher is only 22 years old, yet he’s already <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/this-22-year-old-survives-lebanon-with-a-bitcoin-mining-business-thats-been-earning-2420000-a-month/ar-AA13SM7T" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/this-22-year-old-survives-lebanon-with-a-bitcoin-mining-business-thats-been-earning-2420000-a-month/ar-AA13SM7T&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537717364000&amp;usg=AOvVaw2l8SA84MZp_qGvbbnZDxE3" data-wpel-link="external">making a handsome living</a> as a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/mining/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/mining/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537717364000&amp;usg=AOvVaw1uvbV4ElZfU3FR1q9qsywC" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin miner</a> in his home country of Lebanon.</p>
<h2>Ahmad Abu Daher Is Doing Well as a Miner</h2>
<p>Daher runs a whole team and has been doing so ever since he graduated from university. He entered a world that was wrought with financial ruin, as Lebanon is currently dealing with the full collapse of its financial system and hyperinflation. He says he and his fellow miners work around the clock to constantly be adding new assets and units of bitcoin to the blockchain.</p>
<p>Right now, Daher runs a team of approximately 40 people from both Lebanon and Syria. In an interview, he commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>We can&#8217;t sleep. We can&#8217;t have any break. All my team is still awake. They don&#8217;t sleep. Our shift is working 16 hours per day, and sometimes, up to 18 or 19 hours.</p></blockquote>
<p>Lebanon used to be a solid financial center in the middle of the world. Sadly, the country has suffered due to years of war, bad spending decisions enforced by government regulators, and even Ponzi schemes. As a result, the banking sector in the country has become virtually non-existent in recent years, and many people struggle to remain afloat and maintain their livings.</p>
<p>Daher needed to find a way to make money fast after graduation. He started out small in the mining industry, first extracting units on just two or three outdated machines. From there, he got in touch with a friend that connected him to hydroelectric power, which ultimately allowed him to expand his business and bring more miners into the mix. He says:</p>
<blockquote><p>When we started, it was our great idea to make money while sleeping or eating.</p></blockquote>
<p>Initially, Daher went to school to study architecture, though he saw that many of his classmates were struggling to find work in that department after their studies were over. He realized he had to find a new way to make money, and crypto mining seemed like the prime way to do this. His company has now been in business for over two years and he’s not looking back.</p>
<p>Things have gotten so good that it’s not uncommon for Daher to pull in at least $20K a month through his mining efforts. He also has 400 crypto farms spread out across 42 separate villages.</p>
<h2>How Did Lebanon End Up Like It Is?</h2>
<p>Nicholas Shafer – a University of Oxford academic that’s studying Lebanon’s growing crypto mining sector – described the banking environment in the country, mentioning:</p>
<blockquote><p>Due to sanctions controls, difficulty with using cash, and specifically in Lebanon, the banking system and the inability to use dollars or wire money, USD Tether is essentially a key intermediary currency between people in the Chinese hardware market to Lebanese purchasers.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ahmad-abu-daher-is-a-young-and-wealthy-crypto-miner/">Ahmad Abu Daher Is a Young (and Wealthy) Crypto Miner</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ahmad-abu-daher-is-a-young-and-wealthy-crypto-miner/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>December 10, 2022: the biggest product launch ever planned by My NEO Group.</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/december-10-2022-the-biggest-product-launch-ever-planned-by-my-neo-group/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/december-10-2022-the-biggest-product-launch-ever-planned-by-my-neo-group/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 06:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75940</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEO X it’s the first one Super App which integrates into an all-in-one solution, fintech and crypto services, and hundreds of commonly used apps for online shopping and communication. NEO X The Super App Shift: How consumers want save, shop and spend in the connected economy, My NEO Group look at how consumer demand for<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/december-10-2022-the-biggest-product-launch-ever-planned-by-my-neo-group/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/december-10-2022-the-biggest-product-launch-ever-planned-by-my-neo-group/">December 10, 2022: the biggest product launch ever planned by My NEO Group.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEO X it’s the first one Super App which integrates into an all-in-one solution, fintech and crypto services, and hundreds of commonly used apps for online shopping and communication.</p>
<p><iframe loading="lazy" title="NEO X Super App. The all-in-one Solution powered by MY NEO GROUP" width="1778" height="1000" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/9XPTLemi-2Q?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>NEO X</em></p>
<p><strong>The Super App Shift: </strong></p>
<p><em>How consumers want save, shop and spend in the connected economy, My NEO Group look at how consumer demand for streamlined payment experiences has created widespread interest in a super app to </em><em>manage the complexity of modern life.</em></p>
<p>A broad range of recent technological changes, from advanced mobile devices to artificial intelligence (AI)powered standalone applications to new payments technologies, have changed the parameters of the possibilities for retailers, financial institutions (FIs) and consumers.</p>
<ul>
<li>Real-time connections between payment rails, retailers, essential and nonessential activities and digital identities power today&#8217;s consumer experiences.</li>
<li>We call this decentralized, evolving global infra- structure built for efficiency, security and intuitive user experience the ConnectedEconomy.</li>
</ul>
<p>Within the ConnectedEconomy, con- sumers engage in a range of core activities that power day-to-day life actions that are now fundamental interconnected. For example, shop- ping online can lead to ordering from restaurants via an app, which can nor- malize app-based grocery delivery, opening the door to many other con- nected undertakings. Though these actions are intertwined, the current infrastructure is anything but. The channels consumers use to engage in the ConnectedEconomy are disjointed, a nest of separate apps and websites from myriad providers that can clog smartphone home screens and neces- sitate the creation of overwhelming numbers of accounts (and the remem- brance and safekeeping of just as many account credentials).</p>
<p>A super app may fix this. A super app provides a user interface through which consumers can shop, order food, check social media, bank, crypto and so on — all within a single solution. It can help solve the current ecosys- tem’s decentralization problem and address consumers’ universal desire for consistent, secure and frictionless interactions throughout the pillars of their lives.</p>
<p><strong>Global consumers already want a super app: Approximately seven in 10 respondents report interest in such a solution.</strong></p>
<p>Driven by a desire for convenience and financial wellness — the latter especially among Generation Z consumers — most survey respondents have at least some interest in a solution that would allow them to manage payments and other everyday activities through a centralized tool. Overall, approx- imately onequarter are “very” or “extremely” interested in a super app, and consumers who have fully inte- grated</p>
<p>connective technology into their lives are approximately twice as likely as other respondents to exhibit this high interest.</p>
<p><strong> Consumers desire a super app, particularly for convenience and security.</strong></p>
<p>A core advantage of a super app is its elegance: such a solution takes what once was a tangled thread pile of apps, websites and channels and spools it into a single, centralized experience. Nearly four in 10 consumers who are “slightly” or “somewhat” interested in a super app highly value the benefit of minimizing the risk of losing sensitive information, and among highly interested consumers, that share rises to 57%. An equal share of highly interested consumers greatly values the convenience of coordinating different areas of life in one place.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-75942 aligncenter" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Picture64-600x385.jpg" alt="" width="600" height="385" /></p>
<p><strong>Why does Musk want to make an &#8216;everything app&#8217;?</strong></p>
<p><iframe loading="lazy" title="Could Elon Musk Turn Twitter Into a Super App?" width="1778" height="1000" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/gZqVoEKVwBk?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>Would you like to make your smartphone more efficient by managing all the main apps in a single centralized platform? From social networks, to WhatsApp, to those for online shopping, such as Amazon and many others.</p>
<p>The solution is NEO X. It&#8217;s the first “all-in-one” Super App that aggregates and makes your apps usable quickly, in a single login, freeing up storage space on your phone.</p>
<p>NEO X was conceived and built by MY NEO GROUP. This is why it is a real “Digital Ecosystem”, a versatile and scalable fintech platform, in which banking services and next-generation payment solutions are found. In the Super App you can aggregate all your current accounts, centrally manage transactions, deposit and exchange cryptocurrencies, and thanks to an innovative exchange system, use them to pay with a prepaid card, or with the integrated contactless system.</p>
<p><strong>On December 10, 2022, don&#8217;t miss the official launch of NEO X, live on the social networks of My NEO Group.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Date: December 10, 2022</strong></p>
<p>8:00 a.m. Miami</p>
<p>2:00 p.m. Italy</p>
<p>3:00 p.m. Latvia</p>
<p>6:00 p.m. Dubai</p>
<p>7:00 p.m. Mumbai</p>
<p><strong>Book your place for free now: </strong>shorturl.at/wAJL4</p>
<p><strong>More about My NEO Group: </strong><a href="https://myneo.org" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://myneo.org</a> and <a href="https://myneogroup.com" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://myneogroup.com</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/december-10-2022-the-biggest-product-launch-ever-planned-by-my-neo-group/">December 10, 2022: the biggest product launch ever planned by My NEO Group.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/december-10-2022-the-biggest-product-launch-ever-planned-by-my-neo-group/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Fresh Increase Possible Above This Resistance</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-fresh-increase-possible-above-this-resistance/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-fresh-increase-possible-above-this-resistance/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 05:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75936</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin cash gained pace above the $105 and $108 resistance levels against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above the $110 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $110 on the 4-hours chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-fresh-increase-possible-above-this-resistance/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-fresh-increase-possible-above-this-resistance/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Fresh Increase Possible Above This Resistance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin cash gained pace above the $105 and $108 resistance levels against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above the $110 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $110 on the 4-hours chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair must clear $112 and $114 to continue higher in the near term.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin cash price is climbing above $110 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-upside-break-above-18k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. BCH/USD could start a fresh surge if it clears the $114 level.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin cash price formed a decent support base above the $100 level. BCH started a recovery wave and was able to clear the $105 resistance zone.</p>
<p>The price climbed above the $107 and $108 resistance levels. Recently, there was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $110 on the 4-hours chart of the BCH/USD pair. The pair is now trading above the $110 zone and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-decline-below-105/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $112 level. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $117 swing high to $107 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $114 level or the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $117 swing high to $107 low, above which the price may perhaps rise towards the $120 level. Any more gains above $120 and $122 could set the pace for a move towards the $135 level in the coming days.</p>
<p>An immediate support on the downside is near the $110 level and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). The first major support sits near the $107 level. The next major support is near $100, below which the bears might aim $95. The next target for them may perhaps be near the $88 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_75937" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Bitcoin-Cash-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-75937" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-75937" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Bitcoin-Cash-1.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-75937" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Cash Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BCHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, bitcoin cash price is now trading above the $110 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price must clear $112 and $114 to continue higher in the near term.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for BCH/USD is slowly gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BCH/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $110 and $107.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $112 and $114.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-fresh-increase-possible-above-this-resistance/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Fresh Increase Possible Above This Resistance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-fresh-increase-possible-above-this-resistance/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The FTX Crash: What Experts Are Saying</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-ftx-crash-what-experts-are-saying/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-ftx-crash-what-experts-are-saying/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 17:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Edward Moya]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75392</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What are some experts saying about the rise and fall of FTX, which at one point was one of the largest and most popular digital currency exchanges in the world? FTX Has Crashed and Burned Craig Erlam – senior market analyst at Oanda – recently formed the following opinion about all the drama surrounding the crypto trading<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-ftx-crash-what-experts-are-saying/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-ftx-crash-what-experts-are-saying/">The FTX Crash: What Experts Are Saying</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What are <a href="https://time.com/nextadvisor/investing/cryptocurrency/bitcoin-ethereum-prices-binance-ftx-takeover/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://time.com/nextadvisor/investing/cryptocurrency/bitcoin-ethereum-prices-binance-ftx-takeover/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668531116382000&amp;usg=AOvVaw17A2xa6fxHwFIQVWrP6vyW" data-wpel-link="external">some experts saying about</a> the rise and fall of FTX, which at one point was one of the largest and most popular digital currency exchanges in the world?</p>
<h2>FTX Has Crashed and Burned</h2>
<p>Craig Erlam – senior market analyst at Oanda – recently formed the following opinion about all the drama surrounding the crypto trading platform:</p>
<blockquote><p>For a long time, bitcoin has aligned itself with broader risk appetite in the markets, but it goes without saying that Tuesday was not one of those days. Cryptocurrencies have been pummeled at the start of the week, with bitcoin down almost 20 percent in two days at one stage amid concerns over FTX and the implications for the FTT token.</p></blockquote>
<p>The situation <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried-cryptos-reigning-prince/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried-cryptos-reigning-prince/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668531116382000&amp;usg=AOvVaw1al9qYia5jhPYYOtz6WO1b" data-wpel-link="internal">surrounding FTX is not only</a> huge, but it’s one that nobody expected considering the firm’s standing in the digital currency space. By some measures, it was the second strongest and largest digital currency exchange anywhere, and many felt that nothing could beat it down. In fact, during this entire crypto winter, FTX has come to the aid of many other companies in trouble, providing millions of dollars in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-discusses-his-bailout-of-crypto-firms/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-discusses-his-bailout-of-crypto-firms/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668531116382000&amp;usg=AOvVaw1etDoCLXcm5Z2lnderQO0o" data-wpel-link="internal">bailout money so they wouldn’t</a> need to file bankruptcy or close their doors.</p>
<p>It appears, however, that that decision is now coming back to bite the company in the rear end, as FTX is now dealing with what it calls a “liquidity crunch.” FTX allegedly does not have the funds it needs to stay afloat, and the company later went to its primary rival Binance for help.</p>
<p>For a while, it looked like the larger company was going to bail out the smaller one, though the deal failed to materialize, and Binance issued the following statement about why it would not be moving forward with the acquisition:</p>
<blockquote><p>As a result of corporate due diligence, as well as the latest news reports regarding mishandled customer funds and alleged US agency investigations, we have decided that we will not pursue the potential acquisition of FTX.com.</p></blockquote>
<p>For a long time, FTX was one of those companies that gave crypto investors hope. They saw it as a firm that could survive anything and ensure the survival of others – even when economic turmoil had reached an all-time high. That image, however, is fading fast, and many crypto traders out there are likely feeling that if FTX isn’t safe, then nobody and nothing is.</p>
<h2>This Is a Bad Day for Crypto</h2>
<p>Edward Moya – another senior market analyst at Oanda – threw his two cents into the mix and offered the following commentary on the situation:</p>
<blockquote><p>Today is a bad day in crypto. Binance had to step in to save Sam Bankman-Fried’s FTX crypto exchange. [He] has been the white knight during this crypto winter and a liquidity crunch from him has triggered a wave of uneasiness across the cryptoverse.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-ftx-crash-what-experts-are-saying/">The FTX Crash: What Experts Are Saying</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-ftx-crash-what-experts-are-saying/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Texas Crypto Firm Is in Trouble for Defrauding COVID Program</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/a-texas-crypto-firm-is-in-trouble-for-committing-covid-program-fraud/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/a-texas-crypto-firm-is-in-trouble-for-committing-covid-program-fraud/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 15:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[COVID]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HODL LLC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PPP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75389</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Dallas man and the digital currency company he created are in hot water after being charged with defrauding a financial program introduced during the COVID era that was designed to keep businesses afloat. Crypto Company Fraud Thanks to COVID John Corbin Corona, age 35, was indicted in mid-November on counts of both money laundering and wire<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/a-texas-crypto-firm-is-in-trouble-for-committing-covid-program-fraud/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/a-texas-crypto-firm-is-in-trouble-for-committing-covid-program-fraud/">A Texas Crypto Firm Is in Trouble for Defrauding COVID Program</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Dallas man and the digital currency <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/cryptocurrency-company-owner-charged-with-covid-19-program-fraud/ar-AA13VP7g" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/cryptocurrency-company-owner-charged-with-covid-19-program-fraud/ar-AA13VP7g&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537716472000&amp;usg=AOvVaw2sTjuG2sgAvy1WL0TjeJT_" data-wpel-link="external">company he created are</a> in hot water after being charged with defrauding a financial program introduced during the COVID era that was designed to keep businesses afloat.</p>
<h2>Crypto Company Fraud Thanks to COVID</h2>
<p>John Corbin Corona, age 35, was indicted in mid-November on counts of both money laundering and wire fraud for allegedly inflating the size of his cryptocurrency business – HODL LLC – to garner extra funds through the PPP (Paycheck Protection Program) initiative.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/coronavirus/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/coronavirus/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537716472000&amp;usg=AOvVaw35REiJM2RYha7OQEM782hO" data-wpel-link="internal">COVID</a> was a rough time for everyone. It was a time of shutdowns, death, job losses, bankruptcies, and just about everything else you can imagine that would cause people to lose their minds. The one good thing that came out of it was the state of the crypto space, which seemed to flourish the entire time the pandemic was occurring.</p>
<p>While things ultimately began on a shaky note (the prices of many mainstream digital currencies fell at first), they ultimately picked up, and mainstream tokens like BTC and ETH began to experience serious boosts to their prices that caused them to reach new all-time highs by the time 2020 was over.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, COVID also gave birth to new crime waves, many of which stemmed from those who thought they could take money from already suffering individuals and from government programs. Several companies sought to take advantage of the PPP loan initiative that was put in place by exaggerating their revenue. This would allow them to garner additional funds to ensure their wealth stayed strong and they could enjoy luxury lifestyles.</p>
<p>Corona is allegedly one of those people. U.S. Attorney for the Norther District of Texas Chad E. Meacham explained in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>As millions of small business owners grappled with the fallout from the pandemic, this defendant raked in a couple hundred thousand bucks at his fellow citizens’ expense. The Paycheck Protection Program, funded by taxpayers, was designed to help small businesses stay afloat during the pandemic. The Justice Department will relentlessly pursue those who defrauded the PPP.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Lying to Get Money</h2>
<p>Corona runs a company called HODL LLC. It’s alleged to have operated a bitcoin mining pool know as Bitcoin Bank America. Corona is accused of fraudulently filing for two loans through the PPP program worth a total of $413,000 together. These loans were filed under the names Blue Vine Inc. and Fund Box Inc., both of which are companies that have partnered with HODL LLC in the past.</p>
<p>It is alleged via court documents that Corona lied about how much money his company made in the past to get extra funds. He also greatly exaggerated the number of employees allegedly working through his company and is believed to have even submitted false IRS statements. He faces up to 20 years in prison.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/a-texas-crypto-firm-is-in-trouble-for-committing-covid-program-fraud/">A Texas Crypto Firm Is in Trouble for Defrauding COVID Program</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/a-texas-crypto-firm-is-in-trouble-for-committing-covid-program-fraud/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Block Mate Is Instigating Quick and Easy Crypto Buys</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block-mate-is-instigating-quick-and-easy-crypto-buys/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block-mate-is-instigating-quick-and-easy-crypto-buys/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 13:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Andrew Smith]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Block Mate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain World]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75387</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto firm Block Mate Ventures has launched a new platform that will allow its customers to engage in instant crypto transactions. Traders and investors can log onto the website and instantly purchase assets like bitcoin and Ethereum in mere minutes or seconds. Block Mate Ventures Seeks to Make Crypto Purchases Faster The purchases can be done through credit cards<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block-mate-is-instigating-quick-and-easy-crypto-buys/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block-mate-is-instigating-quick-and-easy-crypto-buys/">Block Mate Is Instigating Quick and Easy Crypto Buys</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto firm Block Mate Ventures has launched a <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/pressreleases/22/11/g29520350/blockmate-launches-cryptocurrency-instant-buy-services-across-premium-blockchain-domains-and-annou" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.benzinga.com/pressreleases/22/11/g29520350/blockmate-launches-cryptocurrency-instant-buy-services-across-premium-blockchain-domains-and-annou&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537726168000&amp;usg=AOvVaw0V0CbY8mg8vdKPNiIlUv6r" data-wpel-link="exclude">new platform that will allow</a> its customers to engage in instant <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/crypto/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537726168000&amp;usg=AOvVaw1u3PYho9xPB20sLjZLmmim" data-wpel-link="internal">crypto</a> transactions. Traders and investors can log onto the website and instantly purchase assets like bitcoin and Ethereum in mere minutes or seconds.</p>
<h2>Block Mate Ventures Seeks to Make Crypto Purchases Faster</h2>
<p>The purchases can be done through credit cards or other local payment methods. Block Mate Ventures is introducing a new simplified interface that will be easy and readable for even those with limited or no trading experience. The onboarding process will also be super simple for anyone interested in engaging in the company’s services.</p>
<p>Andrew Smith – CEO of Blockchain World Ltd, the parent company of Block Mate Ventures – commented in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>The launch of <a href="http://blockchain.com.au/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=http://blockchain.com.au&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537726168000&amp;usg=AOvVaw26Ve4OifOBFMzlvbRsFK8T" data-wpel-link="external">blockchain.com.au</a> and <a href="http://blockchain.eu/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=http://blockchain.eu&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537726168000&amp;usg=AOvVaw3rs4wOWyjKy_ykpJmqoAYM" data-wpel-link="external">blockchain.eu</a> are examples of how Block Mate can monetize a deep portfolio of digital assets suitable for the blockchain and crypto sectors. Onboarding from fiat to crypto is one of the biggest challenges for customers new to the crypto space so addressing these issues with our premium domains enables Block Mate to monetize ownership while the domains appreciate as interest in the blockchain space grows. Although the sector is currently undergoing a crypto winter, we anticipate higher website traffic and demand for crypto onboarding as the sector cycles similar to previous downturns.</p></blockquote>
<p>The above news is a testament to the fact that despite current bearish conditions, the worlds of blockchain and cryptocurrency remains fresh and interesting in everyone’s minds. The digital currency arena has been bombarded with volatility over the last year. The space is not doing well, and the industry has lost more than $2 trillion in overall valuation.</p>
<p>On top of that, mainstream currencies like bitcoin – the world’s largest and most popular digital asset by market cap – have lost more than 70 percent of their value. BTC was initially trading for about $68,000 per unit in November of last year (a new all-time high), though at press time, the asset has fallen into the low $20K region. It’s a sad and ugly sight to see.</p>
<h2>A Super Easy Platform?</h2>
<p>When customers visit Block Mate, they are instantly prompted into selecting their digital currency of choice. They then select a digital wallet they’d like to use for checkout purposes. In the future, the team plans to offer digital wallet creation services for those with a little more trading experience and who would like to have more say in how their assets are handled. The company’s profits will also depend largely on things like transaction volumes and uptake.</p>
<p>As a leading web3 incubator focusing on blockchain businesses, Block Mate has worked to spread decentralized finance (defi) throughout the monetary space, thus giving traders and customers more autonomy. The company has been funding and creating successful ventures since the dotcom era.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block-mate-is-instigating-quick-and-easy-crypto-buys/">Block Mate Is Instigating Quick and Easy Crypto Buys</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block-mate-is-instigating-quick-and-easy-crypto-buys/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EOS Price Analysis: Bulls Aim Steady Increase Above $1</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bulls-aim-steady-increase-above-1/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bulls-aim-steady-increase-above-1/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 06:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EOS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75917</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>EOS price started a fresh increase above the $0.95 resistance against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above $0.95 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.94 on the 4-hours chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bulls-aim-steady-increase-above-1/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bulls-aim-steady-increase-above-1/">EOS Price Analysis: Bulls Aim Steady Increase Above $1</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>EOS price started a fresh increase above the $0.95 resistance against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $0.95 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.94 on the 4-hours chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move up if it clears the $1.00 and $1.02 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>EOS price is rising above $0.95 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-upside-break-above-18k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. The price could resume its increase if it clears the $1.00 and $1.02 resistance levels.</em></p>
<h2>EOS Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This week, EOS price started a fresh increase from the $0.90 zone against the US Dollar. The price gained pace and was able to clear the $0.95 resistance zone.</p>
<p>The price broke the $0.98 resistance zone and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-recovery-possible-if-it-clears-this-resistance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. The bulls even pushed the price above the $1.00 level. However, the bears appeared near the $1.02 level. A high is formed near $1.018 and the price is now consolidating gains.</p>
<p>On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $1.00 level. The first major resistance is near the $1.02 level, above which the price could rise steadily. In the stated case, it could rise towards the $1.10 level. Any more gains might send the price towards the $1.15 level.</p>
<p>On the downside, an immediate support is near the $0.965. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.9176 swing low to $1.0188 high.</p>
<p>The next key support is near the $0.950. There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.94 on the 4-hours chart of the EOS/USD pair. It is close to the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.9176 swing low to $1.0188 high. If there is a downside break below the $0.94 support, the price could revisit the $0.912 support.</p>
<div id="attachment_75918" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/EOS-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-75918" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-75918" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/EOS-1.png" alt="EOS Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-75918" class="wp-caption-text">EOS Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/EOSUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, EOS price is now trading above the $0.95 level and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could continue to move up if it clears the $1.00 and $1.02 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4-hours MACD – The MACD for EOS/USD is gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4-hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $0.95 and $0.94.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $1.00 and $1.10.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bulls-aim-steady-increase-above-1/">EOS Price Analysis: Bulls Aim Steady Increase Above $1</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bulls-aim-steady-increase-above-1/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
