<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 03:11:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ripple Price Analysis: Bulls In Control Above $0.50</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-in-control-above-0-50/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-in-control-above-0-50/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 03:18:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78658</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple price is facing resistance near the $0.550 level against the US dollar. The price is now trading above $0.50 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.5280 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Kraken). The pair could<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-in-control-above-0-50/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-in-control-above-0-50/">Ripple Price Analysis: Bulls In Control Above $0.50</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ripple price is facing resistance near the $0.550 level against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $0.50 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.5280 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start another major increase above the $0.450 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ripple price is rising above $0.510 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-key-resistance-near-28-5k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. XRP price must stay above the $0.500 support to remain in a bullish zone.</em></p>
<h2>Ripple Price Analysis</h2>
<p>After a successful break above the $0.480 level, Ripple price gained bullish momentum against the US Dollar. The XRP/USD pair broke the $0.50 resistance to move into a positive zone.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above the $0.512 resistance and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-upside-break-looms-at-0-485/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. The bulls even pushed the price above the $0.5250 resistance. A high is formed near $0.5464 and the price is now consolidating gains.</p>
<p>It is now trading above $0.500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, the price is facing resistance near $0.5450. The next major resistance is near the $0.5500 level.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $0.5500 resistance zone might start a strong increase. In the stated case, the price could even surpass the $0.5650 resistance. Any more gains might send the price toward the $0.600 resistance. Initial support on the downside is near the $0.5250 level or the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.4433 swing low to the $0.5464 high.</p>
<p>There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.5280 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair. The next major support is near the $0.500 level.</p>
<p>The 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.4433 swing low to the $0.5464 high is also near the $0.495 level. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.480 level, below which the price might even test $0.4650.</p>
<div id="attachment_78659" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Ripple.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78659" class="size-full wp-image-78659" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Ripple.png" alt="Ripple Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78659" class="wp-caption-text">Ripple Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Ripple price is now trading above the $0.50 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start another major increase above the $0.550 resistance.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XRP/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for XRP/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.528, $0.525, and $0.500.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.5450 and $0.5500.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-in-control-above-0-50/">Ripple Price Analysis: Bulls In Control Above $0.50</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-in-control-above-0-50/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sphere Financial Inc: Transforming the World of Finance with Ground breaking Blockchain Solutions</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sphere-financial-inc-transforming-the-world-of-finance-with-ground-breaking-blockchain-solutions/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sphere-financial-inc-transforming-the-world-of-finance-with-ground-breaking-blockchain-solutions/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 17:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78643</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sphere Financial Inc (SFI), a disruptive force in the finance industry, is revolutionizing the financial landscape with its unparalleled blockchain solutions. By empowering individuals and businesses worldwide with decentralized and all-inclusive approaches, SFI is redefining traditional finance and ushering in a new era of possibilities. Founded by visionary leaders disillusioned with exploitative banking practices, SFI<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sphere-financial-inc-transforming-the-world-of-finance-with-ground-breaking-blockchain-solutions/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sphere-financial-inc-transforming-the-world-of-finance-with-ground-breaking-blockchain-solutions/">Sphere Financial Inc: Transforming the World of Finance with Ground breaking Blockchain Solutions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sphere Financial Inc (SFI), a disruptive force in the finance industry, is revolutionizing the financial landscape with its unparalleled blockchain solutions. By empowering individuals and businesses worldwide with decentralized and all-inclusive approaches, SFI is redefining traditional finance and ushering in a new era of possibilities.</p>
<p>Founded by visionary leaders disillusioned with exploitative banking practices, SFI is on a mission to construct a financial ecosystem that transcends borders and extends opportunities to all. The company&#8217;s comprehensive suite of blockchain solutions caters to diverse industry needs, offering innovative solutions that address the pain points of traditional finance.</p>
<p>At the core of SFI&#8217;s mission is the creation of an accessible and inclusive financial ecosystem. The company drives innovation by constantly pushing boundaries, all while placing customers at the forefront of its operations. SFI&#8217;s commitment to customer-centricity, innovation, excellence, and long-term vision sets the company apart in its relentless dedication to sculpting the financial landscape.</p>
<p>SFI&#8217;s commitment to staying ahead of industry trends and embracing technological advancements is reflected in the expertise of its DeFi specialists, known as the DeBrain. This exceptional team ensures that SFI remains at the forefront of the rapidly evolving DeFi landscape, maximizing returns for clients through their cutting-edge strategies.</p>
<p>A ground breaking partnership with Satoshi AI, an industry-leading AI company, has revolutionized operational efficiency and accuracy in mining operations. By leveraging Satoshi AI&#8217;s advanced AI technologies, SFI has enhanced mining capabilities, optimizing resource allocation and improving overall profitability.</p>
<p>SFI&#8217;s ground breaking offerings extend beyond mining solutions. The company&#8217;s SpheriART platform enables creators to transform their digital creations into valuable assets through NFT minting. This innovative platform unlocks new opportunities for artists and content creators, bridging the gap between art and finance.</p>
<p>As part of its commitment to redefine the financial experience, SFI is preparing to launch Esfera, an upcoming wallet that promises convenience and security in decentralized finance. Esfera will provide users with a seamless and user-friendly interface, making decentralized finance accessible to all.</p>
<p>For more information about Sphere Financial Inc and its ground breaking blockchain solutions, please visit <a href="https://sphereinc.io/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://sphereinc.io/</a></p>
<p><strong>About Sphere Financial Inc:</strong></p>
<p>Sphere Financial Inc (SFI) is a disruptive force in the finance industry, offering unparalleled blockchain solutions that empower individuals and businesses worldwide. Through decentralized and all-inclusive approaches, SFI is redefining traditional finance, creating a financial ecosystem that transcends borders and extends opportunities to all. With a comprehensive suite of blockchain solutions, cutting-edge technology, and a commitment to customer-centricity, SFI is transforming the world of finance for a better future.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sphere-financial-inc-transforming-the-world-of-finance-with-ground-breaking-blockchain-solutions/">Sphere Financial Inc: Transforming the World of Finance with Ground breaking Blockchain Solutions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sphere-financial-inc-transforming-the-world-of-finance-with-ground-breaking-blockchain-solutions/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Four Men Indicted in North Korea Illicit Crypto Case</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/four-men-indicted-in-north-korea-illicit-crypto-case/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/four-men-indicted-in-north-korea-illicit-crypto-case/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 17:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[North Korea]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sanctions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78063</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>North Korea is back in the news when it comes to crypto. It appears the country just won’t go away and is still doing all it can to get its paws on illicit digital currencies, but countries like the United States are fighting back. North Korea Is At It Again It has been revealed that<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/four-men-indicted-in-north-korea-illicit-crypto-case/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/four-men-indicted-in-north-korea-illicit-crypto-case/">Four Men Indicted in North Korea Illicit Crypto Case</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>North Korea is back in the news when it comes to crypto. It appears the country just won’t go away and is still doing all it can to get its paws on illicit digital currencies, but countries like the United States are fighting back.</p>
<h2>North Korea Is At It Again</h2>
<p>It has been revealed <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/04/24/us/politics/justice-dept-cryptocurrency-north-korea.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">that the Justice Department</a> (DOJ) has indicted four men for allegedly stealing and laundering digital assets on behalf of an online criminal syndicate based in North Korea. The men are also accused of buying goods with USD in the past as a means of avoiding other sanctions.</p>
<p>The charges were filed in three separate cases in Washington. The coins are alleged to have been obtained by members of the Lazarus Group, which is an infamous hacking organization that has worked hard to garner illicit digital currencies in the past as the means of funding the ongoing nuclear program in North Korea.</p>
<p>The organization has targeted a wide array of digital currency enterprises in the past including <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/axie-infinity-gets-some-of-its-stolen-crypto-back/" data-wpel-link="internal">Axie Infinity</a>, and it’s believed members have stolen <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-north-korea-has-stolen-more-than-1-billion-in-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">more than $1 billion</a> in crypto.</p>
<p>The first charge saw a banker from China being indicted. He is 39-year-old Sim Hyon Sop, and he – along with three separate traders – are believed to have used international mixers and other means to convert stolen digital currencies by North Korean nationals into fiat currencies that were then used to buy illegal goods or fund ongoing nuclear missile production.</p>
<p>In the other indictments, the men who took part in the crimes were not named, though it’s been stated that these individuals used fake identities to garner blockchain jobs in the United States. From there, they utilized their access to said companies to garner more funds, which at the time of writing, are believed to exceed $12 million, all of which passed through Sim’s crypto wallet.</p>
<p>Overall, it’s believed that these individuals took part in more than 1,500 illicit trades, and that their customers – aside from North Korea – were traders and other companies seeking to engage in financial activities without the proper licenses to back themselves up.</p>
<h2>Trying to Fight Back</h2>
<p>While it may appear that North Korea is an unstoppable enemy when it comes to crypto crime, several nations in Europe and the U.S. have shown that they will not stand for illegal trickery and theft and have taken implicit actions to garner stolen funds back.</p>
<p>For example, not long ago, the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/norway-takes-back-stolen-crypto-from-north-korea/" data-wpel-link="internal">nation of Norway managed</a> to locate some of the money stolen from the Axie Infinity online crypto gaming platform that was stolen in 2022 and retrieve some of it. The U.S. has also implemented sanctions against crypto mixers like Tornado Cash to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/north-korea-crypto-mixer-tornado-cash-sanctioned-by-u-s/" data-wpel-link="internal">ensure that the means</a> North Korea uses to steal crypto remain limited.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/four-men-indicted-in-north-korea-illicit-crypto-case/">Four Men Indicted in North Korea Illicit Crypto Case</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/four-men-indicted-in-north-korea-illicit-crypto-case/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fision Uses Blockchain to Ensure the Trustfulness of Its Clothing Line</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-fision-uses-blockchain-to-ensure-the-trustfulness-of-its-clothing-line/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-fision-uses-blockchain-to-ensure-the-trustfulness-of-its-clothing-line/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 15:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cotton]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fision]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78060</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A company called The Fision is using blockchain to create new apparel. T-shirts, to be precise. The firm creates the shirts and sends them out to potential buyers. The big clincher is that they’re made only from trustfully sourced cotton, and blockchain technology is utilized to ensure that all the shirts sent out are fully<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-fision-uses-blockchain-to-ensure-the-trustfulness-of-its-clothing-line/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-fision-uses-blockchain-to-ensure-the-trustfulness-of-its-clothing-line/">The Fision Uses Blockchain to Ensure the Trustfulness of Its Clothing Line</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A company called The Fision is using <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/startup-launched-blockchain-traceable-good-100700159.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">blockchain to create new apparel</a>. T-shirts, to be precise. The firm creates the shirts and sends them out to potential buyers. The big clincher is that they’re made only from trustfully sourced cotton, and blockchain technology is utilized to ensure that all the shirts sent out are fully transparent and traceable from the beginning.</p>
<h2>The Fision Is Using Blockchain</h2>
<p>Josh Gelder – CEO of The Fision – explained in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>Our team is comprised of industry veterans and fueled by a desire to communicate the truth about the environmental and societal costs of the current industry. We see the future of fashion being transparent, and we came together to embark on making real industry change that aligns with our mission-driven values. We hope to showcase to consumers and to our peers alike what is possible utilizing tomorrow’s technologies today so that it becomes the industry norm of the future. We aim to inspire change, to share what we uncover, and to encourage all brands to do the same.</p></blockquote>
<p>The big thing about <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/blockchain/" data-wpel-link="internal">blockchain</a> is its alleged lack of need for middlemen or third parties to confirm information like transactions. This has been the primary notion behind the technology given that it’s mainly used to power the crypto industry.</p>
<p>However, blockchain can also be used to ensure the traceability of specific elements or goods. People want to make sure that they are buying from trusted sources and that the items used to make the products in question were not stolen or garnered through illicit practices.</p>
<p>For example, if you’re worried about palm oil production and you want to make sure your palm oil only comes from lawful, sustainable fields, the blockchain can help you ensure this by showing where the palm oil came from.</p>
<p>The Fision is a B-Corp, meaning that while it’s a money-making corporation, it has tied itself to a specific social cause and/or environmental issue as a means of allegedly trying to better the world. The T-shirts the company sells come from 80 percent Good Earth cotton, meaning the materials come from sustainable farming methods that promote soil health. Gelder continued his comments with:</p>
<blockquote><p>Good Earth Cotton is not only innovative, but also a climate positive leader. Good Earth Cotton’s regenerative farming method allows the soil to sequester more carbon than the entire cotton growth life cycle emits, which is a natural fit for us. We incorporate recycled cotton to encourage [circularity], to reinforce moving away from a purely extractive model and to further reduce the amount of water used in the creation of the T-shirts.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Offering Clean, Sustainable Clothing</h2>
<p>The remaining 20 percent of the cotton used from the T-shirts comes from fully recycled sources.</p>
<p>All the T-shirts are made in Los Angeles.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-fision-uses-blockchain-to-ensure-the-trustfulness-of-its-clothing-line/">The Fision Uses Blockchain to Ensure the Trustfulness of Its Clothing Line</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-fision-uses-blockchain-to-ensure-the-trustfulness-of-its-clothing-line/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>David Marcus Discusses the Future of BTC</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/david-marcus-discusses-the-future-of-btc/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/david-marcus-discusses-the-future-of-btc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 13:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[David Marcus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Libra]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78058</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>David Marcus – the former PayPal executive who worked on Facebook’s failed Libra project – believes that after everything that’s happened over the past two years, that bitcoin will still be the face of both money and payments in the future. David Marcus Sees the Promise in BTC Marcus, in a recent interview, revealed he’s<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/david-marcus-discusses-the-future-of-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/david-marcus-discusses-the-future-of-btc/">David Marcus Discusses the Future of BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>David Marcus – the former PayPal executive who worked on Facebook’s <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/facebook-blockchain-exec-david-marcus-is-leaving-the-company/" data-wpel-link="internal">failed Libra project</a> – believes that after everything that’s happened over the past two years, that <a href="https://www.theverge.com/23696466/bitcoin-crypto-lightning-network-lightspark-ceo-david-marcus" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">bitcoin will still be</a> the face of both money and payments in the future.</p>
<h2>David Marcus Sees the Promise in BTC</h2>
<p>Marcus, in a recent interview, revealed he’s been part of the crypto industry for some time. He, by his own admission, has “lived through” at least three separate crypto winters, though he’s confident he’s seen more than that. Regarding the crypto winter of 2022, he feels that the circumstances were relatively different compared with those of past winters. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think that this one is different because the industry got a lot bigger. So, the downturn affected many more people, touched more consumers, more companies, more investors. There was a ton more capital deployed in this cycle versus the previous cycles. So, it’s just bigger.</p></blockquote>
<p>However, he mentioned there’s still a lot of long-term opportunity for the market and said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Well, look, I think that everything that’s speculative ends up in booms and busts cycles. It’s only if you build something valuable that solves real-world problems that you can create long-standing value. So, I think we’re starting on that journey now. There are a bunch of companies that [have] built things that solve real-world problems, exchanges, wallets, and many more, but there was so much speculation and teams that were just building something just for the sake of listing a token and making a quick buck, and I feel like this era is coming to an end if it hasn’t ended already, and now teams are focusing on building valuable things.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Nobody Controls It</h2>
<p>Marcus is now in charge of a new bitcoin company called Light Spark. He’s moved over from stable currencies like Libra and is now focusing predominantly on BTC. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I had this idea in the back of my mind, but I wasn’t sure yet that I was going to just take the plunge and go with it. Many friends told me, ‘You should take at least nine months off,’ and after month three, I was really going crazy, so it was time for me to get back on the horse, but why Bitcoin? Because I’ve [concluded] that if you want a true, open, interoperable protocol for money on the internet, which is what we’re trying to help build here, it [needs] to be built on something that literally no one controls. Bitcoin is the only network and asset that fits the bill when you think about it that way. There’s no consortium of companies. There’s no people at the helm. There’s no leader. There’s Satoshi Nakamoto, but who knows who they or he or she is? And that’s kind of all the value of the network.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/david-marcus-discusses-the-future-of-btc/">David Marcus Discusses the Future of BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/david-marcus-discusses-the-future-of-btc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Following Shapella, Institutions Are More Interested in Ethereum</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/following-shapella-institutions-are-more-interested-in-ethereum/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/following-shapella-institutions-are-more-interested-in-ethereum/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 17:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shapella]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78048</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ever since the Shapella upgrade, it appears more institutions are interested in Ethereum. Ethereum Is Getting Way More Attention Ethereum is the world’s second largest digital currency by market cap and the primary competitor to bitcoin. Not long ago, the asset rose beyond the $2K mark for the first time in what felt like an<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/following-shapella-institutions-are-more-interested-in-ethereum/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/following-shapella-institutions-are-more-interested-in-ethereum/">Following Shapella, Institutions Are More Interested in Ethereum</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ever since the Shapella upgrade, it appears <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/04/22/bitcoin-and-crypto-now-braced-for-a-parabolic-price-move-as-ethereum-institutional-interest-explodes/?sh=763cce763c7d" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">more institutions are interested</a> in Ethereum.</p>
<h2>Ethereum Is Getting Way More Attention</h2>
<p>Ethereum is the world’s second largest digital currency by market cap and the primary competitor to bitcoin. Not long ago, the asset rose beyond the $2K mark for the first time in what felt like an eternity. The price boost stemmed <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-ethereum-shapella-upgrade-occurred-now-what/" data-wpel-link="internal">from a recent upgrade</a> to its network in which staked Ethereum units were suddenly available for withdrawal.</p>
<p>This has allegedly stirred the interest of institutional investors. According to Ali Martinez, a bitcoin and crypto analyst, the attention for both bitcoin and Ethereum have skyrocketed in recent weeks. Martinez mentioned in a recent Twitter post:</p>
<blockquote><p>Reserve risk just crossed 0 again. This bitcoin indicator signals huge potential. When the bitcoin reserve risk moves above 0, it signals parabolic price moves.</p></blockquote>
<p>Sadly, it appears the recent activity of bitcoin has rubbed traders the wrong way. For example, not long ago, the world’s number one digital currency by market cap <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">rose to a ten-month</a> high of about $30K, though it failed to retain this position <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-falls-to-28k-analysts-are-wondering-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">and eventually dipped</a> into the high $20K range. Yuya Hasegawa – a crypto market analyst at Bit Bank – recently wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>The market is struggling to find a reason to buy and support the price as profit-taking selling pressure and long liquidation have pushed down the price this week, while the U.S. stock market loses its direction. Unfortunately, despite the decline, bulls do not seem to have given up just yet as bitcoin futures market’s funding rate still reads positive, which could limit the upper potential for bitcoin and worsen its short-term drawdown.</p></blockquote>
<p>With activity and love for bitcoin going down in recent days, this has only paved the way for more institutional attention towards Ethereum, which was recently noted in a report by K33 research head Bendik Schei. The report says:</p>
<blockquote><p>As expected, Shanghai was followed by massive Ethereum withdrawals. The market overestimated the Shanghai selling pressure, leading Ethereum to outshine bitcoin on the backdrop of burgeoning institutional activity.</p></blockquote>
<p>In what appears to be a bonus maneuver, the Shapella upgrade <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/declining-bitcoin-ether-correlation-could-impact-crypto-investors-hedging-strategies-coinbase/ar-AA1afDEk" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">has further allowed</a> ETH to distance itself somewhat from BTC. Up to this point, Ethereum and bitcoin have long been correlated. When BTC goes up or down, ETH will usually follow suit, but this is arguably changing, as bitcoin – while traveling downward – is not affecting the bullish signs currently being noticed in Ethereum.</p>
<h2>The Separation of Two Coins</h2>
<p>Analysts David Duong and Brian Cubellis wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>The relevance of this falling correlation for institutional investors is that it can affect quantitative strategies that rely on cross hedging one asset for the other (or using ETH as a hedge for less liquid altcoins). It supports diversification arguments in favor of holding both BTC and ETH.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/following-shapella-institutions-are-more-interested-in-ethereum/">Following Shapella, Institutions Are More Interested in Ethereum</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/following-shapella-institutions-are-more-interested-in-ethereum/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Standard Chartered: BTC Will Hit a Six-Figure Price Soon</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/standard-chartered-btc-will-hit-a-six-figure-price-soon/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/standard-chartered-btc-will-hit-a-six-figure-price-soon/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 15:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Standard Chartered]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78045</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>After receiving a hardcore message of gloom and doom earlier today, it appears not everyone is worried about the state of crypto, and some – such as Standard Chartered – believe assets like bitcoin are well on their way to reaching new highs and the tops of the world’s financial ladders. Standard Chartered on the<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/standard-chartered-btc-will-hit-a-six-figure-price-soon/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/standard-chartered-btc-will-hit-a-six-figure-price-soon/">Standard Chartered: BTC Will Hit a Six-Figure Price Soon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After receiving a hardcore message <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/chamath-palihapitiya-crypto-isnt-doing-well-in-america/" data-wpel-link="internal">of gloom and doom</a> earlier today, it appears not everyone is worried about the state of crypto, and some – such as Standard Chartered – believe assets like bitcoin are well on their way to <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-could-hit-100000-by-end-2024-standard-chartered-says/ar-AA1agwjl" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reaching new highs and</a> the tops of the world’s financial ladders.</p>
<h2>Standard Chartered on the State of BTC</h2>
<p>Not long ago, Standard Chartered issued a report claiming that the crypto winter of 2022 is officially over, and analysts foresee bitcoin reaching a whopping $100,000 per unit in the coming months. This would make a huge change from where the world’s number one digital currency by market cap was just six months ago.</p>
<p>During that time (the end of 2022), the crypto world was suffering like it never had before. Assets like BTC lost more than 70 percent of their value after reaching all-time highs during the previous November, and the crypto world was in a tailspin of depression. The industry lost more than $2 trillion in overall valuation, and many thought crypto was on the verge of going out for good.</p>
<p>However, 2023 has been a year of incredible turnaround, and while there’s still plenty of healing room, the fact remains that bitcoin and many of its digital assets have really recovered from the bearish trends that took them down heavily during the previous 12 months. BTC has recently hit a ten-month high of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">about $30K</a>, and many analysts think the time has arrived for the crypto arena to receive its fair dues.</p>
<p>Geoff Kendrick – the head of digital assets research at Standard Chartered – explained in the report:</p>
<blockquote><p>While sources of uncertainty remain, we think the pathway to the USD 100,000 level is becoming clearer.</p></blockquote>
<p>He went on to suggest that bitcoin has recently garnered more steam behind its alleged “safe haven” status, which had been thinning out in recent months and years given the ugly state of the industry.</p>
<p>He also believes that bitcoin is once again being viewed as a “relative store of value and a means of remittance,” especially during the aftermath of the banking crisis which resulted in the collapse of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-more-banks-fell-bitcoin-rose-beyond-28k/" data-wpel-link="internal">roughly three separate</a> banks in the U.S.</p>
<h2>What Will Push the Asset Forward?</h2>
<p>One of the big things that he thinks will contribute to the surging of bitcoin’s price is the recent set of regulations <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/european-union-passes-heavy-string-of-new-crypto-regulations/" data-wpel-link="internal">implemented by the European</a> Union (EU). The continental organization has become the first of its kind to implement new digital currency-related laws on a broad scale as a means of keeping traders secure and reserved when engaging in investing strategies.</p>
<p>The move was clearly a response to the FTX collapse, which occurred last November. As one of the world’s leading digital currency exchanges, FTX resulted in more <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-the-damage-caused-by-ftx-was-worse-than-initially-thought/" data-wpel-link="internal">than $200 billion</a> in crypto being wiped away permanently.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/standard-chartered-btc-will-hit-a-six-figure-price-soon/">Standard Chartered: BTC Will Hit a Six-Figure Price Soon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/standard-chartered-btc-will-hit-a-six-figure-price-soon/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chamath Palihapitiya: Crypto Isn&#8217;t Doing Well in America</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/chamath-palihapitiya-crypto-isnt-doing-well-in-america/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/chamath-palihapitiya-crypto-isnt-doing-well-in-america/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 13:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chamath Palihapitiya]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78043</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is crypto in America dead? According to early crypto investor and venture capitalist Chamath Palihapitiya, the answer is a resounding “yes.” Chamath Palihapitiya Doesn&#8217;t Think Crypto Has a Future in America During a recent podcast interview, Palihapitiya mentioned that U.S. financial agencies like the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) are going after companies like Coinbase,<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/chamath-palihapitiya-crypto-isnt-doing-well-in-america/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/chamath-palihapitiya-crypto-isnt-doing-well-in-america/">Chamath Palihapitiya: Crypto Isn&#8217;t Doing Well in America</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is crypto in America dead? According to early crypto <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/04/24/crypto-is-dead-in-america-early-bitcoin-investor-issues-stark-coinbase-warning-amid-price-chaos/?sh=129bbd284367" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">investor and venture</a> capitalist Chamath Palihapitiya, the answer is a resounding “yes.”</p>
<h2>Chamath Palihapitiya Doesn&#8217;t Think Crypto Has a Future in America</h2>
<p>During a recent podcast interview, Palihapitiya mentioned that U.S. financial agencies like the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) are going after companies like Coinbase, and that they’re not likely to stop until the entire crypto arena is finished and gone.</p>
<p>He took issue with men like Gary Gensler – the current head of the SEC – who are blaming the crypto industry for the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-more-banks-fell-bitcoin-rose-beyond-28k/" data-wpel-link="internal">present banking crisis</a> we’re seeing in America, and he thinks this is likely to get in the way of further innovation. During the interview, Palihapitiya stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Crypto is dead in America. So, the United States authorities have firmly pointed their guns at crypto.</p></blockquote>
<p>The attacks on crypto were ultimately ramped up last November when leading digital currency exchange <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX</a> fell into a sorry and twisted state of bankruptcy. From there, many allegations arose claiming Sam Bankman-Fried – the man behind the company – took user funds and paid off loans with them or invested in Bahamian luxury real estate. He’s now awaiting trial <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-to-await-trial-at-his-parents-house/" data-wpel-link="internal">at his parents’ California</a> home.</p>
<p>Palihapitiya is very disappointed in that it appears many companies cannot escape the wrath of agencies such as the SEC no matter how hard they try to play by the rules. He again referred to Coinbase when making his point, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>Coinbase played by the rules, stood in line, [and] tried to do the right things. It seems that every step along the way, everything from board composition to executive composition to how they try to interact with the regulators, yet they were probably the furthest away from getting a license. The one that came the closest was the one that was the most fraudulent, which is FTX. How is that even possible? [Crypto companies are] probably the ones that were the most threatening to the establishment, and they were the ones that, in fairness to the regulators, did push the boundaries more than any other sector of the startup economy. So now, they’re paying the price for that. The bill has come due for them.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Going to Bermuda?</h2>
<p>Not long ago, Brian Armstrong – the head of Coinbase – said he’s exploring taking the firm to Bermuda or other outside territories unless the U.S. can take a clearer stance on crypto regulation. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Anything is on the table, including relocating or whatever is necessary. I think the U.S. has the potential to be an important market for crypto, but right now, we are not seeing that regulatory clarity that we need. I think in a number of years, if we don&#8217;t see that regulatory clarity emerge in the U.S., we may have to consider investing more elsewhere in the world.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/chamath-palihapitiya-crypto-isnt-doing-well-in-america/">Chamath Palihapitiya: Crypto Isn&#8217;t Doing Well in America</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/chamath-palihapitiya-crypto-isnt-doing-well-in-america/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Pepe the Frog Meme Currency Is Exploding in Price</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-pepe-the-frog-meme-currency-is-exploding-in-price/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-pepe-the-frog-meme-currency-is-exploding-in-price/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 17:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pepe the Frog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78027</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Meme coins are all the rage, and now it appears one based on the infamous image of Pepe the Frog is making waves in the crypto industry and witnessing price hikes like no other in its category. Pepe the Frog Is Now a Currency! Meme coins have always been extremely popular. One of the biggest<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-pepe-the-frog-meme-currency-is-exploding-in-price/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-pepe-the-frog-meme-currency-is-exploding-in-price/">New Pepe the Frog Meme Currency Is Exploding in Price</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Meme coins are all the rage, and now it appears <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/04/23/the-price-of-this-new-crypto-meme-coin-rose-21000-as-bitcoin-and-ethereum-stalled-but-theres-a-nasty-catch/?sh=2b35a11b3400" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">one based on the infamous</a> image of Pepe the Frog is making waves in the crypto industry and witnessing price hikes like no other in its category.</p>
<h2>Pepe the Frog Is Now a Currency!</h2>
<p>Meme coins have always been extremely popular. One of the biggest ones – <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/dogecoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">Dogecoin</a> – was initially created as a joke. It was literally built to make fun of the crypto arena and all those that sought to utilize its offerings or that had any respect for it. By some odd chance of fate, the currency has literally become one of the biggest digital currencies out there. It presently boasts a market cap that exceeds $1 billion and has been the subject of heavy <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/latest-elon-musk-tweet-sends-dogecoin-soaring/" data-wpel-link="internal">praise from Elon Musk</a>.</p>
<p>Dogecoin spawned other assets such as the Shiba Inu coin. The Shiba Inu dog long served as the cute little mascot for the parent digital asset Doge, and it wasn’t long before a spinoff of sorts was conceived in the Shiba Inu currency, which has also long been loved amongst crypto fans.</p>
<p>But Pepe the Frog appears to be on an entirely different playing field. At the time of writing, the currency is shooting up in price by a whopping 21,000 percent, and this is a currency that was only launched a few weekends ago. It now sits as the sixth-largest meme currency by market cap, which at press time, exceeds $150 million.</p>
<p>In a recent report, crypto research company Messari explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>Meme coins are once again polarizing the crypto world. A new project, Pepe, has amassed a $100 million market cap in less than one week. Similar to previous meme coin price surges, Pepe has generated eye-popping returns for its early investors.</p></blockquote>
<p>Pepe the Frog has been adopted by a wide array of online communities. The image has a circulation of about 420.69 trillion, though it’s not without controversy. The meme currency, for example, comes with a warning on sites like Coinmarketcap.com, which says traders should “exercise caution” if they choose to purchase or trade the asset.</p>
<p>The Messari report also said that while the currency may presently be doing well on paper, it doesn’t feel like it has any real future as a method of payment or as an actual digital token. Right now, the liquidity pool for the meme coin sits at a mere $3 million. Compare this with Ethereum, for example, whose daily trading volume is just shy of $800 million.</p>
<h2>Try to Be Careful</h2>
<p>The report said:</p>
<blockquote><p>One of the earliest buyers has turned a 0.125 Ethereum purchase into close to $2 million on-chain. However, since this individual owns 1.4 percent of the total supply, they will not be able to realize these returns without crashing the market.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-pepe-the-frog-meme-currency-is-exploding-in-price/">New Pepe the Frog Meme Currency Is Exploding in Price</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-pepe-the-frog-meme-currency-is-exploding-in-price/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
