<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 16:53:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Does Edward Snowden Have a Big BTC Stash?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/does-edward-snowden-have-a-big-btc-stash/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/does-edward-snowden-have-a-big-btc-stash/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 17:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[edward snowden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[russia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75705</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Edward Snowden – the U.S. intelligence leaker now living in Moscow – hinted he has quite a few bitcoins to his name, and that he’s got enough to live on “until the f*cking sun dies.&#8221; How Much BTC Does Edward Snowden Own? Since he left the country, many entrepreneurs in Silicon Valley have been sending<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/does-edward-snowden-have-a-big-btc-stash/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/does-edward-snowden-have-a-big-btc-stash/">Does Edward Snowden Have a Big BTC Stash?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Edward Snowden – the U.S. intelligence leaker now living in Moscow – hinted he has <a href="https://money.yahoo.com/snowden-bitcoin-holdings-151914599.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">quite a few bitcoins</a> to his name, and that he’s got enough to live on “until the f*cking sun dies.&#8221;</p>
<h2>How Much BTC Does Edward Snowden Own?</h2>
<p>Since he left the country, many entrepreneurs in Silicon Valley have been sending him bitcoin and crypto units so he could stay afloat. This has turned into a vast and considerable sum over the years, and Snowden appears to be living well thanks to the amount of crypto he’s accumulated.</p>
<p>In October, Snowden made a special panel appearance via satellite and was asked if he was “bitcoin rich.” He laughed this off, claiming that what everyone has read about his alleged bitcoin stash might not be true. While he didn’t give a straight answer, he hinted that his ties to crypto could have been forged and were initially based on a comment that was never meant to go public. This puts things in a weird loop and doesn’t allow crypto fans to fully understand what’s going on.</p>
<p>In the interview, he said:</p>
<blockquote><p>So, one thing I would say [is] don’t trust everything you read in the press. Secondly, that [bitcoin comment] was a private comment that wasn’t meant to be published, but look, my advice is as a privacy advocate. If anybody asks you what crypto you have, what you hold, the answer is, ‘What is crypto?’ but I’m not at risk of going hungry, certainly not this year. Let’s put it that way.</p></blockquote>
<p><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/edward-snowden/" data-wpel-link="internal">Snowden</a> stirred controversy roughly ten years ago when allegations from the U.S. government came about that he had removed more than one million classified documents from various U.S. systems in 2012 and 2013. At the time, Snowden was working as an NSA contractor in Hawaii. He’s believed to have provided over 200,000 of those documents to foreign entities and journalists before fleeing to Russia.</p>
<p>Not long after he fled the U.S., Kremlin-linked lawyer Anatoly Kucherena explained that Snowden was on the verge of building a “new life in Russia.” The attorney also commented that Snowden would hold an IT job with an unnamed enterprise in the country, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>Edward Snowden will begin working in one of the biggest Russian companies. His job will be to provide support and develop one of Russia’s biggest websites.</p></blockquote>
<h2>He&#8217;s Pretty Active</h2>
<p>One would think a man like Snowden would do everything to maintain a low profile, but this isn’t quite the case. In fact, he’s quite active on Twitter, and boasts a following of more than five million people. Following <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">the fall of FTX</a> he mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>There&#8217;s still a lot of trouble ahead, but for the first time in a while, I&#8217;m starting to feel the itch to scale back in.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/does-edward-snowden-have-a-big-btc-stash/">Does Edward Snowden Have a Big BTC Stash?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/does-edward-snowden-have-a-big-btc-stash/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>VISION OF BLOCKCHAIN (VOB) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vision-of-blockchain-vob-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vision-of-blockchain-vob-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 16:53:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76256</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec 30, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed VISION OF BLOCKCHAIN (VOB) on December 30, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the VOB/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading. By providing a stable token economy and opportunities to generate profits worldwide, ONE BIT<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vision-of-blockchain-vob-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vision-of-blockchain-vob-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">VISION OF BLOCKCHAIN (VOB) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec 30, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed VISION OF BLOCKCHAIN (VOB) on December 30, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the VOB/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading.</p>
<p>By providing a stable token economy and opportunities to generate profits worldwide, ONE BIT TEN creates a more advanced platform with its customized AI for trading solutions based on accurate information. Its native token <a href="https://bscscan.com/token/0xdb83921D152f362b8Ae79a1C2ddC33a5588924f7" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">VISION OF BLOCKCHAIN</a> (VOB) has been listed on LBank Exchange at 6:00 UTC on December 30, 2022, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision.</p>
<p><strong>Introducing </strong><strong>ONE BIT TEN</strong></p>
<p>ONE BIT TEN is a startup-sized company whose goal is to globally expand the trading platform through accurate information by combining and processing data based on the trading volume of CEX, DEX, and OTC markets in distributed supercomputers.</p>
<p>One of the major projects of ONE BIT TEN is ONEBOT. It’s an automated computer program designed to execute specific tasks with minimal human intervention. In the world of cryptocurrency, cryptocurrency transaction bots aim to provide AI Trading Indicators and automated transaction bots that automatically trade one or more cryptocurrencies on one or more platforms on behalf of the owner or user to minimize risk and help achieve maximum individual goals.</p>
<p>In the exchange, Tokens&#8217; transaction volume, ask and bid volumes, wallet movement, and numerous past data are combined to discard dummy data and process practical data only. A well performing leading index and trading bot are profitable. It is proven how well ONEBOT has combined automatic and manual trading strategies with monitoring system, which suggests the most efficient leading index and trading bot for trends supported by the user growth.</p>
<p>In short, ONEBOT can import, analyze, and use customized or other exchanges&#8217; trading strategy data to automate trading executions. ONEBOT is classified as a margin trading bot, a leverage bot, and a spot trading bot by using automated and smart technologies such as AI and machine learning, helping investors to maximize profits by efficiently acting as an auxiliary indicator.</p>
<p>ONEBOT is increasing the number of users by delivering constantly efficient data. In that process, ONT BIT TEN provides a more advanced platform by building an ecosystem with technological advancement and ONE BIT TEN&#8217;s Token. Furthermore, the project will provide stable Token Economy and revenue generation opportunities through the activation of NFT.</p>
<p>With all technological approaches to machine learning and deep learning, ONE BIT TEN will continue to develop aggressive development and marketing for global top-tier products in areas related to trading investments. In addition, ONE BIT TEN will further develop and strategically cooperate with developers who are globally distributed, participating in voluntary development, and even supercomputer projects that can handle a lot of data in higher speed.</p>
<p><strong>About VOB Token</strong></p>
<p>VISION OF BLOCKCHAIN (VOB) is the native token of ONE BIT TEN ecosystem. As VOB Token is used as a payment method, users will be able to gain greater flexibility in the application of usage. In addition, ONEBOT will increase flexibility and brand awareness by issuing VOB Token and using it as a payment. This will increase the adoption rate of platform for new members by securing abundant liquidity and enhancing security.</p>
<p>Based on BEP-20, VOB has a total supply of 300 million (i.e., 300,000,000) tokens, of which 1% is provided for presale ,10% is allocated to the management team, 14% is provided for the community, 20% is allocated for the ecosystem, 18% will be used for marketing, 6% is allocated to partners, 7% is allocated to the team and advisors, 9% will be used for development, 5% will be auto-burned, and the remaining 10% is reserved.</p>
<p>VOB token has been listed on LBank Exchange at 6:00 UTC on December 30, 2022, investors who are interested in the ONE BIT TEN investment can easily buy and sell VOB token on LBank Exchange right now. The listing of VOB token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p>
<p><strong>Learn More about</strong><strong> VOB Token:</strong></p>
<p>Official Website: <a href="http://www.vobc.io" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.vobc.io</a><br />
Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/onebittenglobal" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://t.me/onebittenglobal</a><br />
Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/1BIT_10" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/1BIT_10</a><br />
Instagram: <a href="https://www.instagram.com/onebitten_kr/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.instagram.com/onebitten_kr/</a><br />
Facebook: <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ONE-BIT-TEN-105686928470145" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://www.facebook.com/ONE-BIT-TEN-105686928470145</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vision-of-blockchain-vob-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">VISION OF BLOCKCHAIN (VOB) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vision-of-blockchain-vob-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LBank CEO Allen Wei Takes to Twitter to Address Cloud Service Provider Fud</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-ceo-allen-wei-takes-to-twitter-to-address-cloud-service-provider-fud/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-ceo-allen-wei-takes-to-twitter-to-address-cloud-service-provider-fud/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 16:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76253</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A temporary outage of LBank’s trade platform in December sparked discussion among users about how exchanges should approach cloud hosting. LBank CEO Allen Wei addressed the issue during a Twitter Space AMA on December 26th. Why this matters: Veteran crypto exchanges like LBank are trying to uphold a long-standing reputation of seeing little service downtime<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-ceo-allen-wei-takes-to-twitter-to-address-cloud-service-provider-fud/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-ceo-allen-wei-takes-to-twitter-to-address-cloud-service-provider-fud/">LBank CEO Allen Wei Takes to Twitter to Address Cloud Service Provider Fud</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>A temporary outage of LBank’s trade platform in December sparked discussion among users about how exchanges should approach cloud hosting. LBank CEO Allen Wei addressed the issue during a Twitter Space AMA on December 26th.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Why this matters:</strong> Veteran crypto exchanges like LBank are trying to uphold a long-standing reputation of seeing little service downtime and thwarting hackers.</p>
<p><strong>Driving the discussion: </strong>Alibaba Cloud, LBank’s Cloud Service Provider, experienced <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange/status/1604470379787214848" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">technical issues</a> on December 18th, rendering the trade platform temporarily inaccessible for over 7 million users.</p>
<ul>
<li>“Our engineers got word from Alibaba Cloud that there was a server crash ongoing and immediately started collaboration. It took quite some time to recover our services, but luckily we recovered access to our websites through other cloud services quite early on. The incident not only affected us, but a lot of other exchanges and internet companies,” Wei said.</li>
<li>LBank stresses that these kinds of outages have no impact on user assets whatsoever. “We take regular back-ups of platform data. The wallet side is especially secure because we utilize cold storage controlled by our own servers,” Wei added.</li>
<li>Addressing the FUD that popped up on social media during the incident, Wei stated this phenomenon isn’t an abnormality in the financial industry. “We’ve been through this before ever since kicking off in 2015 and are nonetheless still supporting crypto and blockchain tech. The community continues to trust us and trade on our platform, which underlines the potential of crypto,” the LBank CEO said.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>The Big Picture: </strong>Wei points out that exchanges should approach cloud hosting with a multipronged strategy.</p>
<ul>
<li>The exchange will take even more frequent back-ups of platform data in the future and will look towards other Cloud Service Providers to mitigate downtime. “We are slowly moving some of our services to other Cloud Providers, like Amazon”, Wei stated.</li>
<li>Continuing to provide excellent stability of the trading platform is an integral part of LBank’s global goals, Wei said. “In 2023, we would also like to expand on the local community relations we established this year”, he concluded.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank, founded in 2015, is an innovative global trading platform for various crypto assets. The exchange provides its users with safe crypto trading, specialized financial derivatives, and professional asset management services. It has become one of the most popular and trusted crypto trading platforms, with over 7 million users from more than 210 regions around the world.</p>
<p><strong>Press contact:</strong></p>
<p>LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
LBank Exchange<br />
press@lbank.info</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-ceo-allen-wei-takes-to-twitter-to-address-cloud-service-provider-fud/">LBank CEO Allen Wei Takes to Twitter to Address Cloud Service Provider Fud</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-ceo-allen-wei-takes-to-twitter-to-address-cloud-service-provider-fud/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Biden Voices Support for Crypto Regulation</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/biden-voices-support-for-crypto-regulation/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/biden-voices-support-for-crypto-regulation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 15:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75702</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The FTX collapse is going to go down as one of the biggest flops to ever occur in crypto. The event has caused several politicians to enter the regulatory call factory, one of which is Joe Biden. Joe Biden Wants the Crypto Space Regulated Thinking he can somehow make a difference, Biden recently voiced support<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/biden-voices-support-for-crypto-regulation/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/biden-voices-support-for-crypto-regulation/">Biden Voices Support for Crypto Regulation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX collapse</a> is going to go down as one of the biggest flops to ever occur in crypto. The event has caused several politicians to enter the regulatory call factory, <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/billybambrough/2022/11/20/joe-biden-leads-critical-call-for-game-changing-global-bitcoin-and-crypto-rules-after-shock-ftx-collapse/?sh=5bbe678b7f17" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">one of which is</a> Joe Biden.</p>
<h2>Joe Biden Wants the Crypto Space Regulated</h2>
<p>Thinking he can somehow make a difference, Biden recently voiced support for newfound digital currency regulation to ensure that what happened with FTX never happens again.</p>
<p>Biden initially sought to get the ball rolling on such a proposition in March of this year when he issued a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-is-the-biden-crypto-executive-order-all-its-cracked-up-to-be/" data-wpel-link="internal">crypto executive order</a> for financial agencies throughout the United States to begin researching digital currency platforms to see what the benefits and disadvantages could be for everyday Americans and financial systems. The order also opened the door to a digital version of USD.</p>
<p>Now, it looks like several world leaders are getting involved, with many speakers at the recent G20 Summit calling for more regulation of crypto. The G20 leaders issued the following joint statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>It is critical to build public awareness of risks, to strengthen regulatory outcomes, and to support a level playing field, while harnessing the benefits of innovation.</p></blockquote>
<p>In October, the Financial Stability Board (FSB) suggested new rules that would subject the crypto space to the same financial rules one often witnesses in the world of banks and standard monetization. These leaders supported such ideas, claiming:</p>
<blockquote><p>We welcome the FSB’s proposed approach for establishing a comprehensive international framework for the regulation of crypto asset activities based on the principle of ‘same activity, same risk, same regulation.’ The crypto assets ecosystem, including so-called [traditional currency-pegged] stable coins, is closely monitored and [should be] subject to robust regulation, supervision, and oversight to mitigate potential risks to financial stability.</p></blockquote>
<p>One of the big problems that occurred with FTX is that the head honcho behind it, Sam Bankman-Fried, may have taken user funds and lent them out to his second company Alameda Research. This put the FTX exchange in a dark place and caused it to fall $8 billion in debt.</p>
<p>Cristiano Bellavitis – a Syracuse University professor specializing in crypto and blockchain technology – recently mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>This is a wake-up call, rather than just a bump in the road, or even the end of the road. The sector is huge financially but has very limited regulation. The same problems would not have occurred in the mainstream financial system.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Things Will Fix Themselves</h2>
<p>Despite all the trouble, he is confident that the space is going to recover from all this in due time, though he doesn’t deny regulation could help. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>[The collapse of FTX] will diminish confidence in the crypto industry, but this industry and blockchain technology [are] here to stay. More regulation and clearer rules will only strengthen what this industry can do.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/biden-voices-support-for-crypto-regulation/">Biden Voices Support for Crypto Regulation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/biden-voices-support-for-crypto-regulation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Should Every Crypto Exchange Become Decentralized? Analysts Weigh In</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/should-every-crypto-exchange-become-decentralized-analysts-weigh-in/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/should-every-crypto-exchange-become-decentralized-analysts-weigh-in/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 13:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Caitlin Long]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75700</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency exchange FTX has seemingly come and gone. The fall of the exchange will likely go down as one of the biggest embarrassments of the digital currency space, and as a result, many players within the industry are calling for exchanges to become less centralized. They are certain that decentralized finance (or defi as<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/should-every-crypto-exchange-become-decentralized-analysts-weigh-in/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/should-every-crypto-exchange-become-decentralized-analysts-weigh-in/">Should Every Crypto Exchange Become Decentralized? Analysts Weigh In</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX</a> has seemingly come and gone. The fall of the exchange will likely go down as one of the biggest embarrassments of the digital currency space, and as a result, many players within the industry are calling for exchanges to become less centralized. They are certain that decentralized finance (or defi as it’s called for short) is <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/not-your-keys-not-your-coins-after-ftx-collapse-new-focus-on-decentralization-emerges/ar-AA14mZ3e" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">the answer to many</a> of crypto’s problems.</p>
<h2>Every Exchange Is Being Told What to Do</h2>
<p>There is a big idea flowing through the crypto space at the time of writing. It’s:</p>
<blockquote><p>Not your keys, not your coins.</p></blockquote>
<p>What this means is that if you don’t hold the private keys to your crypto account, it doesn’t matter how many units you purchase. They are not really yours, and they can be thrown out from under you anytime the holding exchange sees fit to take such action. Crypto fans are confident only in themselves, not in third parties.</p>
<p>Tracy Wang – a crypto journalist and managing editor – explained in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>A company like FTX was supposed to hold your assets, but they ended up lending them out. This is like taking power back and being… in charge of your own money.</p></blockquote>
<p>There are several exchanges out there that see firsthand the growing fear that stems from the collapse of FTX. Coinbase, for example, appears largely unaffected by the fall. The exchange has put out several notices telling customers that their funds are safe, and that it will never lend their money out without permission. However, some traders don’t feel this is enough reassurance.</p>
<p>Caitlin Long – the founder and CEO of crypto organization Custodia Bank – stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Those of us grizzled veterans have seen this game before. We&#8217;ve been trying to warn folks. Get your coins off exchanges, and there&#8217;s been a huge wave since FTX collapsed.</p></blockquote>
<p>It is now being reported that more than $2 billion in digital currency funds have been removed from crypto exchanges over just the last few weeks alone. The fear is real, and it appears to be getting bigger. This has caused a new call for regulation that would enforce new laws requiring crypto exchanges to protect their customers’ money at all costs. Long continued with:</p>
<blockquote><p>You’re just giving temporary possession for safekeeping. [They] can’t lease it to be used on Uber, and if the garage goes bankrupt, that’s not an asset of the garage. They can&#8217;t drive your car away. This is very simple, very boring, but foundational.</p></blockquote>
<h2>We Need to Be Like Wyoming</h2>
<p>To prove her point, she told traders to look at the current regulatory system in place in Wyoming. Any exchange based in the state, for example, is already being subjected to such rules. She says:</p>
<blockquote><p>If Wyoming&#8217;s regime had been in place, FTX wouldn’t have happened.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/should-every-crypto-exchange-become-decentralized-analysts-weigh-in/">Should Every Crypto Exchange Become Decentralized? Analysts Weigh In</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/should-every-crypto-exchange-become-decentralized-analysts-weigh-in/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Downside Break Below $100 Seems Real</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-downside-break-below-100-seems-real/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-downside-break-below-100-seems-real/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 05:28:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76249</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline from the $105 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below the $102 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $100 on the 4-hours chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-downside-break-below-100-seems-real/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-downside-break-below-100-seems-real/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Downside Break Below $100 Seems Real</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline from the $105 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below the $102 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $100 on the 4-hours chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it breaks the $95 and $92 support levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin cash price is declining from the $105 zone against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-drop-to-new-2022-lows/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. BCH/USD could decline heavily if there is a move below $95.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin cash price struggled to gain pace for a move above the $105 and $106 resistance levels. BCH formed a high near $103.70 and started a fresh decline.</p>
<p>There was a clear move below the $102.50 and $102.00 support levels. The bears even pushed the price below the $100 support and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). It traded as low as $97.22 and is currently consolidating losses.</p>
<p>It is now trading below the $102 zone and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-recovery-could-fade-near-102/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. An immediate resistance is near the $98.80 level. It is near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward wave from the $103.70 swing high to $97.22 low.</p>
<p>There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $100 on the 4-hours chart of the BCH/USD pair. The trend line is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward wave from the $103.70 swing high to $97.22 low.</p>
<p>The main resistance sits near the $104 level.  Any more gains above $104 and $105 could set the pace for a move towards the $110 level. If there is a move above the $110 resistance, the price could rise towards the $120 zone.</p>
<p>An immediate support on the downside is near the $97.50 zone. The next major support is near the $95 level, below which the bears might aim $85. The next target for them may perhaps be near the $80 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_76250" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Bitcoin-Cash-4.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76250" class="size-full wp-image-76250" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Bitcoin-Cash-4.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76250" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Cash Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BCHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, bitcoin cash price is now trading below the $102 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it breaks the $95 and $92 support levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for BCH/USD is gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BCH/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $95 and $92.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $100 and $102.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-downside-break-below-100-seems-real/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Downside Break Below $100 Seems Real</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-downside-break-below-100-seems-real/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vulcan Blockchain’s Auto-Rebasing Layer 1 Set for Release Q1 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vulcan-blockchains-auto-rebasing-layer-1-set-for-release-q1-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vulcan-blockchains-auto-rebasing-layer-1-set-for-release-q1-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 17:21:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76237</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>December 28, 2022, Tallinn, Estonia: Vulcan Blockchain has just announced that its’ novel auto-rebasing Layer 1 protocol will launch in Q1 of 2023. The protocol, which has been under development for some time aims to balance supply side issues affecting market stability. In this vein, the primary key feature of the Vulcan Blockchain is its<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vulcan-blockchains-auto-rebasing-layer-1-set-for-release-q1-2023/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vulcan-blockchains-auto-rebasing-layer-1-set-for-release-q1-2023/">Vulcan Blockchain’s Auto-Rebasing Layer 1 Set for Release Q1 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>December 28, 2022, Tallinn, Estonia: </strong>Vulcan Blockchain has just announced that its’ novel auto-rebasing Layer 1 protocol will launch in Q1 of 2023. The protocol, which has been under development for some time aims to balance supply side issues affecting market stability. In this vein, the primary key feature of the Vulcan Blockchain is its Auto-Rebasing mechanism, which adjusts the circulating supply of $VUL (the native coin) every 15 minutes.</p>
<p>Vulcan, named after the god of fire and forge, features unique never before seen blockchain technology. Auto-Rebasing is a unique feature that allows a blockchain to automatically adjust its supply of circulating coins. This can be an important tool for maintaining the stability and value of the native coin over time, as well as providing a more predictable and transparent monetary policy.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://vulcanblockchain.com" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Vulcan Blockchain</a> is also Auto-Compounding, which means that as a holder of $VUL, your ownership of coins increases with each epoch.</p>
<p><em>“In addition to providing stability, an Auto-Rebasing blockchain can also help to provide greater transparency and predictability,” </em></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">said <strong>Jason Matthison, COO of Vulcan</strong>.</p>
<p><em>“By clearly outlining the rules and conditions under which the supply of tokens will be adjusted, an auto-rebasing blockchain can give users and investors a better understanding of the monetary policy of the network. This can help to increase confidence in the network, making it more attractive to users and investors,”</em> he added.</p>
<p>To add to its Auto-Rebasing, Auto-Compounding capabilities, the Vulcan Blockchain also has a unique burn mechanism, known as the &#8220;Fire Pit” (a null address). 80% of all transaction fees on the network are automatically sent to the Fire Pit, which is totally inaccessible and burns the coins from the circulating supply forever. This feature allows $VUL to become hyper deflationary and a trusted store of value cryptocurrency over time.</p>
<p>The combination of these features, along with the commitment to decentralization, makes the Vulcan Blockchain the ideal platform for DeFi applications. Whether you are a user, developer, or investor, the invitation exists to join the <a href="https://vulcanblockchain.com" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Vulcan Network</a> on this exciting journey and be a part of the future of DeFi.</p>
<h4>About Vulcan Blockchain</h4>
<p>Vulcan Blockchain is the first blockchain with a built-in Auto-Rebasing mechanism, which adjusts the circulating supply of $VUL (the native coin) every 15 minutes. The Vulcan Blockchain is also Auto-Compounding, which means that as a holder of $VUL, your ownership of coins increases with each epoch. The combination of these features, along with the commitment to decentralization, makes the Vulcan Blockchain the ideal platform for DeFi applications.</p>
<p><strong>Media Contact:</strong><br />
Adrian Pante<br />
adrian.p@vulcanblockchain.com</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vulcan-blockchains-auto-rebasing-layer-1-set-for-release-q1-2023/">Vulcan Blockchain’s Auto-Rebasing Layer 1 Set for Release Q1 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vulcan-blockchains-auto-rebasing-layer-1-set-for-release-q1-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Two Men in Estonia Charged with Crypto Fraud</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/two-men-in-estonia-charged-with-crypto-fraud/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/two-men-in-estonia-charged-with-crypto-fraud/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 17:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Estonia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fraud]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75698</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Two men in the eastern European nation of Estonia have been arrested after they defrauded crypto investors of more than $575 million in digital funds. Two Men in Estonia Charged with Crypto Crimes The arrests were issued by federal agents based in the United States. Both Sergei Potapenko and Ivan Turogin – each is 37<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/two-men-in-estonia-charged-with-crypto-fraud/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/two-men-in-estonia-charged-with-crypto-fraud/">Two Men in Estonia Charged with Crypto Fraud</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Two men in the eastern European nation of Estonia have <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/us-authorities-2-estonians-arrested-in-24575m-crypto-scam/ar-AA14q8Gp" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">been arrested after they</a> defrauded crypto investors of more than $575 million in digital funds.</p>
<h2>Two Men in Estonia Charged with Crypto Crimes</h2>
<p>The arrests were issued by federal agents based in the United States. Both Sergei Potapenko and Ivan Turogin – each is 37 years of age – have been charged with crimes like wire fraud and conspiracy to commit money laundering. It is also believed that there were four other accomplices helping the crime duo commit their illicit actions, though these individuals have not been identified at the time of writing. However, it is believed that they are living in either Estonia, Switzerland, or Belarus.</p>
<p>Prosecutors claim the men defrauded hundreds of thousands of people between 2015 and 2019. All potential investors were persuaded to purchase contracts for a crypto mining service known as Hash Flare. They were also lured into investing in an alleged virtual currency banking portal called Polybius Bank. Sadly, both firms operated as classic pyramid schemes, meaning the money that was given to the men was never put towards valid investments.</p>
<p>It is believed that the men utilized the funds to purchase real estate, luxury vehicles, and other items on themselves. Both men are in custody in Estonia and awaiting extradition to the United States for their trials and potential sentencing per a ruling from the Justice Department (DOJ).</p>
<p>In a statement, Seattle U.S. Attorney Nick Brown explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>These defendants capitalized on both the allure of cryptocurrency, and the mystery surrounding cryptocurrency mining, to commit an enormous Ponzi scheme. They lured investors with false representations and then paid early investors off with money from those who invested later. They tried to hide their ill-gotten gain in Estonian properties, luxury cars, bank accounts, and virtual currency wallets around the world.</p></blockquote>
<p>Right now, both <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/estonia/" data-wpel-link="internal">Estonia</a> and the United States are working hand in hand to confiscate all the properties and other luxury items the pair accumulated for themselves. They are also striving to enter their bank accounts and confiscate all the funds they’ve gathered over the years. It is unclear if the men have found legal representation at this time, and the trial is set to occur in Seattle as several of their victims live in the state of Washington.</p>
<h2>Setting Things Straight</h2>
<p>Assistant Attorney General Kenneth A. Polite, Jr. of the Justice Department’s Criminal Division said:</p>
<blockquote><p>New technology has made it easier for bad actors to take advantage of innocent victims – both in the U.S. and abroad – in increasingly complex scams. The department is committed to preventing the public from losing more of their hard-earned money to these scams and will not allow these defendants, or others like them, to keep the fruits of their crimes.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/two-men-in-estonia-charged-with-crypto-fraud/">Two Men in Estonia Charged with Crypto Fraud</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/two-men-in-estonia-charged-with-crypto-fraud/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Paul Krugman: BTC Is on the Verge of Disappearing</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paul-krugman-btc-is-on-the-verge-of-disappearing/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paul-krugman-btc-is-on-the-verge-of-disappearing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 15:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paul Krugman]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75696</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nobel Prize-winning economist Paul Krugman is confident bitcoin and Ethereum, the world’s two biggest digital currencies by market cap, aren’t going to last much longer and are headed for points of no return. Paul Krugman Thinks BTC Is Done A lot has happened in the crypto arena in just the last few months. For one<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paul-krugman-btc-is-on-the-verge-of-disappearing/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paul-krugman-btc-is-on-the-verge-of-disappearing/">Paul Krugman: BTC Is on the Verge of Disappearing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nobel Prize-winning economist Paul Krugman is <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/billybambrough/2022/11/22/headed-for-oblivion-800-billion-crypto-price-shock-sparks-fears-of-catastrophic-end-for-bitcoin-and-ethereum/?sh=779c62771caa" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">confident bitcoin and</a> Ethereum, the world’s two biggest digital currencies by market cap, aren’t going to last much longer and are headed for points of no return.</p>
<h2>Paul Krugman Thinks BTC Is Done</h2>
<p>A lot has happened in the crypto arena in just the last few months. For one thing, the fall of crypto exchange FTX has sent ripples throughout the space that have seemingly caused a lot of other exchanges and blockchain-based companies to feel the heat. Aside from this, the prices of many digital currencies are struggling to maintain their present levels, with assets like BTC now falling into the low $16K range at the time of writing.</p>
<p>This is the lowest the asset has been in over two years, and many analysts think the currency could fall to 2019 levels. Paul Krugman is going a step further and claiming that bitcoin and many of its altcoin cousins are “headed for oblivion.”</p>
<p>In a recent interview, Krugman stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>It&#8217;s hard to see what advantage these firms would have over ordinary banks. Even if the value of bitcoin doesn&#8217;t go to zero (which it still might), there&#8217;s a strong case that the crypto industry, which loomed so large just a few months ago, is headed for oblivion.</p></blockquote>
<p>The FTX disaster is likely going to go down as one of the biggest digital currency embarrassments in history. The enterprise, first beginning in the year 2019, was long considered one of the big golden players in the industry, having accumulated billions of dollars in user funds over the course of three years and eventually rising to the top of the exchange ladder.</p>
<p>It’s founder and head executive, Sam Bankman-Fried, was considered a genius by many, and prior to the company’s fall, his net worth was estimated to be above $16 billion, though that’s all changed now that the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">company has had</a> to file bankruptcy and Bankman-Fried has resigned from his post.</p>
<p>For a while, it looked like larger competitor Binance was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">going to buy the</a> smaller firm out, but this wasn’t meant to be. Now, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/congress-wants-to-really-regulate-crypto-after-ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">regulators everywhere are renewing</a> calls for high-end regulation to ensure that what happened with FTX never happens again.</p>
<h2>Regulation Needs to Come in</h2>
<p>Anna Becker – chief executive of crypto trading firm Endo Tech – said:</p>
<blockquote><p>If crypto is to survive, we will need to see an agreed form of regulation that comes from within the industry and is overseen by regulatory bodies such as the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC) to ensure proposed standards are maintained. Heightened regulation is a matter of urgency and needs to be established immediately. For retail investors who aren’t as well versed in risk as professional investment firms, they deserve trustworthy oversight, guidance, and risk disclosure.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paul-krugman-btc-is-on-the-verge-of-disappearing/">Paul Krugman: BTC Is on the Verge of Disappearing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paul-krugman-btc-is-on-the-verge-of-disappearing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
