<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 19:05:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Lynk Seeks to Redefine Community Governance with Node NFT Program</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lynk-seeks-to-redefine-community-governance-with-node-nft-program/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lynk-seeks-to-redefine-community-governance-with-node-nft-program/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 19:05:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78114</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SocialFi platform Lynk set to launch its exclusive Node NFT Program to foster the growth of a decentralized Web3 community Lynk is setting the stage for a new era in decentralized community governance with the introduction of its Node NFT Program. Aimed at empowering early adopters, this groundbreaking initiative is expected to facilitate the growth<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lynk-seeks-to-redefine-community-governance-with-node-nft-program/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lynk-seeks-to-redefine-community-governance-with-node-nft-program/">Lynk Seeks to Redefine Community Governance with Node NFT Program</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong><em>SocialFi platform Lynk set to launch its exclusive Node NFT Program to foster the growth of a decentralized Web3 community</em></strong></p>
<p>Lynk is setting the stage for a new era in decentralized community governance with the introduction of its <a href="https://app.lynk.im/#/mint/node-nft" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Node NFT Program</a>. Aimed at empowering early adopters, this groundbreaking initiative is expected to facilitate the growth of a vibrant community in Web3, while showcasing the company&#8217;s commitment to innovation and inclusivity.</p>
<p>The SocialFi platform has made great strides in the first quarter of 2023, most notably with the launch of its much anticipated Finder and Keeper NFT collections. In March, Lynk introduced its NFT staking function, allowing users to stake their NFTs to earn attractive rewards. Lynk’s decision to launch on the Arbitrum network, has also enabled faster transactions and lower fees for its users.</p>
<h4>Node NFT Program</h4>
<p>The Node NFT Program is a strategic move designed to provide advanced level Keeper NFTs to community members who are actively contributing and looking to get ahead faster. By offering unique rewards and opportunities, Lynk aims to utilize the program to drive stronger participation within its growing ecosystem. The goal is to ensure that the platform remains dynamic, competitive, and appealing to new users, while also providing existing members with fresh avenues for growth.</p>
<p>There are 3 tiers of Node NFTs that can be minted in Gen I of the program; Common, Special, and Rare tiers. Each of them comes with a different amount of Charisma (CA) points and Attribute Points (AP), offering holders different advantages in levelling up their NFTs for greater rewards and benefits. These Keeper NFTs will advance straight to Legendary rank and members will receive additional rewards as they help to expand and grow the Lynk community.</p>
<h4>Something Different, Something New</h4>
<p>In today&#8217;s fast-paced world of technology, the Lynk Node NFT Program stands as a prime example of how Web3 values can be seamlessly integrated into daily interactions. By focusing on decentralization, ownership, and privacy, Lynk allows users to take control of their digital lives, leading the way for a more equitable and transparent decentralised ecosystem.</p>
<p>The potential for expansion is immense, with plans to introduce additional generations of Node NFTs that may feature even more attractive rewards and benefits. The company believes that a fair and transparent assessment process is crucial for the platform&#8217;s continued success; to guarantee the long-term success and sustainability of the program, Lynk is committed to ongoing evaluation and refinement of its offerings based on user feedback and engagement metrics.</p>
<p>Lynk&#8217;s Node NFT Program is poised to play a significant role in promoting the adoption of Web3 values and help shape a decentralised future. By nurturing a passionate and skilled community of early adopters, the company hopes to collectively work towards the creation of a fairer and more equitable digital world.</p>
<h4>Conclusion</h4>
<p>Lynk&#8217;s vision extends beyond its own platform, aspiring to be a catalyst for change in the broader Web3 space. The company aims to inspire other platforms and communities to embrace values such as decentralization, transparency, and user ownership that can help drive the industry forward. The Node NFT Program is just the beginning of Lynk&#8217;s journey toward realizing this vision, and the company invites interested parties; partners, developers and users, to join them as they embark on this mission.</p>
<p>To stay updated on Lynk’s progress and its latest announcements, be sure to follow the platform&#8217;s social media channels.</p>
<p>Website: <a href="http://lynk.im/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://lynk.im/</a><br />
Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/lynksanctuary" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/lynksanctuary</a><br />
Discord: <a href="https://discord.gg/6JcgvUzdPj" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://discord.gg/6JcgvUzdPj</a><br />
Medium: <a href="https://medium.com/@lynksanctuary" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://medium.com/@lynksanctuary</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lynk-seeks-to-redefine-community-governance-with-node-nft-program/">Lynk Seeks to Redefine Community Governance with Node NFT Program</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lynk-seeks-to-redefine-community-governance-with-node-nft-program/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk Pushes Crypto While Poking Fun of Biden</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-pushes-crypto-while-poking-fun-of-biden/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-pushes-crypto-while-poking-fun-of-biden/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 17:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77599</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Elon Musk is pushing bitcoin and other digital currencies in the midst of the U.S. banking crisis and recently posted a tweet in which he makes fun of criminal-in-chief Joe Biden. Elon Musk Takes Issue with Biden Not long ago, the phony president of the United States issued comments on social media talking about his<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-pushes-crypto-while-poking-fun-of-biden/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-pushes-crypto-while-poking-fun-of-biden/">Elon Musk Pushes Crypto While Poking Fun of Biden</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Elon Musk is pushing bitcoin and other digital currencies in the midst of the U.S. banking crisis and <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/03/23/banks-are-melting-elon-musk-sends-warning-to-joe-biden-and-the-fed-amid-wild-bitcoin-ethereum-and-crypto-price-swings/?sh=48200f1c7198" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">recently posted a tweet</a> in which he makes fun of criminal-in-chief Joe Biden.</p>
<h2>Elon Musk Takes Issue with Biden</h2>
<p>Not long ago, the phony president of the United States issued comments on social media talking about his administration’s climate change achievements. This is the first sign that something is wrong. The banks are failing, the economy is in shambles, people are still left behind in Afghanistan, and you want to be talking about how you’ve lowered carbon emissions by half a point or something? This is downright ridiculous, and Tesla’s Elon Musk was one of the first to notice.</p>
<p>In a response to Biden, Musk wrote the following:</p>
<blockquote><p>The banks are melting.</p></blockquote>
<p>For all that Biden has allegedly done to prevent glaciers from dying, he hasn’t implemented the same tactics for financial institutions, it seems. At the time of writing, several U.S. and European financial firms – like Silvergate, Signature, and Silicon Valley – <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-more-banks-fell-bitcoin-rose-beyond-28k/" data-wpel-link="internal">have crashed and burned</a>, and others were on the brink of collapsing (such as Credit Suisse) <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/03/19/ubs-agrees-to-buy-credit-suisse-as-regulators-look-to-shore-up-global-banking-system.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">before being saved</a> by other institutions at the last minute.</p>
<p>The situation is also not being helped by the Federal Reserve. Not long ago, Jerome Powell – aka the “Fed head” – announced <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/federal-reserve-hikes-rates-again-what-will-happen-to-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">that interest rate hikes</a> were again in order. Another 0.25 basis points were added to America’s already expanding interest rates. Any economist – or general member of the public – could tell these morons that THIS WAS NOT THE TIME for another rate hike. When banks are crashing left and right, at the very least, you leave things the way they are.</p>
<p>Jerome Powell has commented that the U.S. is not out of the woods yet when it comes to inflation, and thus interest rate hikes are still probable throughout 2023. Still, Ilya Volkov – chief executive of Swiss-based international fintech platform You Hodler – commented that the situation could be worse, stating:</p>
<blockquote><p>After the collapse of Silvergate, Silicon Valley Bank and Signature Bank, the Fed reduced its aggressive rhetoric, which was a positive signal for financial markets despite the sharp drops in bank stocks. The positive impact is also clearly seen in the bond market. The yield spread between two-year and ten-year U.S. treasuries, the main indicators for financial professionals, significantly decreased lately. So, a future 25 basis point increase by the Fed is already in the price.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Bitcoin Is Staying Strong</h2>
<p>The good news is that bitcoin and other forms of crypto appear to be weathering the storm. BTC is still trading for over $28,000, meaning it has shot up 70 percent from where it was at the end of 2022.</p>
<p>This is a good sign that the currency has managed to mature somewhat and push beyond the issues of the previous year.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-pushes-crypto-while-poking-fun-of-biden/">Elon Musk Pushes Crypto While Poking Fun of Biden</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-pushes-crypto-while-poking-fun-of-biden/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Texas Is Still a Crypto Mining King</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-is-still-a-crypto-mining-king/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-is-still-a-crypto-mining-king/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 15:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[china]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Texas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77597</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Texas became a serious crypto mining hub about two years ago, and it looks like things are set to stay this way for some time. Despite a wide array of headwinds and problems the industry has been facing, Texas crypto mining has remained quite steady, and the Lone Star State is still being sought out<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-is-still-a-crypto-mining-king/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-is-still-a-crypto-mining-king/">Texas Is Still a Crypto Mining King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Texas became a serious crypto mining hub about two years ago, and it looks like things are set to stay this way for some time. Despite a wide array of headwinds and problems the industry has been facing, Texas crypto mining has remained quite steady, and <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/despite-industry-headwinds-bitcoin-mining-101336236.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">the Lone Star State is still being</a> sought out by new companies and facilities.</p>
<h2>Texas Is Still the High-Ranking Crypto Mining Official</h2>
<p>Texas <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-is-still-a-major-crypto-mining-hub/" data-wpel-link="internal">became a serious region</a> for crypto mining beginning in the summer of 2021. The state attracted a lot of miners from China who were suddenly facing an <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-crypto-mining-clampdown-in-china-is-not-over/" data-wpel-link="internal">oppressive regime out</a> of Beijing that said they either had to move out completely or end their mining operations overnight. The idea was that China wanted to be more carbon neutral, a decision that put a nation that was once responsible for about 65 to 75 percent of the world’s overall mining projects out of commission.</p>
<p>Texas seemed like a good area given it offered vast open land and cheap electricity. The area <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kentucky-and-texas-are-seeing-a-boom-in-crypto-mining-projects/" data-wpel-link="internal">saw a huge burst</a> of activity following China’s ruling and it’s remained in a positive place since.</p>
<p>In a recent interview, Lee Bratcher – president of the industry group Texas Blockchain Council – said that the mining industry in Texas has not been without its issues, and the space has been occasionally bogged down with problems that have put the future of the mining sector in jeopardy. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>There&#8217;s been some challenges with the bitcoin mining industry.</p></blockquote>
<p>Among the issues he’s referring to are bankruptcies, which were rather prominent in 2022 given how bearish the year was. Bitcoin, for example, dropped from its November 2021 all-time high of about $68,000 per unit and fell into the mid-$16K range by the end of the year. This caused many mining companies and other crypto firms centered around BTC to have to enter <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">bankruptcy proceedings</a> and shutter their doors.</p>
<p>According to Matt Prusak – chief commercial officer at crypto miner U.S. Bitcoin Corp – one of the biggest issues facing the crypto mining space is how much flak it gets for its energy usage, and several reports have <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-bitcoin-mining-may-require-more-energy-than-180-countries/" data-wpel-link="internal">been published documenting</a> this in the past. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin mining is a very energy intensive business, which is why we tend to find places like West Texas to be full of bitcoin miners.</p></blockquote>
<h2>So Much Energy Use!</h2>
<p>Joshua Rhodes – a research scientist at the University of Texas at Austin – also threw his two cents into the mix, commenting:</p>
<blockquote><p>There are a lot of bitcoin mines that are trying to connect to the system. If all of them were to connect in the timelines that they are looking to connect, then it probably would present an issue to the grid because that load would be growing way faster than it ever has before.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-is-still-a-crypto-mining-king/">Texas Is Still a Crypto Mining King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-is-still-a-crypto-mining-king/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will Bitcoin Hit $100K Soon? Some Analysts Think So&#8230;</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-at-100k-this-year-some-analysts-think-so/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-at-100k-this-year-some-analysts-think-so/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 13:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[balaji srinivasan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marshall Beard]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77593</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With bitcoin trading for just over $28,000 per unit at the time of this writing, it really looks like the many elements that brought BTC down in 2022 may be behind us, and several analysts are contemplating if a $100K price is in BTC’s immediate future. Many Believe Bitcoin Could Hit $100,000 in 2023 The<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-at-100k-this-year-some-analysts-think-so/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-at-100k-this-year-some-analysts-think-so/">Will Bitcoin Hit $100K Soon? Some Analysts Think So&#8230;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With bitcoin trading for just over $28,000 per unit at the time of this writing, it really looks like the many elements that brought BTC down in 2022 may be behind us, and <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-at-100000-insiders-say-the-cryptocurrency-could-test-new-highs-this-year/ar-AA18XT27" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">several analysts are contemplating</a> if a $100K price is in BTC’s immediate future.</p>
<h2>Many Believe Bitcoin Could Hit $100,000 in 2023</h2>
<p>The price of the world’s number one digital currency by market cap has rallied by more than 70 percent since the end of last year. Among the people who think bitcoin could hit six-figure territory in 2023 is Marshall Beard, chief strategy officer at crypto exchange Gemini. In a recent interview, he said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think bitcoin probably breaks all-time highs this year. It doesn&#8217;t take much more for it to lift.</p></blockquote>
<p>He is confident that if bitcoin is again able to reach its November 2021 high of $68,000 per unit before the year is out, he doesn’t think it’ll have any trouble reaching $100,000.</p>
<p>One of the reasons for bitcoin’s sudden and meteoric rise is the state of the banking industries in both America and Europe. Over the past two months, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-more-banks-fell-bitcoin-rose-beyond-28k/" data-wpel-link="internal">various banks in the</a> United States – including Silvergate, Silicon Valley, and Signature – have crashed and burned, and the idea that centralized exchanges are no longer as stable as we’ve all been told has caused a lot of people to turn their backs on the standard monetary system and put all their money into more risky assets like BTC, thus cementing its position as “digital gold.”</p>
<p>This is why the coin is seeing so much action as of late. Trading has increased, and bitcoin is attracting fans like never before. Oliver Linch – CEO of Bittrex Global – mentioned in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think the rally is explicable by saying people have got freaked out by the banking system by the collapses.</p></blockquote>
<p>Despite all the powerful predictions and the air of positivity that appears to be permeating the space, many analysts have said they don’t want to go overboard, and they are criticizing a recent prediction made by Balaji Srinivasan – the form technology chief of popular digital currency exchange Coinbase – that BTC could hit a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/balaji-srinivasan-btc-will-hit-1-million-in-two-months/" data-wpel-link="internal">price of $1 million within</a> the next two months.</p>
<h2>Maybe $1 Million in 60 Days Is a Bit Much</h2>
<p>For bitcoin to hit that mark, it would need to spike 3,600 percent in the next 60 days. Beard thinks it’s possible BTC could hit $1 million in the future, but not in such a short period. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>There&#8217;s probably a world where bitcoin hits a million dollars. I think for bitcoin to be a million dollars in 90 days, some crazy things are happening in the world, which we don&#8217;t want.</p></blockquote>
<p>He further mentioned that he thinks it will be at least ten more years before BTC hits such a peak.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-at-100k-this-year-some-analysts-think-so/">Will Bitcoin Hit $100K Soon? Some Analysts Think So&#8230;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-at-100k-this-year-some-analysts-think-so/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Risk of Fresh Drop To $100</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-100/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-100/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 03:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78121</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline below the $125 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below the $120 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $120 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-100/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-100/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Risk of Fresh Drop To $100</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline below the $125 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below the $120 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $120 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it stays below the $120 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin cash price is declining below the $125 zone against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-29250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. BCH/USD could extend losses if there is a close below $115.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin cash price struggled to gain pace for a move above the $130 and $132 resistance levels. BCH formed a high near $136.18 and started a fresh decline.</p>
<p>There was a clear move below the $126.00 and $125.00 support levels. The pair even declined below the $120 support. It tested the $112 level. A low is formed near $111.66 and the price is now consolidating losses. It is now trading near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the key drop from the $136.18 swing high to the $111.66 low.</p>
<p>Besides, it is trading below the $120 zone and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bulls-struggle-to-keep-bch-in-bullish-zone/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. Immediate resistance is near the $118.80 level. The next key resistance is near $120.</p>
<p>There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $120 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair. The main resistance is now forming near $124 or the 50% Fib retracement level of the key drop from the $136.18 swing high to the $111.66 low.</p>
<p>Any more gains above $120 and $124 could set the pace for a move toward the $132 level. If there is a move above the $132 resistance, the price could rise toward the $136 zone.</p>
<p>If not, the price might continue lower below $115. Immediate support on the downside is near the $114 zone. The next major support is near the $112 level, below which the bears might aim for $100.</p>
<div id="attachment_78122" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/04/Bitcoin-Cash-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78122" class="size-full wp-image-78122" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/04/Bitcoin-Cash-3.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78122" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Cash Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BCHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Bitcoin cash price is now trading below the $120 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $120 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for BCH/USD is gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BCH/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $114 and $112.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $120 and $124.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-100/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Risk of Fresh Drop To $100</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-100/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The SEC&#8217;s Case Against Ripple Could Result in a Massive Win for the Crypto Company</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-secs-case-against-ripple-could-result-in-a-massive-win-for-the-crypto-company/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-secs-case-against-ripple-could-result-in-a-massive-win-for-the-crypto-company/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 17:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77582</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>XRP – the native digital token of crypto firm Ripple – experienced a sharp price hike in late March after several investors and fans felt they had reason to believe Ripple could potentially win its ongoing court case with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Could Ripple Beat the SEC? The SEC has made a<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-secs-case-against-ripple-could-result-in-a-massive-win-for-the-crypto-company/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-secs-case-against-ripple-could-result-in-a-massive-win-for-the-crypto-company/">The SEC&#8217;s Case Against Ripple Could Result in a Massive Win for the Crypto Company</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>XRP – the native digital token of crypto firm Ripple – <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/03/22/xrp-cryptocurrency-jumps-as-investors-hope-ripple-will-win-sec-case.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">experienced a sharp price hike</a> in late March after several investors and fans felt they had reason to believe Ripple could potentially win its ongoing court case with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<h2>Could Ripple Beat the SEC?</h2>
<p>The SEC has made a habit out of attacking virtually every single digital currency company over the last six or seven years. The agency is going after every firm that took part in token offerings or provided interest or other rewards through token investments. The idea is that these tokens are securities, and thus the firms in question did not follow present SEC regulations when issuing said currencies to traders.</p>
<p>One of the companies that the SEC has been targeting hard over the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-is-looking-to-file-legal-action-against-ripple/" data-wpel-link="internal">past few years is Ripple</a>. Many crypto investors pointed out a supplemental notice issued by Monica Long – the current president of Ripple – saying that she and her fellow executives are very hopeful that the SEC case will result in a win for the digital currency firm. She confirmed in the notice that the “facts and the law” were on the side of Ripple, and that she doesn’t believe the ruling judge will take the side of the SEC.</p>
<p>Following these comments, XRP – which at the time, was at around 45 cents – rose by a whopping 20 percent. Vijay Ayyar – vice president of international crypto exchange Luno – said in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Overall, crypto markets have rallied in the past week or so given the anticipation of a pause or slowdown in interest rates and the slowdown in inflation.</p></blockquote>
<p>In a separate statement, Long commented on why she thinks Ripple has a strong chance of being victorious. She mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>We’re seeing action through enforcement versus setting clear rules and regulation, which is what all of us in the industry desire. Europe is really emerging as a leader in setting really clear regulations and rules that allow crypto companies and also traditional finance to embrace crypto.</p></blockquote>
<p>One of the more recent crypto firms to have been victimized by the SEC was trading platform Kraken, stationed in Northern California. The <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/" data-wpel-link="internal">company was forced</a> to part with a $30 million penalty fee and end all its staking services and activities.</p>
<h2>Gary Gensler on Kraken</h2>
<p>Regarding that scenario, SEC Chair Gary Gensler stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>There’s a handful of tokens that have registered. The intermediaries, the storefronts if you wish, the casinos that people are investing in and investing at need to properly comply and disentangle these bundled products. If this field has any chance of survival and success, it’s time-tested rules and laws to protect the investing public.</p></blockquote>
<p>Ripple should feel confident that the SEC is <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/could-grayscale-actually-defeat-the-sec-in-court/" data-wpel-link="internal">also slated to lose</a> its case with Grayscale, a BTC trust.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-secs-case-against-ripple-could-result-in-a-massive-win-for-the-crypto-company/">The SEC&#8217;s Case Against Ripple Could Result in a Massive Win for the Crypto Company</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-secs-case-against-ripple-could-result-in-a-massive-win-for-the-crypto-company/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>East Lyme Resident Loses $60K to Crypto Scammers</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/east-lyme-resident-loses-60k-to-crypto-scammers/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/east-lyme-resident-loses-60k-to-crypto-scammers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 15:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scam]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[East Lyme]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77578</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An elderly man living in the East Lyme region of Connecticut has allegedly lost more than $60,000 in crypto to scammers at the time of writing. Police are now investigating to understand what happened. East Lyme Resident Loses a Lot of Cash and Crypto Michael Finkelstein – chief of the East Lyme Police Department –<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/east-lyme-resident-loses-60k-to-crypto-scammers/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/east-lyme-resident-loses-60k-to-crypto-scammers/">East Lyme Resident Loses $60K to Crypto Scammers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An elderly man living in the East Lyme region of Connecticut <a href="https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/cryptocurrency-scam-east-lyme-senior-citizen-theft-17850657.php" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">has allegedly lost more</a> than $60,000 in crypto to scammers at the time of writing. Police are now investigating to understand what happened.</p>
<h2>East Lyme Resident Loses a Lot of Cash and Crypto</h2>
<p>Michael Finkelstein – chief of the East Lyme Police Department – says crypto scams have become constant issues in his state, and that his department heads are receiving calls almost on a regular basis from people who believe they have lost money or been victimized. He commented in a recent interview that the $60,000 sum in question has been the largest thus far. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The East Lyme Police Department urges residents to always keep themselves and their accounts safe, and use extreme caution when contacted and told to provide any funding to individuals. We are hopeful that continuing to shine a light on these constant scams will help keep our residents safe.</p></blockquote>
<p>A relative of the victim is alleged to have gotten in touch with East Lyme police to let them know about what was going on. Right now, the identity of the victim has not been revealed. He is only being referred to as a “senior citizen in the community” in documents pertaining to the matter. The relative said that the man had received a call from someone claiming that fraudulent charges had appeared on his bank statements.</p>
<p>From there, the man was transferred to a second person who claimed to be an attorney. The person then gave the victim instructions on how he could send a payment to settle the charges. He had to withdraw a certain amount of money without telling anyone, then travel to a nearby bitcoin ATM and convert the cash to crypto. The money could then be uploaded to a digital wallet and sent to the attorney (aka the scammer).</p>
<p>As much as $60,000 was converted into BTC. There is good news in that members of the investigating police force were able to recover about $40K, though there’s still another $20K to go. Finkelstein said cases like these tend to be difficult in that most crypto is not recoverable once it’s sent. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>In so many of these cases, life savings are stolen and not recoverable.</p></blockquote>
<h2>This Happens Way Too Much</h2>
<p>Crypto scams have become extremely prominent in recent years. Many of them take on the form of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/romance-scam/" data-wpel-link="internal">romance scams</a>, in which hackers target those looking for love online. Once they find people they feel they can victimize, they get to know them well enough that they can convince them to invest in phony crypto platforms.</p>
<p>Once they do, they begin to see returns, though problems arise when they try to make withdrawals, and they’re often unable to get their funds back unless they invest even more.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/east-lyme-resident-loses-60k-to-crypto-scammers/">East Lyme Resident Loses $60K to Crypto Scammers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/east-lyme-resident-loses-60k-to-crypto-scammers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What&#8217;s Really Making Bitcoin Spike? Analysts Weigh In</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/whats-really-making-bitcoin-spike-analysts-weigh-in/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/whats-really-making-bitcoin-spike-analysts-weigh-in/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 13:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[banks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zhong Yang Chan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77576</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What’s really behind the sudden rise of bitcoin? The world’s number one digital currency has had a very successful 2023 thus far, spiking by as much as $12,000 in the last three months, but while it’s easy to assume that the asset is on the rise strictly because of banking failures in America, some analysts<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/whats-really-making-bitcoin-spike-analysts-weigh-in/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/whats-really-making-bitcoin-spike-analysts-weigh-in/">What&#8217;s Really Making Bitcoin Spike? Analysts Weigh In</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What’s really behind the sudden rise of bitcoin? The world’s number one digital currency has had a very successful 2023 thus far, spiking by as much as $12,000 in the last three months, but while it’s easy to assume that the asset is on the rise strictly because of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-just-got-higher-and-higher-in-mid-march/" data-wpel-link="internal">banking failures</a> in America, some analysts believe the truth is <a href="https://www.usnews.com/news/top-news/articles/2023-03-22/analysis-whats-behind-bitcoins-latest-surge" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">more complicated</a> than that.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Is Really Moving Up This Year</h2>
<p>Not long ago, bitcoin reached a new <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-more-banks-fell-bitcoin-rose-beyond-28k/" data-wpel-link="internal">nine-month high of $28,000</a>. While this wasn’t where the currency stood in November of 2021 (during that time, bitcoin hit a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit), things are starting to look up for the currency, especially when one considers how bad 2022 really was.</p>
<p>During that year, the crypto space lost more than $2 trillion in valuation. This was due, in part, to major assets such as BTC losing as much as 70 percent of their overall values, and many investors wound up on the losing side of the spectrum.</p>
<p>So, the big question is, “What’s fueling these present gains?” Noelle Acheson, an economist that’s been tracking the crypto sector for the past seven years, says that indeed the banking failure of America is largely behind the rise, though there are smaller aspects within that realm that seem to be contributing as well.</p>
<p>In a recent interview, she said central bank hikes are more the reason for the sudden spikes along with the fact that credit costs are nearing their peak. This is causing a lot of people to turn their backs on centralized financial services and find alternative methods of investing and garnering capital, and bitcoin is becoming a major answer for several of them. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The macro narrative is the number one. Bitcoin is not just a risk asset; it is arguably the most sensitive to monetary liquidity out of all of the risk assets.</p></blockquote>
<p>She also said bitcoin is still greatly propelled by a belief that it will someday fulfill the prophecy of pushing credit cards, checks, and fiat currencies to the side and serve as the ultimate payment method.</p>
<p>Other analysts are rather dismissive of the idea that BTC is doing well because banks are not. Usman Ahmad – CEO of Zodia Markets – explained in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>It&#8217;s rather narrow-minded to say that bitcoin is going to succeed because a bank failed, but confidence is almost a critical factor. Confidence in the banking system has been damaged.</p></blockquote>
<h2>There Are Many Investors Playing Important Roles</h2>
<p>Zhong Yang Chan – head of research at Coin Gecko – also threw his two cents into the mix, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin&#8217;s recent bull run looks to be mainly supported by individual investors, ranging from retail to whales, as we have seen evidence of institutions exiting during this rally.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/whats-really-making-bitcoin-spike-analysts-weigh-in/">What&#8217;s Really Making Bitcoin Spike? Analysts Weigh In</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/whats-really-making-bitcoin-spike-analysts-weigh-in/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leading Gaming Token FUN Token Partners With DWF Labs</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leading-gaming-token-fun-token-partners-with-dwf-labs/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leading-gaming-token-fun-token-partners-with-dwf-labs/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 08:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78111</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Isle of Man, Apr. 27, 2023 &#8212; Today, FUN Token signed an undisclosed deal with DWF Labs that will support the vision of decentralizing the online casino space. FUN Token is a leading gaming token with over 350,000 users. It is backed by FreeBitco.in, the biggest Bitcoin faucet in the world with over 51 million<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leading-gaming-token-fun-token-partners-with-dwf-labs/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leading-gaming-token-fun-token-partners-with-dwf-labs/">Leading Gaming Token FUN Token Partners With DWF Labs</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Isle of Man, Apr. 27, 2023 </strong>&#8212; Today, FUN Token signed an undisclosed deal with DWF Labs that will support the vision of decentralizing the online casino space.</p>
<p>FUN Token is a leading gaming token with over 350,000 users. It is backed by FreeBitco.in, the biggest Bitcoin faucet in the world with over 51 million crypto-savvy users.</p>
<p>FUN Token is preparing to launch a revamped version of the XFUN Wallet – the flagship product of the FUN ecosystem. The XFUN Wallet is an innovative multi-asset non-custodial wallet that can store a wide range of cryptocurrencies, tokens, and NFTs.</p>
<p>The XFUN Wallet allows users to effortlessly exchange FUN Token for XFUN – the utility token of the ecosystem based on the Polygon blockchain. XFUN enables quicker, more cost-effective transactions while facilitating enhanced scalability.</p>
<p>Most importantly, the XFUN Wallet allows players to retain control of their funds. This technology eliminates intermediaries and enables users to play straight from the wallet. The XFUN Wallet is already integrated into several gaming platforms, including Dplay Casino, XFUN Casino, XFUN.bet, and XFUN Arcade.</p>
<p>FUN Token also employs advanced escrowing and token-burning practices to maintain the token’s deflationary character. The company is committed to utilizing 50% of its net gaming revenue to burn tokens quarterly.</p>
<p>FUN Token seeks to expand its ecosystem by bringing the technology to more casinos, exchanges, payment gateways, and platforms. They will soon release final upgrades to the XFUN API, a tool that allows third-party dApps to integrate seamlessly into the XFUN ecosystem.</p>
<h4>About FUN Token</h4>
<p>FUN Token’s objective is simple – harnessing the power of blockchain tech to create “trustless” gaming ecosystems that users can rely on and operators can implement seamlessly.</p>
<p>FUN Token is backed by the best in the business – FreeBitco.in is committed to fueling FUN Token’s efforts of making non-custodial gaming an industry standard.</p>
<p><a href="https://funtoken.io/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Website</a> | <a href="https://twitter.com/@FUNtoken_io" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a> | <a href="https://snapto.link/funtoken.io" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Portfolio</a> | <a href="https://t.me/officialFUNToken" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a> | <a href="https://medium.com/@FUNtoken" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Medium</a> | <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/FUN_Token/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Reddit</a> | <a href="https://linkedin.com/in/funtoken/mycompany/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong> </strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leading-gaming-token-fun-token-partners-with-dwf-labs/">Leading Gaming Token FUN Token Partners With DWF Labs</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leading-gaming-token-fun-token-partners-with-dwf-labs/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
