<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 06:22:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Grayscale BTC Trust Won&#8217;t Show Proof of Reserves</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/grayscale-btc-trust-wont-share-its-proof-of-reserves/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/grayscale-btc-trust-wont-share-its-proof-of-reserves/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 17:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grayscale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vitalik buterin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75680</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Grayscale – one of the largest bitcoin trusts in the world – says it’s not going to be sharing its proof of reserves with customers, causing a lot of heads to turn, eyebrows to hike, and fear to surge. Why Won&#8217;t Grayscale Spill the Beans? The concern amongst digital currency enthusiasts and analysts is that<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/grayscale-btc-trust-wont-share-its-proof-of-reserves/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/grayscale-btc-trust-wont-share-its-proof-of-reserves/">Grayscale BTC Trust Won&#8217;t Show Proof of Reserves</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Grayscale – one of the largest bitcoin trusts in the world – says <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/grayscale-refuses-to-share-proof-of-reserves-due-to-security-concerns-as-shares-trade-at-a-45-discount-to-bitcoin/ar-AA14mNVa" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">it’s not going to be sharing</a> its proof of reserves with customers, causing a lot of heads to turn, eyebrows to hike, and fear to surge.</p>
<h2>Why Won&#8217;t Grayscale Spill the Beans?</h2>
<p>The concern amongst digital currency enthusiasts and analysts is that Grayscale is somehow not too far off the mark from where FTX stood. FTX is a failed digital currency exchange that was at one time considered the golden player of the arena. Many thought the company could do no wrong, though things really hit a bad spot in mid-November of this year after it was announced that the company was suffering from a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">liquidity crunch</a> and needed assistance.</p>
<p>It was originally looking like Binance was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">going to step</a> in and purchase the smaller, ailing firm. However, this didn’t happen, as Binance took one <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">look at all the problems</a> the company was facing and resoundingly stated, “no thanks.” From there, FTX <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">filed bankruptcy</a> and the man behind it, Sam Bankman-Fried, was forced to step down.</p>
<p>The company has since been thrown into a swirling pool of criminality and speculation, and many are worried about what could be hiding behind the doors of many of crypto’s biggest names, one of which is Grayscale. The company explained in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>Due to security concerns, we do not make such on-chain wallet information and confirmation data publicly available through a cryptographic proof of reserve or other advanced cryptographic accounting procedure.</p></blockquote>
<p>Of course, this is causing Grayscale customers to worry. Does the company not have enough money in the bank? Is it lying about its finances? What is it trying to hide? Why not just share the information at hand and let all its customers’ minds be at ease once and for all?</p>
<p>Grayscale wrote on social media that it’s expected to take some flak for the maneuver. It’s fully aware of what’s going on with FTX, but it says that the ensuing panic isn’t a good enough reason for it to reveal what it refers to as sensitive financial information. The company said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Panic sparked by others is not a good enough reason to circumvent complex security arrangements.</p></blockquote>
<p>In a separate tweet, Grayscale mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Laws, regulations, and documents that define Grayscale&#8217;s digital asset products prohibit the digital assets underlying the products from being lent, borrowed, or otherwise encumbered.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Keeping Companies Transparent</h2>
<p>Not long ago, Vitalik Buterin – the man behind famed digital currency network Ethereum – introduced a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vitalik-buterin-wants-all-crypto-exchanges-to-be-transparent-about-their-financials/" data-wpel-link="internal">new set of protocols</a> that could be utilized by crypto exchanges and related businesses to show all their customers proof of their reserves.</p>
<p>The protocols were released in response to the FTX debacle. Buterin said this would calm a lot of the nerves people were feeling and give companies more legitimacy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/grayscale-btc-trust-wont-share-its-proof-of-reserves/">Grayscale BTC Trust Won&#8217;t Show Proof of Reserves</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/grayscale-btc-trust-wont-share-its-proof-of-reserves/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Innovator Nikolai Mushegian Dies in Puerto Rico</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-innovator-nikolai-mushegian-dies-in-puerto-rico/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-innovator-nikolai-mushegian-dies-in-puerto-rico/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nikolai Mushegian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Puerto Rico]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75678</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nikolai Mushegian – a young crypto pioneer – was recently found dead on a beach in Puerto Rico after claiming on social media that intelligence agencies were trying to kill him. Nikolai Mushegian Dead in Puerto Rico Leaving his $6 million condo on the morning of October 28, Mushegian was found by a surfer only<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-innovator-nikolai-mushegian-dies-in-puerto-rico/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-innovator-nikolai-mushegian-dies-in-puerto-rico/">Crypto Innovator Nikolai Mushegian Dies in Puerto Rico</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nikolai Mushegian – a young <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">crypto</a> pioneer – was <a href="https://nypost.com/2022/11/09/drowning-death-of-crypto-visionary-fuels-conspiracy-theories/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">recently found dead</a> on a beach in Puerto Rico after claiming on social media that intelligence agencies were trying to kill him.</p>
<h2>Nikolai Mushegian Dead in Puerto Rico</h2>
<p>Leaving his $6 million condo on the morning of October 28, Mushegian was found by a surfer only hours later. His body was discovered in the waves, and he still had his wallet on him. He had said just hours earlier that the CIA and several other agencies around the world were involved in a criminal ring and were looking to frame him for crimes he didn’t commit. He also stated that his girlfriend was a spy of some sort and that he was going to be tortured “to death” if caught.</p>
<p>At only 29 years of age, Mushegian was considered one of the youngest – and most brilliant – crypto entrepreneurs and innovators out there. His death has given rise to several theories online about what could have happened. One came from Ameen Soleimani, the CEO of Spank Chain, who stated in a series of tweets:</p>
<blockquote><p>So, Nikolai is still F–KING DEAD. My money is on him being murdered. He was found drowned four hours after his riskiest tweet ever. He had all year to drown randomly or be mugged, so it seems unlikely that his death was unrelated to his tweet.</p></blockquote>
<p>Mushegian was an earlier developer of Maker DAO, a large and decentralized crypto trading platform. He was also one of the world’s biggest developers of stable coin networks.</p>
<p>An unnamed source is claiming that he suffered from extreme bouts of paranoia, thus shedding doubt on the ideas shared in the tweets prior to his death. At the same time, the source was also quick to point out that there was reason for at least some of the paranoia to be there. The source said:</p>
<blockquote><p>He had mental problems. He saw a psychiatrist at times. He smoked a lot of pot. A tremendous amount. Some of his paranoia was based on fact. He’d discover things. He knew things. Nikolai got bored a lot with the mundane of life. He’d go after things, constantly putting himself in weird positions. It wasn’t for the money. He was interested in why things were the way they were and the corruption behind it.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Trying to Protect Himself</h2>
<p>The source continued with:</p>
<blockquote><p>He was a very quirky guy. He and I spent a lot of time together and I knew everything about him. He came across as cocky and arrogant, but that was just his autism. He was a big nerd, but he wouldn’t let anyone bully him. He had a collection of guns — long guns, handguns, rifles. He liked guns and he knew he wanted to protect himself.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-innovator-nikolai-mushegian-dies-in-puerto-rico/">Crypto Innovator Nikolai Mushegian Dies in Puerto Rico</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-innovator-nikolai-mushegian-dies-in-puerto-rico/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Two New Cases of Crypto Fraud Have Occurred</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/two-new-cases-of-crypto-fraud-have-occurred/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/two-new-cases-of-crypto-fraud-have-occurred/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 13:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[conspiracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto fraud]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Randall V. Rule]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75676</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Two new cases of crypto fraud are in the books. Crypto Fraud Is Getting Too Big The first involved two bad actors. One is Randall V. Rule, age 71, of Reno, Nevada. His partner in crime was Gregory C. Nysewander, age 64, of Irmo, South Carolina. Both have been charged with money laundering conspiracy, money<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/two-new-cases-of-crypto-fraud-have-occurred/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/two-new-cases-of-crypto-fraud-have-occurred/">Two New Cases of Crypto Fraud Have Occurred</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Two new cases of crypto fraud <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/2-men-indicted-for-money-laundering-2-4-million-through-cryptocurrency/ar-AA14hVtL" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">are in the books</a>.</p>
<h2>Crypto Fraud Is Getting Too Big</h2>
<p>The first involved two bad actors. One is Randall V. Rule, age 71, of Reno, Nevada. His partner in crime was Gregory C. Nysewander, age 64, of Irmo, South Carolina. Both have been charged with money laundering conspiracy, money laundering, and conspiracy to violate the Bank Secrecy Act. The pair sought to hide illicitly garnered funds through crypto portals.</p>
<p>The U.S. attorney’s office said in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>The defendants and their co-conspirators made false representations and concealed material facts to avoid discovery of the fraudulent nature of deposits, wires, and transfers, such as providing instructions to co-conspirators and victims to label wire transfers as ‘loan repayments’ and ‘advertising.’</p></blockquote>
<p>The second <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/ohio-man-charged-with-2410m-cryptocurrency-fraud-scheme/ar-AA14jScU" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">case of crypto fraud</a> involves a single party. This one was an Ohio man named Rathnakishore Giri, who by contrast to the initial pair, is quite young at only 27 years of age. He has been charged with defrauding investors in a crypto scam that saw customers lose more than $10 million in total. According to the Justice Department (DOJ), Giri has a history of investment fraud, and this was likely just another scheme in his eyes.</p>
<p>It is alleged that Giri promised all his investors specific returns, though he had no means of guaranteeing anything. He also “fraudulently” promoted himself as a crypto expert, purporting that he knew all there was to know about digital currencies and that he could engage in successful trades across the board.</p>
<p>Court documents state:</p>
<blockquote><p>As defendant Giri knew, he had a history of failing to fulfill such promises to investors. Among other things, defendant Giri repeatedly failed to repay investors&#8217; principal investments, having taken no steps to protect such principal.</p></blockquote>
<p>He was also able to lure people in by bragging about his own luxurious lifestyle and personal wealth. This caught many people by surprise and caused them to figure there was truth to his words, enticing them to jump aboard. It is believed he drove several luxury vehicles including a Tesla, two Lamborghinis, and an Audi R8.</p>
<p>The documents further claim:</p>
<blockquote><p>Instead of using all investor funds for cryptocurrency investments as promised, defendant Giri diverted certain investor funds to other purposes such as payment of his own personal expenses or repayment of principal or interest on earlier investments in a manner consistent with a Ponzi scheme.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Potentially Long Prison Sentence</h2>
<p>Aside from the vehicles, Giri also wore watches that were worth hundreds of thousands of dollars. He flew on private jets and rented luxury homes. He has been charged with five counts of wire <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/fraud/" data-wpel-link="internal">fraud</a>.</p>
<p>If convicted, he could spend the next 100 years in jail given that each count carries a maximum penalty of 20 years behind bars.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/two-new-cases-of-crypto-fraud-have-occurred/">Two New Cases of Crypto Fraud Have Occurred</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/two-new-cases-of-crypto-fraud-have-occurred/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Bears Aim $0.052 or Lower</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bears-aim-0-052-or-lower/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bears-aim-0-052-or-lower/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 07:48:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76213</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tron price started a fresh decline from the $0.0558 level against the US Dollar. TRX price is now trading below $0.0550 and near the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0540 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could continue to move<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bears-aim-0-052-or-lower/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bears-aim-0-052-or-lower/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Bears Aim $0.052 or Lower</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Tron price started a fresh decline from the $0.0558 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>TRX price is now trading below $0.0550 and near the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0540 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it breaks the $0.0533 support zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>TRON price started a fresh decline below the $0.0550 against the US Dollar, similar <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-drop-to-new-2022-lows/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. TRX price could accelerate lower if there is a move below $0.0533.</em></p>
<h2>Tron Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, tron price started a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bullish-signal-above-this-hurdle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">steady increase</a> above the $0.0535 resistance level against the US Dollar. TRX price struggled to gain pace for more gains and formed a top near $0.0558.</p>
<p>The price started a fresh decline below the $0.0550 level. There was a move below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.0518 swing low to $0.0558 high. The price is now trading below $0.0550 and near the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</p>
<p>There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0540 on the 4-hours chart. On the upside, TRX is facing resistance near the $0.0540 level.</p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $0.0555 level. A close above $0.0555 and $0.0558 is a must for a fresh increase. In the stated case, the price could rise towards the $0.0600 resistance in the near term.</p>
<p>On the downside, an initial support is near the $0.0533 level. It is near the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.0518 swing low to $0.0558 high.</p>
<p>The next major support is now forming near $0.0520. If there is a downside break below the $0.0520 support, the price might revisit the $0.0500 support. Any more losses might call for a move towards the $0.0465 zone in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_76214" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/TRON-TRX-4.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76214" class="size-full wp-image-76214" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/TRON-TRX-4.png" alt="Tron (TRX) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76214" class="wp-caption-text">Tron (TRX) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/TRXUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that TRX price is now trading below $0.0550 and near the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it breaks the $0.0533 support zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for TRX/USD is slowly gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for TRX/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.0533 and $0.0520.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.0540, $0.0555 and $0.0580.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bears-aim-0-052-or-lower/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Bears Aim $0.052 or Lower</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bears-aim-0-052-or-lower/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Could Drop To New 2022 Lows</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-drop-to-new-2022-lows/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-drop-to-new-2022-lows/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 06:28:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76210</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price started a fresh decline below the $17,000 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $17,000 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There was a break below a connecting bullish trend line with support near $16,825 on the 4-hours chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-drop-to-new-2022-lows/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-drop-to-new-2022-lows/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Could Drop To New 2022 Lows</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin price started a fresh decline below the $17,000 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $17,000 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There was a break below a connecting bullish trend line with support near $16,825 on the 4-hours chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it stays below the $17,000 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin price is struggling below $17,000 against the US Dollar. BTC might extend losses if it stays below the $17,000 and $17,200 resistance levels.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price started a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-at-risk-of-another-crash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">fresh decline</a> below the $17,000 zone. There was a steady decline below the $16,900 and $16,800 support levels. Earlier, the price attempted an upside break, but the bears were active near the $17,000 zone.</p>
<p>During the recent decline, there was a break below a connecting bullish trend line with support near $16,825 on the 4-hours chart of the BTC/USD pair. The decline gained pace below the $16,700 level and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</p>
<p>The bears even pushed the price below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $16,273 swing low to $17,060 high.</p>
<p>The price is now trading below $16,800 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-more-upsides-18k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. An immediate resistance on the upside is near the $16,800 level. The next major resistance might near the $17,000 zone. The first major resistance is near the $17,200 level.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $17,200 level might send the price towards $18,000, above which the price might rise towards the $18,500 level.</p>
<p>Any more gains might push the price towards the $19,000 zone. If there is no upside break, the price might continue to decline below $16,500. The next key support is near the $16,450 level or the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $16,273 swing low to $17,060 high, below which the price might accelerate lower.</p>
<p>In the stated case, the price could decline towards the $16,000 level. Any more losses might send the price towards the $15,500 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_76211" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Bitcoin-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76211" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-76211" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Bitcoin-3.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76211" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XBTUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, bitcoin price is clearly trading below $17,000 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $17,000 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD is now gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $16,450 and $16,000.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $16,800, $17,000 and $17,200.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-drop-to-new-2022-lows/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Could Drop To New 2022 Lows</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-drop-to-new-2022-lows/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brian Armstrong Thinks Coinbase Is Going to Make a Return</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brian-armstrong-thinks-coinbase-is-going-to-make-a-return/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brian-armstrong-thinks-coinbase-is-going-to-make-a-return/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 17:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brian armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75674</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase is a digital currency exchange that has suffered exponentially this year. The digital currency trading platform initially went public on the Nasdaq in April of 2021. Since then, it has seen its stock price crash roughly 80 percent in less than two years, and the fall can largely be attributed to the fact that<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brian-armstrong-thinks-coinbase-is-going-to-make-a-return/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brian-armstrong-thinks-coinbase-is-going-to-make-a-return/">Brian Armstrong Thinks Coinbase Is Going to Make a Return</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase is a digital currency exchange that has suffered exponentially this year. The digital currency trading platform initially went public on the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-spikes-following-public-debut-of-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">Nasdaq in April of 2021</a>. Since then, it has seen its stock price crash roughly 80 percent in less than two years, and the fall can largely be attributed to the fact that bitcoin – and many other digital currencies – have been falling like crazy since reaching new all-time highs in November of last year.</p>
<h2>Coinbase Is &#8220;Undervalued&#8221; Says Founder</h2>
<p>During that time, bitcoin was trading at a whopping $68,000 per unit, though now, the world’s number one digital currency has fallen into the low $16K range. It’s a sad and ugly sight to see, and one that’s likely not going to change for some time.</p>
<p>Brian Armstrong – the CEO and founder of the digital currency exchange – <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/billybambrough/2022/11/19/undervalued-coinbase-ceo-reveals-bullish-crypto-prediction-after-200-billion-ftx-bitcoin-and-ethereum-price-crash/?sh=3dea18274608" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">says he’s not too worried</a> about the present situation and he feels bitcoin, Ethereum, and many other leading digital currencies are going to make serious comebacks soon when regulators step into the mix. He commented that tip-top regulation in the United States could potentially help many of crypto’s largest companies make surefire returns from the doldrums.</p>
<p>He further stated that he thinks his own company Coinbase is undervalued, and he believes its stock will eventually return to form. He mentioned in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>I’m so glad that [went public]. I’m glad that we’re helping the market kind of understand crypto cycles better&#8230; because that’s kind of been our history as a company, [that] we want to blaze a trail, legitimize the whole industry. We don’t mind being misunderstood or questioned for a few years. We’re playing this for the long term.</p></blockquote>
<p>The fall of bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies has caused Coinbase <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-says-its-laying-off-several-employees/" data-wpel-link="internal">to have to cut its staff</a> by roughly 18 percent. Initially, 2022 was going to be a year in which the exchange brought on three times more staff members and grew to exponential peaks, though things really didn’t turn out this way as the last several months have produced one of the worst bear markets in the history of crypto, and what began as a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-says-its-freezing-all-2022-hiring-plans/" data-wpel-link="internal">hiring freeze</a> turned into a complete meltdown of the exchange’s employee offices.</p>
<h2>Will Things Move More Towards Defi?</h2>
<p>With the recent <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">collapse of FTX</a>, some are wondering if centralized exchanges have much of a chance anymore and if defi won’t take over the space, but Serhii Zhdanov – chief executive of crypto exchange EXMO – doesn’t believe this will happen. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>It would be logical to assume that there will be a shift in the market structure in favor of decentralized platforms. Nevertheless, the FTX story could be a reason for regulators to tighten their requirements for crypto companies, which, on the contrary, will lead to stronger centralization to ensure full control from governments.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brian-armstrong-thinks-coinbase-is-going-to-make-a-return/">Brian Armstrong Thinks Coinbase Is Going to Make a Return</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brian-armstrong-thinks-coinbase-is-going-to-make-a-return/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>El Salvador Is in Debt Because of BTC; It&#8217;s Turning to China for Help</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-is-in-debt-because-of-btc-its-turning-to-china-for-help/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-is-in-debt-because-of-btc-its-turning-to-china-for-help/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 15:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[china]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[El Salvador]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75666</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>El Salvador has lost so much for buying bitcoin that it’s now engaging in a new free-trade plan with China, something that’s causing many analysts to worry. They believe El Salvador’s sovereignty will eventually be up for sale, which could put the Central American nation into an even darker place. How Much Trouble Is El<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-is-in-debt-because-of-btc-its-turning-to-china-for-help/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-is-in-debt-because-of-btc-its-turning-to-china-for-help/">El Salvador Is in Debt Because of BTC; It&#8217;s Turning to China for Help</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>El Salvador has lost so much for buying bitcoin <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/after-cryptocurrency-dip-el-salvador-seeks-cash-from-china/ar-AA14jrDn" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">that it’s now engaging in</a> a new free-trade plan with China, something that’s causing many analysts to worry. They believe El Salvador’s sovereignty will eventually be up for sale, which could put the Central American nation into an even darker place.</p>
<h2>How Much Trouble Is El Salvador in?</h2>
<p>El Salvador has lost money due to its love for bitcoin. The country was the first in the world to declare bitcoin legal tender, doing so <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-fully-legal-in-el-salvador-beginning-september-7/" data-wpel-link="internal">in September of last year</a>. The nation made it illegal for businesses to turn away customers seeking to pay for everyday goods and services with BTC, which they could use alongside USD (a currency the nation has long been dependent on).</p>
<p>Right now, many regulators in the nation are not willing to share information regarding the country’s bitcoin trading and investing habits. Ricardo Castaneda, the country coordinator for El Salvador at the Central American Institute for Fiscal Studies (ICEFI), stated in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Unfortunately, if one asks for information about the extent of investments into bitcoin, the answer is either that this information doesn&#8217;t exist or it&#8217;s confidential.</p></blockquote>
<p>He further stated that right now, the only information out there that helps national regulators determine how much BTC the nation has purchased comes from the tweets of Nayib Bukele, the president of El Salvador. From the messages, it can be assumed the country has bought about $120 million worth of bitcoin.</p>
<p>Over the past several months, the asset has lost more than 70 percent of its overall value, falling from about $68,000 per unit in November of last year (a new all-time high) into the low $16K range at the time of writing. Robert Rubio Fabian, executive director of the National Foundation for Development and Transparency International’s representative in El Salvador, stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>When the international markets see how high the fiscal deficit is, how spending can&#8217;t be paid for and how debt is accumulating, they are going to be more cautious and consider you [a] high risk.</p></blockquote>
<p>El Salvador is having to pursue other means of pumping money into its economy, one of which is forging a free-trade deal with China. Right now, the Asian country has made a few separate investments in the region. Rubio Fabian detailed what those investments were:</p>
<blockquote><p>China made three donations to El Salvador: the construction of a sort of beach amusement park, a stadium that has yet to be built, and a library. These investments improve China&#8217;s image and, obviously, our country&#8217;s image, too.</p></blockquote>
<h2>China Is Behaving Generously</h2>
<p>Per Felix Ulloa, the vice president of El Salvador, China is offering to purchase El Salvador’s debt, which at press time, is just shy of $700 million. He’s not sure if the country will utilize this route, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>China offered to buy all our debt, but we need to tread with caution.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-is-in-debt-because-of-btc-its-turning-to-china-for-help/">El Salvador Is in Debt Because of BTC; It&#8217;s Turning to China for Help</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-is-in-debt-because-of-btc-its-turning-to-china-for-help/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Clowncoin Is Dancing Its Way Into the Crypto Space</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/clowncoin-is-dancing-its-way-into-the-crypto-space/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/clowncoin-is-dancing-its-way-into-the-crypto-space/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 13:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clowncoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dave Mattarocci]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75663</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new cryptocurrency called “Clowncoin” is coming to the market. While other currencies can grow and earn their owners some potential profits, this one will wear white face makeup and a red nose while performing circus acts to entertain kids. Clowncoin Has Arrived! Eh, not quite. Despite its goofball name, the asset is slated to<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/clowncoin-is-dancing-its-way-into-the-crypto-space/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/clowncoin-is-dancing-its-way-into-the-crypto-space/">Clowncoin Is Dancing Its Way Into the Crypto Space</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new cryptocurrency called “Clowncoin” is <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/pueblo-native-helps-launch-clowncoin-130031364.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">coming to the market</a>. While other currencies can grow and earn their owners some potential profits, this one will wear white face makeup and a red nose while performing circus acts to entertain kids.</p>
<h2>Clowncoin Has Arrived!</h2>
<p>Eh, not quite. Despite its goofball name, the asset is slated to do many of the other things that present altcoins do. The currency was founded by Dave Mattarocci, an information technology graduate of Pueblo Community College. He’s now trying hard to promote Clowncoin on social media at night while working as a first responder during the day.</p>
<p>In a recent interview, Mattarocci discussed the importance of digital currency and talked about what he thinks makes Clowncoin different from its virtual counterparts. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Cryptocurrency is a digital currency that is a newer concept which is starting to grow. The purpose is to invest and make money or use it as a form of paying for services.</p></blockquote>
<p>He further stated that buying digital currency can be a little difficult to do on one’s own. Thus, despite the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">crash of FTX</a>, he thinks exchanges can still serve heavy purposes within the realm of the crypto trading arena. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>With an exchange, you are buying the cryptocurrency that they own in their wallet, and they say, &#8216;You own this amount of it,&#8217; but they technically own the coin unless you move it to your own wallet. There is the potential for loss if the cryptocurrency is held within an exchange. FTX basically went under because it is a bear market right now. Not a whole lot of people are making money in investing right now and there are a lot of crypto exchanges out there that make their money on fees, so it puts them in a tender spot when people are not buying.</p></blockquote>
<h2>How Can People Own the Coin?</h2>
<p>He says that crypto ownership with Clowncoin is different from the ownership process of virtually any other kind of digital currency in existence. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>With Clowncoin, we have renounced ownership, which means nobody owns it and no one can pull funds out. It is completely safe and completely community run. It is a stress-free investment and is unique because we have a ten percent tax anytime someone buys or sells the coin. With that, five percent is redistributed to Clowncoin holders, so you make money just by holding the coin. The remaining five percent is put into a liquidity pool, which is like a locked bank account that grows and increases the coin&#8217;s value. So even if there is a mass selloff of the coin, it holds value because of that locked bank account.</p></blockquote>
<p>With each transaction, a unit of currency will be burned, ensuring the supply stays fully under control.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/clowncoin-is-dancing-its-way-into-the-crypto-space/">Clowncoin Is Dancing Its Way Into the Crypto Space</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/clowncoin-is-dancing-its-way-into-the-crypto-space/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Key Resistance And Downtrend Intact</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-key-resistance-and-downtrend-intact/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-key-resistance-and-downtrend-intact/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 04:58:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76184</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ADA price is trading in a bearish zone below the $0.30 support zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above $0.26 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.285 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken). The price could continue<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-key-resistance-and-downtrend-intact/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-key-resistance-and-downtrend-intact/">Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Key Resistance And Downtrend Intact</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>ADA price is trading in a bearish zone below the $0.30 support zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $0.26 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.285 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The price could continue to move down if it stays below the $0.2850 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Cardano price is struggling below $0.285 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-at-risk-of-another-crash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. ADA price could start a recovery wave if it clears the $0.275 and $0.285 resistance levels.</em></p>
<h2>Cardano Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Earlier this month, cardano price saw a fresh decline below the $0.300 zone against the US Dollar. The ADA/USD pair declined below the $0.295 and $0.285 support levels.</p>
<p>The price even declined below the $0.265 support and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-bears-in-control-upsides-could-be-limited/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hour)</a>. A low was formed near $0.2467 and the price is now consolidating losses. The price is now trading above $0.26 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</p>
<p>On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $0.265 zone. It is near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3290 swing high to $0.2467 low. The first major resistance is near the $0.275 level.</p>
<p>The next major resistance could be near the $0.285 zone. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.285 on the 4-hours chart. The trend line is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3290 swing high to $0.2467 low.</p>
<p>A clear upside break above the $0.285 level might send the price towards the $0.300 resistance. Any more gains could start a steady increase towards the $0.320 level.</p>
<p>On the downside, an immediate support is near the $0.260 level. The next major support is near the $0.250 level, below which the price may perhaps decline towards the $0.235 support level. Any more losses might call for a test of the $0.212 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_76185" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Cardano-Price-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76185" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-76185" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Cardano-Price-3.png" alt="Cardano (ADA) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76185" class="wp-caption-text">Cardano (ADA) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ADAUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that ADA price is now trading above $0.260 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $0.285 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ADA/USD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for ADA/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.260 and $0.250.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.275 and $0.285.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-key-resistance-and-downtrend-intact/">Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Key Resistance And Downtrend Intact</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-key-resistance-and-downtrend-intact/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
