<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 18:58:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Satoshi Nakamoto, the BTC Creator, Recently Had a Birthday</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/satoshi-nakamoto-the-btc-creator-recently-had-a-birthday/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/satoshi-nakamoto-the-btc-creator-recently-had-a-birthday/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 17:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nick Szabo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Satoshi Nakamoto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77798</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto fans everywhere have been celebrating the birthday of Satoshi Nakamoto, the famed creator of bitcoin. Satoshi Nakamoto Just Turned 48 Occurring in mid-April, the birthday celebrations were for a man (or woman – it’s not entirely clear at the time of writing) who has earned a solid reputation in the growing digital currency space.<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/satoshi-nakamoto-the-btc-creator-recently-had-a-birthday/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/satoshi-nakamoto-the-btc-creator-recently-had-a-birthday/">Satoshi Nakamoto, the BTC Creator, Recently Had a Birthday</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto fans everywhere have been <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/who-is-satoshi-nakamoto-bitcoin-inventor-crypto-steve-jobs-apple-2023-4" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">celebrating the birthday</a> of Satoshi Nakamoto, the famed creator of bitcoin.</p>
<h2>Satoshi Nakamoto Just Turned 48</h2>
<p>Occurring in mid-April, the birthday celebrations were for a man (or woman – it’s not entirely clear at the time of writing) who has earned a solid reputation in the growing digital currency space. Widely considered the father of crypto, bitcoin – the invention of Nakamoto – was first introduced in whitepaper form on Halloween of 2008, a time when the banks of America were crashing and burning, and the Great Recession had practically taken full form.</p>
<p>It’s alleged that Satoshi Nakamoto is 48 years old. Everyone who has traded bitcoin or crypto loves and respects him. There’s just one big problem… Nobody knows who he is. Despite coming up with one of the biggest financial technologies in the world just 15 years ago, the identity of Nakamoto remains as big a mystery as ever.</p>
<p>Not long ago, the whitepaper that introduced BTC to the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-btc-whitepaper-is-apparently-available-on-every-mac-computer/" data-wpel-link="internal">world was found to be included</a> on virtually every Mac computer. The discovery was made by Andy Baio, a technologist and former executive with Kickstarter. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>While trying to fix my printer today, I discovered that a PDF copy of Satoshi Nakamoto&#8217;s bitcoin’s whitepaper apparently shipped with every copy of macOS since Mojave in 2018.</p></blockquote>
<p>The document reads as follows:</p>
<blockquote><p>A purely peer-to-peer version of electronic cash would allow online payments to be sent directly from one party to another without going through a financial institution.</p></blockquote>
<p>At the time of writing, bitcoin has grown into the largest digital currency in the world. It presently boasts a market cap of more than $540 billion. The currency has delivered intrigue to investors everywhere, part of the reason being that Nakamoto has been extremely elusive, and many are wondering who he is.</p>
<p>Several analysts believe that the chances of Nakamoto being a single person are slim to none. They say it’s highly unlikely something as big, revolutionary, and as technically complicated as BTC could have been established by a single figure. Dan Kaminsky – a leading internet security researcher – explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>Either there&#8217;s a team of people who worked on this or this guy is a genius.</p></blockquote>
<p>About ten years ago, there was much speculation about computer scientist Nick Szabo, who drew quite a bit of attention to himself through a paper about something called “bit gold” that he published in 1998. Szabo has since denied claims that he’s Nakamoto or that he has anything to do with the creation of BTC.</p>
<h2>Not Everyone&#8217;s Convinced Szabo Ain&#8217;t Their Guy</h2>
<p>This hasn’t stopped journalist Nathaniel Popper – who writes for <em>The New York Times</em> – from singling him out. Popper said of Szabo:</p>
<blockquote><p>The most convincing evidence pointed to a reclusive American man of Hungarian descent named Nick Szabo.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/satoshi-nakamoto-the-btc-creator-recently-had-a-birthday/">Satoshi Nakamoto, the BTC Creator, Recently Had a Birthday</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/satoshi-nakamoto-the-btc-creator-recently-had-a-birthday/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Upcoming Jobs Report Could Help Bitcoin Get Bigger</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-upcoming-jobs-report-could-help-bitcoin-get-bigger/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-upcoming-jobs-report-could-help-bitcoin-get-bigger/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 15:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jobs report]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Silk Road]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77796</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Assets like bitcoin and Ethereum continue to show signs of recovering from the bearish market conditions traders and investors witnessed last year. The Many Bitcoin Developments Set to Occur Not long ago, the U.S. government seized more than $215 million in bitcoin taken from the Silk Road dark web market, started by Ross Ulbricht. While<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-upcoming-jobs-report-could-help-bitcoin-get-bigger/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-upcoming-jobs-report-could-help-bitcoin-get-bigger/">The Upcoming Jobs Report Could Help Bitcoin Get Bigger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Assets like bitcoin and Ethereum continue to show signs of recovering from the bearish market conditions traders and investors witnessed last year.</p>
<h2>The Many Bitcoin Developments Set to Occur</h2>
<p>Not long ago, the U.S. government seized more than $215 <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/04/05/bitcoin-and-crypto-are-suddenly-braced-for-a-1-billion-us-earthquake-after-ethereum-bnb-xrp-cardano-dogecoin-polygon-and-solana-price-surge/?sh=79ef0b801ea3" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">million in bitcoin taken from</a> the Silk Road dark web market, started by Ross Ulbricht. While the man in <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-sdny/pr/ross-ulbricht-aka-dread-pirate-roberts-sentenced-manhattan-federal-court-life-prison" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">charge may be in prison</a>, the enterprise continues to operate as though nothing has changed.</p>
<p>Now, it looks like there’s going to be another $1 billion in BTC sold over the next year, and many analysts think this could have huge effects on the price of bitcoin and where the asset goes within the next 12 months. Alex Kuptsikevich – an FX Pro senior market analyst – explained in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>The former cryptocurrency is stuck in local highs, above which it has been unable to consolidate since March 19. This prolonged consolidation sets the stage for the next big move. The resolution of this consolidation is likely to be linked to the market&#8217;s reaction to Friday&#8217;s non-farm payrolls. Technically, a pullback to the $27,000 level to correct the rally of March 10 is more likely at the moment.</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition to the bitcoin sale occurring later in the year, the annual jobs report will be emerging soon. Usually, when this document becomes available for all to read, the country gets an idea of the state of the economy as when jobs are added, one can assume that things are moving up, whereas if job counts are lower than expected, it likely means the economy isn’t in a great state.</p>
<p>Nobody doubts that the economic conditions of America are not in fantastic shape right now. Inflation is <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/inflation-is-having-harsher-effects-on-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">still running rampant</a>, and the Fed has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/federal-reserve-hikes-rates-again-what-will-happen-to-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">made it clear</a> that while 2023 was initially going to be a time in which interest rates either fell or remained in place, they’re likely to continue going up unless inflation decides to calm down outright, which the Fed doesn’t think will occur just yet.</p>
<h2><em> </em>What Will the Jobs Report Do?</h2>
<p>Putting all this aside, if the job report is high enough, this could bear positive outcomes for bitcoin and other digital currencies and cause them to spike higher. Many analysts are crossing their fingers and hoping for the best. Yuya Hasegawa – a crypto market analyst at Bit Bank in Tokyo – said:</p>
<blockquote><p> With concerns for the U.S. banking system subsiding, the market&#8217;s concern is yet again on the Fed’s rate hike decision in May. Bitcoin could retest $29,000, but it needs to close above that level to call it a &#8216;breakout,&#8217; otherwise, it could be another &#8216;fake-out.’</p></blockquote>
<p>While things can always be much better, bitcoin has already risen by 70 percent from where it was at the end of 2022, arguably the worst year on record for the asset.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-upcoming-jobs-report-could-help-bitcoin-get-bigger/">The Upcoming Jobs Report Could Help Bitcoin Get Bigger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-upcoming-jobs-report-could-help-bitcoin-get-bigger/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Analysts: The Banking Crisis Proved the Points of Many BTC Fans</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-the-banking-crisis-proved-the-points-of-many-btc-fans/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-the-banking-crisis-proved-the-points-of-many-btc-fans/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 13:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[banking crisis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77794</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The banking crisis in America and Europe – which appears to be drawing back somewhat at the time of writing – truly vindicated several BTC and Ethereum believers according to many analysts in the industry. BTC Fanatics Have Been Proven Right The banking crisis saw at least three separate institutions in the U.S. – including<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-the-banking-crisis-proved-the-points-of-many-btc-fans/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-the-banking-crisis-proved-the-points-of-many-btc-fans/">Analysts: The Banking Crisis Proved the Points of Many BTC Fans</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The banking crisis in America and Europe – which appears to be drawing back somewhat at the time of writing – truly vindicated several BTC and Ethereum believers <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/04/07/shock-jpmorgan-price-prediction-reveals-catastrophic-doomsday-scenario-may-be-just-the-start-for-bitcoin-and-ethereum/?sh=196eb7b5313e" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">according to many analysts</a> in the industry.</p>
<h2>BTC Fanatics Have Been Proven Right</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/did-crypto-cause-banks-to-fall-experts-weigh-in/" data-wpel-link="internal">banking crisis saw</a> at least three separate institutions in the U.S. – including Silvergate, Silicon Valley Bank, and Signature Bank – shutter their doors for good. Meanwhile, the problems spread to several monetary houses in Europe <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-more-banks-fell-bitcoin-rose-beyond-28k/" data-wpel-link="internal">like Credit Suisse</a>, which was saved at the last minute when it was purchased for about $3 billion by UBS.</p>
<p>People are now looking at BTC and other crypto holders as individuals with good heads on their shoulders. JPMorgan strategist Nikolaos Panigirtzoglou commented in a recent note:</p>
<blockquote><p>For crypto supporters, the U.S. banking crisis exposed the weaknesses of the traditional financial system given banks&#8217; maturity mismatch is susceptible to bank runs. Crypto supporters have been arguing for a long time that the crypto ecosystem is superior, not least because deposits are held in entities such as stable coins which as a digital form of money market funds are 100% backed with high-quality liquid assets and are thus less susceptible to runs.</p></blockquote>
<p>His sentiment is very different from the thoughts of JPMorgan head Jamie Dimon, who in the past has referred to BTC and other forms of crypto as <a href="https://nypost.com/2022/09/22/jamie-dimon-calls-bitcoin-a-decentralized-ponzi-scheme/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Ponzi schemes</a>. In 2024, the next bitcoin halving is all set to occur. This is an event that happens every four years or so in which bitcoin is set to see the rewards delivered to miners cut in half, hence the word halving.</p>
<p>These kinds of circumstances cause the currency to become rarer, thus increasing its value, so traders can likely expect the asset to shoot up in price in about 12 months or so. Panigirtzoglou said:</p>
<blockquote><p>This would mechanically double bitcoin&#8217;s production cost to around $40,000, creating a positive psychological effect. This is because bitcoin’s production cost has historically acted as an effective lower bound.</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition, he also said that the recent introduction of BTC-based <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-ordinals-nfts-are-bringing-the-space-back-from-disaster/" data-wpel-link="internal">non-fungible tokens</a> (NFTs) could help the asset do better as well. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>This is because metadata such as text [and] images can be inscribed on the bitcoin network itself, without relying on smart contracts as seen with other blockchains, where NFTs are created through smart contracts.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Really Helping NFTs</h2>
<p>John Stefanidis – chief executive of Balthazar, an NFT-based gaming platform – says Ordinals and other BTC-centered NFTs have done great things for the industry thus far. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>The recent movement in bitcoin is also positive for the NFT market, as all boats rise with the tide. It’s likely to have a positive impact on the overall sentiment of the market. Bitcoin is currently trading above US$28,000, which we haven’t seen since June last year.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-the-banking-crisis-proved-the-points-of-many-btc-fans/">Analysts: The Banking Crisis Proved the Points of Many BTC Fans</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-the-banking-crisis-proved-the-points-of-many-btc-fans/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Judge Orders $112 Million in Crypto to Be Given Back to Pig Butchering Victims</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/judge-orders-112-million-in-crypto-to-be-given-back-to-pig-butchering-victims/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/judge-orders-112-million-in-crypto-to-be-given-back-to-pig-butchering-victims/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 17:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scam]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pig butchering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[romance scams]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77783</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ) has seized as much as $112 million in digital currency from addresses tied to pig butchering scams. Pig Butchering Is a Huge Problem Judges in several states – including Arizona, Idaho, and California – have issued at least six separate warrants for the seizure of digital currency housed in<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/judge-orders-112-million-in-crypto-to-be-given-back-to-pig-butchering-victims/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/judge-orders-112-million-in-crypto-to-be-given-back-to-pig-butchering-victims/">Judge Orders $112 Million in Crypto to Be Given Back to Pig Butchering Victims</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ) has seized <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/feds-seize-112m-in-cryptocurrency-linked-to-pig-butchering-finance-scams/ar-AA19tJ0g" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">as much as $112 million</a> in digital currency from addresses tied to pig butchering scams.</p>
<h2>Pig Butchering Is a Huge Problem</h2>
<p>Judges in several states – including Arizona, Idaho, and California – have issued at least six separate warrants for the seizure of digital currency housed in various addresses. Authorities claim victims were tricked into investing much of their savings into phony digital schemes. California court documents explain:</p>
<blockquote><p>In this case, the FBI Phoenix Division has identified at least 69 victims with an estimated loss of at least $33.9 million related to these various fraudulent investment platforms.</p></blockquote>
<p>Pig butchering scams are like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/romance-scams/" data-wpel-link="internal">romance scams</a> in that they often start with WhatsApp messages or something similar from illicit actors reaching out to potential victims. From there, they earn their trust and persuade them to get involved in online digital currency trading platforms that unbeknownst to the victims, are controlled by “friends” of the scammers.</p>
<p>They eventually give in and start investing and after a while, they start to see their profits grow. Things are looking great until they try to take some of their money out or they try to make a withdrawal. This is when the problems arise, as they’re usually told they need to pay fees or invest more before they can take any money out. Before long, they realize things are fraudulent, and the victims are forced to walk away with bruised egos and empty pockets.</p>
<p>The court documents attest to this and say:</p>
<blockquote><p>Eventually, most victims are completely locked out of their accounts and lose all of their funds.</p></blockquote>
<p>Pig butchering scams ultimately got their start in the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-pig-butchering-crypto-romance-scam-emerges-in-florida/" data-wpel-link="internal">region of Florida back</a> in September of last year. During that time, Jimmy Patronis – a chief financial officer – explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>In Florida, we embrace emerging technology and innovation, but consumers must always stay on guard for scams, especially as new financial products like bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies become increasingly popular. Reports say cryptocurrency scams have bilked millions out of unsuspecting crypto investors, many of which were scammed through online dating apps over the course of several months. Just like with any major financial decision, consumers should do research and never transfer funds to someone they think is suspicious, untrustworthy, or whose identity they haven’t verified. You may as well kiss your money goodbye. If you feel you have been the victim of a scam, report it immediately at FraudFreeFlorida.com. Always remember: if an opportunity sounds too good to be true, it is.</p></blockquote>
<h2>One Man Lost Millions</h2>
<p>The court documents detail a specific case in which a scammer who went by the name “Jenny” approached a man online called “JZ.”</p>
<p>Her deceitful actions caused the man to lose more than $2 million in crypto by the time the scam had finished.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/judge-orders-112-million-in-crypto-to-be-given-back-to-pig-butchering-victims/">Judge Orders $112 Million in Crypto to Be Given Back to Pig Butchering Victims</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/judge-orders-112-million-in-crypto-to-be-given-back-to-pig-butchering-victims/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The BTC Whitepaper is Apparently Available on Every Mac Computer</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-btc-whitepaper-is-apparently-available-on-every-mac-computer/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-btc-whitepaper-is-apparently-available-on-every-mac-computer/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 15:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mac]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[whitepaper]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77781</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Andy Baio – the former CTO of Kickstarter – has discovered something unusual about Apple’s Mac computers. They all seem to come with copies of the bitcoin whitepaper. The Whitepaper for Bitcoin is a Regular Mac Resident The whitepaper for bitcoin was first introduced on Halloween of 2008. During that time, major countries like the<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-btc-whitepaper-is-apparently-available-on-every-mac-computer/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-btc-whitepaper-is-apparently-available-on-every-mac-computer/">The BTC Whitepaper is Apparently Available on Every Mac Computer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Andy Baio – the former CTO of Kickstarter – has discovered something unusual <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/former-kickstarter-cto-finds-bitcoin-white-paper-hidden-in-mac-operating-system/ar-AA19yz0c" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">about Apple’s Mac computers</a>. They all seem to come with copies of the bitcoin whitepaper.</p>
<h2>The Whitepaper for Bitcoin is a Regular Mac Resident</h2>
<p>The whitepaper for bitcoin was first introduced on Halloween of 2008. During that time, major countries like the U.S. and much of Europe were entering the early stages of the Great Recession that would last through the next few years, and bitcoin was introduced as a tool that could potentially aid those who were in need.</p>
<p>Banks were closing left and right (boy, doesn’t that <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-trouble-with-crypto-bank-silvergate-is-growing/" data-wpel-link="internal">feel familiar right about</a> now), and bitcoin would be a universal money and investment protocol that could aid those who were deeply affected by what was going on. The situation led to several bankruptcies, foreclosures, and a stock market that would crash and not even begin to witness any form of recovery until 2014 (six years later). It was a sad and ugly moment in the history of the world.</p>
<p>The idea that the whitepaper is now hidden within the realms of virtually every Apple Mac out there (at least that’s what it’s looking like at press time) feels like Satoshi Nakamoto – the pseudonymous creator of bitcoin – is trying to tell users something. Maybe that bitcoin is there to help them get out of whatever financial jam they’re experiencing if they’re willing to try it and trust it.</p>
<p>Baio – in an interview – stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I’ve asked over a dozen Mac-using friends to confirm, and it was there for every one of them.</p></blockquote>
<p>The idea that it’s there to be viewed in every Mac device suggests the creators of Mac or the executives behind the company made a conscious decision to include it there, but Baio doesn’t think it’s that simple. Continuing his statement on the matter, he explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>In its early history, Apple developers used to hide Easter eggs in the operating system, but I get the impression this wasn&#8217;t something that management would have approved of. Basically, the decision of a single engineer.</p></blockquote>
<p>In the long run, it appears Apple may have known about the inclusion of the whitepaper and tasked the engineer who had put it in each device to remove it. This could easily explain why the duty was never completed and the whitepaper has remained… Because the engineer <em>wants</em> it there. Baio said:</p>
<blockquote><p>With this new attention to it, I&#8217;ll be surprised if it isn&#8217;t removed in the next beta.</p></blockquote>
<h2>This was Done on Purpose</h2>
<p>He <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/04/06/theres-a-bitcoin-blueprint-hidden-inside-every-mac/?sh=5b7cb8f56381" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">further commented on</a> his blog:</p>
<blockquote><p>A little bird tells me that someone internally filed it [the bitcoin whitepaper] as an issue nearly a year ago, assigned to the same engineer who put the PDF there in the first place, and that person hasn’t taken action or commented on the issue since.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-btc-whitepaper-is-apparently-available-on-every-mac-computer/">The BTC Whitepaper is Apparently Available on Every Mac Computer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-btc-whitepaper-is-apparently-available-on-every-mac-computer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>North Kingston Police Discuss Growing Crypto Scams</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/north-kingston-police-warn-of-growing-crypto-scams/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/north-kingston-police-warn-of-growing-crypto-scams/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 13:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto scams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[North Kingston]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[romance scams]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77778</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Police in North Kingston are warning residents about a whole new array of crypto-based scams that have made themselves prominent in the area. Crypto Scams: Will They Ever Stop? Crypto scams are nothing new. In fact, they’ve practically been around since the industry was first developed nearly 15 years ago, but never have they taken<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/north-kingston-police-warn-of-growing-crypto-scams/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/north-kingston-police-warn-of-growing-crypto-scams/">North Kingston Police Discuss Growing Crypto Scams</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Police in North Kingston are warning residents about <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/north-kingstown-police-warn-about-a-rise-in-cryptocurrency-scams/ar-AA19vFW9" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">a whole new array</a> of crypto-based scams that have made themselves prominent in the area.</p>
<h2>Crypto Scams: Will They Ever Stop?</h2>
<p>Crypto scams are nothing new. In fact, they’ve practically been around since the industry was first developed nearly 15 years ago, but never have they taken on such drastic and varied forms. For example, among the most prominent forms of digital currency scams as of late <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/romance-scams/" data-wpel-link="internal">are romance scams</a>, which seek to target those looking for love online.</p>
<p>Many crypto scammers will set up fake or phony online “love” profiles. They narrow in on their victims and establish long-term relationships. They get to know them, they make things feel very personal and clear, and before long (once they’ve gotten their victims’ trust and attention), they tell the other parties about “fantastic” new crypto investment opportunities, and that they’d be fools to avoid getting in on the action.</p>
<p>From there, the victims feel compelled to put money into the platforms, and they do. In the beginning, they ultimately see gains and start to feel excited. In many cases, they invest more money once they see the numbers going up, but when they try to make withdrawals or take money out, problems arise. They’re often told they must invest more and before long they realize what’s happened.</p>
<p>The platforms were controlled by illicit actors and the likelihood of them getting their funds back is slim to none. Steve Weisman – author of “Identity Theft Alert” – said in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>Seniors are often targeted at this and unfortunately, they end up losing a lot of money. The cryptocurrency companies that have these ATMs, they don&#8217;t want to be working with criminals and they do post the warnings there on the ATM which is good if someone you know is at least going to be giving that moment of hesitation.</p></blockquote>
<h2>How to Talk to Bank Tellers</h2>
<p>As he said, the fraud in question occurs through bitcoin ATMs at convenience and grocery stores. However, sometimes the victims are required to withdraw money from their banks, and the scammers have given them a list of things to say should the bank tellers ask questions or appear suspicious in some way. Weisman said:</p>
<blockquote><p>They will tell the people not to respond to certain things. That &#8216;No, I am aware that this is legitimate, this is a business transaction.&#8217; Anything they can to try and get around the warnings and the people being concerned about those warnings, and that&#8217;s a problem because once they&#8217;ve hooked that person in, very often, it becomes very difficult to dissuade them.</p></blockquote>
<p>At the end of the day, while the crypto space appears to be growing like never before, the crime centered within its bounds is also expanding.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/north-kingston-police-warn-of-growing-crypto-scams/">North Kingston Police Discuss Growing Crypto Scams</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/north-kingston-police-warn-of-growing-crypto-scams/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk (Briefly) Changes the Twitter Logo to the Dogecoin Dog</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-briefly-changes-the-twitter-logo-to-the-dogecoin-dog/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-briefly-changes-the-twitter-logo-to-the-dogecoin-dog/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 17:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77756</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Elon Musk – the South African billionaire behind companies like Tesla and SpaceX – played a last-minute April Fools’ joke and changed the Twitter logo (Twitter being the most recent company he bought) to that of the Dogecoin dog. Elon Musk Pulls a Twitter Twist The move aided Dogecoin and brought the coin up by<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-briefly-changes-the-twitter-logo-to-the-dogecoin-dog/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-briefly-changes-the-twitter-logo-to-the-dogecoin-dog/">Elon Musk (Briefly) Changes the Twitter Logo to the Dogecoin Dog</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Elon Musk – the South African billionaire behind companies like Tesla and SpaceX – played a last-minute April Fools’ joke and <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-ae/news/other/cryptocurrency-dogecoin-surges-as-musk-changes-twitter-logo-to-meme-dog/ar-AA19s1qA" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">changed the Twitter logo</a> (Twitter being the most <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-fan-elon-musk-now-fully-controls-twitter/" data-wpel-link="internal">recent company he bought</a>) to that of the Dogecoin dog.</p>
<h2>Elon Musk Pulls a Twitter Twist</h2>
<p>The move aided Dogecoin and brought the coin up by more than 20 percent. The asset initially was trading at eight cents but moved up to ten cents respectively after the logo was altered.</p>
<p>The sudden change – no matter how brief it may have been – shouldn’t come as a surprise to most diehard crypto followers given how much of an advocate for Dogecoin Musk has been during the past several years. Not long ago, he referred to the currency as the “<a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-affirms-his-position-on-doge-its-the-peoples-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">people’s crypto</a>.” He also stated he’d like to literally leave a Dogecoin <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-wants-to-literally-leave-dogecoin-on-the-moon/" data-wpel-link="internal">unit on the moon with</a> one of his SpaceX rockets.</p>
<p>At the same time, while the maneuver may have led to short-term results (a small spike in the Dogecoin price), it may not be in Musk’s best interest right now to mess around with Dogecoin considering he’s currently involved <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-asks-judge-to-toss-out-dogecoin-centered-lawsuit/" data-wpel-link="internal">in a $258 billion lawsuit</a> over his promotion of the asset.</p>
<p>Last year, several investors (plaintiffs) got together and sued Musk, claiming that they invested in Dogecoin after they saw him speak positively about it again and again. They said they never would have invested in the asset if Musk hadn’t been so forthcoming about the altcoin, though they eventually gave in and clearly invested funds they didn’t have into the currency.</p>
<p>2022 was marred by a terrible bear market that saw many coins lose more than 70 percent of their value or more. This caused the crypto space to lose more than $2 trillion in overall valuation. It was a sad and ugly sight to see, and there were many traders that lost everything they had.</p>
<p>The plaintiffs named in the present case certainly lost quite a bit, and they say that Musk behaved irresponsibly in his promotion of Dogecoin. They are now suing him and hoping to obtain much of their missing money back.</p>
<p>Musk is being accused of a pump and dump, though his lawyers are asking that the case be rejected given that he did not force anyone to invest in the asset. Not everyone is impressed or convinced by this argument, however. Recently, comedian Jesse McLaren – commenting on the Twitter logo change – said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Why do I get the feeling the Doge icon was added so when you search &#8216;Elon&#8217; and &#8216;Doge&#8217; the story of his racketeering lawsuit will be buried?</p></blockquote>
<h2>Manipulating the Asset?</h2>
<p>Court <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2023/apr/04/twitter-changes-logo-to-dogecoin-cryptocurrency-image-in-apparent-late-april-fools-day-gag?ref=upstract.com" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">documents regarding the case</a> state the following:</p>
<blockquote><p>Musk used his pedestal as [the] world’s richest man to operate and manipulate the Dogecoin pyramid scheme for profit, exposure and amusement.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-briefly-changes-the-twitter-logo-to-the-dogecoin-dog/">Elon Musk (Briefly) Changes the Twitter Logo to the Dogecoin Dog</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-briefly-changes-the-twitter-logo-to-the-dogecoin-dog/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>North Korea Is Again on a Mission to Attack Crypto Companies</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/north-korea-is-again-on-a-mission-to-attack-crypto-firms/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/north-korea-is-again-on-a-mission-to-attack-crypto-firms/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 15:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto firms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cyberattack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[North Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77753</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hackers in North Korea have installed new code across a wide array of apps as a means of breaking into digital currency exchanges and related companies. North Korea Is Up to Its Same Old Tricks The nation has long played host to notorious hacking groups such as Lazarus, which are eagerly seeking new ways to<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/north-korea-is-again-on-a-mission-to-attack-crypto-firms/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/north-korea-is-again-on-a-mission-to-attack-crypto-firms/">North Korea Is Again on a Mission to Attack Crypto Companies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hackers in North Korea have <a href="https://www.wired.com/story/3cx-supply-chain-attack-north-korea-cryptocurrency-targets/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">installed new code</a> across a wide array of apps as a means of breaking into digital currency exchanges and related companies.</p>
<h2>North Korea Is Up to Its Same Old Tricks</h2>
<p>The nation has long <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/north-korea-lashes-out-at-u-s-after-its-called-a-criminal-organization-seeking-to-steal-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">played host to notorious</a> hacking groups such as Lazarus, which are eagerly seeking new ways to garner cryptocurrencies illicitly through malware, cyberattacks, and related means so they can have the funds necessary to continually build out the nation’s ongoing nuclear program.</p>
<p>Thus far, North Korea has attacked a wide array of regions across the world including several Asian countries, European countries, and the U.S. It’s estimated that North Korea has made off with well over a billion dollars’ <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-north-korea-stole-more-crypto-in-2022-than-in-any-other-year/" data-wpel-link="internal">worth of digital currency</a> to boost its nukes.</p>
<p>Researchers at Russian cybersecurity firm Kaspersky identified a small number of crypto-focused businesses and enterprises that fell victim to 3CX software supply-chain attacks, all of which unfolded during either early April or late March. While none of the companies have been named at the time of writing, Kaspersky has commented they’re all based in “western Asia.”</p>
<p>Georgy Kucherin – a researcher at Kaspersky – put out a statement following the attacks and his company’s research study. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>This was all just to compromise a small group of companies, maybe not just in cryptocurrency, but what we see is that one of the interests of the attackers is cryptocurrency companies. Cryptocurrency companies should be especially concerned about this attack because they are the likely targets, and they should scan their systems for further compromise.</p></blockquote>
<p>The malware North Korea is using could affect as many as 600,000 separate businesses according to the research conducted by Kaspersky. Kucherin further said the cyberthreats emerging from North Korea are getting bigger and bigger. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>This is becoming very common. During supply-chain attacks, the threat actor conducts reconnaissance on the victims, collecting information, then they filter out this information, selecting victims to deploy a second-stage malware.</p></blockquote>
<p>The good news, he mentioned, is that many of the attacks (or attempted attacks, at least) have been relatively easy to spot. He says North Korea likes to think it can stay hidden in the shadows, but that at the end of the day, many of its methods come off as amateur. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>They tried to be stealthy, but they failed. Their first-stage implants were discovered.</p></blockquote>
<h2>It&#8217;s not Just Crypto Companies in Danger</h2>
<p>Despite this, Tom Hegel – a security researcher with Sentinel One – commented that it would be a mistake to assume only crypto companies have been targeted thus far, and the cyberattacks still pose certain dangers in that not all of them have been uncovered yet. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The current theory at this point is that the attackers did initially target crypto firms to get into those high-value organizations.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/north-korea-is-again-on-a-mission-to-attack-crypto-firms/">North Korea Is Again on a Mission to Attack Crypto Companies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/north-korea-is-again-on-a-mission-to-attack-crypto-firms/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Watchmakers Are Trying to Attract Millennials Through BTC</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/watchmakers-are-trying-to-attract-millennials-through-btc/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/watchmakers-are-trying-to-attract-millennials-through-btc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 13:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Millennials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[watches]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77750</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new survey suggests that millennials and Gen Z are getting into luxury items. Luxury watchmakers are now taking advantage of this and looking to attract younger buyers using products like bitcoin and Snapchat. Millennials Don&#8217;t Usually Wear Watches The funny thing is that many millennials and younger generations are not used to wearing watches<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/watchmakers-are-trying-to-attract-millennials-through-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/watchmakers-are-trying-to-attract-millennials-through-btc/">Watchmakers Are Trying to Attract Millennials Through BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new survey suggests that millennials and Gen Z are <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/luxury-watchmakers-woo-generation-z-144228613.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">getting into luxury items</a>. Luxury watchmakers are now taking advantage of this and looking to attract younger buyers using products like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a> and Snapchat.</p>
<h2>Millennials Don&#8217;t Usually Wear Watches</h2>
<p>The funny thing is that many millennials and younger generations are not used to wearing watches as they usually just have the time on their phones, but watchmakers believe they can make a huge dent in their sales and retail progression in the coming years given they have more spending power than virtually any other group before them.</p>
<p>In an interview, Rolex chief executive Jean-Frederic Dufour explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>It is very important that once a year, we showcase that wearing a watch is trendy, and even something for the youngest generation which is not used to wearing watches.</p></blockquote>
<p>At a recent conference, representatives of Snapchat announced a new application that would allow people to try on watches virtually, either through a tablet or smartphone. It adapts to a user’s wrist size and shows off Cartier watch models. From there, users can ultimately customize things like colors. Jean-Philippe Bertschy – an analyst with Swiss investment managers Vontobel – said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The younger generation, contrary to popular belief, have more economic power than any generation that preceded them. They are earning more, saving more, and investing earlier and at a higher rate than previous generations.</p></blockquote>
<p>He mentioned that an interesting phenomenon is on its way in that millennials and Gen Z are slated to garner a massive amount of wealth over the next two decades, either through inheritance or other means. He says they’re projected to rake in as much as $80 trillion by the time we reach 2045.</p>
<p>At the same time, both generations are stifled by many rising costs including mortgage costs. Analysts with Morgan Stanley commented that nearly half of people between the ages of 18 and 29 still live with their parents, something not witnessed in roughly 80 years. They said:</p>
<blockquote><p>They simply have more disposable income to be allocated to discretionary spending.</p></blockquote>
<p>Not long ago, H. Moser sold a watch for roughly ten bitcoins. Chief executive Edouard Meylan said bitcoin and crypto transactions are great for attracting younger consumers to the mix given they’ve become more “digitized” over the years. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>More than 50 percent of sales in China are to Gen Z and millennials.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Trying to Attract Younger Customers</h2>
<p>Christopher Hoppe – a Frenchman now living in the nation of Australia, where he founded the Bausele watch brand after spending many years making timepieces in Switzerland – says that younger people are often looking for watches and similar products many other people simply “won’t have.” He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>We had lost this generation with mobile phones but found it again with the Apple Watch.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/watchmakers-are-trying-to-attract-millennials-through-btc/">Watchmakers Are Trying to Attract Millennials Through BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/watchmakers-are-trying-to-attract-millennials-through-btc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
