<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 10:50:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Crypto Manager Alex Pack Says He Never Trusted FTX</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-manager-alex-pack-says-he-never-trusted-ftx/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-manager-alex-pack-says-he-never-trusted-ftx/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 17:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alex Pack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75539</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FTX appeared to be the golden player of the crypto space for the last three years, but some investors – including Alex Pack, who manages New York-based venture capital firm Hack VC – were never convinced of the company’s prowess, and they say the company showed serious “red flags” from the start. Alex Pack Says<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-manager-alex-pack-says-he-never-trusted-ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-manager-alex-pack-says-he-never-trusted-ftx/">Crypto Manager Alex Pack Says He Never Trusted FTX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX</a> appeared to be the golden player of the crypto space for the last three years, <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/cryptocurrency-investor-says-he-saw-serious-red-flags-with-ftx-founder-sam-bankman-fried/ar-AA14erqt" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">but some investors</a> – including Alex Pack, who manages New York-based venture capital firm Hack VC – were never convinced of the company’s prowess, and they say the company showed serious “red flags” from the start.</p>
<h2>Alex Pack Says There Were Issues with FTX from the Beginning</h2>
<p>Pack first met Sam Bankman-Fried, the man behind FTX, roughly four years ago. At the time, Bankman-Fried had not created the now infamous exchange and was instead seeking additional startup funds for Alameda Research, another company he was creating at the time. When they met in 2018, Pack was running a crypto firm called Dragonfly Capital, and Bankman-Fried was seeking what he calls “single-digit millions” for his new enterprise.</p>
<p>In the beginning, Pack said he was “captivated” by Bankman-Fried. He said he had a lot of presence for such a young man, and he was impressed with his intelligence and business acumen, though he said this only lasted for about a month or so. In a recent interview, he commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>I was captivated by him for the first month until he showed us everything.</p></blockquote>
<p>He stated that he continued to meet with Bankman-Fried over the next five to six months. During that time, he performed due diligence on both the crypto founder and the company he was founding and claimed that there were simply too many holes in the game. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>After spending months with him, we realized his risk-taking was catastrophic. We looked at it and saw red flags. Too much risk.</p></blockquote>
<p>At the time, he said that Alameda was facing roughly $10 million in overall losses, which caused many alarm bells to ring with him and his partners. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>We could never figure [it] out. Was it fraud? Was it massive risk-taking? Was it a bunch of honest mistakes?</p></blockquote>
<p>He also said Bankman-Fried was “hemorrhaging” money to pay for what would eventually be FTX. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>We asked him, &#8216;What&#8217;s going on here?’ Pretty nonchalantly, he said, &#8216;I can&#8217;t remember if I told you I had this idea for an exchange. For that reason, I&#8217;ve been spending most of my time on it, so we have been neglecting the core business.&#8217; There was a lot he would or wouldn&#8217;t share. There was a clear pattern of hidden massive risk. He never really showed Alameda&#8217;s books to any future investor. That&#8217;s where all the bad stuff was happening.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Sam Bankman-Fried Tells His Side of the Story</h2>
<p>Contrary to what Pack has stated, Sam Bankman-Fried recently posted a series of tweets discussing the encounters from his own point of view. The FTX founder said:</p>
<blockquote><p>They expressed interest in Alameda and [a] desire to help it grow. They understood the business. Alameda has never taken an external investor, but this seemed like a good opportunity.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-manager-alex-pack-says-he-never-trusted-ftx/">Crypto Manager Alex Pack Says He Never Trusted FTX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-manager-alex-pack-says-he-never-trusted-ftx/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Australia Hints Crypto Regulation Will Arrive in 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/australia-hints-crypto-regulation-will-arrive-in-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/australia-hints-crypto-regulation-will-arrive-in-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 15:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[australia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75537</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The government of Australia has hinted it’s going to be implementing cryptocurrency regulations in 2023. The announcement comes on the heels of the FTX collapse, which will likely go down as one of the biggest embarrassments of the crypto space. Australia Could Regulate Crypto Next Year Australian Treasurer Jim Chalmers has stated that regulators are<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/australia-hints-crypto-regulation-will-arrive-in-2023/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/australia-hints-crypto-regulation-will-arrive-in-2023/">Australia Hints Crypto Regulation Will Arrive in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The government of Australia has hinted it’s going <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-in/news/india/australian-government-expected-to-initiate-cryptocurrency-regulations-next-year-amid-ftx-s-collapse/ar-AA14dpGH" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">to be implementing cryptocurrency</a> regulations in 2023. The announcement comes on the heels of the FTX collapse, which will likely go down as one of the biggest embarrassments of the crypto space.</p>
<h2>Australia Could Regulate Crypto Next Year</h2>
<p>Australian Treasurer Jim Chalmers has stated that regulators are eager to ensure crypto traders remain protected. Chalmers acknowledges that digital currency trading in Australia is reaching new highs, and he’s concerned that so long as people continue investing in an unregulated space, what happened with FTX will happen again, and additional firms will either fall completely or run off with investors’ money. He figures that if people are not willing to step away, at least they can instill the necessary protections to ensure criminality remains at a minimum.</p>
<p>Chalmers said:</p>
<blockquote><p>These developments highlight the lack of transparency and consumer protection in the crypto market, which is why our government is taking action to improve the regulatory frameworks while still promoting innovation.</p></blockquote>
<p>In his recent discussion regarding crypto regulation, Chalmers pointed to the fall of FTX as one of the main reasons as to why the government is now so eager to move forward with regulatory action. FTX, at only three years of age, was considered one of the top exchanges in the space, though mid-November saw it suddenly swamped with problems, and founder Sam Bankman-Fried went to his larger rival Binance for help with this firm’s <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">alleged liquidity crunch</a>.</p>
<p>For a while, it appeared Binance <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">was going to buy</a> out the smaller firm, though this did not occur, as the larger exchange explained on social media that FTX was dealing with too many issues. From there, Sam <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">Bankman-Fried resigned</a> from his post and FTX became the latest crypto firm to engage in bankruptcy proceedings. It was a sad and ugly sight to see; one that will forever mar the image people once had of what was labeled one of crypto’s golden players.</p>
<h2>Could Regulation Make a Difference?</h2>
<p>Michael Bacina – a digital asset manager at Piper Alderman lawyers – said in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Regulatory certainty is key to rebuilding trust in relation to centralized exchanges, and while law cannot eliminate bad behavior, it can set powerful norms and standards which make that behavior easier to find. The challenge will be ensuring that regulation does as intended to effectively protect consumers without suppressing industry growth… When Australia brings in technology-enabling custody rules for centralized holders of crypto assets, we will either be a leader in the space or catching up, depending on how fast other jurisdictions, like Singapore and Europe, move to make rules.</p></blockquote>
<p>Australia has long <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/australias-asic-is-looking-to-regulate-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">hinted that it would</a> like to regulate crypto, though this is arguably the first time when the state appears to be dead serious about doing so.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/australia-hints-crypto-regulation-will-arrive-in-2023/">Australia Hints Crypto Regulation Will Arrive in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/australia-hints-crypto-regulation-will-arrive-in-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Congressional House Committee Vows to Investigate FTX</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/congressional-house-committee-vows-to-investigate-ftx/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/congressional-house-committee-vows-to-investigate-ftx/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 13:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Congress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75534</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The House Financial Services Committee has said that it is opening an investigation into fallen cryptocurrency exchange FTX and its disgraced head executive Sam Bankman-Fried. FTX Will Be the Subject of a Congressional Inquiry The announcement came from Maxine Waters, a democrat from California that heads the committee. She stated that the team also expects<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/congressional-house-committee-vows-to-investigate-ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/congressional-house-committee-vows-to-investigate-ftx/">Congressional House Committee Vows to Investigate FTX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The House Financial Services Committee has said that it is <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/house-to-probe-ftx-collapse-expects-sam-bankman-fried-to-testify/ar-AA14bIbP" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">opening an investigation</a> into fallen cryptocurrency exchange FTX and its disgraced head executive Sam Bankman-Fried.</p>
<h2>FTX Will Be the Subject of a Congressional Inquiry</h2>
<p>The announcement came from Maxine Waters, a democrat from California that heads the committee. She stated that the team also expects Bankman-Fried to testify on what occurred and hinted that Congress is using what happened with the company to get serious about developing regulation for the digital currency space.</p>
<p>Waters said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The fall of FTX has posed tremendous harm to over one million users, many of whom were everyday people who invested their hard-earned savings into the FTX cryptocurrency exchange, only to watch it all disappear within a matter of seconds. Unfortunately, this event is just one out of many examples of cryptocurrency platforms that have collapsed just this past year.</p></blockquote>
<p>The fall of FTX will likely go down as one of the crypto space’s biggest blunders. Beginning in 2019, the company rose to prominence over a three-year period, achieving billion-dollar greatness in a relatively short frame of time. Sam Bankman-Fried was lauded as a genius by many people, and his net worth – just before the company crashed – was valued at roughly $16 billion.</p>
<p>However, mid-November saw <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX approaching its larger</a> rival Binance for help. It was insinuated that the bigger company would potentially buy out the smaller one and aid it following the announcement of the firm’s “liquidity crunch,” and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">while a deal appeared</a> to be moving forward for roughly 24 hours, the larger exchange eventually backed off, claiming that FTX’s issues were simply too big to handle.</p>
<p>From there, FTX filed <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">bankruptcy and</a> Sam Bankman-Fried stepped down from his post. Patrick T. McHenry – a republican from North Carolina who also serves on the House Committee – explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>Oversight is one of Congress’ most critical functions, and we must get to the bottom of this for FTX’s customers and the American people It’s essential that we hold bad actors accountable so responsible players can harness technology to build a more inclusive financial system.</p></blockquote>
<p>Despite the confidence of the committee players, some – like Senator Sherrod Brown, an Ohio democrat – believes that Sam Bankman-Fried testifying is something of a fantasy, largely because he is now facing multiple investigations and lawsuits. Brown also mentioned that he doesn’t think SBF is the only person behind what’s happened, and that there are probably several people in the wings that need to answer for potential crimes.</p>
<h2>Many People Involved?</h2>
<p>Brown mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>’I think that a lot of them [need] to explain what they’ve done.</p></blockquote>
<p>FTX is not the only company to reach a sudden demise in 2022. Other firms, such as the Celsius Network and Voyager Digital have also been <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-in-the-age-of-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">forced into bankruptcy</a> proceedings following the heavy volatility this year has delivered.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/congressional-house-committee-vows-to-investigate-ftx/">Congressional House Committee Vows to Investigate FTX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/congressional-house-committee-vows-to-investigate-ftx/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto.com Sends Lots of Money to the Wrong Place</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-com-sends-lots-of-money-to-the-wrong-place/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-com-sends-lots-of-money-to-the-wrong-place/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto.com]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kris Marszalek]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75522</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Popular digital currency exchange Crypto.com is in hot water after it allegedly sent a lot of digital money to the wrong account. Crypto.com Sent Money to the Wrong Area At the time of writing, Crypto.com is purported to have sent as much as $400 million in Ethereum funds to a wallet stationed on the platform<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-com-sends-lots-of-money-to-the-wrong-place/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-com-sends-lots-of-money-to-the-wrong-place/">Crypto.com Sends Lots of Money to the Wrong Place</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Popular digital currency exchange Crypto.com is in hot water <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/esports/crypto-com-accidentally-sent-400-million-to-a-competitor/ar-AA146oKn" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">after it allegedly sent</a> a lot of digital money to the wrong account.</p>
<h2>Crypto.com Sent Money to the Wrong Area</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Crypto.com is purported to have sent as much as $400 million in Ethereum funds to a wallet stationed on the platform of its competitor and rival Gate.io. CEO Kris Marszalek took to social media to express his remorse over the situation and explain things to potential investors. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>It was supposed to be a move to a new cold storage address but was sent to a whitelisted external exchange address. We worked with [the] Gate team and the funds were subsequently returned to our cold storage.</p></blockquote>
<p>The maneuver resulted in some negative attention for the exchange, and Cronos – the native token of Crypto.com – is presently down roughly 40 percent over the course of the last few weeks. In addition, the company’s daily trading volumes – which at one point exceeded $4 billion – are now down to about $284 at press time. It’s a sad and embarrassing scenario, and probably one that could have been easily avoided with a little double checking.</p>
<p>The event is also <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/some-fear-crypto-com-could-become-the-next-ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">hiking speculation around</a> Crypto.com, with many analysts wondering if it has what it takes to remain afloat in a world that seems to be on its last legs.</p>
<p>2022 has been a very bad year for crypto. Not only have prices taken harsh beatings, but several digital currency companies have up and vanished, the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">most recent being FTX</a>.</p>
<p>Long considered the poster company for crypto and financial autonomy, FTX experienced a huge liquidity crunch in mid-November and approached Binance for help through a possible merger. Within 24 hours, the larger company declined the offer, claiming that the problems the firm was facing were too big to handle. Since then, FTX has entered bankruptcy proceedings and its main executive, Sam Bankman-Fried, has resigned from his post.</p>
<p>Crypto.com has put out a statement claiming that it is not in a position similar with that of FTX. The company says it has enough reserves onboard to stay operational, and that investors don’t have anything to worry about. This sentiment was supported by Owen Rapaport, co-founder and CEO of Argus, who in a recent interview said:</p>
<blockquote><p>To its credit, Crypto.com continues to have the funds to meet these withdrawals, lending further credence to its CEO’s claims that their assets are backed 1:1.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Getting Its Money Back</h2>
<p>At one stage, Crypto.com was heavily tied into FTX’s finances, something that has garnered criticism in recent days. However, Crypto.com immediately responded to the flak it was taking by saying much of the funds stored on the FTX exchange have been recovered. In a YouTube video, Marszalek explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>We recovered $990 million from FTX.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-com-sends-lots-of-money-to-the-wrong-place/">Crypto.com Sends Lots of Money to the Wrong Place</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-com-sends-lots-of-money-to-the-wrong-place/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Iran Hacks U.S. Servers So It Can Mine Cryptocurrency</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/iran-hacks-u-s-servers-so-it-can-mine-cryptocurrency/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/iran-hacks-u-s-servers-so-it-can-mine-cryptocurrency/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 15:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Iran]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lazarus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[North Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75520</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hackers from the sanctioned nation of Iran have allegedly hacked several servers of the United States government as a means of installing software to mine digital currencies. These hackers also allegedly sought to steal various network passwords and compromise the nation’s systems. Iran May Have Compromised the U.S. It is believed that hacking attempts by<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/iran-hacks-u-s-servers-so-it-can-mine-cryptocurrency/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/iran-hacks-u-s-servers-so-it-can-mine-cryptocurrency/">Iran Hacks U.S. Servers So It Can Mine Cryptocurrency</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hackers from the sanctioned nation of Iran <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/iranian-hackers-compromise-us-government-network-in-cryptocurrency-generating-scheme-officials-say/ar-AA14bpr7" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">have allegedly hacked several</a> servers of the United States government as a means of installing software to mine digital currencies. These hackers also allegedly sought to steal various network passwords and compromise the nation’s systems.</p>
<h2>Iran May Have Compromised the U.S.</h2>
<p>It is believed that hacking attempts by Iran may have started back in February of this year. This means that U.S. networks have been in danger for ten months, and regulators only seem to be aware of the situation <em>now</em>. It is alleged that the hackers exploited vulnerabilities the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) began warning about several months ago. Either nobody listened or the information fell on deaf ears.</p>
<p>It is alleged that hackers from Iran are sponsored by members of the region’s government. This shouldn’t come as a surprise given that Iran and the U.S. have never been on the best terms. Situations like this have occurred with other U.S. enemies in the past, a perfect example being the Lazarus hacking group in North Korea.</p>
<p>Lazarus has been <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/hackers-in-north-korea-blamed-for-harmony-attack/" data-wpel-link="internal">caught stealing cryptocurrencies</a> on multiple occasions as a means of funding the nuclear arms program of its home nation of North Korea, another region that has not always been friendly with or to the United States. Both Iran and North Korea are presently dealing with various sanctions enforced by the U.S., which has prevented them from gaining access to standard or traditional financial outlets.</p>
<p>As a result, it appears both have turned to cryptocurrencies to get what they want. In the case of North Korea, Lazarus has been utilized to hack exchanges and digital accounts in multiple countries, one of which was the United States, to garner digital funds so the nation could continue to build and test nuclear arms. It is estimated that the amount of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/north-korea-has-upped-its-attempts-to-garner-crypto-since-2017/" data-wpel-link="internal">money stolen by Lazarus</a> at press time is in the billions.</p>
<p>It has also been suggested that various digital currency companies have either helped these nations avoid U.S. sanctions or engage in cryptocurrency transactions regardless of whether they were lawful. Recently, crypto exchange Binance faced criticism after it was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/did-binance-help-iran-avoid-financial-sanctions/" data-wpel-link="internal">alleged the company</a> helped the nation of Iran take part in roughly $8 billion worth of crypto transactions.</p>
<h2>Governments Use Hackers Against Their Enemies</h2>
<p>Binance later defended its actions, claiming it enforces a top vetting process for all parties engaging in trades and that it didn’t notice anything that would arouse suspicion.</p>
<p>Governments of these countries along with others like China will often hire hackers as contractors. This gives top-standing individuals in those chains of government plausible deniability, meaning they can say they knew nothing of what was going on, nor did they have any control. On several occasions, Iran has denied illegally accessing U.S. data systems.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/iran-hacks-u-s-servers-so-it-can-mine-cryptocurrency/">Iran Hacks U.S. Servers So It Can Mine Cryptocurrency</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/iran-hacks-u-s-servers-so-it-can-mine-cryptocurrency/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Crypto Firm Block Fi Next in Line to File Bankruptcy?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-crypto-firm-block-fi-next-in-line-to-file-bankruptcy/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-crypto-firm-block-fi-next-in-line-to-file-bankruptcy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 13:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bankruptcy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Block Fi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75516</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>2022 has been an atrocious year for cryptocurrency. Many digital asset companies have been forced into dark places and filed for bankruptcy, and it looks like leading blockchain firm Block Fi might be next. Things Aren&#8217;t Looking Good for Block Fi Throughout 2022, the crypto space has been hit harder than it ever has in<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-crypto-firm-block-fi-next-in-line-to-file-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-crypto-firm-block-fi-next-in-line-to-file-bankruptcy/">Is Crypto Firm Block Fi Next in Line to File Bankruptcy?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>2022 has been an atrocious year for cryptocurrency. Many digital asset companies have been forced into dark places and filed for bankruptcy, and it looks like <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/billybambrough/2022/11/16/new-crypto-warning-bankruptcy-fears-suddenly-spread-after-ftx-collapse-wipes-billions-from-the-price-of-bitcoin-ethereum-and-crypto/?sh=4936814e26bd" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">leading blockchain firm</a> Block Fi might be next.</p>
<h2>Things Aren&#8217;t Looking Good for Block Fi</h2>
<p>Throughout 2022, the crypto space has been hit harder than it ever has in its short, 14-year history. Bitcoin, for example, has dropped from its all-time high of about $68,000 per unit – which it achieved in November of last year – and has fallen into the mid-$16K range at the time of writing. The world’s number one digital asset has lost more than 70 percent of its value, and overall, the digital currency space has shed more than $2 trillion in valuation.</p>
<p>Many digital currency companies have also up and vanished because they can no longer deal with ongoing speculation and volatility. Several firms – including the Celsius Network, Voyager Digital, Three Arrows Capital, and recently top <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">exchange FTX</a> – <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-in-the-age-of-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">have all entered bankruptcy</a> proceedings. It’s a sad and ugly sight to see, and one that’s instilling fear in traders’ hearts.</p>
<p>Now, it has been insinuated that Block Fi could be the next to disappear, and investors are not happy. Not long ago, the company hinted in a statement that it was dealing with financial issues and that it was looking for ways to work around them. The company mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>There are a number of scenarios that may be available to us, and we are doing the work now to determine the best path forward.</p></blockquote>
<p>The notice came after it had suspended withdrawals, which <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/another-mega-bitcoin-crash-is-in-the-books/" data-wpel-link="internal">appears to be the token</a> mark of a company that’s about to go under. Dan Ashmore, a crypto analyst, says everyone is on pins and needles following the dreadful collapse of FTX, which was considered one of the strongest and most stable enterprises in the crypto space. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The FTX insolvency is devastating for the entire cryptocurrency industry. Bankruptcy proceedings are long, drawn out, and will likely only end with customers getting pennies on the dollar.</p></blockquote>
<p>In a recent blog post, Block Fi appeared to contradict the idea that it was somehow running out of money, writing:</p>
<blockquote><p>Block Fi has the necessary liquidity to explore all options, and we have engaged expert outside advisors that are helping us navigate Block Fi’s next steps.</p></blockquote>
<h2>People Will Panic</h2>
<p>According to Cory Kippstein, however, this isn’t going to be enough to stop people from panicking. The chief executive of the bitcoin-buying app Swan Bitcoin said in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>All of these centralized businesses with large piles of altcoins on their balance sheets are literally confidence games. They are inherently fragile, susceptible to a Lehman-like collapse at any time, and the only hope once under pressure is that another player will bail them out.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-crypto-firm-block-fi-next-in-line-to-file-bankruptcy/">Is Crypto Firm Block Fi Next in Line to File Bankruptcy?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-crypto-firm-block-fi-next-in-line-to-file-bankruptcy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brazilian Footballer David Luiz is Now the Brand Ambassador for BC.GAME</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brazilian-footballer-david-luiz-is-now-the-brand-ambassador-for-bc-game/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brazilian-footballer-david-luiz-is-now-the-brand-ambassador-for-bc-game/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 10:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76137</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BC.GAME has announced that David Luiz, a Brazilian professional football player of the Flamengo team, has become its official brand ambassador. As the crypto casino’s brand ambassador, Luiz will consistently collaborate with BC.GAME to help promote the casino platform and engage with its community through social media and live-streaming platforms. David Luiz as a Brand<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brazilian-footballer-david-luiz-is-now-the-brand-ambassador-for-bc-game/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brazilian-footballer-david-luiz-is-now-the-brand-ambassador-for-bc-game/">Brazilian Footballer David Luiz is Now the Brand Ambassador for BC.GAME</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://bc.game/i-8wa14xt6-n" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">BC.GAME</a> has announced that David Luiz, a Brazilian professional football player of the Flamengo team, has become its official brand ambassador. As the crypto casino’s brand ambassador, Luiz will consistently collaborate with BC.GAME to help promote the casino platform and engage with its community through social media and live-streaming platforms.</p>
<p><strong>David Luiz as a Brand Ambassador for BC.GAME</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/Cmb8VwPOO23/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">David Luiz</a>’s association with BC.GAME will not only help the crypto casino gain more exposure. As a BC.GAME ambassador and one of Brazil’s most prominent football players, he can connect the Brazilian football community with the crypto casino platform and grow the brand’s player base in Brazil.</p>
<p>David will primarily engage and connect with the crypto casino community through social media activities. He will also be connecting with many players and fans through Twitch, an interactive streaming platform made for gaming and entertainment.</p>
<p>David shared,<em> “I’m very very happy to be partnering with BC.GAME and very excited for the collaboration coming soon.” </em></p>
<p><strong>BC.GAME’s Opportunity For Growth</strong></p>
<p>Brazil has seen a rise in the number of players participating in online casinos, with many opting to play at crypto casinos for their excellent accessibility and offered security. BC.GAME has also recently included sports betting in its gaming portfolio, which also happens to be one of the most popular forms of gambling games in Brazil.</p>
<p>The partnership is an excellent opportunity for BC.GAME to penetrate the Brazilian market and reach more audiences as it expands. With BC.GAME’s entry into the Brazilian casino and sports betting scene, Brazilian football fans and sports betting enthusiasts will have more opportunities to participate in virtual sports and casino events. This includes welcoming grander sports betting opportunities for highly-anticipated sports events like the 2022 FIFA World Cup.</p>
<p>Coco, the emblem of BC.GAME, said, <em>“Brazil has dominated 2022 in regards to tech innovation and regulatory framework for cryptocurrencies and iGaming. BC.GAME has proudly contributed to this since the doors first opened. We are very pleased to be moving into 2023 with this announcement of our partnership with David Luiz. Our combined efforts will help to maintain this trend, with Brazil at the focal point for tech advancements and crypto mass adoption. The world is watching.”</em></p>
<p><strong>About David Luiz</strong></p>
<p>David Luiz Marinho, also known professionally as David Luiz, is a professional football player from Diadema, Brazil. He is part of the Flamengo Rowing Club, a Brazilian sports club headquartered in Rio de Janeiro. Although Luiz mainly plays as a center-back, he’s also known for taking on other roles, such as a defensive midfielder or full-back.</p>
<p>In the 2009 – 2010 season, David was named the LPFP Primeira Liga Player of the Year. He was hailed as the FIFA Club World Cup Silver Ball winner in 2012. He has also earned two FA cups (2011 – 2012 and 2017 – 2018) and holds one FIFA Confederations cup title.</p>
<p><strong>About BC.GAME</strong></p>
<p>BC.GAME is a licensed online crypto casino platform that offers a wide variety of casino games, live casinos, and sports betting events. Besides integrating cryptocurrency and blockchain technology in its platforms, the crypto casino is also one of the first casinos to support lightning networks, Binance Smart Chain, Arbitrum, and other Layer 2 solutions,  further revolutionizing the casino industry and the world of blockchain.</p>
<p>This year, BC.GAME has received the “Crypto Casino Of The Year” title from the 2022 Sigma Awards. It also formed partnerships with the <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/bcgame-is-now-argentine-football-associations-global-crypto-casino-sponsor-301620425.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Argentine Football Association (AFA)</a> and <a href="https://cloud9.gg/latest/cloud9-welcomes-a-new-crypto-casino-partner-bc-game/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Cloud9</a>.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brazilian-footballer-david-luiz-is-now-the-brand-ambassador-for-bc-game/">Brazilian Footballer David Luiz is Now the Brand Ambassador for BC.GAME</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brazilian-footballer-david-luiz-is-now-the-brand-ambassador-for-bc-game/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Recovery Could Fade Near $102</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-recovery-could-fade-near-102/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-recovery-could-fade-near-102/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 04:58:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76134</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline from the $112 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below the $105 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $103 on the 4-hours chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-recovery-could-fade-near-102/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-recovery-could-fade-near-102/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Recovery Could Fade Near $102</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline from the $112 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below the $105 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $103 on the 4-hours chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it breaks the $98 and $95 support levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin cash price is declining from the $112 zone against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-at-risk-of-another-crash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. BCH/USD could decline heavily if there is a move below $95.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin cash price struggled to gain pace for a move above the $111 and $112 resistance levels. BCH formed a high near $111.38 and started a fresh decline.</p>
<p>There was a clear move below the $110 and $105 support levels. The bears even pushed the price below the $100 support and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bears-in-action-can-they-clear-the-100-support/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. It traded as low as $97.52 before there was an upside correction.</p>
<p>The price climbed above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward wave from the $111.38 swing high to $97.52 low. However, the price is struggling to rise above the $102 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</p>
<p>There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $103 on the 4-hours chart of the BCH/USD pair. The trend line is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward wave from the $111.38 swing high to $97.52 low.</p>
<p>The main resistance sits near the $105 level.  Any more gains above $103 and $105 could set the pace for a move towards the $112 level. If there is a move above the $112 resistance, the price could rise towards the $120 zone.</p>
<p>An immediate support on the downside is near the $98 zone. The next major support is near the $95 level, below which the bears might aim $88. The next target for them may perhaps be near the $80 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_76135" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Bitcoin-Cash-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76135" class="size-full wp-image-76135" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Bitcoin-Cash-3.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76135" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Cash Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BCHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, bitcoin cash price is now trading below the $105 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it breaks the $98 and $95 support levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for BCH/USD is losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BCH/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $98 and $95.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $102 and $105.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-recovery-could-fade-near-102/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Recovery Could Fade Near $102</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-recovery-could-fade-near-102/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Anthony Scaramucci on the Fall of FTX</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/anthony-scaramucci-on-the-fall-of-ftx/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/anthony-scaramucci-on-the-fall-of-ftx/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 17:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthony Scaramucci]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75514</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Anthony Scaramucci – the founder of Sky Bridge Capital and the former communications director for President Donald Trump – has given his thoughts on the FTX debacle and the fall of what was labeled one of the biggest and most prominent crypto exchanges in the space. Anthony Scaramucci Gives His Thoughts on FTX FTX took<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/anthony-scaramucci-on-the-fall-of-ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/anthony-scaramucci-on-the-fall-of-ftx/">Anthony Scaramucci on the Fall of FTX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Anthony Scaramucci – the founder of Sky Bridge Capital and the former communications director for President Donald Trump – has <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/11/11/scaramucci-on-ftx-sam-bankman-fried-and-the-worst-week-in-cryptocurrency-history.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">given his thoughts on</a> the FTX debacle and the fall of what was labeled one of the biggest and most prominent crypto exchanges in the space.</p>
<h2>Anthony Scaramucci Gives His Thoughts on FTX</h2>
<p>FTX took a 30 percent stake in Sky Bridge last September. At the time of writing, the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">company has filed</a> bankruptcy and the executive behind it all, Sam Bankman-Fried, has resigned from his post. The company began experiencing trouble in mid-November after it attempted to be bought out by Binance following what online posts described as a “liquidity crunch.”</p>
<p>From there, it looked <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">like there was going</a> to be a merger between Binance and FTX, though this was later cancelled given Binance felt the problems FTX was dealing with would be too big to handle. This is what led the firm into further demise and eventual bankruptcy.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, Bankman-Fried is getting a lot of flak for his role in the enterprise’s fall. Some are claiming that he played around with investors’ money and took too many chances. Others are stating that his greed and malicious nature led to FTX’s collapse. Scaramucci is dismissing all these claims for now, and he’s reluctant to say that there was any fraud contributing to what occurred.</p>
<p>In an interview, he commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>I don’t want to call it fraud at this moment because that’s a legal term. I would implore Sam and his family to tell the truth to their investors. Get to the bottom of it.</p></blockquote>
<p>Scaramucci feels that more than likely what happened is Bankman-Fried made mistakes while coping with the bear market, which he thinks can be said for many companies including Voyager Digital and even the Celsius Network, two firms <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-in-the-age-of-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">that eventually went</a> on to file bankruptcy earlier in the year. He doesn’t necessarily think these companies are bad or did anything malicious.</p>
<p>Rather, he wonders if they simply “lost their cool” as a means of dealing with the bearish conditions 2022 has brought on, and that they weren’t thinking clearly during this time. He further stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>When Three Arrows went down, it could be possible that Sam had difficulty then, and then he made some decisions that turned out to be disastrous for him and both sides of this business.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Maybe Nothing Nasty Was Happening</h2>
<p>Scaramucci then went on to say that he had spent time personally looking into what might have happened, and his research leads him to conclude that there was no illegal activity involved. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Duped I guess is the right word, but I am very disappointed because I do like Sam. I don’t know what happened because I was not an insider at FTX.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/anthony-scaramucci-on-the-fall-of-ftx/">Anthony Scaramucci on the Fall of FTX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/anthony-scaramucci-on-the-fall-of-ftx/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
