<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:18:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/cropped-fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Coin Ex Settles Suit in New York, Vows to Leave the U.S.</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coin-ex-settles-suit-in-new-york-vows-to-leave-the-u-s/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 17:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coin Ex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Leticia James]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New York]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78840</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coin Ex is a digital currency exchange based in Hong Kong. Not long ago, the company was faced with a lawsuit from New York Attorney General Leticia James, who said the firm had violated various financial laws and put traders and investors in danger. Coin Ex Settles, Set to Exit America Now, it looks like [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coin-ex-settles-suit-in-new-york-vows-to-leave-the-u-s/">Coin Ex Settles Suit in New York, Vows to Leave the U.S.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coin Ex is a digital currency exchange based in Hong Kong. Not long ago, the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leticia-james-sues-coin-ex-alleging-crypto-fraud/">company was faced</a> with a lawsuit from New York Attorney General Leticia James, who said the firm had violated various financial laws and put traders and investors in danger.</p>
<h2>Coin Ex Settles, Set to Exit America</h2>
<p>Now, it looks like Coin Ex has <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/coinex-settles-for-17-million-ceases-new-york-operations/ar-AA1cCyIJ">agreed to settle with James</a> for nearly $2 million to get the suit off its back. In addition, the company is also ceasing all its U.S. operations, and the American branch of the exchange is facing imminent shutdown.</p>
<p>The lawsuit against Coin Ex was filed in February of this year. Allegations came about that the company had violated what’s known as the Martin Act, which was enacted in 1921 (over 100 years ago). The law disallows the selling and offering of any securities by companies that haven’t registered as dealers, brokers, or salesmen within specific regions or states (in this case, New York).</p>
<p>By allegedly failing to register either with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) or the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), the company was in violation of the Act and therefore subject to penalties. Leticia James issued a statement regarding the matter that read:</p>
<blockquote><p>Today’s agreement should serve as a warning to crypto companies that there are hefty consequences for ignoring New York’s laws. My office will continue to crack down on crypto companies that brazenly disregard the law, mislead investors, and put New Yorkers at risk… Rampant fraud and dysfunction have become the hallmarks of cryptocurrency, and it is time to bring law and order to the multi-billion-dollar industry.</p></blockquote>
<p>Coin Ex has also mentioned that while the lawsuit ultimately contributed to the decision to leave the U.S., the regulatory atmosphere in America has become too convoluted and confusing for it to handle anymore. Thus, the country will no longer be privy to the exchange’s services or product offerings.</p>
<h2>So Many Crypto Companies Victimized</h2>
<p>This sentiment is shared by several digital asset enterprises at the time of writing. For the past several months, agencies like the SEC have employed harsh methods of enforcing regulation. For example, the SEC has filed major lawsuits against large crypto companies like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-hit-with-sec-lawsuit-says-it-operated-as-an-exchange-broker/">Coinbase</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sues-binance-alleges-selling-of-illegal-securities/">Binance</a>, and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/">Kraken</a>. Not long ago, Coinbase even opened an <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-is-now-active-in-bermuda/">office in Bermuda</a> and said it would be focusing more on international crypto trading and activities until the U.S. can get its rules and priorities in place.</p>
<p>Also, Leticia James can act like she’s concerned for investors’ safety all she wants, but the fact remains that, like the SEC, she’s simply made a habit of going after crypto every chance she can. Several firms – including <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-yorks-leticia-james-sues-crypto-firm-nexo/">Nexo</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-attorney-generals-office-now-suing-ku-coin-exchange/">Ku Coin</a> – have fallen victim to her wrath and been subjected to heavy financial penalties or other punishments.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coin-ex-settles-suit-in-new-york-vows-to-leave-the-u-s/">Coin Ex Settles Suit in New York, Vows to Leave the U.S.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Panel: NFTs Need to Have Real-World Value if They&#8217;re to Succeed</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/panel-nfts-need-to-have-real-world-value-if-theyre-to-succeed/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 15:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jordan Fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rob Nelson]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78838</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Where will non-fungible tokens (NFTs) be in the next few years? NFTs&#8230; Where Will the Future Take Them? NFTs were, at one point, the big rage of the crypto industry. They saw a lot of action and activity, and within two or three years, the arena was worth billions of dollars and was all the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/panel-nfts-need-to-have-real-world-value-if-theyre-to-succeed/">Panel: NFTs Need to Have Real-World Value if They&#8217;re to Succeed</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Where will non-fungible tokens (NFTs) <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/nfts-beyond-the-hype-the-future-of-blockchain-identity/ar-AA1cDeXW">be in the next few</a> years?</p>
<h2>NFTs&#8230; Where Will the Future Take Them?</h2>
<p>NFTs were, at one point, the big rage of the crypto industry. They saw a lot of action and activity, and within two or three years, the arena was worth billions of dollars and was all the rage of crypto fanatics. However, since then, NFTs have <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-ordinals-nfts-are-bringing-the-space-back-from-disaster/">taken a serious dive</a>, and we’re not seeing that many people engaged with them anymore.</p>
<p>In a recent roundtable that saw the participation of several NFT creators and experts, the topic of where these pixelated art tokens are going to be in the next five to ten years raised a lot of questions and delivered a few answers. Each of the participants gave their thoughts and ideas on where these tokens will arrive and what traders can potentially expect.</p>
<p>One of them was Jordan Fried, who introduced the idea of a “soul bound token.” This item would be an NFT that is permanently tied to a single person. It cannot be transferred, sold, or disposed of through conventional means. He commented to the moderator of the panel Rob Nelson:</p>
<blockquote><p>It would be the Rob Nelson coin. It&#8217;d be you. It&#8217;d be the roundtable coin for the brand, but it can&#8217;t be transferred. It&#8217;s non-transferrable. Its soul bound. It&#8217;s bound to this account forever, and that&#8217;s likely what will capture identity as it&#8217;s a version of a non-fungible token, but it&#8217;s a non-transferable, non-fungible token… The greatest problem in the NFT space right now is that there&#8217;s no one sitting anywhere in the world saying, ‘If I just had an NFT, that would be the solution to my problem.&#8217;</p></blockquote>
<p>The idea of having a token permanently tied to you is a little scary, but Jordan clarified his thoughts a tad more by commenting that these tokens would also be built to resolve various problems being faced by the individual or by the public. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>To have a crypto punk meant something about you, but for the technology to actually live up to its promise, you&#8217;re going to have to have NFTs that solve real problems. NFTs that actually have real-world value.</p></blockquote>
<h2>No Real-World Value</h2>
<p>Right now, most non-fungible tokens are simply seen as collectibles. While some have sold for hundreds of thousands of dollars, the “collectible” nature of most NFTs is what Jordan thinks has led to the demise of the space. He commented that they need to be able to tackle certain issues. They must have real-world use if they’re going to carve out a legitimate space for themselves. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>We&#8217;ve got to tokenize actual value as NFTs. Otherwise, the whole purpose of buying an NFT, it&#8217;s just not going to be there for most people.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/panel-nfts-need-to-have-real-world-value-if-theyre-to-succeed/">Panel: NFTs Need to Have Real-World Value if They&#8217;re to Succeed</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is the U.S. Government Hiding a Big BTC Stash Somewhere?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-u-s-government-hiding-a-big-btc-stash-somewhere/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Morgan Creek]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[U.S. government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78836</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. government appears to be very anti crypto as of late. Everywhere you look, regulators in the Biden administration are doing what appears to be all they can to ensure bitcoin and crypto don’t have futures in America. The U.S. Government and Bitcoin&#8230; It&#8217;s Complicated! The SEC, for example, is suing or criminally charging [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-u-s-government-hiding-a-big-btc-stash-somewhere/">Is the U.S. Government Hiding a Big BTC Stash Somewhere?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. government appears to be very anti crypto as of late. Everywhere you look, regulators in the Biden administration are doing what appears to be all they can to ensure bitcoin and crypto don’t have futures in America.</p>
<h2>The U.S. Government and Bitcoin&#8230; It&#8217;s Complicated!</h2>
<p>The SEC, for example, is suing or criminally charging every <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-hit-with-sec-lawsuit-says-it-operated-as-an-exchange-broker/">single digital currency</a> company it can, while Biden is looking to initiate an Obama-era policy that will <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-biden-using-an-obama-era-program-to-ban-btc/">potentially shut all crypto</a> firms out of the traditional finance fray. Thus, it seems like the U.S. government wouldn’t hold much bitcoin and it wouldn’t be <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/us-government-owns-way-more-bitcoin-than-any-other-country-so-why-aren-t-they-selling-it/ar-AA1cDjZk">keeping a private bitcoin</a> stash somewhere… Right?</p>
<p>Wrong. As it turns out, the U.S. government has more than $5 billion in bitcoin secretly hocked away. It’s all illicit bitcoin that representatives have gathered following various seizures over the years, and for one reason or another, they’ve been reluctant to get rid of it or sell it. Why?</p>
<p>Perhaps one reason is because they know <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/inflation/">inflation</a> (which they’re responsible for) is a major issue in the country. They know the dollar is flailing, and they want to have bitcoin as a “backup plan” of sorts because they’re worried about what the prospects of traditional finance are. In many ways, the U.S. government has likely come to see bitcoin as the “safe haven” so many others view it as.</p>
<p>Right now, it’s estimated the U.S. Treasury has more than 207,000 individual bitcoin units stored away somewhere. The money has been garnered over the course of several years through several events, a big one being a Justice Department seizure of more than $1 billion in BTC in 2020. A doctoral thesis written by Sachin Jaitly, a general partner at investment advisory firm Morgan Creek Capital, states the following:</p>
<blockquote><p>By matching publicly available information through the media and blockchain, Elementus is able to map out the universe of sovereign digital wallets and maintain this map over time.</p></blockquote>
<p>Elementus is the blockchain startup Morgan Creek is working with to track the history of the U.S.’s bitcoin collecting habits. CEO Max Galka was also quick to throw his two cents in. He commented that the company has, thus far, recorded at least 11 world governments that are holding bitcoin. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>All of that bitcoin is held by those government agencies, but that does not mean that that is the only bitcoin that is held by those governments, nor that other governments are not using bitcoin.</p></blockquote>
<h2>What Other Entities Hold BTC?</h2>
<p>Jaitly concluded with:</p>
<blockquote><p>As money supply was increasing, and as fear of inflation was increasing, bitcoin adoption on a sovereign level was also increasing, and so there was a relationship that was statistically significant.</p></blockquote>
<p>They have also worked to gather information for North Korea, but that data has proven largely unobtainable.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-u-s-government-hiding-a-big-btc-stash-somewhere/">Is the U.S. Government Hiding a Big BTC Stash Somewhere?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FUN Token Pioneers Blockchain Evolution with 20 Million FUN Seed Fund Initiative</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fun-token-pioneers-blockchain-evolution-with-20-million-fun-seed-fund-initiative/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Gautham]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 12:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79545</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FUNToken is delighted to announce the launch of the FUN Token Seed Fund, an innovative program designed to accelerate the integration of FUN Token into the rapidly expanding blockchain industry. The company set aside a 20 million FUN Tokens reserve and will award 40 dapps with 500,000 FUNToken each. The goal is to inspire these [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fun-token-pioneers-blockchain-evolution-with-20-million-fun-seed-fund-initiative/">FUN Token Pioneers Blockchain Evolution with 20 Million FUN Seed Fund Initiative</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FUNToken is delighted to announce the launch of the <a href="https://bit.ly/459euCA">FUN Token Seed Fund</a>, an innovative program designed to accelerate the integration of FUN Token into the rapidly expanding blockchain industry.</p>
<p>The company set aside a 20 million FUN Tokens reserve and will award 40 dapps with 500,000 FUNToken each. The goal is to inspire these projects to develop creative applications, services, or products incorporating FUN Token, thereby boosting its value and usefulness.</p>
<p>As another advantage to applying for the seed fund, qualified dapps would also gain access to 50 million crypto users by Freebitco.in, further extending their reach and potential impact.</p>
<p>The 500,000 FUN Tokens will be a game-changer for the selected projects, empowering them to improve various aspects of their business, including development, marketing, and operations. The aim is to help them grow quickly and establish a strong market presence.</p>
<p>This initiative will benefit dapps and promote the visibility and adoption of FUN Token. As more platforms adopt FUN, demand for the token will increase, leading to a potential surge in value. The selected projects will also gain recognition and credibility within the crypto industry, attracting more investment and partnerships.</p>
<p>If you&#8217;re eager to participate in this transformational journey, we encourage you to apply by completing the<a href="https://forms.gle/1CTPRzPNUrPFWjDV6"> FUN Token Seed Fund Application Form</a>. The FUN Token Seed Fund is a catalyst for innovation and growth, aligning the future of blockchain with the present through <a href="https://bit.ly/3YdJ77G">FUNToken</a>. We welcome everyone to join us on this journey. With FUN, the future of blockchain integration is brighter and more promising than ever!</p>
<h4>About FUN Token</h4>
<p>FUN Token&#8217;s mission is to leverage the power of blockchain technology to create &#8220;trustless&#8221; gaming ecosystems that users can trust, and operators can implement effortlessly. Supported by industry veteran FreeBitco.in, FUN Token strives to make non-custodial gaming the new industry standard.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fun-token-pioneers-blockchain-evolution-with-20-million-fun-seed-fund-initiative/">FUN Token Pioneers Blockchain Evolution with 20 Million FUN Seed Fund Initiative</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>GAMMA 4, Powered by Bluzelle, Launches Private Beta: Invites Testers to Play and Reshape Crypto Sci-Fi Gaming!</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gamma-4-powered-by-bluzelle-launches-private-beta-invites-testers-to-play-and-reshape-crypto-sci-fi-gaming/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 12:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79526</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>GAMMA 4, the Crypto Sci-Fi Epic, is now available for select players who can also earn early rewards for helping shape the game, powered by Bluzelle ~ Bringing GameFi on Cosmos! Singapore, August 01, 2023 &#8211; Bluzelle, a pioneering blockchain for GameFi, proudly announces the highly-anticipated launch of GAMMA 4 Private Beta, an enthralling sci-fi [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gamma-4-powered-by-bluzelle-launches-private-beta-invites-testers-to-play-and-reshape-crypto-sci-fi-gaming/">GAMMA 4, Powered by Bluzelle, Launches Private Beta: Invites Testers to Play and Reshape Crypto Sci-Fi Gaming!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>GAMMA 4, the Crypto Sci-Fi Epic, is now available for select players who can also earn early rewards for helping shape the game, powered by Bluzelle ~ Bringing GameFi on Cosmos!</em></p>
<p><strong><em>Singapore, August 01, 2023</em></strong> &#8211; Bluzelle, a pioneering blockchain for GameFi, proudly announces the highly-anticipated launch of <a href="http://gamma4.com/">GAMMA 4 Private Beta</a>, an enthralling sci-fi RPG for the Cosmos ecosystem. After 18 months of relentless development by a world-class team, GAMMA 4 is now ready to take players on an extraordinary journey through a galaxy filled with powerful races, NFTs, and thrilling battles.</p>
<h4>Innovations in Web3 Gaming</h4>
<p>GAMMA 4 introduces groundbreaking innovations in Web3 gaming, including card strategy, character breeding, and the captivating use of NFTs. Players will find themselves immersed in a universe where a newly discovered energy source, Elementi, binds with various species  across the galaxy, unleashing formidable abilities. As a cataclysmic event sparks a planetary battle, players must choose sides and embark on a quest of strategic brilliance and epic encounters.</p>
<p>The game&#8217;s features include card deck building, genetic breeding of characters, team selection, exhilarating battles, and NFT character collecting, providing players with a vast array of options and immersive gameplay.</p>
<p>Commenting on the game, <a href="https://bluzelle.com/">Bluzelle</a> CEO and GAMMA 4 Executive Producer Pavel Bains added, &#8220;<em>We&#8217;re excited to announce that GAMMA 4’s private beta will have two full chapters, each consisting of eight levels, totaling 16 levels, and this includes exhilarating Boss Battles. The gameplay is designed to offer an immersive and enjoyable experience, allowing players to explore and provide us with valuable feedback. Our goal is to create a game that not only captivates players but also incorporates their insights to make it truly exceptional.</em>&#8221;</p>
<p>He further commented, &#8220;<em>It&#8217;s a feature complete game but running two levels, and then we&#8217;ll have more. The goal is to put all these good features in, get all the feedback from everybody, and then us and the team keep building more levels.</em>&#8221;</p>
<h4>Exclusive Opportunity for 50 Players</h4>
<p>The GAMMA 4 Private Beta is limited to just 50 players, offering an exclusive opportunity for enthusiastic gamers to join and actively shape the game. Pavel also expressed his excitement, &#8220;<em>We&#8217;re thrilled to offer this opportunity to a select group of 50 players. Their valuable feedback will be instrumental in helping us refine and enhance the gaming experience. It&#8217;s a unique chance to be a part of GAMMA 4&#8217;s development journey from the start.</em>&#8221;</p>
<h4>Rewards for Building a Better Game</h4>
<p>To reward the dedication of the selected players in shaping the game, Bluzelle will offer three exclusive NFT character cards as players progress through the campaigns. Players&#8217; feedback will be helpful in building and enhancing the game, and they will receive three unique NFT character entities as a token of appreciation. These rare NFTs will become cherished collector&#8217;s items, symbolizing their role in GAMMA 4&#8217;s legacy.</p>
<p>With the GAMMA 4 Private Beta release, Bluzelle aims to gather valuable feedback from the community and build a dynamic and captivating gaming experience that will push the boundaries of GameFi entertainment.</p>
<p>The GAMMA 4 Private Beta is LIVE now. Complete the Quests on Zealy and be among the first 50 players to access and play the game now.</p>
<p>To Complete the Quests on Zealy, visit : <a href="https://zealy.io/c/gamma4/questboard">https://zealy.io/c/gamma4/questboard</a></p>
<p>Watch the GAMMA 4 Private Beta World Premiere to learn more: <a href="https://bit.ly/3PX3ZxO">https://bit.ly/3PX3ZxO</a></p>
<p>For more information, visit <a href="http://gamma4.com">http://gamma4.com</a>.</p>
<p><strong>Follow GAMMA 4 ~The Crypto Sci-Fi Epic</strong></p>
<p><a href="http://www.gamma4.com/">Website</a> | <a href="https://twitter.com/gamma_four?s=21">Twitter</a> | <a href="http://capella.bluzelle.com/">Capella</a> | <a href="https://t.co/MQIgGclevf">Discord</a></p>
<p><strong>About Bluzelle</strong></p>
<p>Bluzelle is an advanced L1 blockchain with 10K TPS, set to transform the Web3 gaming landscape with high-quality games. Upgraded to the latest Stargate V9, Bluzelle is <em>bringing GameFi on Cosmos </em>with codebase enhancements, IBC compatibility, Osmosis integration, fast &amp; affordable cross-chain transfers, and more.</p>
<p>Bluzelle R2, a decentralized storage layer, uses a multi-node backup mechanism to ensure enhanced security of users’ assets in the Bluzelle ecosystem on GAMMA 4 and Capella, the first NFT Marketplace on Bluzelle.</p>
<p>Keep an eye out on Bluzelle’s official social channels to learn more.</p>
<p><a href="https://bluzelle.com/">Website</a> | <a href="https://twitter.com/bluzellehq?s=21">Twitter</a> | <a href="https://t.me/bluzelle">Telegram</a> | <a href="https://discord.com/invite/af7byz6">Discord</a> | <a href="https://blog.bluzelle.com/">Medium</a> | <a href="https://www.binance.com/en-IN/feed/profile/35193718">Binance Feed</a></p>
<p><strong> </strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gamma-4-powered-by-bluzelle-launches-private-beta-invites-testers-to-play-and-reshape-crypto-sci-fi-gaming/">GAMMA 4, Powered by Bluzelle, Launches Private Beta: Invites Testers to Play and Reshape Crypto Sci-Fi Gaming!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Finance Professor Disagrees with United Kingdom Sentiment Towards Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/finance-professor-disagrees-with-united-kingdom-sentiment-towards-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gavin Brown]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United Kingdom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78830</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, regulators in the United Kingdom said crypto trading was akin to gambling. In other words, betting on bitcoin was like sitting at a blackjack table. Not exactly the best metaphor, but we get what the country means. Is the United Kingdom Wrong About Crypto? However, there are many that don’t agree with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/finance-professor-disagrees-with-united-kingdom-sentiment-towards-crypto/">Finance Professor Disagrees with United Kingdom Sentiment Towards Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, regulators in the United Kingdom said <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-united-kingdom-wants-gambling-laws-to-apply-to-crypto-trading/">crypto trading was akin</a> to gambling. In other words, betting on bitcoin was like sitting at a blackjack table. Not exactly the best metaphor, but we get what the country means.</p>
<h2>Is the United Kingdom Wrong About Crypto?</h2>
<p>However, there are many <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-au/money/markets/labelling-cryptocurrency-as-gambling-shows-lack-of-understanding-and-misses-the-solution-expert-says/ar-AA1cyjeZ">that don’t agree with</a> this sentiment. In fact, they think it’s downright wrong, and they say it shows a dangerous lack of understanding. Amongst the people that feel this way is Gavin Brown, an associate professor in financial technology at the University of Liverpool.</p>
<p>In a recent interview, Brown criticized lawmakers in the United Kingdom for not bothering to comprehend the ins and outs of blockchain and crypto a bit better. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>[The committee] didn&#8217;t really understand the technology.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also mentioned that the people of the country know much more about crypto than those that have been placed in charge, and he thinks this is going to lead the United Kingdom down a dark path that will eventually put it behind other regions. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I see that all the time. I&#8217;ll get a taxi in London and the taxi driver will know ten times more [about cryptocurrency] than the CEO of a multinational bank I&#8217;m about to visit. We still see that disparity of knowledge, and not just from people on the street, but also from people who are actually making the policies who should know better.</p></blockquote>
<p>He says the time has come for everyday people and politicians to recognize crypto once and for all, and to acknowledge the idea that it’s here to stay. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Western Anglo-Saxon economies are stuck between a rock and a hard place because it&#8217;s not going away, and it&#8217;s a constant threat… The problem we have with things like… bitcoin, is that it&#8217;s not controllable or ban-able in a traditional sense because… [it] doesn&#8217;t have a CEO, a head office, any employees, an email address, doesn&#8217;t file any accounts, doesn&#8217;t have any buildings, has no AGM, [and] has no shareholders. Literally, bitcoin is an idea. It&#8217;s a computer program that&#8217;s being run globally all over the world at the same time… [Cryptocurrency] has been deliberately constructed in a way that is anti-state, and almost naturally beyond the reach of regulators.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Understanding Must Grow</h2>
<p>Natasha Gillezeau – a SXSW Sydney production lead and former Australian journalist – echoed Brown’s sentiment and said:</p>
<blockquote><p>People need to understand how serious [cryptocurrency] is. We [need] to understand how much of a marketing and advertising push that crypto [companies have] done in the last few years… We&#8217;re talking sports stadiums [sponsored by] Crypto.com, we&#8217;re talking outreach to influencers… We&#8217;re in a different point in the cycle of how much the marketing and advertising industry has legitimized it.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/finance-professor-disagrees-with-united-kingdom-sentiment-towards-crypto/">Finance Professor Disagrees with United Kingdom Sentiment Towards Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Opinion: Bitcoin Will Reach $60K Next Year, a New High in 2025, and Drop in 2026</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-bitcoin-will-reach-60k-next-year-a-new-high-in-2025-and-drop-in-2026/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 15:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Opinion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OpEd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin patterns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78826</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin could be back at its $60K high next year (if it doesn’t shoot slightly beyond that). In 2025, the currency will likely reach a new price peak, and in 2026, the currency may drop again. The Repeating Price Patterns of Bitcoin This isn’t just random speculation. Rather, it&#8217;s a complete consideration of all the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-bitcoin-will-reach-60k-next-year-a-new-high-in-2025-and-drop-in-2026/">Opinion: Bitcoin Will Reach $60K Next Year, a New High in 2025, and Drop in 2026</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin could be back at its $60K high next year (if it doesn’t shoot slightly beyond that). In 2025, the currency will likely reach a new price peak, and in 2026, the currency may drop again.</p>
<h2>The Repeating Price Patterns of Bitcoin</h2>
<p>This isn’t just random speculation. Rather, it&#8217;s a complete consideration of all the price routines bitcoin has endured over the past 11 years or so. When one looks at how bitcoin has behaved, it seems to fall onto the same path every four years.</p>
<p>Look at 2012, 2013, and 2014, for example. During that first year, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitcoin/">bitcoin</a> was still new. It was trading for a few nickels or dollars. Nothing special to report. The following year, by the time we reached the final months (November and December), the world’s number one digital currency had <a href="https://www.globaldata.com/data-insights/financial-services/bitcoins-price-history/#:~:text=During%20its%20initial%20years%2C%20bitcoin%20had%20limited%20popularity,attained%20the%20%241%2C127.45%20price%20on%20November%2030%2C%202013.">shot up to about</a> $1,000 per unit. In 2014, the asset <a href="https://www.in2013dollars.com/bitcoin-price-in-2014">sunk into the $400 range</a>, thus experiencing its first major drop.</p>
<p>Now, let’s shift our focus to 2015, 2016, 2017, and 2018. 2015 saw bitcoin struggling, though it eventually began to show more signs of life towards the ending months, rising from the high $100 range to about $300. The next year, during the time of a presidential election, the currency shot up to about $900 or $1,000 again briefly, thus again reaching its 2013 high. After that, BTC rose to almost $20K, thus recording a new price peak for itself before sinking into oblivion and losing about 70 percent of its value in 2018 (the currency fell into the mid-$3,000 range).</p>
<p>Let’s then look at the next four years: 2019, 2020, 2021, and 2022. 2019 was very similar to 2015 in that bitcoin showed small signs of life here and there. It rose a bit towards the end of the year, but nothing that significant occurred. 2020 – the year of another election – arrived, and bitcoin surpassed its previous $20K high. 2021 brought the currency to a new pinnacle, and 2022 removed all the positive price action from the books and is considered the worst year on record for BTC and crypto (the space wound up losing more than $2 trillion in overall valuation).</p>
<h2>Healing Now, Then Everything Else Will Follow Over Three Years</h2>
<p>We are now in 2023, and thus far, it’s looking a lot like 2015 and 2019. There’s a little bit of healing in the mix, but nothing big is happening (yet). We are once again entering into the patterns we saw during the previous four-year roundabouts.</p>
<p>This new cycle encompasses 2023, 2024, 2025, and 2026. With light healing happening now, one can assume that next year (another election year) will bring bitcoin back to the $60K range, its previous high (like we saw in 2016 and 2020). If things continue in the same direction, we’ll see BTC reach a new high in 2025 (as we witnessed in 2017 and 2021), and bitcoin may be in for another major drop in 2026 (like in 2018 and 2022).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-bitcoin-will-reach-60k-next-year-a-new-high-in-2025-and-drop-in-2026/">Opinion: Bitcoin Will Reach $60K Next Year, a New High in 2025, and Drop in 2026</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Experienced Huge Fall in Mid-June Following Fed Announcement</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-experienced-huge-fall-in-mid-june-following-fed-announcement/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 13:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[federal reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Safai]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78824</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin fell below the $25,000 mark for the first time in a while in mid-June of this year after the Federal Reserve threw yet another monkey wrench into America’s economic plans. Major June Dip for Bitcoin During that time, the Federal Reserve announced that while it was not going to be hiking rates again in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-experienced-huge-fall-in-mid-june-following-fed-announcement/">Bitcoin Experienced Huge Fall in Mid-June Following Fed Announcement</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin fell below the $25,000 mark for the <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-drops-below-25000-tethers-stablecoin-falls-under-its-dollar-peg/ar-AA1cAtPV">first time in a while</a> in mid-June of this year after the Federal Reserve threw yet another monkey wrench into America’s economic plans.</p>
<h2>Major June Dip for Bitcoin</h2>
<p>During that time, the Federal Reserve announced that while it was not going to be hiking rates again in the immediate future, citizens of the U.S. could potentially expect to experience the effects of at least two more rate hikes before the end of the year. In other words, two more hikes would occur within the next six months.</p>
<p>Bitcoin didn’t take too kindly to the news and reacted somewhat violently, dropping into the $24K range after it had been trading for about $25,800 for the past 48 hours or so. That’s a drop of about $1,000 in just a few days. It just goes to show traders that bitcoin is still highly sensitive to present macroeconomic conditions being faced by the U.S., and while the crypto winter of last year may be marginally over, things aren’t quite as strong as they could (or should) be.</p>
<p>Michael Safai – managing partner at Dexterity Capital – commented on the bitcoin dip to occur after the Federal Reserve announcement. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>This has little to do with the FOMC and more to do with thinner liquidity and weak sentiment. Given how thin trading volumes are [now], a sizable (but not massive) sell order is enough to set off liquidations. Traders are more inclined to keep their money off the table [amid] this regulatory backlash, especially when it comes to altcoins, so there isn&#8217;t going to be much new capital flowing in to buoy prices so readily.</p></blockquote>
<p>To be fair, a lot has been going on in the last six weeks that bitcoin should have reacted more to, yet for some reason, it didn’t. For example, major lawsuits stemming from the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) against <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sues-binance-alleges-selling-of-illegal-securities/">Binance</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-hit-with-sec-lawsuit-says-it-operated-as-an-exchange-broker/">Coinbase</a> – the two biggest digital currency exchanges in the world – should have ultimately caused bitcoin to tank like no other event has.</p>
<h2>Is Regulation Coming or Not?</h2>
<p>However, bitcoin remained relatively resilient during all that, losing only a few hundred dollars here and there and experiencing marginal bumps after the news made headlines. Safai added:</p>
<blockquote><p>Further confusion about the legality of popular altcoins is keeping capital on the sidelines, and it&#8217;ll take a long run of good news or no news to get traders feeling excited about a recovery. Bitcoin prices will stay relatively rangebound between $25,000 and $27,000 until the next set of regulatory headlines tell us whether we&#8217;re heading towards resolution or even more obfuscation.</p></blockquote>
<p>The issue of regulatory clarity in the crypto space has long been a huge one, and calls have only increased tenfold since the fall of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/">FTX last November</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-experienced-huge-fall-in-mid-june-following-fed-announcement/">Bitcoin Experienced Huge Fall in Mid-June Following Fed Announcement</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Aims Fresh Increase To $0.18</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-aims-fresh-increase-to-0-18/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 05:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar Lumens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79523</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stellar lumen price is attempting a fresh increase from the $0.14 zone against the US Dollar. XLM price is now trading above $0.150 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $0.145 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-aims-fresh-increase-to-0-18/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Aims Fresh Increase To $0.18</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Stellar lumen price is attempting a fresh increase from the $0.14 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>XLM price is now trading above $0.150 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $0.145 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a major increase if there is a clear move above the $0.1650 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Stellar lumen price is trading above $0.150 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. XLM price must clear $0.1650 to start a fresh increase.</em></p>
<h2>Stellar Lumen Price Analysis (XLM to USD)</h2>
<p>After a steady increase, Stellar lumen price saw a downside correction below the $0.180 level against the US Dollar. The XLM/USD pair traded below the $0.165 support and tested the $0.140 zone.</p>
<p>A low is formed near $0.1404 and the price is now attempting a recovery wave. There was a break above the $0.145 resistance zone. Besides, there was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $0.145 on the 4-hour chart.</p>
<p>The price climbed above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.1807 swing high to the $0.1404 low. XLM is now trading above $0.150 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-remains-supported-for-fresh-rally-above-0-18/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $0.165 zone. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.1807 swing high to the $0.1404 low. The next major resistance is near the $0.180 level.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $0.180 level might send the price toward the $0.192 level. Any more gains could lead the price toward the $0.200 level or even $0.2150.</p>
<p>Initial support on the downside is near the $0.1520 level. The main support is near the $0.140 zone. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.1250 level in the near term, below which the price might even retest $0.1120.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79524" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79524" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-4.png"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-79524" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-4.png" alt="Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price" width="1835" height="839" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-4.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-4-600x274.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-4-1100x503.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-4-768x351.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-4-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-4-750x343.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-4-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79524" class="wp-caption-text">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XLMUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a> indicates that XLM price is now trading above $0.150 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start a major increase if there is a clear move above the $0.1650 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XLM/USD is losing momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for XLM/USD is now near the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.1520 and $0.1400.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.165, $0.180, and $0.200.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-aims-fresh-increase-to-0-18/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Aims Fresh Increase To $0.18</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
