<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 03:35:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Brian Armstrong Thinks Coinbase Is Going to Make a Return</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brian-armstrong-thinks-coinbase-is-going-to-make-a-return/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brian-armstrong-thinks-coinbase-is-going-to-make-a-return/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 17:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brian armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75674</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase is a digital currency exchange that has suffered exponentially this year. The digital currency trading platform initially went public on the Nasdaq in April of 2021. Since then, it has seen its stock price crash roughly 80 percent in less than two years, and the fall can largely be attributed to the fact that<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brian-armstrong-thinks-coinbase-is-going-to-make-a-return/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brian-armstrong-thinks-coinbase-is-going-to-make-a-return/">Brian Armstrong Thinks Coinbase Is Going to Make a Return</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase is a digital currency exchange that has suffered exponentially this year. The digital currency trading platform initially went public on the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-spikes-following-public-debut-of-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">Nasdaq in April of 2021</a>. Since then, it has seen its stock price crash roughly 80 percent in less than two years, and the fall can largely be attributed to the fact that bitcoin – and many other digital currencies – have been falling like crazy since reaching new all-time highs in November of last year.</p>
<h2>Coinbase Is &#8220;Undervalued&#8221; Says Founder</h2>
<p>During that time, bitcoin was trading at a whopping $68,000 per unit, though now, the world’s number one digital currency has fallen into the low $16K range. It’s a sad and ugly sight to see, and one that’s likely not going to change for some time.</p>
<p>Brian Armstrong – the CEO and founder of the digital currency exchange – <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/billybambrough/2022/11/19/undervalued-coinbase-ceo-reveals-bullish-crypto-prediction-after-200-billion-ftx-bitcoin-and-ethereum-price-crash/?sh=3dea18274608" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">says he’s not too worried</a> about the present situation and he feels bitcoin, Ethereum, and many other leading digital currencies are going to make serious comebacks soon when regulators step into the mix. He commented that tip-top regulation in the United States could potentially help many of crypto’s largest companies make surefire returns from the doldrums.</p>
<p>He further stated that he thinks his own company Coinbase is undervalued, and he believes its stock will eventually return to form. He mentioned in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>I’m so glad that [went public]. I’m glad that we’re helping the market kind of understand crypto cycles better&#8230; because that’s kind of been our history as a company, [that] we want to blaze a trail, legitimize the whole industry. We don’t mind being misunderstood or questioned for a few years. We’re playing this for the long term.</p></blockquote>
<p>The fall of bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies has caused Coinbase <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-says-its-laying-off-several-employees/" data-wpel-link="internal">to have to cut its staff</a> by roughly 18 percent. Initially, 2022 was going to be a year in which the exchange brought on three times more staff members and grew to exponential peaks, though things really didn’t turn out this way as the last several months have produced one of the worst bear markets in the history of crypto, and what began as a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-says-its-freezing-all-2022-hiring-plans/" data-wpel-link="internal">hiring freeze</a> turned into a complete meltdown of the exchange’s employee offices.</p>
<h2>Will Things Move More Towards Defi?</h2>
<p>With the recent <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">collapse of FTX</a>, some are wondering if centralized exchanges have much of a chance anymore and if defi won’t take over the space, but Serhii Zhdanov – chief executive of crypto exchange EXMO – doesn’t believe this will happen. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>It would be logical to assume that there will be a shift in the market structure in favor of decentralized platforms. Nevertheless, the FTX story could be a reason for regulators to tighten their requirements for crypto companies, which, on the contrary, will lead to stronger centralization to ensure full control from governments.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brian-armstrong-thinks-coinbase-is-going-to-make-a-return/">Brian Armstrong Thinks Coinbase Is Going to Make a Return</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brian-armstrong-thinks-coinbase-is-going-to-make-a-return/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>El Salvador Is in Debt Because of BTC; It&#8217;s Turning to China for Help</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-is-in-debt-because-of-btc-its-turning-to-china-for-help/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-is-in-debt-because-of-btc-its-turning-to-china-for-help/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 15:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[china]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[El Salvador]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75666</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>El Salvador has lost so much for buying bitcoin that it’s now engaging in a new free-trade plan with China, something that’s causing many analysts to worry. They believe El Salvador’s sovereignty will eventually be up for sale, which could put the Central American nation into an even darker place. How Much Trouble Is El<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-is-in-debt-because-of-btc-its-turning-to-china-for-help/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-is-in-debt-because-of-btc-its-turning-to-china-for-help/">El Salvador Is in Debt Because of BTC; It&#8217;s Turning to China for Help</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>El Salvador has lost so much for buying bitcoin <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/after-cryptocurrency-dip-el-salvador-seeks-cash-from-china/ar-AA14jrDn" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">that it’s now engaging in</a> a new free-trade plan with China, something that’s causing many analysts to worry. They believe El Salvador’s sovereignty will eventually be up for sale, which could put the Central American nation into an even darker place.</p>
<h2>How Much Trouble Is El Salvador in?</h2>
<p>El Salvador has lost money due to its love for bitcoin. The country was the first in the world to declare bitcoin legal tender, doing so <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-fully-legal-in-el-salvador-beginning-september-7/" data-wpel-link="internal">in September of last year</a>. The nation made it illegal for businesses to turn away customers seeking to pay for everyday goods and services with BTC, which they could use alongside USD (a currency the nation has long been dependent on).</p>
<p>Right now, many regulators in the nation are not willing to share information regarding the country’s bitcoin trading and investing habits. Ricardo Castaneda, the country coordinator for El Salvador at the Central American Institute for Fiscal Studies (ICEFI), stated in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Unfortunately, if one asks for information about the extent of investments into bitcoin, the answer is either that this information doesn&#8217;t exist or it&#8217;s confidential.</p></blockquote>
<p>He further stated that right now, the only information out there that helps national regulators determine how much BTC the nation has purchased comes from the tweets of Nayib Bukele, the president of El Salvador. From the messages, it can be assumed the country has bought about $120 million worth of bitcoin.</p>
<p>Over the past several months, the asset has lost more than 70 percent of its overall value, falling from about $68,000 per unit in November of last year (a new all-time high) into the low $16K range at the time of writing. Robert Rubio Fabian, executive director of the National Foundation for Development and Transparency International’s representative in El Salvador, stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>When the international markets see how high the fiscal deficit is, how spending can&#8217;t be paid for and how debt is accumulating, they are going to be more cautious and consider you [a] high risk.</p></blockquote>
<p>El Salvador is having to pursue other means of pumping money into its economy, one of which is forging a free-trade deal with China. Right now, the Asian country has made a few separate investments in the region. Rubio Fabian detailed what those investments were:</p>
<blockquote><p>China made three donations to El Salvador: the construction of a sort of beach amusement park, a stadium that has yet to be built, and a library. These investments improve China&#8217;s image and, obviously, our country&#8217;s image, too.</p></blockquote>
<h2>China Is Behaving Generously</h2>
<p>Per Felix Ulloa, the vice president of El Salvador, China is offering to purchase El Salvador’s debt, which at press time, is just shy of $700 million. He’s not sure if the country will utilize this route, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>China offered to buy all our debt, but we need to tread with caution.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-is-in-debt-because-of-btc-its-turning-to-china-for-help/">El Salvador Is in Debt Because of BTC; It&#8217;s Turning to China for Help</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-is-in-debt-because-of-btc-its-turning-to-china-for-help/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Clowncoin Is Dancing Its Way Into the Crypto Space</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/clowncoin-is-dancing-its-way-into-the-crypto-space/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/clowncoin-is-dancing-its-way-into-the-crypto-space/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 13:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clowncoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dave Mattarocci]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75663</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new cryptocurrency called “Clowncoin” is coming to the market. While other currencies can grow and earn their owners some potential profits, this one will wear white face makeup and a red nose while performing circus acts to entertain kids. Clowncoin Has Arrived! Eh, not quite. Despite its goofball name, the asset is slated to<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/clowncoin-is-dancing-its-way-into-the-crypto-space/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/clowncoin-is-dancing-its-way-into-the-crypto-space/">Clowncoin Is Dancing Its Way Into the Crypto Space</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new cryptocurrency called “Clowncoin” is <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/pueblo-native-helps-launch-clowncoin-130031364.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">coming to the market</a>. While other currencies can grow and earn their owners some potential profits, this one will wear white face makeup and a red nose while performing circus acts to entertain kids.</p>
<h2>Clowncoin Has Arrived!</h2>
<p>Eh, not quite. Despite its goofball name, the asset is slated to do many of the other things that present altcoins do. The currency was founded by Dave Mattarocci, an information technology graduate of Pueblo Community College. He’s now trying hard to promote Clowncoin on social media at night while working as a first responder during the day.</p>
<p>In a recent interview, Mattarocci discussed the importance of digital currency and talked about what he thinks makes Clowncoin different from its virtual counterparts. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Cryptocurrency is a digital currency that is a newer concept which is starting to grow. The purpose is to invest and make money or use it as a form of paying for services.</p></blockquote>
<p>He further stated that buying digital currency can be a little difficult to do on one’s own. Thus, despite the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">crash of FTX</a>, he thinks exchanges can still serve heavy purposes within the realm of the crypto trading arena. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>With an exchange, you are buying the cryptocurrency that they own in their wallet, and they say, &#8216;You own this amount of it,&#8217; but they technically own the coin unless you move it to your own wallet. There is the potential for loss if the cryptocurrency is held within an exchange. FTX basically went under because it is a bear market right now. Not a whole lot of people are making money in investing right now and there are a lot of crypto exchanges out there that make their money on fees, so it puts them in a tender spot when people are not buying.</p></blockquote>
<h2>How Can People Own the Coin?</h2>
<p>He says that crypto ownership with Clowncoin is different from the ownership process of virtually any other kind of digital currency in existence. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>With Clowncoin, we have renounced ownership, which means nobody owns it and no one can pull funds out. It is completely safe and completely community run. It is a stress-free investment and is unique because we have a ten percent tax anytime someone buys or sells the coin. With that, five percent is redistributed to Clowncoin holders, so you make money just by holding the coin. The remaining five percent is put into a liquidity pool, which is like a locked bank account that grows and increases the coin&#8217;s value. So even if there is a mass selloff of the coin, it holds value because of that locked bank account.</p></blockquote>
<p>With each transaction, a unit of currency will be burned, ensuring the supply stays fully under control.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/clowncoin-is-dancing-its-way-into-the-crypto-space/">Clowncoin Is Dancing Its Way Into the Crypto Space</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/clowncoin-is-dancing-its-way-into-the-crypto-space/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Key Resistance And Downtrend Intact</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-key-resistance-and-downtrend-intact/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-key-resistance-and-downtrend-intact/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 04:58:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76184</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ADA price is trading in a bearish zone below the $0.30 support zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above $0.26 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.285 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken). The price could continue<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-key-resistance-and-downtrend-intact/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-key-resistance-and-downtrend-intact/">Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Key Resistance And Downtrend Intact</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>ADA price is trading in a bearish zone below the $0.30 support zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $0.26 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.285 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The price could continue to move down if it stays below the $0.2850 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Cardano price is struggling below $0.285 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-at-risk-of-another-crash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. ADA price could start a recovery wave if it clears the $0.275 and $0.285 resistance levels.</em></p>
<h2>Cardano Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Earlier this month, cardano price saw a fresh decline below the $0.300 zone against the US Dollar. The ADA/USD pair declined below the $0.295 and $0.285 support levels.</p>
<p>The price even declined below the $0.265 support and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-bears-in-control-upsides-could-be-limited/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hour)</a>. A low was formed near $0.2467 and the price is now consolidating losses. The price is now trading above $0.26 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</p>
<p>On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $0.265 zone. It is near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3290 swing high to $0.2467 low. The first major resistance is near the $0.275 level.</p>
<p>The next major resistance could be near the $0.285 zone. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.285 on the 4-hours chart. The trend line is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3290 swing high to $0.2467 low.</p>
<p>A clear upside break above the $0.285 level might send the price towards the $0.300 resistance. Any more gains could start a steady increase towards the $0.320 level.</p>
<p>On the downside, an immediate support is near the $0.260 level. The next major support is near the $0.250 level, below which the price may perhaps decline towards the $0.235 support level. Any more losses might call for a test of the $0.212 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_76185" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Cardano-Price-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76185" class="size-full wp-image-76185" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Cardano-Price-3.png" alt="Cardano (ADA) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76185" class="wp-caption-text">Cardano (ADA) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ADAUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that ADA price is now trading above $0.260 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $0.285 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ADA/USD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for ADA/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.260 and $0.250.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.275 and $0.285.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-key-resistance-and-downtrend-intact/">Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Key Resistance And Downtrend Intact</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-key-resistance-and-downtrend-intact/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Could Attempt Fresh Increase Above $1,240</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-attempt-fresh-increase-above-1240/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-attempt-fresh-increase-above-1240/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 03:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76179</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum price is slowly moving higher above the $1,200 level against the US Dollar. ETH price is now trading above $1,200 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $1,210 on the 4-hours chart (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could start a decent increase<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-attempt-fresh-increase-above-1240/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-attempt-fresh-increase-above-1240/">Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Could Attempt Fresh Increase Above $1,240</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ethereum price is slowly moving higher above the $1,200 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>ETH price is now trading above $1,200 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $1,210 on the 4-hours chart (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could start a decent increase if it clears the $1,240 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ethereum price is struggling below $1,240 against the US Dollar. ETH/USD could start another decline if it remains below the $1,250 zone.</em></p>
<h2>Ethereum Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, ethereum saw a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-turns-red-again-risk-of-more-downsides/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">strong decline</a> below the $1,250 level against the US Dollar. ETH price declined below the $1,220 level and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</p>
<p>The price traded as low as $1,150 before the bulls appeared. ETH price started a decent recovery wave above the $1,180 and $1,185 resistance levels. The price climbed above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $1,350 swing high to $1,151 low.</p>
<p>The price is now trading above $1,200 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-bulls-aim-upside-break-above-1300/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. Besides, there is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $1,210 on the 4-hours chart.</p>
<p>An immediate resistance is near the $1,230 level. The first major resistance is near the $1,250 level. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $1,350 swing high to $1,151 low. The next major resistance is near the $1,275 zone.</p>
<p>The main resistance is near the $1,300 zone. A clear move above the $1,275 and $1,300 resistance levels might call for a decent increase to $1,350. Any more gains could even send the price above the $1,400 resistance zone.</p>
<p>On the downside, an initial support is near the $1,210 level and the trend line. The next major support is now near the $1,200 level. A break below the $1,200 support could push the price to $1,150. If the bulls struggle to protect the $1,150 support, the price might decline towards $1,100.</p>
<div id="attachment_76180" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Ethereum-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76180" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-76180" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Ethereum-3.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76180" class="wp-caption-text">Ethereum Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Ethereum price is clearly trading above $1,200 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, ether price could start a decent increase if it clears the $1,240 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $1,200, followed by the $1,150 zone.</p>
<p>Key Resistance$ Levels – $1,250 and $1,275.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-attempt-fresh-increase-above-1240/">Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Could Attempt Fresh Increase Above $1,240</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-attempt-fresh-increase-above-1240/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>John Ray III: FTX Is the Most Mismanaged Company I&#8217;ve Ever Seen</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/john-ray-iii-ftx-is-the-most-mismanaged-company-ive-ever-seen/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/john-ray-iii-ftx-is-the-most-mismanaged-company-ive-ever-seen/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[John Ray III]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75572</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>John Ray III is an attorney that’s been in the news a lot, lately. He’s the man who cleaned up the Enron mess close to 20 years ago, and now he’s been called in to fix the problems surrounding failed digital currency exchange FTX. John Ray III Has Been Called in to Fix FTX As<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/john-ray-iii-ftx-is-the-most-mismanaged-company-ive-ever-seen/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/john-ray-iii-ftx-is-the-most-mismanaged-company-ive-ever-seen/">John Ray III: FTX Is the Most Mismanaged Company I&#8217;ve Ever Seen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>John Ray III is an attorney that’s been in the news a lot, lately. He’s the man who cleaned up the Enron mess close to 20 years ago, and <a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/sanfrancisco/news/ftx-cryptocurrency-complete-failure-sam-bankman-fried-john-ray-ceo/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">now he’s been called in</a> to fix the problems surrounding failed digital currency exchange <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX</a>.</p>
<h2>John Ray III Has Been Called in to Fix FTX</h2>
<p>As the new CEO of the now bankrupt digital currency firm, Ray commented that he has never seen such a poorly governed company in all his life, nor has ever witnessed such mismanagement of funds. He stated in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Never in my career have I seen such a complete failure of corporate controls and such a complete absence of trustworthy financial information as occurred here. From compromised systems integrity and faulty regulatory oversight abroad, to the concentration of control in the hands of a very small group of inexperienced, unsophisticated, and potentially compromised individuals, this situation is unprecedented.</p></blockquote>
<p>It is being reported that user funds stored within the digital currency exchange were used to purchase luxury homes and other items in the Bahamas for company employees. At the peak of the firm’s collapse, Ray was brought on as the new CEO, with his first day being November 11 of this year.</p>
<p>Sam Bankman-Fried has also been called out because he recently admitted in an interview that he only made appearances in Washington and spoke of regulation as a means of attracting attention to the company. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Regulators, they make everything worse.</p></blockquote>
<p>Ray furthered his discussion with:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bankman-Fried is not employed by the debtors and does not speak for them. In the Bahamas, I understand that corporate funds of the FTX Group were used to purchase homes and other personal items for employees and advisors. I understand that there does not appear to be documentation for certain of these transactions as loans, and that certain real estate was recorded in the personal name of these employees and advisors on the records of the Bahamas.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A King Has Become a Pauper</h2>
<p>The drama surrounding FTX has likely marred the crypto space on a permanent basis. At one time, FTX was considered the golden child of the crypto arena. The cryptocurrency exchange first came to fruition in the year 2019 and quickly rose to prominence as one of the largest digital currency trading platforms in the world. Sam Bankman-Fried was lauded as a genius and many felt the company had a solid and clear future in the world of crypto.</p>
<p>Sadly, this image is fading fast as the company has fallen into a hole of criminality and mistrust. Each day, more information comes out about the enterprise that puts it in a very poor light, and one must wonder if this incident is going to prevent some people from ever trusting this new financial space.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/john-ray-iii-ftx-is-the-most-mismanaged-company-ive-ever-seen/">John Ray III: FTX Is the Most Mismanaged Company I&#8217;ve Ever Seen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/john-ray-iii-ftx-is-the-most-mismanaged-company-ive-ever-seen/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Michael Saylor Gives His Thoughts on the Fall of FTX</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-gives-his-thoughts-on-the-fall-of-ftx/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-gives-his-thoughts-on-the-fall-of-ftx/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 15:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Saylor]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75570</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Former head of MicroStrategy Michael Saylor recently gave his thoughts and opinions on the digital currency scam surrounding FTX, the now fallen cryptocurrency exchange that was once labeled the ultimate golden player in the space. Michael Saylor on the FTX Collapse His conversation began with the statement that what was happening around FTX was “tragic.”<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-gives-his-thoughts-on-the-fall-of-ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-gives-his-thoughts-on-the-fall-of-ftx/">Michael Saylor Gives His Thoughts on the Fall of FTX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Former head of MicroStrategy Michael Saylor <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/michael-saylor-on-ftx-collapse-crypto-may-have-been-the-problem-but-bitcoin-is-still-the-solution/ar-AA149sCZ" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">recently gave his thoughts</a> and opinions on the digital currency scam surrounding FTX, the now fallen cryptocurrency exchange that was once labeled the ultimate golden player in the space.</p>
<h2>Michael Saylor on the FTX Collapse</h2>
<p>His conversation began with the statement that what was happening around FTX was “tragic.” It then transitioned into a discussion of FTT, the native token of the crypto exchange. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Since the supply was largely in friendly hands, they were able to manipulate the price of those tokens up through insider wash trading… Normally, the cynical bitcoiners think, ‘You know, these crypto casinos are just manipulating the price of the token up to dump it on retail,’ but [Bankman-Fried] came up with a particularly diabolical twist to the entire thing.</p></blockquote>
<p>FTX will likely go down as one of the biggest blunders in the history of crypto. First arising in the year 2019, FTX soon developed into one of the biggest and most prominent digital currency trading platforms, giving companies like Coinbase and even Binance runs for their money. The man behind the exchange, a young 30-something named Sam Bankman-Fried, was lauded as a genius by many high-ranking players in the industry, though sadly, that reputation is fading fast.</p>
<p>Mid-November saw trouble begin for the digital currency exchange after it was announced that FTX was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">experiencing a liquidity crunch</a>, and it needed fast cash to stay in business. From there, it turned to Binance for help, and it appeared that the larger company was going to buy out the smaller one, though this <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">merger never occurred</a>.</p>
<p>Within days, Binance issued a statement saying that it would not be purchasing the firm given that the problems FTX was facing were larger than what Binance felt it could handle. From there, Sam Bankman-Fried resigned from his post as the head executive of the firm and the company was forced into bankruptcy proceedings.</p>
<p>Saylor briefly described what user funds were invested in or spent on:</p>
<blockquote><p>They proceeded to spend the money on politicians and lobbying and stadium rights and advertisements and celebrity endorsements and condos in the Bahamas, and then they traded a bunch and made a bunch of bad trades, and then they lost the money.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Bitcoin Is Still a Valid Solution</h2>
<p>Despite all the issues that Saylor has experienced with bitcoin over the last year or so, he still feels that it could be a valid solution to what’s happening. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>It means you don&#8217;t have to trust the FTXs of the world, so yeah. I am a big believer because I believe that although crypto in this case may have been the problem, bitcoin is still the solution, and [Bankman-Fried] may have made a million bitcoin maximalists with this crash.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-gives-his-thoughts-on-the-fall-of-ftx/">Michael Saylor Gives His Thoughts on the Fall of FTX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-gives-his-thoughts-on-the-fall-of-ftx/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>El Salvador Vows to Buy At Least One BTC Each Day</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-vows-to-buy-at-least-one-btc-each-day/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-vows-to-buy-at-least-one-btc-each-day/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[El Salvador]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nayib Bukele]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75568</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nayib Bukele – the president of El Salvador – has issued a tweet saying he is going to be purchasing at least one bitcoin every day during the present market slump. Right now, BTC is trading in the $16K range, and the nation is looking to take advantage of the collapsing price. El Salvador Clearly<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-vows-to-buy-at-least-one-btc-each-day/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-vows-to-buy-at-least-one-btc-each-day/">El Salvador Vows to Buy At Least One BTC Each Day</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nayib Bukele – the president of El Salvador – has <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/el-salvador-plans-to-buy-more-bitcoin-every-day-despite-losing-millions-already/ar-AA14dEb9" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">issued a tweet saying he</a> is going to be purchasing at least one bitcoin every day during the present market slump. Right now, BTC is trading in the $16K range, and the nation is looking to take advantage of the collapsing price.</p>
<h2>El Salvador Clearly Still Loves BTC</h2>
<p>The maneuver is stirring mixed reactions from analysts, some of whom claim it will ensure El Salvador’s digital dominance when the market repairs itself. They believe that when things eventually come back to form, El Salvador will have so many digital reserves to its name that it will never fall into a dark financial hole again.</p>
<p>However, there are others that think El Salvador is making a big mistake. They say that the nation has lost a lot of money already, as during the present dip, the country continued to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nayib-bukele-just-bought-even-more-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">buy assets on a regular</a> basis. This hasn’t helped the nation in many ways given that the price of BTC has continued to slip deeper and deeper into oblivion. They are convinced that by the time BTC is done with its present bear market, El Salvador will have bought so much BTC and wasted so much cash that it will never rebound.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s difficult to say which outlook is correct. In any case, El Salvador has clearly shown itself to be one of the most BTC-devoted nations on the face of the Earth. The country was the first to declare bitcoin legal tender, doing so in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-fully-legal-in-el-salvador-beginning-september-7/" data-wpel-link="internal">September of last year</a>. The nation declared that all people could use BTC to purchase goods and services alongside the U.S. dollar, which up to that point, El Salvador had long been dependent on.</p>
<p>Businesses were also required to accept BTC payments and could not discriminate against those who were using it to make their everyday purchases. The nation experienced heavy resistance from organizations like the World Bank, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-world-bank-will-not-help-el-salvador-with-its-btc-plans/" data-wpel-link="internal">which stated it would</a> not be helping El Salvador with the implementation of its bitcoin agenda given that the currency was too volatile and speculative, and thus could not be taken seriously by financial regulators.</p>
<h2>A Lot of Resistance</h2>
<p>El Salvador didn’t let this little setback bring it down too much. Instead, the country went forth without help and created a new wallet system it called Chivo, which is slang for “cool” amongst the people. The wallet system would allow citizens to store their bitcoin units, and each one was gifted with an early <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/each-el-salvador-resident-could-receive-30-in-free-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">amount of $30 to help</a> them get used to how crypto worked.</p>
<p>Many were not <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-residents-protest-forced-btc-usage/" data-wpel-link="internal">happy about allegedly</a> being “forced” to play by BTC’s rules. There were riots and protests in the streets of San Salvador, the country’s capital city, amongst those who were happy simply using USD.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-vows-to-buy-at-least-one-btc-each-day/">El Salvador Vows to Buy At Least One BTC Each Day</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-vows-to-buy-at-least-one-btc-each-day/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Struggle Continues, Key Resistance Intact</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-struggle-continues-key-resistance-intact/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-struggle-continues-key-resistance-intact/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 06:28:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar Lumens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76175</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stellar lumen price is showing bearish signs below the $0.076 resistance zone against the US Dollar. XLM price is now trading below $0.078 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0780 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could start a<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-struggle-continues-key-resistance-intact/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-struggle-continues-key-resistance-intact/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Struggle Continues, Key Resistance Intact</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Stellar lumen price is showing bearish signs below the $0.076 resistance zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>XLM price is now trading below $0.078 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0780 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a major decline if there is a clear move below the $0.0725 support.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Stellar lumen price is trading below $0.0760 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-at-risk-of-another-crash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. XLM price must stay above the $0.0725 support to avoid more losses.</em></p>
<h2>Stellar Lumen Price Analysis (XLM to USD)</h2>
<p>After a major rejection above the $0.0900 zone, stellar lumen price started a fresh decline against the US Dollar. The XLM/USD pair traded below the $0.0850 support to move into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>There was a move below the $0.0800 and $0.0780 levels. The price even settled below the $0.078 level and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-signals-downturn-upsides-could-be-limited/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. A low was formed near $0.0725 and the price is now consolidating losses. The bears seem to be active below the $0.0760 level.</p>
<p>The price is now trading below $0.078 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $0.0770 level.</p>
<p>The 23.6% Fib retracement level of the key decline from the $0.0910 swing high to $0.0725 low is also near the $0.0769 level. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0780 on the 4-hours chart. A clear upside break above the trend line might send the price towards $0.0800.</p>
<p>Besides, the next major resistance is near the $0.0818 zone. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the key decline from the $0.0910 swing high to $0.0725 low.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $0.0818 level might send the price towards the $0.0850 level. Any more gains could lead the price towards the $0.0880 level or even $0.0910.</p>
<p>An initial support on the downside is near the $0.0738 level. The main support is near the $0.0725 zone. Any more losses could lead the price towards the $0.0700 level in the near term, below which the price might even retest $0.0680.</p>
<div id="attachment_76176" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76176" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-76176" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-3.png" alt="Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76176" class="wp-caption-text">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XLMUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that XLM price is now trading below $0.078 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could start a major decline if there is a clear move below the $0.0725 support.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XLM/USD is losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for XLM/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.0735 and $0.0725.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.0770, $0.0800 and $0.0820.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-struggle-continues-key-resistance-intact/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Struggle Continues, Key Resistance Intact</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-struggle-continues-key-resistance-intact/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
