<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 03:39:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/cropped-fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Risk of More Losses Below $90</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-90/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 03:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79355</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin is showing bearish signs and trading below $100 against the US Dollar. LTC price is now trading below $95 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $93.80 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-90/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Risk of More Losses Below $90</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Litecoin is showing bearish signs and trading below $100 against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>LTC price is now trading below $95 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $93.80 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could start a decent increase if it clears the $95 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Litecoin price is struggling below $95 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-regain-strength-above-this-hurdle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. LTC price could continue to decline if it stays below the $95 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, there was a short-lived recovery in Bitcoin, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-resume-increase-above-1950/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-aim-fresh-rally-to-0-85/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple</a>, and Litecoin against the US Dollar. Earlier, LTC settled below the $100 resistance zone to move into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>The price broke the $95 support zone and started a fresh decline. It even traded below the $92 support. A low is formed near $89.28 and the price is now consolidating losses. It is now trading below $95 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $93.80 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair. Immediate resistance is near the $92.80 level. It is close to the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $104.48 swing high to the $89.28 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $94 level or the trend line. A clear move above the $94 level could pump the price toward the $95 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $104.48 swing high to the $89.28 low. The next major resistance could be $100.</p>
<p>On the downside, immediate support is near the $91.50 level. The next key support is near the $90 level. If there is a downside break below the $90 support, the price could accelerate lower toward the $85 level in the near term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79356" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79356" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-2.png"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-79356" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-2.png" alt="Litecoin (LTC) Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-2.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-2-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-2-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-2-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-2-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-2-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-2-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79356" class="wp-caption-text">Litecoin (LTC) Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, Litecoin price is clearly trading below $95 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $95 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LTC/USD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $92.00 and $90.00.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $94.00 and $95.00.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-90/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Risk of More Losses Below $90</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mike McGlone: Bitcoin Still Isn&#8217;t in a Great Place</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-mcglone-bitcoin-still-isnt-in-a-great-place/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 17:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mike McGlone]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78652</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bloomberg crypto strategist Mike McGlone doesn’t believe that the worst days of bitcoin are behind it, and he says the world’s number one digital currency by market cap is likely to run into trouble again like it did in 2022. Mike McGlone on the Future of BTC That year was arguably the worst on record [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-mcglone-bitcoin-still-isnt-in-a-great-place/">Mike McGlone: Bitcoin Still Isn&#8217;t in a Great Place</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bloomberg</em> crypto strategist Mike McGlone doesn’t <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/06/32703561/heres-why-one-analyst-says-the-worst-for-bitcoin-may-not-be-over">believe that the worst days</a> of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitcoin/">bitcoin</a> are behind it, and he says the world’s number one digital currency by market cap is likely to run into trouble again like it did in 2022.</p>
<h2>Mike McGlone on the Future of BTC</h2>
<p>That year was arguably the worst on record for bitcoin, with the asset losing as much as 70 percent of its value. The currency rose to a new all-time high in November of 2021 ($68,000), though a year later, it was in the mid-$16K range.</p>
<p>In a recent report called “Still, Don’t Fight the Fed,” McGlone said bitcoin is likely to experience further dips in the coming months due to fears surrounding a recession in the U.S. His document explains:</p>
<blockquote><p>June may show more of the first half of the year bias for rising risk assets and bitcoin in a worst-is-over scenario, or it could roll over into a US recession. Our bias is the latter, notably as markets appear to have priced in an optimistic outcome from the long and variable lags of aggressive central-bank rate hikes, which are still rising.</p></blockquote>
<p>McGlone says the recent price bumps the world’s leading digital asset has experienced shouldn’t fool traders into thinking the gloom and doom is over. He is warning everyone that further headwinds are likely to arise, and that traders need to be prepared in the coming weeks. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The potential for the rising Nasdaq 100 Stock Index to lift all boats may be ephemeral. The graphic of 100-week moving averages shows downtrends for the stock index and bitcoin. It’s a question of the worst being over or respecting the trend, notably as prices have bounced. Our downward perspective is guided by the lessons of liquidity pumps that reverse and are still dumping, as indicated by federal funds futures in one year (FF13). As a result, it may take a decline in equities for rates to fall.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Will Things Go Down Further?</h2>
<p>In May, McGlone claimed that the stock market was likely to fall in ways nobody was anticipating. He also said there are several altcoins out there that are going to be experiencing major corrections soon. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>My base case is going to 3,000. bitcoin is going to go down, [and] I don’t know how far. It might make a new low. Cryptos will go down hard. We’re going to purge some of these 24,000 cryptos. Get rid of some. They’re just silly… Bitcoin’s high of about $30,000 in 2023 vs. the 100-week mean around $33,000 may show the pre-eminent, 24/7, globally traded risk indicator feeling gravity from the comfort zone around $7,000 before the unprecedented 2020-21 liquidity boost. That the widely expected US recession has not yet started may pressure risk assets accordingly.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-mcglone-bitcoin-still-isnt-in-a-great-place/">Mike McGlone: Bitcoin Still Isn&#8217;t in a Great Place</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Congressman French Hill is Trying to Help Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-congressman-french-hill-is-trying-to-help-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 15:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[French Hill]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Glenn Thompson]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78649</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>French Hill – a republican representative of Arkansas – is passionate about crypto, and he’s taking a leading role in ensuring the U.S. invokes appropriate crypto regulation in the coming future. French Hill and Digital Currency Hill is currently leading a discussion amongst House republicans on the uncertainty of crypto in the U.S. He also [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-congressman-french-hill-is-trying-to-help-crypto/">How Congressman French Hill is Trying to Help Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>French Hill – a republican representative of Arkansas – is passionate about crypto, and he’s taking a leading role in ensuring the U.S. invokes appropriate crypto <a href="https://www.arkansasonline.com/news/2023/jun/04/arkansas-lawmaker-playing-role-in-setting/">regulation in the coming</a> future.</p>
<h2>French Hill and Digital Currency</h2>
<p>Hill is currently leading a discussion amongst House republicans on the uncertainty of crypto in the U.S. He also serves as the House Financial Services Committee’s vice chair and leads its Subcommittee on Digital Assets, Financial Technology and Inclusion. In a recent interview, Hill said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Legislation from Congress is needed to protect U.S. consumers and investors, as well as to preserve America&#8217;s role as a global leader in finance, technology, and innovation. The discussion draft from the House Financial Services and Agriculture Committees represents a common approach to digital asset regulation that would bring existing consumer and investor protections to digital asset-related activities and intermediaries under the principle of &#8216;same risk, same regulation.&#8217;</p></blockquote>
<p>The lack of regulation in the U.S. regarding crypto is leading to danger for several reasons, a big one being that the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) feels it can now police the arena with a persecuting hand (and a bad attitude, to boot). The agency has done everything it can to bring crypto companies down, and it’s not just going after small names. Big firms, like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/">Kraken</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/">Coinbase</a>, are now falling victim to Gary Gensler’s antics.</p>
<p>Carol Rose Goforth – professor of law at the University of Arkansas – has spent a long time studying crypto and the technology behind it. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Sometimes, figuring out how to comply with these preexisting rules is really hard. If all we do is force crypto assets into regulatory structures that were drafted with different kinds of interests in mind, it often does not work well… You have the companies that are spending thousands of man hours trying to figure out how to comply, [who are] competing with companies that may be much less interested in devoting their resources to that. It&#8217;s like the good companies are actually at a tremendous disadvantage because it&#8217;s so much cheaper just to not comply and hope you don&#8217;t get caught.</p></blockquote>
<p>Like many lawmakers in this country, Hill believes the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/">collapse of FTX</a> last November is the main reason to bring about crypto regulation in the country. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>What we are doing in the House is writing the first bills that will give a regulatory framework for digital assets that protects investors, protects consumers, but very importantly, creates an innovation space here in the U.S. for the expansion of the use of digital assets.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Writing the Right Rules</h2>
<p>House Agriculture Committee Chairman Glenn Thompson of Pennsylvania said:</p>
<blockquote><p>For months, our committees have worked collaboratively to establish a viable regulatory framework for digital assets necessary to protect consumers and promote American innovation.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-congressman-french-hill-is-trying-to-help-crypto/">How Congressman French Hill is Trying to Help Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Musk Dogecoin Lawsuit Amended to Include Insider Trading Charges</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/musk-dogecoin-lawsuit-amended-to-include-insider-trading-charges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 13:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lawsuit]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78647</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Last year, a lawsuit was filed against South African entrepreneur and billionaire Elon Musk. The lawsuit alleged that Musk took measures to manipulate the price of Dogecoin, which he’s been fond of and spoken highly of for some time. The plaintiffs in the lawsuit claim to have lost millions of dollars during the 2022 bear [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/musk-dogecoin-lawsuit-amended-to-include-insider-trading-charges/">Musk Dogecoin Lawsuit Amended to Include Insider Trading Charges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Last year, a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-investor-sues-elon-musk-over-doge-promotions/">lawsuit was filed</a> against South African entrepreneur and billionaire Elon Musk. The lawsuit alleged that Musk took measures to manipulate the price of Dogecoin, which he’s been fond of and spoken highly of for some time. The plaintiffs in the lawsuit claim to have lost millions of dollars during the 2022 bear market, and they’re blaming the SpaceX founder for his alleged role in their losses.</p>
<h2>Elon Musk Lawsuit Changed Up</h2>
<p>Now, it appears the lawsuit <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/elon-musk-hit-with-insider-trading-claims-over-his-dogecoin-crypto-hype/ar-AA1c3o60">against Musk has taken</a> a new turn to include charges of insider trading. The complaint was filed in early June of this year in the Southern District of New York, and it says Musk took distinct measures to violate financial laws in the U.S. The document reads:</p>
<blockquote><p>This is a securities fraud class action arising from a deliberate course of carnival barking market manipulation and insider trading by the world’s richest man Elon Musk, who hijacked an emergent pop-culture phenomenon to cross-promote himself and his companies, and to pad his obscene fortune, preying on the earnest hopes of vulnerable Americans including war veterans, blue collar workers, and the elderly.</p></blockquote>
<p>One of the bits of evidence the complaint is using against Musk is that <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-briefly-changes-the-twitter-logo-to-the-dogecoin-dog/">he briefly changed</a> the Twitter logo from its recognizable blue bird to the Dogecoin dog. Once this occurred, the price of Doge rose as much as 30 percent over a short period, though the price was quick to come down once the logo was switched back.</p>
<p>However, during the time of the switch and the subsequent price hike, Musk is accused of unloading as much as $100 million in Doge, thus making a hefty profit. He is also alleged to have garnered benefits from paid influencers, and that his company Tesla traded in the currency and garnered insider knowledge surrounding Doge activity. The complaint continues with:</p>
<blockquote><p>Musk traded Dogecoin profitably through one or more wallets and domestic exchanges using foreknowledge then unknown and undisclosed to Dogecoin investors generally or publicly of his own intended moves to manipulate the market. Tesla, Inc, also traded profitably through one or more wallets and domestic exchanges during the class period, having been tipped off to this information by defendant Musk.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Did He Cause People to Lose Doge?</h2>
<p>Musk has repeatedly <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-asks-judge-to-toss-out-dogecoin-centered-lawsuit/">worked to have the currency</a> lawsuit dismissed in court, claiming he never forced anybody to invest in crypto. The fact remains that he’s a Doge fan who’s tried to talk about it whenever he could, but he hasn’t held a weapon to anyone’s head and forced them to invest at the expense of their lives. The amended lawsuit finishes with:</p>
<blockquote><p>In subsequent tweets, Musk, who had tens of millions of Twitter followers at the time, dubbed himself &#8216;the Dogefather,&#8217; and has tweeted about Dogecoin over one hundred times since then.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/musk-dogecoin-lawsuit-amended-to-include-insider-trading-charges/">Musk Dogecoin Lawsuit Amended to Include Insider Trading Charges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Indicators Suggest Fresh Rally To $0.085</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-indicators-suggest-fresh-rally-to-0-085/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 05:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79334</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tron price started a fresh increase from the $0.0750 level against the US Dollar. TRX price is now trading above $0.0765 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.0792 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could continue to move [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-indicators-suggest-fresh-rally-to-0-085/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Indicators Suggest Fresh Rally To $0.085</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Tron price started a fresh increase from the $0.0750 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>TRX price is now trading above $0.0765 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.0792 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move up if it breaks the $0.0808 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>TRON price started a fresh increase above $0.0750 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-regain-strength-above-this-hurdle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. TRX’s price could rise further if it clears the $0.0808 resistance.</em></p>
<h2>Tron Price Analysis</h2>
<p>After a downside correction, Tron price found support near the $0.0788 zone against the US Dollar. TRX’s price formed a base and recently started a fresh increase from the $0.07883 low.</p>
<p>There was a break above the $0.0792 and $0.0800 levels. The price climbed above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward wave from the $0.0826 swing high to the $0.0788 low. TRX is now trading above $0.0780 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bulls-aim-another-rally-to-0-085/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.0792 on the 4-hours chart. On the upside, TRX is facing resistance near the $0.0808 level. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward wave from the $0.0826 swing high to the $0.0788 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $0.082 level. A close above $0.082 could send the price toward the $0.0850 resistance zone.</p>
<p>Any more gains might send TRX price toward $0.0880, above which the price could even rise toward $0.090. On the downside, initial support is near the $0.0792 level and the trend line. The next major support is now forming near $0.0788.</p>
<p>If there is a downside break below the $0.0788 support, the price might revisit the $0.0750 support. Any more losses might call for a move toward the $0.072 zone in the near term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79335" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79335" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/TRON-TRX-2.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-79335" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/TRON-TRX-2.png" alt="Tron (TRX) Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/TRON-TRX-2.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/TRON-TRX-2-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/TRON-TRX-2-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/TRON-TRX-2-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/TRON-TRX-2-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/TRON-TRX-2-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/TRON-TRX-2-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79335" class="wp-caption-text">Tron (TRX) Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/TRXUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a> indicates that TRX’s price is now trading above $0.0765 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move up if it breaks the $0.0808 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for TRX/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for TRX/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.0792 and $0.0788.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.0808, $0.0820, and $0.085.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-indicators-suggest-fresh-rally-to-0-085/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Indicators Suggest Fresh Rally To $0.085</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Could Regain Strength Above This Hurdle</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-regain-strength-above-this-hurdle/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 03:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79331</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price is attempting a fresh increase from the $29,525 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $30,400 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,180 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-regain-strength-above-this-hurdle/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Could Regain Strength Above This Hurdle</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin price is attempting a fresh increase from the $29,525 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $30,400 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,180 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could start a fresh increase if it clears the $30,400 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin price is rising from $29,525 against the US Dollar. BTC might eye another increase if the bulls remain active above the $29,500 zone.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price started a fresh decline it failed to clear the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-restart-rally-above-this-resistance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$31,800 resistance</a>. BTC declined below the $30,500 and $30,000 support levels to enter a short-term bearish zone.</p>
<p>The recent swing low was formed near $29,525 before the price moved higher. The bulls were able to push the price above the $29,650 and $29,850 levels. The price is now approaching the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward wave from the $31,862 swing high to the $29,525 low.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is now trading below $30,400 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-more-upsides-above-31250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. Immediate resistance on the upside is near the $30,150 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,180 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>The next major resistance might be near the $30,400 zone or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward wave from the $31,862 swing high to the $29,525 low.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $30,400 and $30,600 resistance levels might send the price toward $31,200. Any more gains might push the price toward the $32,000 zone. If there is no upside break, the price might start a fresh decline below the $30,000 level.</p>
<p>The first major support is near $29,525. The next key support is near the $29,250 level, below which the price might accelerate lower. In the stated case, the price could decline toward the $28,400 level.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79332" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79332" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-3.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-79332 size-full" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-3.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-3.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-3-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-3-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-3-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-3-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-3-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-3-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79332" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XBTUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, Bitcoin’s price is trading below $30,400 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start a fresh increase if it clears the $30,400 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD is now losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $29,850 and $29,525.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $30,180, $30,400, and $30,600.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-regain-strength-above-this-hurdle/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Could Regain Strength Above This Hurdle</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mike Novogratz: Crypto&#8217;s &#8220;Lackadaisical&#8221; Right Now</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-novogratz-cryptos-lackadaisical-right-now/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mike Novogratz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rug pulls]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78638</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, we put out an article talking about how May was the worst month for bitcoin this year. The currency ended May about two percent less than where it had been in previous months, and this was the first time this year in which BTC didn’t finish a 30-day period on a high. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-novogratz-cryptos-lackadaisical-right-now/">Mike Novogratz: Crypto&#8217;s &#8220;Lackadaisical&#8221; Right Now</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, we put out an article talking about <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/may-has-been-the-worst-month-for-bitcoin-this-year/">how May was the worst</a> month for bitcoin this year. The currency ended May about two percent less than where it had been in previous months, and this was the first time this year in which BTC didn’t finish a 30-day period on a high. Mike Novogratz – a bitcoin bull and hedge fund manager – had a lot to say on <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/technology/galaxy-digital-ceo-mike-novogratz-says-the-dog-days-of-summer-came-early-for-crypto-as-bitcoin-posts-worst-month-since-november/ar-AA1c03cO">the matter as he made</a> clear in a recent interview.</p>
<h2>Mike Novogratz on the Current State of BTC</h2>
<p>In his discussion, Novogratz described the situation as the “dog days of summer” coming early for the world’s leading digital currency by market cap. He stated with an air of gloom and doom:</p>
<blockquote><p>The dog days of summer started early in crypto. That doesn&#8217;t make me thrilled. That&#8217;s just the reality.</p></blockquote>
<p>The good news, however, is that bitcoin is still about 60 percent higher than where it ended last year. 2022 was arguably the worst period on record for bitcoin. Things started off well in November of 2021 when BTC reached a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit.</p>
<p>Sadly, while everyone thought bitcoin was an unstoppable asset and likely to reach the pinnacles of finance, the following 12 months proved harsh and gruesome in ways that nobody thought possible, and bitcoin wound up losing more than 70 percent of its overall value and dipping into mid-$16K territory.</p>
<p>The trouble didn’t quite stop there. The rest of the crypto industry lost more than $2 trillion in value, as several additional coins chose to follow in BTC’s ugly and twisted footsteps. It was a rough and depressing sight.</p>
<p>And while bitcoin is up right now when compared with the horrendous conditions it faced last year, it’s certainly not where it could be, and it’s not in a position that’s even comparable with where it was two Novembers ago. Novogratz took note of this and said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Crypto&#8217;s lackadaisical right now. There&#8217;s a constant bid from retail. We&#8217;re seeing it through all the platforms. There&#8217;s not a lot of institutional excitement right now.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Lot of Deception</h2>
<p>As other news has related, it wasn’t just the price of bitcoin that makes May a relatively weak month. The period also saw lots <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/crypto-investors-lost-54m-to-rugpulls-scams-in-may-blockchain-security-firm-defi-1032367227">of new fraud and rug pulls</a> taking place, and it appears many investors lost more than $50 million in combined assets.</p>
<p>Rug pulls often occur when new crypto companies enter the fray and seek to raise funds for their operations. The more money they get, the higher their tokens spike. All who invested early see their portfolios rise and things look solid, but it isn’t long before all the executives shut down and run off with the money they’ve earned, leaving their supporters in bad states and their portfolios in shambles.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-novogratz-cryptos-lackadaisical-right-now/">Mike Novogratz: Crypto&#8217;s &#8220;Lackadaisical&#8221; Right Now</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Arthur Hayes: BTC Will Explode at the End of 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/arthur-hayes-btc-will-explode-at-the-end-of-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 15:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arthur Hayes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Halving]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78635</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Arthur Hayes – the former chief executive of crypto exchange BitMEX – has commented that quarters three and four of this year are going to be among the best for bitcoin. Arthur Hayes on the Fate of BTC For the most part, 2023 has been a powerful year for the crypto arena. The world’s biggest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/arthur-hayes-btc-will-explode-at-the-end-of-2023/">Arthur Hayes: BTC Will Explode at the End of 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Arthur Hayes – the former chief executive of crypto exchange BitMEX – <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/06/02/crypto-now-braced-for-a-powder-keg-that-could-play-havoc-with-the-price-of-bitcoin-and-ethereum/?sh=1d04c95a38d9">has commented that</a> quarters three and four of this year are going to be among the best for bitcoin.</p>
<h2>Arthur Hayes on the Fate of BTC</h2>
<p>For the most part, 2023 has been a powerful year for the crypto arena. The world’s biggest and most popular digital currency by market cap has surged more than 60 percent from where it was at the end of last year, though this doesn’t mean that there isn’t still room for improvement.</p>
<p>The fact remains that in November of 2021, bitcoin reached a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit, though it spent the next 12 or 13 months traveling through the doldrums and hitting new lows, and while things may be up in 2023, they are not where they were two Novembers ago. In a recent interview, Hayes mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>You’re basically putting this powder keg together of a situation that’s going to be exploding in [the third and fourth quarter] of this year, and I think, ultimately, it will be good for bitcoin. It will be quite volatile on the upside and the downside.</p></blockquote>
<p>While all the drama with the debt deal in the United States has come to an end, things are still up in the air thanks to the Treasury being engaged in a few questionable <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-treasury-is-set-to-make-things-rough-for-bitcoin/">practices at the time of writing</a>… practices that could make things very rough for bitcoin and its altcoin cousins.</p>
<p>Hayes commented that more than $1 trillion in Treasury bills could wind up coming our way over the next few months. He believes that this could liquidate millions or even billions of dollars in the crypto marketplace, and that in that sense, things won’t go well for the world’s primary assets.</p>
<p>However, he was also quick to suggest that the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-next-btc-halving-is-a-year-away-whats-going-to-happen/">next bitcoin halving</a> – currently set to take place in April of next year – will bear similar results with all the crypto arena’s past halvings, and that BTC and Ethereum are likely to rise to new levels following this event. In fact, he believes bitcoin could wind up reaching a price of $70K. Hayes stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I don’t think we’ll get up to $70,000 this year. I think next year is when we cross that barrier, then we get the blow off top [2025], [2026] and then it’s Armageddon. It doesn’t have to be too straightforward; we just have this situation. We have this tinderbox of too much money, no trust, and people trying to eke out a living for themselves.</p></blockquote>
<h2>So Much Financial Drama!</h2>
<p>At press time, the price of bitcoin is hovering between the $27,000 and $28,000 marks.</p>
<p>There has been quite a bit of hoopla surrounding America’s financial situation, and this hasn’t helped BTC decide on a lasting position.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/arthur-hayes-btc-will-explode-at-the-end-of-2023/">Arthur Hayes: BTC Will Explode at the End of 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brad Garlinghouse: Ripple&#8217;s Battle with the SEC Will End Soon</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brad-garlinghouse-the-ripple-sec-battle-will-end-in-a-few-weeks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 13:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brad Garlinghouse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78633</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Brad Garlinghouse – the CEO of leading crypto platform Ripple – is confident his company is going to put the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in its place. Where Will Ripple Stand? Not long ago, the SEC announced its plans to sue Ripple and charge it with securities violations. This isn’t the first time something [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brad-garlinghouse-the-ripple-sec-battle-will-end-in-a-few-weeks/">Brad Garlinghouse: Ripple&#8217;s Battle with the SEC Will End Soon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Brad Garlinghouse – the CEO of leading crypto platform Ripple – is <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/05/31/confident-ripple-ceo-helps-the-xrp-price-outperform-bitcoin/?sh=4a15961e77a7">confident his company is going</a> to put the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in its place.</p>
<h2>Where Will Ripple Stand?</h2>
<p>Not long ago, the SEC announced its plans to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-secs-case-against-ripple-could-result-in-a-massive-win-for-the-crypto-company/">sue Ripple and charge</a> it with securities violations. This isn’t the first time something like this has happened. There have been many crypto companies over the years that have fallen victim to the financial agency, but many of them chose to settle and move on. However, Ripple selected a different route.</p>
<p>Rather than curl up into a ball and allow itself to get whipped, the company chose to go to court with the SEC and fight back, and now it looks like the company could win the case against it. In a recent interview, Garlinghouse said he’s confident the case will come to an end in the coming weeks rather than the coming months, suggesting things could be over soon. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I feel very confident that we’ll see a decision from the courts this year. In fact, I think I would guess that it will be in weeks, not months… The judge ruled against the SEC&#8217;s effort to redact certain information, a very kind of infamous speech that the then director of corporate finance Bill Hinman gave talking about why ETH, in his view, is not a security.</p></blockquote>
<p>The SEC has developed a reputation for being a bully in the crypto arena. Not long ago, the agency went after big-name firms such as Kraken and Coinbase, two of the largest digital currency exchanges in existence. The <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/">latter was forced</a> to end all its staking services and activities while also parting with a $30 million fee.</p>
<p>At Coinbase, executives were <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/">served a Wells notice</a>, implying that while they hadn’t been charged with anything yet, the day was not far off when charges would be thrown in their direction. Garlinghouse further commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>The court just ruled last week that the notes in the emails associated with that are going to be made public and should be public&#8230; So, I think that’s a huge win for transparency, but what it really calls out is there really hasn’t been clarity despite calls and demands from leaders across the crypto industry.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Never Back Down</h2>
<p>Thus far, the company’s legal battle with the SEC has lasted a whopping two years, though it could be argued that Ripple is setting a precedent for <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-ripple-is-showing-crypto-firms-how-to-handle-a-bully-in-its-sec-fight/">how to defeat a bully</a>. Garlinghouse concluded with:</p>
<blockquote><p>Ripple decided to lean in and fight this fight, both for Ripple and the whole industry. We’ve spent a lot of money defending it, and I think what we’ve called out is the government in the United States, and the SEC particularly, is putting politics ahead of smart policy.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brad-garlinghouse-the-ripple-sec-battle-will-end-in-a-few-weeks/">Brad Garlinghouse: Ripple&#8217;s Battle with the SEC Will End Soon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
