<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 02:45:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Could Drop Below $1,700</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-drop-below-1700/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-drop-below-1700/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 02:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78340</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum price is gaining bearish momentum below the $1,880 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH price is now trading below $1,850 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $1,820 on the 4-hour chart (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could continue<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-drop-below-1700/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-drop-below-1700/">Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Could Drop Below $1,700</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ethereum price is gaining bearish momentum below the $1,880 resistance against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>ETH price is now trading below $1,850 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $1,820 on the 4-hour chart (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it stays below $1,850 and $1,880.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ethereum price is declining below $1,850 against the US Dollar. ETH/USD remains at a risk of more downsides below the $1,700 support zone.</em></p>
<h2>Ethereum Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, Ethereum started a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-at-risk-of-downside-break/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">fresh decline</a> below $1,920 against the US Dollar. ETH price moved into a bearish zone below the $1,880 level.</p>
<p>A low was formed near $1,737 before the price started an upside correction. There was a move above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $2,020 swing high to the $1,737 low. Besides, there was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $1,820 on the 4-hour chart.</p>
<p>It is now trading below $1,850 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-faces-increase-in-bearish-pressure/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. On the upside, the price is now facing resistance near the $1,850 level.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $1,880 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $2,020 swing high to the $1,737 low, above which it could rise toward the $1,920 resistance zone. A clear move above the $1,880 and $1,920 resistance levels might call for a fresh move to $2,000. Any more gains could even send the price toward the $2,120 resistance zone or even $2,200 in the near term.</p>
<p>On the downside, initial support is near the $1,780 level. The next major support is now near the $1,740 level. A break below the $1,740 support could push the price to $1,700. If the bulls fail to protect the $1,700 support, the price might decline toward $1,650.</p>
<div id="attachment_78341" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Ethereum-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78341" class="size-full wp-image-78341" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Ethereum-2.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78341" class="wp-caption-text">Ethereum Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Ethereum price is trading below $1,880 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, Ether’s price could continue to move down if it stays below $1,850 and $1,880.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for ETH/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $1,740, followed by the $1,700 zone.</p>
<p>Key Resistance$ Levels – $1,840 and $1,880.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-drop-below-1700/">Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Could Drop Below $1,700</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-drop-below-1700/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leaked Memo Suggests Democrats Are Trying to Kill the Crypto Industry</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leaked-memo-suggests-democrats-are-trying-to-kill-the-crypto-industry/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leaked-memo-suggests-democrats-are-trying-to-kill-the-crypto-industry/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 17:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[democrats]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[memo]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78309</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new memo shows that democrats really hate cryptocurrency. So much so, that they’re looking to instill new rules that would make it very hard to attain and keep. Democrats Wage War Against Crypto A leaked memo sent to democrat House financial services committee members reveals that left leaners are seeking to ensure all digital<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leaked-memo-suggests-democrats-are-trying-to-kill-the-crypto-industry/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leaked-memo-suggests-democrats-are-trying-to-kill-the-crypto-industry/">Leaked Memo Suggests Democrats Are Trying to Kill the Crypto Industry</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new memo shows that democrats really hate cryptocurrency. So much so, that they’re looking to instill new <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/05/12/leak-reveals-secret-democrat-plan-for-a-game-changing-us-crypto-crackdown-that-could-hit-the-price-of-bitcoin-and-ethereum/?sh=4dad93cf1568" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">rules that would make</a> it very hard to attain and keep.</p>
<h2>Democrats Wage War Against Crypto</h2>
<p>A leaked memo sent to democrat House financial services committee members reveals that left leaners are seeking to ensure all digital currencies, in the future, are classified as securities. This doesn’t necessarily mean they cannot be obtained, but they will be subjected to all kinds of new taxation rules that will make these assets very hard to keep. In addition, this will also likely cause hell for all kinds of crypto companies.</p>
<p>If it suddenly becomes law that every digital currency ever created must be categorized as a security, there are plenty of issuing companies that will probably be subjected to all kinds of fees and penalties from organizations like the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). If this happens, you can expect to see a whirlwind of negativity hitting the industry. Prices will easily collapse, and there’s a good chance several crypto companies will not survive. The memo reads as follows:</p>
<blockquote><p>The problem isn’t ambiguity. It’s mass non-compliance with existing laws. We can&#8217;t invent new accommodating regulatory structures simply because crypto companies refuse to follow clear rules of the road.</p></blockquote>
<p>The memo also clearly outlines an attempt from the republican party to protect both consumers and investors. Right wingers are working hard to ensure all crypto regulations are clear and justifiable, something the democrats are purportedly trying to get in the way of. The document continues:</p>
<blockquote><p>They [republicans] are working to provide clarity to the markets by carving out space for the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) in crypto&#8230; Republicans are proving that they really aren&#8217;t serious about protecting investors and consumers.</p></blockquote>
<p>Joe Biden and his legion of democrats have been waging an all-out war on the crypto arena since they first took the White House over two years ago. Men like Gary Gensler – head of the SEC – have worked hard to ensure all crypto companies are persecuted and attacked as though they are enemies of the state, and big names like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/" data-wpel-link="internal">Kraken</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">Coinbase</a> have fallen victim to their antics.</p>
<h2>Trying to Tie Things Up</h2>
<p>The memo further states:</p>
<blockquote><p>Both the SEC and CFTC are aligned on the fact that the SEC is the regulator to determine if crypto assets are securities, and the SEC has made clear that nearly all crypto assets are securities. End of story… Republicans want to reverse course and tie the hands of the SEC. The SEC must continue to lead the regulation of the U.S. crypto market, and Congress must do its part to provide them with the resources they need.</p></blockquote>
<p>The document, naturally, is earning criticism from digital currency analysts everywhere.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leaked-memo-suggests-democrats-are-trying-to-kill-the-crypto-industry/">Leaked Memo Suggests Democrats Are Trying to Kill the Crypto Industry</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leaked-memo-suggests-democrats-are-trying-to-kill-the-crypto-industry/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chiron Investigations Can Find Your Lost Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/chiron-investigations-can-find-your-lost-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/chiron-investigations-can-find-your-lost-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chiron Investigations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Theft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Losses]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77802</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chiron Investigations is earning a reputation as the go-to platform for those who have lost crypto either due to theft or because they’ve misplaced their private keys. Chiron Investigations Seeks to Aid Victims of Crypto Loss The crypto space has grown like crazy over the past several years. Many people have a newfound love of<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/chiron-investigations-can-find-your-lost-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/chiron-investigations-can-find-your-lost-crypto/">Chiron Investigations Can Find Your Lost Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chiron Investigations is earning a reputation as the go-to platform for those <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/stocks/chiron-investigations-leading-the-way-in-cryptocurrency-and-asset-recovery-services-1032220364" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">who have lost crypto</a> either due to theft or because they’ve misplaced their private keys.</p>
<h2>Chiron Investigations Seeks to Aid Victims of Crypto Loss</h2>
<p>The crypto space has grown like crazy over the past several years. Many people have a newfound love of investing and are eager to add to their bitcoin stashes as best they can. However, there are many things that can get in the way, crypto crime being a big one.</p>
<p>Over the years, we’ve heard countless stories of trading platforms and exchanges being attacked by cyberthieves that make off with digital reserves. Sometimes, these thieves target specific accounts or addresses and run off with the funds that are owned by the individual owners. When situations like these occur, they can be rather devastating, a big reason being that stolen crypto is hard to recover… Very hard to recover.</p>
<p>It is often said that when <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/north-kingston-police-warn-of-growing-crypto-scams/" data-wpel-link="internal">crypto is gone</a>, it’s gone for good. This is because much of the technology allowing for the transactions is privacy-based, and thus the identities of those involved are usually unseen. Also, when crypto is moved by criminals, it often goes through a wash process that prevents it from being traceable. It’s moved in and out of addresses that ultimately make it so that it’s part of other batches. This can make the process of finding the crypto in question even harder.</p>
<p>In other situations, the people who own the units wind up losing their private keys or their passwords. Thus, the crypto hasn’t been moved. It’s still stored on the hard wallet or wherever the owner stored the units, but they can no longer gain access to them. The assets are staring them in the face and cannot be withdrawn or added to for a lack of login data.</p>
<p>Chiron aims to assist with these situations. The head of the company explained in a recent statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>Our commitment to providing capable and efficient recovery services while recognizing the importance of these digital assets to their clients. Chiron Investigations not only assists those affected by forex trading crimes, but also offers aid to victims of bitcoin theft. Through swift response, the company ensures that clients receive timely, effective results.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Helping Those Who Have Lost Assets</h2>
<p>Chiron presently employs an entire team of investigators that seek to help clients regardless of where they’re situated. Usually, by the time clients go to Chiron, it’s because they’ve exhausted all other attempts and they need professionals to step in and take over where they’ve failed.</p>
<p>The company is not a one-size-fits-all delivery firm that seeks to present the same option to each person. Rather, it provides customized experiences to those who require assistance depending on their unique needs and circumstances.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/chiron-investigations-can-find-your-lost-crypto/">Chiron Investigations Can Find Your Lost Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/chiron-investigations-can-find-your-lost-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Buncombe County Considers Crypto Mining Moratorium</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/buncombe-county-considers-crypto-mining-moratorium/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/buncombe-county-considers-crypto-mining-moratorium/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 13:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buncombe County]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New York]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77800</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Buncombe County in North Carolina doesn’t like the fact that so many crypto miners have set up operations within its borders. Officials of the region are now considering taking a page out of New York’s books and establishing a temporary moratorium on crypto mining facilities. Buncombe County Doesn&#8217;t Think Much of Crypto Mining New York<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/buncombe-county-considers-crypto-mining-moratorium/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/buncombe-county-considers-crypto-mining-moratorium/">Buncombe County Considers Crypto Mining Moratorium</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Buncombe County in North Carolina doesn’t like the fact that so many crypto miners have set up operations within its borders. Officials of the region are now <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/buncombe-commissioners-consider-temporary-block-on-cryptocurrency-mining-whens-the-vote/ar-AA19uJ4a" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">considering taking a page</a> out of New York’s books and establishing a temporary moratorium on crypto mining facilities.</p>
<h2>Buncombe County Doesn&#8217;t Think Much of Crypto Mining</h2>
<p>New York was one of the first regions in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-signs-crypto-moratorium-into-law/" data-wpel-link="internal">recent years to create</a> a crypto moratorium. Right now, the time through which crypto companies cannot set up shop in New York is two years, though there are several regulators out there that <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/some-want-the-crypto-moratorium-in-new-york-to-last-longer/" data-wpel-link="internal">want the period extended</a>.</p>
<p>Buncombe County is now considering something similar, though there are a few people in high-ranking city positions that are pushing for more than a moratorium and instead feel that a full-on crypto mining ban is the right choice to make.</p>
<p>Commissioner Terry Wells explained in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Based on my time on the commission, we have not had anything like this come in front of us before. We felt like we wanted to make sure that with the (comprehensive plan) coming, we [can] assess everything going forward. With the moratorium, it definitely gives us a chance to make sure that we’re getting ahead of it and looking at the big picture.</p></blockquote>
<p>There is a difference in this moratorium, however, in that while New York was worried that crypto mining would potentially present hazardous conditions to the atmosphere and environment, Buncombe County is worried that the mines are creating too much noise for residents. The situation is rough because the machines tend to be quite noisy along with the fans that are consistently running as a means of keeping the said rigs cool so that they don’t overheat and break down.</p>
<p>This is causing a wide array of problems for those living within the region’s borders, and city officials don’t want to put anyone nearby through more trouble.</p>
<p>In addition, while there are some that have argued these mining facilities have potentially given rise to new jobs and employment opportunities for residents, the local government doesn’t feel that these numbers have been high enough to warrant the growing mining presence.</p>
<p>The government of Buncombe County hasn’t said for sure if such a moratorium will be put in place. Right now, those on the city board are considering their options and taking time to figure out what the right plan of attack is.</p>
<h2>So Many Haters!</h2>
<p>The last few years have seen many environmental activists mentally shut out crypto, claiming it does too much damage to Mother Earth. There have also been several reports published saying that crypto mining is a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-bitcoin-mining-may-require-more-energy-than-180-countries/" data-wpel-link="internal">dangerous venture that uses</a> more energy than most developing nations.</p>
<p>Even crypto advocates like Elon Musk have expressed <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-has-taken-a-nasty-stumble-many-are-blaming-elon-musk/" data-wpel-link="internal">concerns with energy</a> use in crypto mining projects.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/buncombe-county-considers-crypto-mining-moratorium/">Buncombe County Considers Crypto Mining Moratorium</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/buncombe-county-considers-crypto-mining-moratorium/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Turns Sell on Rallies Near $0.092</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-turns-sell-on-rallies-near-0-092/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-turns-sell-on-rallies-near-0-092/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 05:08:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar Lumens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78332</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stellar lumen price is struggling below the $0.0950 resistance zone against the US Dollar. XLM price is now trading below $0.0920 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0920 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could start a recovery<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-turns-sell-on-rallies-near-0-092/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-turns-sell-on-rallies-near-0-092/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Turns Sell on Rallies Near $0.092</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Stellar lumen price is struggling below the $0.0950 resistance zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>XLM price is now trading below $0.0920 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0920 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a recovery wave if it clears the $0.092 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Stellar lumen price is trading below $0.0920 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-29k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. XLM price could extend losses if it stays below $0.0920.</em></p>
<h2>Stellar Lumen Price Analysis (XLM to USD)</h2>
<p>After a close below $0.0950, Stellar Lumen price moved into a bearish zone against the US Dollar. The XLM/USD pair gained bearish momentum below the $0.090 support zone.</p>
<p>Finally, there was a spike below the $0.085 level. A low is formed near $0.0828 and the price is now correcting losses. It is still trading below $0.0920 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-drops-below-0-10-as-bears-take-control/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0920 on the 4-hour chart.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $0.090 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.0948 swing high to the $0.0827 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $0.0920 zone and the trend line. It is close to the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.0948 swing high to the $0.0827 low. A clear upside break above the $0.092 zone might send the price toward $0.0950. Any more gains could lead the price toward the $0.1000 level or even $0.1050.</p>
<p>Initial support on the downside is near the $0.0875 level. The main support is near the $0.085 zone. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.0820 level in the near term, below which the price might even retest $0.0800.</p>
<div id="attachment_78333" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78333" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78333" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-2.png" alt="Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78333" class="wp-caption-text">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XLMUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that XLM price is now trading below $0.0920 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start a major decline if there is a clear move below the $0.0875 support.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XLM/USD is gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for XLM/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.0875 and $0.082.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.090, $0.0920, and $0.0950.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-turns-sell-on-rallies-near-0-092/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Turns Sell on Rallies Near $0.092</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-turns-sell-on-rallies-near-0-092/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Price Analysis: XRP Could Face Hurdles Near 0.45</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-could-face-hurdles-near-0-45/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-could-face-hurdles-near-0-45/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 03:38:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78329</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple price started a fresh decline from the $0.470 zone against the US dollar. The price is now trading below $0.450 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.440 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Bittrex). The pair<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-could-face-hurdles-near-0-45/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-could-face-hurdles-near-0-45/">Ripple Price Analysis: XRP Could Face Hurdles Near 0.45</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ripple price started a fresh decline from the $0.470 zone against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $0.450 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.440 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Bittrex).</li>
<li>The pair could extend losses if it stays below the $0.450 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ripple price is struggling below $0.450 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-29k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. XRP price could decline further if it settles below the $0.450 support in the near term.</em></p>
<h2>Ripple Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, Ripple price started a fresh decline from well above $0.4600 against the US Dollar. The XRP/USD pair gained bearish momentum below the $0.4500 level.</p>
<p>The bears were able to push the price below the $0.4320 support. It even traded below the 55 simple moving average (4 hours) and spiked below the $0.420 support. A low is formed near $0.4100 and the price is now attempting a recovery wave.</p>
<p>XRP is now trading below $0.440 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-turns-red-and-at-risk-below-0-45/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. Besides, there is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.440 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near $0.440. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.4704 swing high to the $0.4100 low. The next major resistance is near the $0.4480 level and the trend line.</p>
<p>It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.4704 swing high to the $0.4100 low. A clear move above the trend line resistance and $0.4480 might start a fresh increase. In the stated case, the price could even surpass the $0.450 resistance. Any more gains might send the price toward the $0.480 resistance.</p>
<p>Initial support on the downside is near $0.416. The next major support is near the $0.410 level. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.400 level, below which the price might even test $0.388.</p>
<div id="attachment_78330" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Ripple-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78330" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78330" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Ripple-2.png" alt="Ripple Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78330" class="wp-caption-text">Ripple Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">chart</a>, Ripple’s price is now trading below the $0.450 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could extend losses if it stays below the $0.450 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XRP/USD is now losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for XRP/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.4160, $0.4100, and $0.4000.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.4400 and $0.4500.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-could-face-hurdles-near-0-45/">Ripple Price Analysis: XRP Could Face Hurdles Near 0.45</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-could-face-hurdles-near-0-45/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Satoshi Nakamoto, the BTC Creator, Recently Had a Birthday</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/satoshi-nakamoto-the-btc-creator-recently-had-a-birthday/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/satoshi-nakamoto-the-btc-creator-recently-had-a-birthday/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 17:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nick Szabo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Satoshi Nakamoto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77798</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto fans everywhere have been celebrating the birthday of Satoshi Nakamoto, the famed creator of bitcoin. Satoshi Nakamoto Just Turned 48 Occurring in mid-April, the birthday celebrations were for a man (or woman – it’s not entirely clear at the time of writing) who has earned a solid reputation in the growing digital currency space.<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/satoshi-nakamoto-the-btc-creator-recently-had-a-birthday/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/satoshi-nakamoto-the-btc-creator-recently-had-a-birthday/">Satoshi Nakamoto, the BTC Creator, Recently Had a Birthday</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto fans everywhere have been <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/who-is-satoshi-nakamoto-bitcoin-inventor-crypto-steve-jobs-apple-2023-4" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">celebrating the birthday</a> of Satoshi Nakamoto, the famed creator of bitcoin.</p>
<h2>Satoshi Nakamoto Just Turned 48</h2>
<p>Occurring in mid-April, the birthday celebrations were for a man (or woman – it’s not entirely clear at the time of writing) who has earned a solid reputation in the growing digital currency space. Widely considered the father of crypto, bitcoin – the invention of Nakamoto – was first introduced in whitepaper form on Halloween of 2008, a time when the banks of America were crashing and burning, and the Great Recession had practically taken full form.</p>
<p>It’s alleged that Satoshi Nakamoto is 48 years old. Everyone who has traded bitcoin or crypto loves and respects him. There’s just one big problem… Nobody knows who he is. Despite coming up with one of the biggest financial technologies in the world just 15 years ago, the identity of Nakamoto remains as big a mystery as ever.</p>
<p>Not long ago, the whitepaper that introduced BTC to the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-btc-whitepaper-is-apparently-available-on-every-mac-computer/" data-wpel-link="internal">world was found to be included</a> on virtually every Mac computer. The discovery was made by Andy Baio, a technologist and former executive with Kickstarter. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>While trying to fix my printer today, I discovered that a PDF copy of Satoshi Nakamoto&#8217;s bitcoin’s whitepaper apparently shipped with every copy of macOS since Mojave in 2018.</p></blockquote>
<p>The document reads as follows:</p>
<blockquote><p>A purely peer-to-peer version of electronic cash would allow online payments to be sent directly from one party to another without going through a financial institution.</p></blockquote>
<p>At the time of writing, bitcoin has grown into the largest digital currency in the world. It presently boasts a market cap of more than $540 billion. The currency has delivered intrigue to investors everywhere, part of the reason being that Nakamoto has been extremely elusive, and many are wondering who he is.</p>
<p>Several analysts believe that the chances of Nakamoto being a single person are slim to none. They say it’s highly unlikely something as big, revolutionary, and as technically complicated as BTC could have been established by a single figure. Dan Kaminsky – a leading internet security researcher – explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>Either there&#8217;s a team of people who worked on this or this guy is a genius.</p></blockquote>
<p>About ten years ago, there was much speculation about computer scientist Nick Szabo, who drew quite a bit of attention to himself through a paper about something called “bit gold” that he published in 1998. Szabo has since denied claims that he’s Nakamoto or that he has anything to do with the creation of BTC.</p>
<h2>Not Everyone&#8217;s Convinced Szabo Ain&#8217;t Their Guy</h2>
<p>This hasn’t stopped journalist Nathaniel Popper – who writes for <em>The New York Times</em> – from singling him out. Popper said of Szabo:</p>
<blockquote><p>The most convincing evidence pointed to a reclusive American man of Hungarian descent named Nick Szabo.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/satoshi-nakamoto-the-btc-creator-recently-had-a-birthday/">Satoshi Nakamoto, the BTC Creator, Recently Had a Birthday</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/satoshi-nakamoto-the-btc-creator-recently-had-a-birthday/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Upcoming Jobs Report Could Help Bitcoin Get Bigger</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-upcoming-jobs-report-could-help-bitcoin-get-bigger/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-upcoming-jobs-report-could-help-bitcoin-get-bigger/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 15:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jobs report]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Silk Road]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77796</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Assets like bitcoin and Ethereum continue to show signs of recovering from the bearish market conditions traders and investors witnessed last year. The Many Bitcoin Developments Set to Occur Not long ago, the U.S. government seized more than $215 million in bitcoin taken from the Silk Road dark web market, started by Ross Ulbricht. While<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-upcoming-jobs-report-could-help-bitcoin-get-bigger/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-upcoming-jobs-report-could-help-bitcoin-get-bigger/">The Upcoming Jobs Report Could Help Bitcoin Get Bigger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Assets like bitcoin and Ethereum continue to show signs of recovering from the bearish market conditions traders and investors witnessed last year.</p>
<h2>The Many Bitcoin Developments Set to Occur</h2>
<p>Not long ago, the U.S. government seized more than $215 <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/04/05/bitcoin-and-crypto-are-suddenly-braced-for-a-1-billion-us-earthquake-after-ethereum-bnb-xrp-cardano-dogecoin-polygon-and-solana-price-surge/?sh=79ef0b801ea3" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">million in bitcoin taken from</a> the Silk Road dark web market, started by Ross Ulbricht. While the man in <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-sdny/pr/ross-ulbricht-aka-dread-pirate-roberts-sentenced-manhattan-federal-court-life-prison" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">charge may be in prison</a>, the enterprise continues to operate as though nothing has changed.</p>
<p>Now, it looks like there’s going to be another $1 billion in BTC sold over the next year, and many analysts think this could have huge effects on the price of bitcoin and where the asset goes within the next 12 months. Alex Kuptsikevich – an FX Pro senior market analyst – explained in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>The former cryptocurrency is stuck in local highs, above which it has been unable to consolidate since March 19. This prolonged consolidation sets the stage for the next big move. The resolution of this consolidation is likely to be linked to the market&#8217;s reaction to Friday&#8217;s non-farm payrolls. Technically, a pullback to the $27,000 level to correct the rally of March 10 is more likely at the moment.</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition to the bitcoin sale occurring later in the year, the annual jobs report will be emerging soon. Usually, when this document becomes available for all to read, the country gets an idea of the state of the economy as when jobs are added, one can assume that things are moving up, whereas if job counts are lower than expected, it likely means the economy isn’t in a great state.</p>
<p>Nobody doubts that the economic conditions of America are not in fantastic shape right now. Inflation is <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/inflation-is-having-harsher-effects-on-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">still running rampant</a>, and the Fed has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/federal-reserve-hikes-rates-again-what-will-happen-to-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">made it clear</a> that while 2023 was initially going to be a time in which interest rates either fell or remained in place, they’re likely to continue going up unless inflation decides to calm down outright, which the Fed doesn’t think will occur just yet.</p>
<h2><em> </em>What Will the Jobs Report Do?</h2>
<p>Putting all this aside, if the job report is high enough, this could bear positive outcomes for bitcoin and other digital currencies and cause them to spike higher. Many analysts are crossing their fingers and hoping for the best. Yuya Hasegawa – a crypto market analyst at Bit Bank in Tokyo – said:</p>
<blockquote><p> With concerns for the U.S. banking system subsiding, the market&#8217;s concern is yet again on the Fed’s rate hike decision in May. Bitcoin could retest $29,000, but it needs to close above that level to call it a &#8216;breakout,&#8217; otherwise, it could be another &#8216;fake-out.’</p></blockquote>
<p>While things can always be much better, bitcoin has already risen by 70 percent from where it was at the end of 2022, arguably the worst year on record for the asset.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-upcoming-jobs-report-could-help-bitcoin-get-bigger/">The Upcoming Jobs Report Could Help Bitcoin Get Bigger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-upcoming-jobs-report-could-help-bitcoin-get-bigger/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Analysts: The Banking Crisis Proved the Points of Many BTC Fans</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-the-banking-crisis-proved-the-points-of-many-btc-fans/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-the-banking-crisis-proved-the-points-of-many-btc-fans/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 13:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[banking crisis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77794</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The banking crisis in America and Europe – which appears to be drawing back somewhat at the time of writing – truly vindicated several BTC and Ethereum believers according to many analysts in the industry. BTC Fanatics Have Been Proven Right The banking crisis saw at least three separate institutions in the U.S. – including<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-the-banking-crisis-proved-the-points-of-many-btc-fans/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-the-banking-crisis-proved-the-points-of-many-btc-fans/">Analysts: The Banking Crisis Proved the Points of Many BTC Fans</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The banking crisis in America and Europe – which appears to be drawing back somewhat at the time of writing – truly vindicated several BTC and Ethereum believers <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/04/07/shock-jpmorgan-price-prediction-reveals-catastrophic-doomsday-scenario-may-be-just-the-start-for-bitcoin-and-ethereum/?sh=196eb7b5313e" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">according to many analysts</a> in the industry.</p>
<h2>BTC Fanatics Have Been Proven Right</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/did-crypto-cause-banks-to-fall-experts-weigh-in/" data-wpel-link="internal">banking crisis saw</a> at least three separate institutions in the U.S. – including Silvergate, Silicon Valley Bank, and Signature Bank – shutter their doors for good. Meanwhile, the problems spread to several monetary houses in Europe <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-more-banks-fell-bitcoin-rose-beyond-28k/" data-wpel-link="internal">like Credit Suisse</a>, which was saved at the last minute when it was purchased for about $3 billion by UBS.</p>
<p>People are now looking at BTC and other crypto holders as individuals with good heads on their shoulders. JPMorgan strategist Nikolaos Panigirtzoglou commented in a recent note:</p>
<blockquote><p>For crypto supporters, the U.S. banking crisis exposed the weaknesses of the traditional financial system given banks&#8217; maturity mismatch is susceptible to bank runs. Crypto supporters have been arguing for a long time that the crypto ecosystem is superior, not least because deposits are held in entities such as stable coins which as a digital form of money market funds are 100% backed with high-quality liquid assets and are thus less susceptible to runs.</p></blockquote>
<p>His sentiment is very different from the thoughts of JPMorgan head Jamie Dimon, who in the past has referred to BTC and other forms of crypto as <a href="https://nypost.com/2022/09/22/jamie-dimon-calls-bitcoin-a-decentralized-ponzi-scheme/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Ponzi schemes</a>. In 2024, the next bitcoin halving is all set to occur. This is an event that happens every four years or so in which bitcoin is set to see the rewards delivered to miners cut in half, hence the word halving.</p>
<p>These kinds of circumstances cause the currency to become rarer, thus increasing its value, so traders can likely expect the asset to shoot up in price in about 12 months or so. Panigirtzoglou said:</p>
<blockquote><p>This would mechanically double bitcoin&#8217;s production cost to around $40,000, creating a positive psychological effect. This is because bitcoin’s production cost has historically acted as an effective lower bound.</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition, he also said that the recent introduction of BTC-based <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-ordinals-nfts-are-bringing-the-space-back-from-disaster/" data-wpel-link="internal">non-fungible tokens</a> (NFTs) could help the asset do better as well. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>This is because metadata such as text [and] images can be inscribed on the bitcoin network itself, without relying on smart contracts as seen with other blockchains, where NFTs are created through smart contracts.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Really Helping NFTs</h2>
<p>John Stefanidis – chief executive of Balthazar, an NFT-based gaming platform – says Ordinals and other BTC-centered NFTs have done great things for the industry thus far. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>The recent movement in bitcoin is also positive for the NFT market, as all boats rise with the tide. It’s likely to have a positive impact on the overall sentiment of the market. Bitcoin is currently trading above US$28,000, which we haven’t seen since June last year.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-the-banking-crisis-proved-the-points-of-many-btc-fans/">Analysts: The Banking Crisis Proved the Points of Many BTC Fans</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-the-banking-crisis-proved-the-points-of-many-btc-fans/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
