<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 05:48:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Didi Taihuttu Is Moving All His BTC to Defi Platforms</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/didi-taihuttu-is-moving-all-his-btc-to-decentralized-exchanges/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/didi-taihuttu-is-moving-all-his-btc-to-decentralized-exchanges/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Decentralized exchanges]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Didi Taihuttu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75850</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Didi Taihuttu and his family – often dubbed the “bitcoin family” due to their devotion to the world’s number one digital currency – are still confident in bitcoin and aren’t letting last year’s price flops and the collapse of FTX get to them. However, things have changed enough that they’re moving their bitcoin over and<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/didi-taihuttu-is-moving-all-his-btc-to-decentralized-exchanges/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/didi-taihuttu-is-moving-all-his-btc-to-decentralized-exchanges/">Didi Taihuttu Is Moving All His BTC to Defi Platforms</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Didi Taihuttu and his family – often dubbed the “bitcoin family” due to their devotion to the world’s number one digital currency – are still confident <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/bitcoin-family-is-moving-more-than-1-million-into-decentralized-exchanges-after-sam-bankman-fried-s-ftx-disaster/ar-AA14KAAc" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">in bitcoin and aren’t</a> letting last year’s price flops and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">collapse of FTX</a> get to them. However, things have changed enough that they’re moving their bitcoin over and finding new ways of securing it.</p>
<h2>Didi Taihuttu Feels Strongly About Defi</h2>
<p>Many years ago, Taihuttu, his wife, and their three daughters <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/didi-taihuttu-and-his-family-are-putting-everything-they-have-into-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">sold everything they owned</a> and exchanged it for bitcoin. Since then, they have begun a life on the road. Last year, they settled in a coastal city in Portugal, where Taihuttu <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/didi-taihuttu-opens-bitcoin-bar-in-portugal/" data-wpel-link="internal">opened what’s known</a> as the “bitcoin bar.”</p>
<p>Up to this point, he’s stored all his crypto assets in exchanges, both centralized and decentralized. Since so many crypto companies are now in the process of filing for bankruptcy, he’s putting all his faith only in decentralized exchanges. He’s moving more than $1 million in crypto assets to said platforms, as they cannot prevent a person from accessing their funds should they decide to go dark.</p>
<p>He commented in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>For me, bitcoin is still about freedom, and decentralized currency should be able to be used by everyone in the world without needing to do KYC or any other regulatory stuff.</p></blockquote>
<p>He is concerned because many centralized exchanges do not give traders private keys. These individuals are fully reliant on the exchanges for buying, selling, and trading their digital assets. Thus, their ownership of the assets is always in question.</p>
<p>Taihuttu isn’t crazy about this. He wants to be able to access his money at any point during an emergency, and he’s now putting all his time, hope, and energy into the world of defi. No KYC protocols, no blockades, just traders and quick access to their money.</p>
<p>He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>You never send your bitcoin to an exchange. Your bitcoin stays in your own wallet, meaning you have complete custody of your coins. You connect to a DEX, and by making that connection, you trade out of your own wallet. If the DEX collapses, it doesn&#8217;t matter because the bitcoin [is] always in your own wallet.</p></blockquote>
<p>Taihuttu and his family are presently living on .3 bitcoin a month. This amounts to roughly $5,000 USD at the time of writing. They are also buying back all the BTC they sold last year. At that time, the BTC price was around $55,000 per unit. They now have a chance to get all their funds back at only a fraction of the cost.</p>
<h2>Never Trusting of FTX?</h2>
<p>He further stated he’s always had a bad feeling about FTX, and he’s not surprised by its sudden fall. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Too many influencers were paid too much money to promote that one.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/didi-taihuttu-is-moving-all-his-btc-to-decentralized-exchanges/">Didi Taihuttu Is Moving All His BTC to Defi Platforms</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/didi-taihuttu-is-moving-all-his-btc-to-decentralized-exchanges/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Allegedly Gave Just as Much Money to Republicans as It Did to Democrats</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-allegedly-gave-just-as-much-money-to-republicans-as-it-did-to-democrats/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-allegedly-gave-just-as-much-money-to-republicans-as-it-did-to-democrats/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[democrats]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[republicans]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75848</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The drama surrounding FTX is getting a lot worse. Initially, it was believed that Sam Bankman-Fried – the man behind the now failed digital currency exchange – gave a lot of money to democrat politicians, and he did. However, it’s now being alleged by him that equal money was given to republicans, only those donations<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-allegedly-gave-just-as-much-money-to-republicans-as-it-did-to-democrats/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-allegedly-gave-just-as-much-money-to-republicans-as-it-did-to-democrats/">FTX Allegedly Gave Just as Much Money to Republicans as It Did to Democrats</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The drama surrounding FTX is getting a lot worse. Initially, it <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-billionaire-sam-bankman-fried-spends-big-in-the-name-of-politics/" data-wpel-link="internal">was believed that</a> Sam Bankman-Fried – the man behind the now failed digital currency exchange – gave a lot of money to democrat politicians, and he did. However, it’s now being alleged by him that equal money was given to republicans, only those donations <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2022/nov/30/ftx-billionaire-sam-bankman-fried-dark-money-republicans" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">were more secret</a>.</p>
<h2>FTX Also Allegedly Delivered Funds to Republicans</h2>
<p>FTX collapsed in mid-November of last year following what SBF referred to as a “<a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">liquidity crunch</a>” on social media. He initially sought the aid of Binance and approached the company about being bought out. However, Binance said that the problems the firm was dealing with were too big to handle, and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">thus the buyout did not</a> occur.</p>
<p>From there, FTX had no choice <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">but to file bankruptcy</a>, and its founder resigned from his post. The company has caused ripples throughout the space, and many other enterprises – <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block-fi-is-the-latest-crypto-company-to-go-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">such as Block Fi</a> – have been forced into similar bankruptcy proceedings as a result.</p>
<p>Last year, it was reported that Bankman-Fried was the second largest donor to the democrat party. When this knowledge was made public, many right-leaning politicians – such as Texas Senator Ted Cruz – jumped on it and took to social media to attack members of the left. On Twitter, Cruz wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>Will Joe Biden and democrats who cashed Bankman-Fried’s checks give that money to the people SBF screwed?</p></blockquote>
<p>Now, however, Bankman-Fried has come out to say he gave just as much to republicans as he did to democrats, though many of those donations occurred on a more secretive level. He said in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>I donated to both parties. I donated about the same amount to both parties. All my republican donations were dark. The reason was not for regulatory reasons. It’s because reporters freak the f*ck out if you donate to republicans. They’re all super liberal, and I didn’t want to have that fight.</p></blockquote>
<p>It is alleged that much of the money for republicans was delivered via FTX US per data from Open Secrets. However, much of the money that SBF himself donated to politicians largely went to leftwingers. Open Secrets shows that Bankman-Fried donated nearly $1 million to specific democrat candidates in the last election cycle, while nearly $40 million went to democrat-centered groups.</p>
<p>By contrast, it appears he gave less than $250K of his money to republican candidates, so clearly bias exists.</p>
<h2>Scary for Many Reasons</h2>
<p>The situation raises several questions. It’s not exactly easy to take SBF’s word on anything, anymore. The allegation that his company utilized customer funds to purchase luxury condos in the Bahamas suggests he doesn’t have a penchant for the truth.</p>
<p>At the same time, if what he’s saying is real, this is far more frightening given many members of the U.S. government either couldn’t recognize corruption when they saw it, or worse – they’re part of the corruption themselves.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-allegedly-gave-just-as-much-money-to-republicans-as-it-did-to-democrats/">FTX Allegedly Gave Just as Much Money to Republicans as It Did to Democrats</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-allegedly-gave-just-as-much-money-to-republicans-as-it-did-to-democrats/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Exchange Kraken Lays Off Over 1,000 Employees</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kraken-to-lay-off-30-of-its-staff/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kraken-to-lay-off-30-of-its-staff/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 13:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kraken]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Layoffs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75844</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Kraken – a popular digital currency trading platform based in northern California – is laying off more than 1,000 employees as it attempts to deal with the ongoing crypto winter. Kraken Says Bye to a Lot of Workers The crypto exchange says that the maneuver has nothing to do with the fall of FTX, which<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kraken-to-lay-off-30-of-its-staff/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kraken-to-lay-off-30-of-its-staff/">Crypto Exchange Kraken Lays Off Over 1,000 Employees</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Kraken – a popular digital currency trading platform based in northern California – is laying off more than 1,000 employees as it attempts <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/kraken-layoffs-crypto-exchange-ftx-winter-jesse-powell-2022-11" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">to deal with the ongoing</a> crypto winter.</p>
<h2>Kraken Says Bye to a Lot of Workers</h2>
<p>The crypto exchange says that the maneuver has nothing to do with <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">the fall of FTX</a>, which has caused a serious firestorm in the digital currency world. The exchange collapsed in mid-November and has sent ripples throughout the space, making several other firms – <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block-fi-is-the-latest-crypto-company-to-go-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">such as Block Fi</a> – follow in its footsteps and file for bankruptcy.</p>
<p>However, Kraken wants it made clear that this has nothing to do with FTX. Rather, the crypto winter has not subsided, and the company is working to ensure it can stay afloat while the market repairs itself. A spokesperson for the firm said:</p>
<blockquote><p>No. Kraken was already reviewing its business and workforce needs when news of [the] FTX bankruptcy was made public. Kraken had no material exposure to FTX.</p></blockquote>
<p>Kraken is specifically pointing the finger at “macro-economic and geopolitical factors” as the reasons behind its new string of layoffs. With more than 1,000 people saying goodbye to their jobs with the exchange, the company is losing approximately 30 percent of its workforce. In a statement, Kraken said:</p>
<blockquote><p>This resulted in significantly lower trading volumes and fewer client sign-ups. We responded by slowing hiring efforts and avoiding large marketing commitments. Unfortunately, negative influences on the financial markets have continued, and we have exhausted preferable options for bringing costs in line with demand.</p></blockquote>
<p>Employees who are being let go are not leaving empty handed. They are being offered 16 weeks of pay, which amounts to roughly four months of additional money as they spend time looking for employment elsewhere. They will also receive an extension of benefits including health coverage and counseling services. They are also being given access to stock options, while employees on visas are being given immigration support.</p>
<p>Jesse Powell – the CEO of Kraken – continued the initial statement with:</p>
<blockquote><p>I&#8217;m confident the steps we are taking today will ensure we can continue to deliver on our mission which the world needs now more than ever before. I remain extremely bullish on crypto and Kraken.</p></blockquote>
<h2>The Drama of the Space Continues</h2>
<p>To say it’s been a rough time for crypto and bitcoin would be a huge understatement. Many crypto companies – such as <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gemini-exchange-says-major-layoffs-are-coming/" data-wpel-link="internal">Gemini</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-says-its-laying-off-several-employees/" data-wpel-link="internal">Coinbase</a> – have been forced to let go of staff members as they endure the growing effects of the weakening industry. Many mainstream tokens like bitcoin have also fallen drastically from the all-time highs they achieved in November of 2021.</p>
<p>During that time, BTC was trading at a whopping $68,000 per unit. Now, the asset has fallen into the low $17K range. Here’s to hoping that 2023 will be kinder to this young financial arena.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kraken-to-lay-off-30-of-its-staff/">Crypto Exchange Kraken Lays Off Over 1,000 Employees</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kraken-to-lay-off-30-of-its-staff/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Regains Traction, What Could Be The Target?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-regains-traction-what-could-be-the-target/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-regains-traction-what-could-be-the-target/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 07:28:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar Lumens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76405</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stellar lumen price started a fresh increase above the $0.070 resistance zone against the US Dollar. XLM price is now trading above $0.0750 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $0.0738 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-regains-traction-what-could-be-the-target/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-regains-traction-what-could-be-the-target/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Regains Traction, What Could Be The Target?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Stellar lumen price started a fresh increase above the $0.070 resistance zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>XLM price is now trading above $0.0750 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $0.0738 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to rise if it stays above the $0.0780 and $0.0750 support levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Stellar lumen price is trading above $0.0750 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-steady-increase-to-18k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. XLM price must stay above the $0.0750 support to rise further.</em></p>
<h2>Stellar Lumen Price Analysis (XLM to USD)</h2>
<p>After forming a base above the $0.070 level, stellar lumen price started a fresh increase against the US Dollar. The XLM/USD pair broke the $0.0750 resistance zone to move into a positive zone.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $0.0738 on the 4-hours chart. The price even broke the $0.0780 resistance and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-keeps-moving-lower-bears-remain-active/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. The price is now trading comfortably above the $0.0785 level.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $0.0808 level. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.0919 swing high to $0.0704 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $0.0830 level. It coincides with the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.0919 swing high to $0.0704 low. A clear move above the $0.0830 level might send the price towards the $0.0880 level.</p>
<p>Any more gains could lead the price towards the $0.0920 level or even $0.1000 in the coming days. An initial support on the downside is near the $0.0780 level.</p>
<p>The next major support sits near the $0.0760 level. The main support is near the $0.0750 zone. Any more losses could lead the price towards the $0.070 level in the near term, below which the price might even retest $0.0640.</p>
<div id="attachment_76406" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76406" class="size-full wp-image-76406" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-1.png" alt="Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76406" class="wp-caption-text">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XLMUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that XLM price is now trading above $0.0750 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could continue to rise if it stays above the $0.078 and $0.075 support levels.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XLM/USD is gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for XLM/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.0780 and $0.0750.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.0808, $0.0860 and $0.0920.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-regains-traction-what-could-be-the-target/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Regains Traction, What Could Be The Target?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-regains-traction-what-could-be-the-target/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Price Analysis: Bulls Aim Higher Above $0.37</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-aim-higher-above-0-37/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-aim-higher-above-0-37/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 05:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76402</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple price is slowly moving higher above the $0.35 level against the US dollar. The price is now trading above $0.3400 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $0.3410 on the 4-hours chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Bittrex). The<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-aim-higher-above-0-37/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-aim-higher-above-0-37/">Ripple Price Analysis: Bulls Aim Higher Above $0.37</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ripple price is slowly moving higher above the $0.35 level against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $0.3400 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $0.3410 on the 4-hours chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Bittrex).</li>
<li>The pair could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $0.3560 resistance zone in the near term.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ripple price is rising steadily above $0.340 against the US Dollar, unlike <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-steady-increase-to-18k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. XRP price must clear $0.356 to continue higher in the coming sessions.</em></p>
<h2>Ripple Price Analysis</h2>
<p>After forming a base near the $0.3320 zone, ripple price started a fresh increase against the US Dollar. The XRP/USD pair was able to clear the $0.3380 resistance zone.</p>
<p>The price even broke the $0.3400 resistance and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There was also a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $0.3410 on the 4-hours chart of the XRP/USD pair. The pair is now trading above the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3727 swing high to $0.3013 low.</p>
<p>It is now trading above $0.3400 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-risk-of-a-drop-below-0-30/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near $0.3560.  It is near the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3727 swing high to $0.3013 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $0.3720 level. A clear move above the $0.3720 resistance zone might start a fresh increase. In the stated case, the price could even surpass the $0.3800 resistance. Any more gains might send the price towards the $0.4200 resistance.</p>
<p>An initial support on the downside is near the $0.3450 level. The next major support is near the $0.3400 level and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Any more losses could lead the price towards the $0.3320 level, below which the price might even test $0.3050.</p>
<div id="attachment_76403" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Ripple-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76403" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-76403" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Ripple-1.png" alt="Ripple Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76403" class="wp-caption-text">Ripple Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, ripple price is now trading above the $0.3400 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $0.3560 resistance zone in the near term.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XRP/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for XRP/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.3450, $0.3400 and $0.3320.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.3560 and $0.3720.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-aim-higher-above-0-37/">Ripple Price Analysis: Bulls Aim Higher Above $0.37</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-aim-higher-above-0-37/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Etalon (ETAL) Will Be Listed on LBank Exchange This April</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/etalon-etal-will-be-listed-on-lbank-exchange-this-april/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/etalon-etal-will-be-listed-on-lbank-exchange-this-april/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 04:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76393</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Jan 4, 2023 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list Etalon (ETAL) in April 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the ETAL/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading this April. Connecting the online and offline world with the crypto market, Etalon (ETAL) enables users to<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/etalon-etal-will-be-listed-on-lbank-exchange-this-april/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/etalon-etal-will-be-listed-on-lbank-exchange-this-april/">Etalon (ETAL) Will Be Listed on LBank Exchange This April</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Jan 4, 2023 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list Etalon (ETAL) in April 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the ETAL/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading this April.</p>
<p>Connecting the online and offline world with the crypto market, <a href="https://bscscan.com/token/0xfbf17daa8d22cd954928ff394f67923ac9c166cb" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Etalon</a> (ETAL) enables users to unlock and enjoy numerous discounts, services, and benefits worldwide with just one token. The ETAL token will be listed on LBank Exchange this April, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision. To support this innovative project, LBank joined Etalon as a strategic partner and a Provider, see details at <a href="https://etalon.cash/join" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://etalon.cash/join</a></p>
<p><strong>Introducing </strong><strong>Etalon</strong></p>
<p>The global e-commerce retail market, now worth $5.5 trillion, is expected to grow at a compound annual growth rate of 9-10%. In this growing market, competition for consumers is fiercer every day. The emergence of crypto assets has defined a financially free, conscious consumer community, free from the disadvantages of centralized control, whose purchasing power is well represented by the total capitalization of the crypto market.</p>
<p>Etalon is a project and utility token providing a simple way to connect not only the seasoned crypto experts, but people new to decentralized finance to manufacturers and service providers around the world, who are joining its ever-growing community. Users do not have to spend their Etalon to receive benefits, all that is required is ownership of at least one token (you do not have to spend it ever, just HODL it), which allows users to access discounts, products, and services available worldwide, granted by registered and verified Providers.</p>
<p>Developed by the team that created Clarabot Nano, one of the world&#8217;s most secure Opensource data sharing and communication software, Etalon strives to establish accessible and secure global information sharing systems, while connecting individuals with companies providing exclusive benefits for token holders. If you do support a decentralized future, this project is definitely for you. Did you know that a purchase of a single ETAL grants you lifelong access to Clarabot Nano, which is 5 EUR per month otherwise if you subscribe for it? Please note that Clarabot is the Finalist of Cyber Defense Magazine Black Unicorn 2022<span style="text-decoration: line-through;">.</span> Clarabot also won the prestigious Global Infosec Award in 2021 on encrypted data sharing and 2022 was named one of the top 10 Infosec innovators. In case you are looking for a future where your data belongs to you and not multinational companies, you should definitely take a look on Clarabot Nano and Etalon. The underlying value of the service granted by Clarabot only predicts the ultimate success of Etalon. Not to mention, several other well known Providers (<a href="https://etalon.cash/providers" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://etalon.cash/providers</a>) already joined the project, granting real life value for the Etalon community and token holders. Opposed to many ICOs, Etalon is not a promise as the system is already in place and workin</p>
<p>Be it either with a discounted purchase opportunity of a product, or access to a valuable service, Etalon connects the online and offline world with the crypto market. The flagship utility for a limited number of Etalon owners is a perpetual license for Nano, giving access to current and future Nano services, as long as Etalon is held. Clarabot is paving the way for other manufacturers, retailers and service providers (90 Providers so far joined the initiative, but this number is growing day by day) to offer significant discounts and become Providers. And eventually, an online marketplace named Etaverse for Etalon&#8217;s community of Beneficiary members, manufacturers, retailers, and service providers offering endlessly expanding benefits is formed.</p>
<p>The vision of Etalon is to build technologies, ecosystems, and communities that promote secure, easily accessible, global information sharing systems with privacy and freedom in mind. It will continue to promote and develop new technologies that provide modern answers to issues that the 21st century brought, in a way that is easy to use for people even with little or no IT experience.</p>
<p><strong>About ETAL Token</strong></p>
<p>ETAL is a BEP-20 “Smart Contract” cryptocurrency that runs on BSC. Unlike centralized banks, the token uses peer-to-peer technology to operate without central authority. Being a BEP20 standard, Etalon can be transferred and traded like any other token, making it possible to exchange for other crypto assets, or even fiat currency.</p>
<p>In addition, the Proof-of-Staked-Authority (PoSA) used by BSC allows for much higher transaction throughput and significantly reduced environmental impact and energy usage. This improvement also keeps the system secure, and dramatically reduces the fees associated with transactions.</p>
<p>As a utility cryptocurrency that provides valuable services and discounts, ETAL grants access to users even if they only have one token in their crypto wallet. Compared to other crypto tokens, ETAL is unique as its value is determined not just by supply and demand, but by the quality and number of benefits that it provides. Token holders gain access to meaningful services, top quality products, and discounts. And as the list of Providers grow, making more exclusive discounts and services available, Etalon’s added value to token holders increases.</p>
<p>A total of 5 million (i.e., 5,000,000) ETAL tokens are available. The ICO of ETAL just started and more than 300 000 tokens out of 5 million already found its owner. Don’t miss the opportunity to join now.</p>
<p>The ETAL token will be listed on LBank Exchange this April, investors who are interested in the Etalon investment can easily buy and sell ETAL token on LBank Exchange once it’s listed, or through the official website of Etalon.cash during the ICO. The listing of ETAL token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p>
<p><strong>Learn More about</strong><strong> ETAL Token:</strong></p>
<p>Official Website: <a href="https://etalon.cash" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://etalon.cash</a><br />
Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/EtalonToken" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://t.me/EtalonToken</a><br />
Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/EtalonCash" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/EtalonCash</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media: </strong></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Facebook</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong></p>
<p>LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
LBank Exchange<br />
<a href="mailto:marketing@lbank.info">marketing@lbank.info</a><br />
<a href="mailto:business@lbank.info">business@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/etalon-etal-will-be-listed-on-lbank-exchange-this-april/">Etalon (ETAL) Will Be Listed on LBank Exchange This April</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/etalon-etal-will-be-listed-on-lbank-exchange-this-april/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LBank Exchange Will List SHIKOKU INU (SHIK) on January 9, 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-shikoku-inu-shik-on-january-9-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-shikoku-inu-shik-on-january-9-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 17:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76399</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Jan 6, 2023 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list SHIKOKU INU (SHIK) on January 9, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the SHIK/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading at 13:00 UTC on January 9, 2023. As a decentralized memecoin experiment with far-reaching goals,<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-shikoku-inu-shik-on-january-9-2023/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-shikoku-inu-shik-on-january-9-2023/">LBank Exchange Will List SHIKOKU INU (SHIK) on January 9, 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Jan 6, 2023 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list SHIKOKU INU (SHIK) on January 9, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the SHIK/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading at 13:00 UTC on January 9, 2023.</p>
<p>As a decentralized memecoin experiment with far-reaching goals, <a href="https://etherscan.io/token/0x24da31e7bb182cb2cabfef1d88db19c2ae1f5572" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">SHIKOKU INU</a> (SHIK) is here to create a decentralized ecosystem of applications and tools, and educate investors about self-custody in an engaging way. The SHIK token will be listed on LBank Exchange at 13:00 UTC on January 9, 2023, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision.</p>
<p><strong>Introducing </strong><strong>SHIKOKU INU</strong></p>
<p>SHIKOKU INU is a decentralized experiment, launched on the 7th of November 2022, by the founder, Shikoshi, as a fresh opportunity for those who were struggling in the midst of the biggest bear market since.</p>
<p>The community of SHIKOKU INU is agile and tenacious, just like Shikoku Ken, the loyal protectors of the Japanese mountainous island of Shikoku. Born out of trials and tribulation, the SHIKOKU INU community is one of the strongest communities, supportive of one another, and pushing each other towards success.</p>
<p>Furthermore, SHIKOKU INU proposes a novel concept for community retention and engagement. That is, the publishing of the private key of the developer account for all to see and use, to harbor a truly decentralized community. SHIKOKU INU has no permanent allotted owner, instead, it is owned by all that wish to own it.</p>
<p>In addition to the main page, there’re various websites belonging to SHIKOKU INU that merge to create a complete decentralized ecosystem called SIDE (Shikoku Inu Decentralized Ecosystem). These websites include shikoku.app, a hub for decentralized applications; shikoku.space, a community blackboard space where members can collaborate on ideas and bring them to fruition; shikoku.world, an area for a world map of the SHIKOKU INU community; shikoku.life, an area for mental health checks for members of the SHIKOKU INU community, as well as tips and tricks for things in their day to day life; shikoku.store, a hub for official SHIKOKU INU merchandise; shikoku.fun, an area for all things fun such as community games, events, and get-togethers; and many more. By the development of the SIDE with SHIK being the centerpiece and store of value, it aims to create a thriving community full of creators, investors, developers, and holders.</p>
<p>SHIKOKU INU plans to assist the common investor with knowledge on how to safely custody their assets in an interesting and engaging way, while allowing them to be part of a decentralized and vibrant community of those with similar goals. SHIKOKU INU, while beginning as an experiment, plans to grow into a decentralized ecosystem, where the value will be provided by the community, for the community, and for those outside the community who are looking to learn more about decentralization and cryptocurrency as a whole.</p>
<p><strong>About SHIK Token</strong></p>
<p>SHIKOKU INU (SHIK) resides on the Ethereum blockchain. The most simplistic ERC-20 contract was used, ensuring stability in trades without outliers and efficiency in gas processing for those who wish to trade it. Although SHIK begins as a decentralized experiment, coupled with what can most succinctly be referred to as a meme coin, its goals are far-reaching, assuming the necessary community adoption and rally takes place.</p>
<p>If a user wishes to participate in SHIKOKU INU and its’ community, it is advised that an individual holds the SHIK token, as it will be used as the primary token to power all areas of the SIDE. However, if for any reason an individual wishes to participate in the community outside of the SIDE, they are welcome to do so. The token is simply a cog in the much larger wheel of mass adoption, education, and change that SHIKOKU INU plans to bring.</p>
<p>The total supply of SHIK is 1 quadrillion (i.e., 1,000,000,000,000,000) tokens, and no additional tax will be collected when buying and selling the token. It will be listed on LBank Exchange at 13:00 UTC on January 9, 2023, investors who are interested in the SHIKOKU INU investment can easily buy and sell SHIK token on LBank Exchange by then. The listing of SHIK token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p>
<p><strong>Learn More about</strong><strong> SHIK Token:</strong><br />
Official Website: <a href="https://shikoku.io" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://shikoku.io</a><br />
Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/SHIKARMY" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://t.me/SHIKARMY</a><br />
Discord: <a href="https://discord.gg/E7crTVsRXG" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://discord.gg/E7crTVsRXG</a><br />
Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/shikokuinucoin" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/shikokuinucoin</a><br />
Facebook: <a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/shikokuinu/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://www.facebook.com/groups/shikokuinu/</a><br />
YouTube: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCORRl3-7nvDy6PgvmiXTTBQ" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCORRl3-7nvDy6PgvmiXTTBQ</a><br />
Medium: <a href="https://medium.com/@shikokuinuarmy" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://medium.com/@shikokuinuarmy</a></p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media: </strong></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Facebook</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong><br />
LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
LBank Exchange<br />
<a href="mailto:marketing@lbank.info">marketing@lbank.info</a><br />
<a href="mailto:business@lbank.info">business@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-shikoku-inu-shik-on-january-9-2023/">LBank Exchange Will List SHIKOKU INU (SHIK) on January 9, 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-shikoku-inu-shik-on-january-9-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Miners Aren&#8217;t Giving Lenders Their Money Back</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-miners-arent-giving-lenders-their-money-back/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-miners-arent-giving-lenders-their-money-back/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 17:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Block Fi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celsius]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lenders]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75842</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Of all the people or companies in the crypto space, lenders likely have it worse than anyone or anything. They are the ones giving money to the crypto companies that are now failing or struggling to stay afloat. In many cases, they are not able to repay the funds they’ve utilized or borrowed, which really<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-miners-arent-giving-lenders-their-money-back/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-miners-arent-giving-lenders-their-money-back/">Crypto Miners Aren&#8217;t Giving Lenders Their Money Back</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Of all the people or companies in the crypto space, <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/crypto-lenders-woes-worsen-bitcoin-133831455.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">lenders likely have</a> it worse than anyone or anything. They are the ones giving money to the crypto companies that are now failing or struggling to stay afloat. In many cases, they are not able to repay the funds they’ve utilized or borrowed, which really puts a lot of these lending firms on edge.</p>
<h2>Lenders Are Enduring Trouble from Crypto Miners</h2>
<p>Instead of money, lenders are instead receiving machines from miners – who at one point, earned more than $4 billion through their professions – as collateral. They figure if they can’t pay their bills with cash, they can at least send these lenders the items and equipment they’re using to show that they’re “good for it.” The problem is that in this economy, cash is king, and everything else is likely to carry some degree of uselessness or risk alongside it.</p>
<p>Several firms – including New York Digital Investment Group (NYDIG), <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/celsius-network-is-next-crypto-company-to-file-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">Celsius Network</a>, Block Fi, and Galaxy Digital – have lent out machines and money to mining companies to get their jobs done. Now, with the industry being in the state it’s in, everything is coming to a crashing halt, and several of the above-named companies have been forced into bankruptcy due to liquidity issues and related concerns.</p>
<p>Ethan Vera – chief operations officer at crypto mining services firm Luxor Technologies – said in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>People were pouring dollars into the mining space. Miners ended up dictating a lot of the loan terms, so the financiers moved ahead with a lot of the deals where only the machines were collateral.</p></blockquote>
<p>Companies like Iris Energy Ltd. are expected to default on as much as $108 million in the coming months. The firm has borrowed from the NYDIG on several occasions, with its most recent loan being delivered in March of 2022. Another firm that’s borrowed from NYDIG is Core Scientific, which some are whispering could <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-firm-core-scientific-says-its-considering-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">be one of the next crypto</a> firms to file bankruptcy. NYDIG had also provided a $54 million loan to the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block-fi-is-the-latest-crypto-company-to-go-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">now bankrupt Block Fi</a>.</p>
<p>Michael Wursthorn – a spokesperson for Galaxy Digital – said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We continue to take a prudent, risk-managed approach toward financing arrangements in the mining space. In the third quarter, for example, Galaxy’s mining arm closed three existing machine leases collectively worth about $8 million at expected terms without defaults, delinquencies, or losses.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Didn&#8217;t Do Your Due Diligence, Did Ya?</h2>
<p>One of the big problems – according to Matthew Kimmel, a digital asset analyst at crypto firm Coin Shares – is that many of these lenders did not bother to really check and see if the companies they were giving money to were solid enough. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>There hasn’t necessarily been the best due diligence on whether a miner was credit worthy or not.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-miners-arent-giving-lenders-their-money-back/">Crypto Miners Aren&#8217;t Giving Lenders Their Money Back</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-miners-arent-giving-lenders-their-money-back/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>European Central Bank: Bitcoin Is Quickly Becoming Irrelevant</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/european-central-bank-bitcoin-is-quickly-becoming-irrelevant/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/european-central-bank-bitcoin-is-quickly-becoming-irrelevant/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 15:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European Central Bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75840</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The European Central Bank has issued a statement claiming that bitcoin is on its way out and closely approaching “irrelevance.” The European Central Bank Is not a Bitcoin Fan The financial institution released a blog entitled “Bitcoin’s Last Stand” that details the fall of the world’s number one digital currency. Interestingly, the bank does not<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/european-central-bank-bitcoin-is-quickly-becoming-irrelevant/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/european-central-bank-bitcoin-is-quickly-becoming-irrelevant/">European Central Bank: Bitcoin Is Quickly Becoming Irrelevant</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The European Central Bank has issued a <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/european-central-bank-says-bitcoin-is-on-the-road-to-irrelevance/ar-AA14JSOc" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">statement claiming that bitcoin</a> is on its way out and closely approaching “irrelevance.”</p>
<h2>The European Central Bank Is not a Bitcoin Fan</h2>
<p>The financial institution released a blog entitled “Bitcoin’s Last Stand” that details the fall of the world’s number one digital currency. Interestingly, the bank does <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">not refer to FTX</a> and its November collapse as the reason as to why bitcoin is doing so poorly. Rather, it hints that bitcoin was on a destructive path long before the company began sinking into oblivion.</p>
<p>When the blog was first published, the bank made note of bitcoin’s rise beyond the $17,000 mark, the first time it had done so in approximately two weeks. However, while the rise is likely to get some people excited, the bank dismissed the maneuver, claiming it wasn’t going to last. The blog says:</p>
<blockquote><p>More likely, however, it is an artificially induced last gasp before the road to irrelevance, and this was already foreseeable before FTX went bust and sent the bitcoin price to well below USD $16,000.</p></blockquote>
<p>Some of the reasons the blog speaks the way it does of bitcoin is because, it says, the digital currency does not meet the requirements of a valid investment, nor does it work as a payment method. In many ways, the currency has not proven itself to work in any way, shape, or form. It says:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin&#8217;s conceptual design and technological shortcomings make it questionable as a means of payment. Real bitcoin transactions are cumbersome, slow, and expensive. Bitcoin has never been used to any significant extent for legal real-world transactions. Bitcoin is also not suitable as an investment. It does not generate cash flow (like real estate) or dividends (like equities), cannot be used productively (like commodities) or provide social benefits (like gold). The market valuation of bitcoin is therefore based purely on speculation.</p></blockquote>
<p>With so much talk of regulation following the FTX failure, many are wondering if perhaps a few laws overseeing the space will allow bitcoin and its crypto cousins to rise through the ranks again, though the blog makes it clear that this may not happen, and that fans shouldn’t get too stuck on the idea.</p>
<h2>Regulation Won&#8217;t Help</h2>
<p>It reads:</p>
<blockquote><p>The belief that space must be given to innovation at all costs stubbornly persists. Firstly, these technologies have so far created limited value for society, no matter how great the expectations [are] for the future. Secondly, the use of a promising technology is not a sufficient condition for an added value of a product based on it.</p></blockquote>
<p>To say it has been a rough year for bitcoin would be a heavy understatement. The currency has fallen by more than 70 percent over the last 14 months since hitting a new all-time high of $68K in November 2021.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/european-central-bank-bitcoin-is-quickly-becoming-irrelevant/">European Central Bank: Bitcoin Is Quickly Becoming Irrelevant</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/european-central-bank-bitcoin-is-quickly-becoming-irrelevant/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
