<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 08:56:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Blocktrade is Changing the Game of Crypto Trading &#8211;  A Remarkable First Move with €4.5 Million Worth of BTEX Sold</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blocktrade-is-changing-the-game-of-crypto-trading-a-remarkable-first-move-with-e4-5-million-worth-of-btex-sold/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blocktrade-is-changing-the-game-of-crypto-trading-a-remarkable-first-move-with-e4-5-million-worth-of-btex-sold/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 08:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sponsored]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78399</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrencies are upending the elitist, paper-shuffling world of traditional finance. They’re creating new stores of value and reigniting financial interest amongst a new class of investors. Blocktrade is taking cryptocurrency engagement to a new level through its gamified universe &#8211; a cryptocurrency trading platform that incorporates levels, collectibles, leaderboards and challenges into crypto trading. Making<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blocktrade-is-changing-the-game-of-crypto-trading-a-remarkable-first-move-with-e4-5-million-worth-of-btex-sold/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blocktrade-is-changing-the-game-of-crypto-trading-a-remarkable-first-move-with-e4-5-million-worth-of-btex-sold/">Blocktrade is Changing the Game of Crypto Trading &#8211;  A Remarkable First Move with €4.5 Million Worth of BTEX Sold</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrencies are upending the elitist, paper-shuffling world of traditional finance. They’re creating new stores of value and reigniting financial interest amongst a new class of investors. <a href="https://blocktrade.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Blocktrade</a> is taking cryptocurrency engagement to a new level through its gamified universe &#8211; a cryptocurrency trading platform that incorporates levels, collectibles, leaderboards and challenges into crypto trading.</p>
<p>Making financial knowledge more accessible is a cornerstone of Web3, and Blocktrade is transforming how people engage with and learn about digital assets. The gamification of crypto fills the education gap by applying game design elements to non-gaming contexts, such as trading cryptocurrencies. By making trading exciting, this platform is onboarding the next generation of crypto investors who want an easy, simple way to create wealth.</p>
<p>Powered by the <a href="https://blocktrade.com/btex-token" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">BTEX token</a>, Blocktrade offers a fully gamified universe. As users participate in specific activities and progress through levels on Blocktrade’s platform, they earn BTEX tokens and XP points along the way, unlocking a wide array of benefits and rewards such as trading bonuses and discount fees. Minigames on the platform have already racked up more than 90,000 plays in the first four weeks since beta launch, emphasizing the appetite in the trading community for this new form of engagement.</p>
<p>The wave of NFT popularity that reached new highs in the last years is still only the beginning of investment into digital worlds and personas. Now, crypto investments, digital collectables, and unique, personalizable avatars are all available on a single platform: Blocktrade.</p>
<p>As part of this gamified crypto universe, Blocktrade has just launched a Crypto Greek Gods collection, introducing 50 unique avatars representing Greek Gods for users to immerse themselves in a world where mythological creatures come to life. The collection features five female goddesses: Aphrodite, Artemis, Athena, Hera, and Nemesis, and five male gods: Apollo, Ares, Hades, Poseidon, and Zeus. These limited-edition digital collectible avatars, meticulously designed by a talented NFT artist, serve as a symbol of accomplishment within the rewards program. By intertwining gaming and crypto through a Greek God theme, Blocktrade is creating a captivating connection that bridges the past and future.</p>
<p>The world of cryptocurrency is constantly evolving, pushing the boundaries of what is possible in the digital landscape, and Blocktrade is a crypto platform designed for the future. Gamification is the next step in trading culture and a move that will leave traditional finance further behind. On gamified platforms, routine tasks become exciting challenges, and platforms like Blocktrade deliver an engaging, intuitive experience for investors that want accessible opportunities to make money. This development epitomizes Blocktrade’s goal to democratize investing and bring innovative wealth-creation opportunities to the masses.</p>
<p>Blocktrade&#8217;s vision for gamified cryptocurrency trading is being realized though BTEX, a token that functions as the fuel for Blocktrade’s gamified universe. BTEX has already attracted more than 1400 supporters from all over the world, who bought more than €4,500,000 worth of BTEX in the successful exclusive round of the token sale.</p>
<p>The public round of the token sale is ongoing until June 9th. Anyone with an account on Blocktrade can participate, acquire BTEX at a discounted rate and be a part of the future of cryptocurrency trading. Learn more at <a href="https://blocktrade.com/btex-token" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">blocktrade.com/btex-token</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blocktrade-is-changing-the-game-of-crypto-trading-a-remarkable-first-move-with-e4-5-million-worth-of-btex-sold/">Blocktrade is Changing the Game of Crypto Trading &#8211;  A Remarkable First Move with €4.5 Million Worth of BTEX Sold</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blocktrade-is-changing-the-game-of-crypto-trading-a-remarkable-first-move-with-e4-5-million-worth-of-btex-sold/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Risk of Fresh Drop to $105</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-105/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-105/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 03:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78396</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline below the $120 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below the $118 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support at $116.00 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-105/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-105/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Risk of Fresh Drop to $105</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline below the $120 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below the $118 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support at $116.00 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it stays below the $116 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin cash price is declining below the $118 zone against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-27250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. BCH/USD could extend losses if there is a close below $112.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin cash price struggled to gain pace for a move above the $120 and $122 resistance levels. BCH formed a high near $120.93 and started a fresh decline.</p>
<p>There was a clear move below the $118.00 and $116.00 support levels. The pair even declined below the $116 support. It tested the $112 zone. A low is formed near $112.89 and the price is now consolidating losses. It is now trading above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $120.93 swing high to the $112.89 low.</p>
<p>Besides, it is trading below the $118 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Immediate resistance is near the $116.00 level and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bears-aim-fresh-drop-to-100/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>The 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $120.93 swing high to the $112.89 low is also near $116. The next key resistance is near $118. Any more gains above $116 and $118 could set the pace for a move toward the $120 level.</p>
<p>If there is a move above the $120 resistance, the price could rise toward the $128 zone. If not, the price might continue lower below $112. Immediate support on the downside is near the $110 zone. The next major support is near the $105 level, below which the bears might aim for $100.</p>
<div id="attachment_78397" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Bitcoin-Cash-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78397" class="size-full wp-image-78397" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Bitcoin-Cash-2.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78397" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Cash Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BCHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Bitcoin cash price is now trading below the $118 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $120 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for BCH/USD is losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BCH/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $112 and $110.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $116 and $118.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-105/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Risk of Fresh Drop to $105</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-105/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brazil Village Centers Itself Around Bitcoin Payments</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brazil-village-centers-itself-around-bitcoin-payments/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brazil-village-centers-itself-around-bitcoin-payments/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brazil]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Praia Bitcoin Project]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77835</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A group of business owners have gathered in Brazil to create a new economic center to accept bitcoin as a form of payment. Bitcoin Is Getting Bigger in Brazil Known as the Praia Bitcoin project, the engagement is designed to set a world record for peer-to-peer transactions on the Lightning Network, which as we reported<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brazil-village-centers-itself-around-bitcoin-payments/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brazil-village-centers-itself-around-bitcoin-payments/">Brazil Village Centers Itself Around Bitcoin Payments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A group of business owners have gathered in Brazil to create a <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/04/09/brazils-bitcoin-beach-says-lightning-network-works-better-than-visa/?sh=7a34299e7e7e" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">new economic center</a> to accept bitcoin as a form of payment.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Is Getting Bigger in Brazil</h2>
<p>Known as the Praia Bitcoin project, the engagement is designed to set a world record for peer-to-peer transactions on the Lightning Network, which as we reported earlier today, is <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-to-integrate-the-btc-lightning-network/" data-wpel-link="internal">now being integrated</a> into Coinbase, one of the largest and most prominent digital currency exchanges in the world. In under three and a half minutes, more than 70 separate BTC transactions occurred, thus setting the time for the shortest period in the crypto history books.</p>
<p>The Lightning Network works to take smaller BTC transactions off-chain, thus allowing the network to operate faster and with lesser costs. Praia Bitcoin’s creator Fernando Motolese proudly explained in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>This was only possible because the Lightning Network is ready for the masses. Right now, there is no other option that is as prepared for this kind of market with a functional solution as Lightning. It is superior to Visa.</p></blockquote>
<p>Initially working as a musician, Motolese was used to a time where money was very scarce. This is what ultimately caused him to turn to bitcoin in the first place, and it’s what inspired him to give business dealings and entrepreneurship a try. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>I asked for help from Bitcoin Beach, but that only came a year later. They were just the inspiration at first, but after the release of their Bitcoin Beach whitepaper,<em> </em>they became a role model and an important partner.</p></blockquote>
<p>Initially, the presence of the Lightning Network in the area had to be built up through consumer donations, which Motolese says was a rather hard undertaking. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Getting donations is very difficult. At each stage of our development, we update our crowdfunding campaign with new goals and proof of the work we have done with those donations. I started this by donating 0.02 BTC, which was around $1,000 at the time. Now we have around 2.43 BTC.</p></blockquote>
<h2>The Government Wants to See BTC Thrive</h2>
<p>The Brazilian government, according to Foxbit CEO Ricardo Dantas, is allegedly working to implement new digital currency rules that will help build out the space and ensure a lasting presence for crypto tokens. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>A better understanding of the regulations will light some fire under Brazilian investor demand for bitcoin because today there are a lot of cold feet regarding cryptocurrency… There is a sense that bitcoin technology is relatively complex and has no rules, which gives people the sense that it is totally lawless. We work hard to change that perception even though it’s not something people see, and it’s not something everyone in crypto will follow, but with better rules will come more adoption [and] more investor confidence.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brazil-village-centers-itself-around-bitcoin-payments/">Brazil Village Centers Itself Around Bitcoin Payments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brazil-village-centers-itself-around-bitcoin-payments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase to Integrate the BTC Lightning Network</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-to-integrate-the-btc-lightning-network/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-to-integrate-the-btc-lightning-network/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 15:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lightning Network]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77832</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase – the largest and most popular crypto exchange in the U.S. – has confirmed it’s going to be integrating the bitcoin Lightning Network onto its platform, thus ensuring bitcoin transactions scale and move along at quicker paces. Coinbase and Lightning: The Perfect Match? The Lightning Network has been all the rage in the bitcoin<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-to-integrate-the-btc-lightning-network/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-to-integrate-the-btc-lightning-network/">Coinbase to Integrate the BTC Lightning Network</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase – the largest and most popular crypto exchange in the U.S. – has confirmed it’s going to be integrating <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/04/09/coinbase-ceo-confirms-major-bitcoin-upgrade-as-ethereum-braces-for-24-billion-price-earthquake/?sh=2076f3423eba" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">the bitcoin Lightning Network</a> onto its platform, thus ensuring bitcoin transactions scale and move along at quicker paces.</p>
<h2>Coinbase and Lightning: The Perfect Match?</h2>
<p>The Lightning Network has been all the rage in the bitcoin community for some time. The idea is that it helps move various (smaller) bitcoin transactions off-chain, thus ensuring the network has less baggage to deal with. Removing some of these lesser transactions from the BTC mainframe allows bitcoin to move faster when being transferred between wallets. It also ensures transactions are less costly, which has been a problem with bitcoin in the past.</p>
<p>The news involving the Lightning Network was announced on Twitter by Brian Armstrong, the CEO of Coinbase. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Lightning is great and something we&#8217;ll integrate.</p></blockquote>
<p>The news comes at an interesting time given Coinbase is dealing with quite a bit right now. Not long ago, the trading platform announced it received a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">Wells notice from</a> the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), which has become a major bully on the crypto playground. The agency has made a living out of attacking crypto <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/" data-wpel-link="internal">firms such as Kraken</a>, which was recently forced to part with a $30 million penalty fee and end all its staking services.</p>
<p>A Wells notice doesn’t charge a company with any crime. However, it’s a warning to the company receiving the notice that it’s going to likely be charged in the future. This gives the firm time to prepare and get a good legal team to fight on its behalf.</p>
<p>It’s hard to know if Coinbase has truly done something wrong or if this is just another attempt on the SEC’s part to ensure crypto innovation dies in the U.S., which it appears to have been pursuing for some time. There are several crypto companies out there that have fallen victim to the agency’s drama over the past two years, and very few of them (if any at all) have admitted guilt. It seems the agency is simply looking to garner as much penalty money as it can from digital currency enterprises.</p>
<p>The news surrounding the Lightning Network has got several people excited, with Gabor Gurbacs – a crypto entrepreneur and advisor to Van Eck – saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>Looking forward to seeing Lightning support on Coinbase. Bitfinex has done a great job with Lightning earlier.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Ethereum&#8217;s Also Looking Good</h2>
<p>In the meantime, analysts at K33 Research are commenting on Ethereum, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>1.1 million Ethereum related to partial reward withdrawals could face the market, while Celsius [network] is likely to sell its 158,000 staked balance as part of its bankruptcy process. These two numbers represent nearly 1.3 million Ethereum or approximately $2.4 billion worth of potential sell-side pressure to face the market.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-to-integrate-the-btc-lightning-network/">Coinbase to Integrate the BTC Lightning Network</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-to-integrate-the-btc-lightning-network/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>North Korea Is Still Stealing Crypto, and It&#8217;s Getting Stronger</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/north-korea-is-still-stealing-crypto-and-its-getting-stronger/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/north-korea-is-still-stealing-crypto-and-its-getting-stronger/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 13:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[North Korea]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nukes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77830</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The United States, South Korea, and Japan have all issued a joint statement saying that they’re worried about North Korea and its regular willingness to pursue digital currencies to build its ongoing nuclear program. North Korea: Still a Crypto-Driven Threat Several analysts say that North Korea has played host to a wide array of crypto<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/north-korea-is-still-stealing-crypto-and-its-getting-stronger/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/north-korea-is-still-stealing-crypto-and-its-getting-stronger/">North Korea Is Still Stealing Crypto, and It&#8217;s Getting Stronger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The United States, South Korea, and Japan have all issued a joint <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-in/news/other/us-south-korea-and-japan-claim-stolen-cryptocurrency-funds-used-to-finance-north-korea-s-nuclear-program/ar-AA19zIQY" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">statement saying that they’re</a> worried about North Korea and its regular willingness to pursue digital currencies to build its ongoing nuclear program.</p>
<h2>North Korea: Still a Crypto-Driven Threat</h2>
<p>Several analysts say that North Korea has played <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-north-korea-stole-more-crypto-in-2022-than-in-any-other-year/" data-wpel-link="internal">host to a wide array of</a> crypto hacking networks, Lazarus being a big one. Their mission is to steal digital currencies from neighboring regions so they can grow the nation’s nuclear arms program. The country has stolen well over a billion dollars in digital funds and has washed the money clean through mixers and similar services so that it cannot be traced. It is believed that North Korea has stolen crypto from sources in America, Europe, and other regions of Asia.</p>
<p>The joint statement reads as follows:</p>
<blockquote><p>We reiterate with concern that overseas DPRK IT workers continue using forged identities and nationalities. We are also deeply concerned about how the DPRK supports these programs by stealing and laundering funds as well as gathering information through malicious cyber activities.</p></blockquote>
<p>According to Kim Gunn – the chief nuclear negotiator of South Korea – the nation of North Korea is consistently utilizing propaganda that is convincing the people living within its borders that nuclear power is a necessity the nation cannot do without. Thus, it can maintain its image of launching and testing nukes without arousing too much suspicion amongst its people.</p>
<p>However, he insists that nuclear power is a tool that can do nothing but lead to war and conflict across the globe, and that said power will have no positive results in the end. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>North Korea is misguiding its people to believe that nuclear weapons are a magic wand that can solve all of its problems.</p></blockquote>
<p>Not long ago, the U.S. and South Korea engaged in a joint military exercise that caused Kim Jong Un to retaliate by ordering a boost to his nation’s military and nuclear activities. The North Korean dictator says that both countries engaged in an act of war against his country and that he’s not one to stand around waiting for two superpowers to engage in some sort of retaliatory action against his armies.</p>
<h2>More Nukes Launched?</h2>
<p>He also unveiled new nuclear warheads that he claims can hit any spot in the U.S. without being noticed beforehand. Responding to the threats, Japan has since announced that it will extend its present two-year trade ban on all goods from North Korea, though it is leaving the door open to humanitarian causes and related programs.</p>
<p>One of the biggest crypto thefts to occur at the hands of North Korea took place in mid-2022 when crypto gaming platform Axie Infinity lost more <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lazarus-linked-to-axie-infinity-crypto-heist-in-march/" data-wpel-link="internal">than $600 million to</a> one of the nation’s hacking groups.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/north-korea-is-still-stealing-crypto-and-its-getting-stronger/">North Korea Is Still Stealing Crypto, and It&#8217;s Getting Stronger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/north-korea-is-still-stealing-crypto-and-its-getting-stronger/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EOS Price Analysis: Signs of Recovery Toward $1.0</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-signs-of-recovery-toward-1-0/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-signs-of-recovery-toward-1-0/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 03:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EOS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78385</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>EOS price is trading in a bearish zone below the $0.95 support against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above $0.88 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $0.87 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-signs-of-recovery-toward-1-0/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-signs-of-recovery-toward-1-0/">EOS Price Analysis: Signs of Recovery Toward $1.0</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>EOS price is trading in a bearish zone below the $0.95 support against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $0.88 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $0.87 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could start a recovery wave if it clears the $0.935 and $0.962 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>EOS price is struggling below $1.00 against the US Dollar, unlike <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-27250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. The price might attempt to recover if there is a clear move above $0.935.</em></p>
<h2>EOS Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, EOS price range moves below the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-more-losses-seem-likely-below-0-92/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">$0.95 resistance</a> against the US Dollar. The price remained stable above the $0.835 and $0.84 support levels.</p>
<p>A low is formed near $0.8362 and the price is now attempting an upside correction. There was a move above the $0.865 and $0.88 resistance levels. Besides, there was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $0.87 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair.</p>
<p>The price is now trading above $0.88 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $0.935 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $1.034 swing high to the $0.8362 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $0.962 level or the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $1.034 swing high to the $0.8362 low, above which the price might test the $0.98 level. Any more gains might send the price toward the $1.00 level.</p>
<p>On the downside, immediate support is near the $0.88 level or the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). The next key support is near the $0.85 level. If there is a downside break below the $0.850 support, the price could test the $0.82 support in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_78386" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/EOS-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78386" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78386" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/EOS-2.png" alt="EOS Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78386" class="wp-caption-text">EOS Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/EOSUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, EOS price is now trading above the $0.88 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start a recovery wave if it clears the $0.935 and $0.962 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4-hours MACD – The MACD for EOS/USD is losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4-hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $0.88 and $0.85.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $0.935 and $0.962.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-signs-of-recovery-toward-1-0/">EOS Price Analysis: Signs of Recovery Toward $1.0</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-signs-of-recovery-toward-1-0/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Regain Strength Above $92</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-regain-strength-above-92/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-regain-strength-above-92/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 02:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78381</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin started a steady increase above $92 against the US Dollar. LTC price is now trading above $92 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance at $85 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-regain-strength-above-92/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-regain-strength-above-92/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Regain Strength Above $92</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Litecoin started a steady increase above $92 against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>LTC price is now trading above $92 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance at $85 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $95 and $98 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Litecoin price is showing positive signs above $92 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-27250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. LTC price could climb further if there is a clear move above $95.</em></p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few sessions, there were mostly positive moves in Bitcoin, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-drop-below-1700/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Ethereum</a>, Ripple, and Litecoin against the US Dollar. Earlier, LTC formed a base above the $75 level and started a fresh increase.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above the $80 and $92 resistance levels. During the increase, there was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance at $85 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair. The pair even cleared the $92 resistance zone.</p>
<p>It is now trading above $92 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). A high is formed near $95.00 and the price is now consolidating gains.</p>
<p>On the downside, initial support is near the $90.40 level. It is near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $75.32 swing low to the $95.00 high. The next major support is near the $85 level and the trend line.</p>
<p>The 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $75.32 swing low to the $95.00 high is also near the $85 level. If there is a downside break below the $85 support, the price could accelerate lower toward the $80 level in the near term.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $95 level. A clear move above the $95 level could push the price toward the $98 level. The next major resistance sits near the $100 level. Any more gains might send the price toward the $112 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_78382" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Litecoin-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78382" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78382" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Litecoin-2.png" alt="Litecoin (LTC) Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78382" class="wp-caption-text">Litecoin (LTC) Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Litecoin price is clearly trading above $92 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $95 and $98 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LTC/USD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $90 and $85</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $95 and $98.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-regain-strength-above-92/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Regain Strength Above $92</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-regain-strength-above-92/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Volatility Still a Major Problem, Analysts Say</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-volatility-still-a-major-problem-analysts-say/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-volatility-still-a-major-problem-analysts-say/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 17:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[volatility]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77828</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has appeared to be on something of a roll over the past three months, but according to many analysts, the problem of volatility is not quite over. In fact, 2023 could be prone to some rather unexpected volatility trends that may lead to a short squeeze, thus causing value losses for the BTC network.<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-volatility-still-a-major-problem-analysts-say/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-volatility-still-a-major-problem-analysts-say/">Bitcoin Volatility Still a Major Problem, Analysts Say</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has appeared to be on something of a roll over the past three months, but according to many analysts, the problem <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-faces-low-risk-of-liquidations-induced-price-volatility-after-70-surge/ar-AA19FzSs" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">of volatility is not quite</a> over. In fact, 2023 could be prone to some rather unexpected volatility trends that may lead to a short squeeze, thus causing value losses for the BTC network.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Isn&#8217;t Out of the Woods Yet</h2>
<p>Over the past four or five months, BTC has risen by about 70 percent from where it was at the end of 2023. During that period, bitcoin was trading in the mid-$16K range, a huge dip from the all-time high of about $68,000 per unit it achieved in November of 2021. Nothing could have predicted that bitcoin was going to endure what arguably turned out to be the worst year on record for the world’s number one digital currency by market cap.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, the asset is just below the $28K mark, meaning that while there’s still plenty of room to heal, the currency has done much better for itself during the previous quarter, and the digital token is on the road towards recovery.</p>
<p>Still, analysts at Block Ware Solutions don’t think traders and investors are quite out of the woods yet. They said in a recent report that the currency remains prone to price swings, and that the level of volatility they’re predicting could make 2023 another problematic year for the digital asset. They said:</p>
<blockquote><p>High open interest relative to market cap means the market could be vulnerable to a short squeeze or liquidation cascade, which would result in a price swing being more volatile than it otherwise would have been due to forced buying or selling, respectively… The medium-term trend of decreasing open interest/market cap has not been broken, which is reassurance that, even in the event of downward volatility, price is most likely not going to decrease to the level it was at to begin the year.</p></blockquote>
<p>The futures open interest to market ratio has been trapped in a downward spiral since the collapse of the trading platform FTX in November of last year. Despite the recent price consolidation of bitcoin, investors haven’t been as eager to jump into this arena of bitcoin trading for a while. They said:</p>
<blockquote><p>BTC has essentially traded sideways for the past three weeks, yet we haven’t seen a build-up in open interest. This is a signal that the market is still in a risk-off mode.</p></blockquote>
<h2>FTX: A Major Embarrassment</h2>
<p>FTX has affected the crypto space in more ways than anyone could have possibly imagined. The digital currency exchange was listed in the top five exchanges just three years after it came to fruition.</p>
<p>However, it eventually collapsed into a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">heaping pile of bankruptcy</a> and fraud, and its former chief executive is <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-to-await-trial-at-his-parents-house/" data-wpel-link="internal">now awaiting trial</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-volatility-still-a-major-problem-analysts-say/">Bitcoin Volatility Still a Major Problem, Analysts Say</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-volatility-still-a-major-problem-analysts-say/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dieter Wermuth: Bitcoin Is a Complete Waste of Investor Funds</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dieter-wermuth-bitcoin-is-a-complete-waste-of-investor-funds/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dieter-wermuth-bitcoin-is-a-complete-waste-of-investor-funds/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 15:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dieter Wermuth]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77826</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dieter Wermuth – a noted economist and partner at Wermuth Asset Management – explained in a recent note that he thinks the overall economy would be better without bitcoin, and that people should try to forget about the currency for a little while. Dieter Wermuth on Why Bitcoin is Pointless Bitcoin has been traveling a<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dieter-wermuth-bitcoin-is-a-complete-waste-of-investor-funds/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dieter-wermuth-bitcoin-is-a-complete-waste-of-investor-funds/">Dieter Wermuth: Bitcoin Is a Complete Waste of Investor Funds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dieter Wermuth – a noted economist and partner at Wermuth Asset Management – <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/the-economy-would-be-better-off-without-bitcoin-as-it-s-a-negative-sum-investment-that-comes-at-a-social-cost-economist-says/ar-AA19E0BE" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">explained in a</a> recent note that he thinks the overall economy would be better without bitcoin, and that people should try to forget about the currency for a little while.</p>
<h2>Dieter Wermuth on Why Bitcoin is Pointless</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a> has been traveling a meandering road over the past two years or so. In 2021, things were really rather solid for the world’s number one digital currency by market cap. It rose to a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit in November of that year and it looked as though the currency was unstoppable.</p>
<p>However, things took a very ugly and drastic turn just a few months later when the asset lost more than $20,000 during the early portions of 2022. Throughout that year, the currency continued to lose value and ultimately fell into the mid-$16K range by the time the end of 2022 rolled along. This means that in just over a year, the asset lost over 70 percent of its value.</p>
<p>Now, the asset appears to be on a turnaround mission, though while there’s been plenty of progress for BTC to enjoy in just the last few months alone, the currency still has a way to go, and apparently, Wermuth doesn’t think this is a path worth taking. He commented that BTC was a wasteful investment that ultimately steals funds away from other things that could lead to valid, legitimate growth of the American economy. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin activities are a negative-sum game. Without crypto, the economy would be better off. There would be more money for consumption and investment… Bitcoin has been brought to market with the narrative that it would be a better, more stable currency than traditional money. This story has been a deception.</p></blockquote>
<p>He says that at this time, bitcoin cannot be widely used as a method of payment, which ultimately works against the asset holding value. He also said that its volatility is a major problem not likely to lead to solid results in the coming future. Lastly, he doesn’t like that it’s not utilized to pay taxes. Wermuth said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Back in November 2021, bitcoin&#8217;s market capitalization reached 1.27 trillion dollars. When Lehman Brothers went belly up in 2008, a smaller amount of money had triggered the largest financial crisis and the deepest recession of the post-World War period.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Too Much Environmental Damage</h2>
<p>In his final comments, he issued the age-old argument that bitcoin mining is contributing heavily to climate change and to many other environmental problems. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I wonder whether it will be enough to just up regulatory efforts, or to forbid the participation of banks and other financial institutions, or to get rid of these markets altogether (if this is still an option).</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dieter-wermuth-bitcoin-is-a-complete-waste-of-investor-funds/">Dieter Wermuth: Bitcoin Is a Complete Waste of Investor Funds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dieter-wermuth-bitcoin-is-a-complete-waste-of-investor-funds/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
