<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 18:22:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/cropped-fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Fan and Miami Mayor Francis Suarez Enters Presidential Race</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-fan-and-miami-mayor-francis-suarez-enters-presidential-race/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 17:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Francis Suarez]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78822</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As we’ve mentioned in previous articles, it’s likely bitcoin and crypto are going to be huge topics in next year’s presidential election. Recently, another bitcoin-loving candidate threw himself into the race… Republican mayor of Miami Francis Suarez. Francis Suarez is Running for President Suarez has long been a bitcoin advocate, going so far as to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-fan-and-miami-mayor-francis-suarez-enters-presidential-race/">Bitcoin Fan and Miami Mayor Francis Suarez Enters Presidential Race</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As we’ve mentioned in previous articles, it’s likely bitcoin and crypto are <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-bitcoin-could-be-a-big-topic-in-next-years-presidential-election/">going to be huge topics</a> in next year’s presidential election. Recently, another bitcoin-loving <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/new-presidential-contender-bitcoin-mayor-francis-suarez-is-major-crypto-evangelist/ar-AA1cBeuP">candidate threw himself</a> into the race… Republican mayor of Miami Francis Suarez.</p>
<h2>Francis Suarez is Running for President</h2>
<p>Suarez has long been a bitcoin advocate, going so far as <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mayors-eric-adams-and-francis-suarez-are-eager-for-btc-based-salaries/">to announce in 2021 that</a> he would accept his entire mayoral salary in bitcoin (a move shared by New York City mayor Eric Adams). In an interview at the time, he mentioned he wanted to send a message to the world that Miami was going to be one of the most innovative and tech-happy cities on Earth.</p>
<p>He also said he wanted to potentially start a trend and see how many other politicians and government employees would follow suit. He explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>It will be completely optional. We want our employees to have that option, but it certainly is not going to be something we are going to force on them, understanding that a decision like that is a personal decision they [must] make if they want to make it.</p></blockquote>
<p>His bullishness didn’t end there. He also <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/francis-suarez-miami-coin-isnt-going-anywhere/">introduced Miami Coin</a>, a unique token for residents of his town. The idea was that the currency could potentially raise funds for the city’s growth and could also be used amongst citizens to pay utilities and related expenses. When it was launched in early 2022, the currency garnered more than $5 million in disbursements from City Coins (the minting company), which ultimately went towards a city rental assistance program.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, the coin didn’t get very far, only hiking to a price of about five cents per unit. Following the crypto winter of 2022, the asset was soon considered useless, and it was only ever offered on one crypto exchange. That exchange (called OK Coin) has since decided to suspend all trading of the token. In a statement, the company said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Limited liquidity for these coins on our platform has created the possibility of price manipulation and fraudulent activity. As a result, we will suspend trading until we can address these potential risks and protect our customers.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Trying to Get More Companies Involved</h2>
<p>Still, Suarez isn’t allowing this to bring him down. He has worked hard to bring about a Silicon Valley-type air to Miami, only he’s pushing hard for crypto companies to come and set up headquarters there. Among the ones to set up shop in the region were the now defunct crypto exchange FTX and Blockchain.com. Speaking of the latter’s arrival, Suarez said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Blockchain.com’s arrival in Miami perfectly encapsulates what the Miami movement is all about — leveraging Miami&#8217;s talent against the world&#8217;s top companies to build towards our goal of becoming a Miami that lasts forever and a Miami that works for everyone.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-fan-and-miami-mayor-francis-suarez-enters-presidential-race/">Bitcoin Fan and Miami Mayor Francis Suarez Enters Presidential Race</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apple Threatens to Remove Bitcoin Tipping Social App from Its Store</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/apple-threatens-to-remove-bitcoin-tipping-social-app-from-its-store/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Damus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78819</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jack Dorsey and Elon Musk aren’t too happy with the Apple company as of late. Apple Ain&#8217;t No Bitcoin Tipping Fan Not long ago, the technology conglomerate said it was looking into potentially removing the social media app Damus from its store. The reason was because the application offered a bitcoin tipping feature, and Apple [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/apple-threatens-to-remove-bitcoin-tipping-social-app-from-its-store/">Apple Threatens to Remove Bitcoin Tipping Social App from Its Store</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jack Dorsey and Elon Musk aren’t <a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/elon-musk-dorsey-apple-nostr-damus-app-rcna89328">too happy with the</a> Apple company as of late.</p>
<h2>Apple Ain&#8217;t No Bitcoin Tipping Fan</h2>
<p>Not long ago, the technology conglomerate said it was looking into potentially removing the social media app Damus from its store. The reason was because the application offered a bitcoin tipping feature, and Apple doesn’t want anything to do with such services. The company then made it clear to Damus: get rid of the feature, or you will no longer be offered in our store.</p>
<p>It’s not so much bitcoin that’s angering Apple, but rather the reason it’s being used. Damus is giving content creators a chance to earn compensation for material they post when it’s often free on other platforms. The social app says all content creators have a right to garner pay when they create something, and bitcoin is just a way to get them the money they need.</p>
<p>Apple claims Damus is “selling digital content,” which allegedly violates its present terms and conditions, and all gifts connected to receiving such content are required to use the in-app purchase functionality. In any case, Musk and Dorsey are choosing to focus more on the crypto aspects of the situation at hand, and they believe this is more an attempt to get bitcoin out of the picture. In a tweet, Dorsey mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>This is still incorrect @apple. Tipping on posts is not selling digital content. It’s a form of feedback… Why limit people sending bitcoin to each other? This is our one opportunity to build a truly global payment protocol for the internet (which would benefit your company immensely).</p></blockquote>
<p>Musk was also quick to throw his two cents into the mix, tweeting:</p>
<blockquote><p>If Apple competes against the whole world, Apple will have the whole world against it. This is not a winning scenario.</p></blockquote>
<p>Tim Sweeney, the CEO and co-founder of video game developer Epic Games, was also very critical of Apple’s sentiment, claiming:</p>
<blockquote><p>Apple is coming for money transfer and funding apps like Damus, Patreon, Venmo, maybe PayPal and Stripe… If digital goods may be somehow involved in the transfer, now they want 30 percent. If Apple can tax this, they can tax digital banking, payroll, and anything else.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Lot of Crypto Love</h2>
<p>Both Dorsey and Musk have been huge crypto advocates in the past. There was a time that Tesla vehicles, for example, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-permits-bitcoin-payments-for-tesla-vehicles/">were going to be purchasable</a> via bitcoin, though Musk has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-has-taken-a-nasty-stumble-many-are-blaming-elon-musk/">since rescinded this</a> decision. However, he still focuses <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/latest-elon-musk-tweet-sends-dogecoin-soaring/">heavily on Dogecoin</a>.</p>
<p>Dorsey has also been a huge bitcoin <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jack-dorsey-backs-btc-fan-robert-kennedy-jr-for-president/">fanatic and is now pushing</a> Robert F. Kennedy, Jr. – a democratic candidate for president – as the person to consider for the White House given Kennedy is supporting bitcoin use in America and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-hopeful-robert-kennedy-jr-appeared-at-this-years-miami-btc-conference/">recently spoke at this year’s</a> Miami Bitcoin Conference.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/apple-threatens-to-remove-bitcoin-tipping-social-app-from-its-store/">Apple Threatens to Remove Bitcoin Tipping Social App from Its Store</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BLK DNM Fashion Brand Acquired By Leading Blockchain Firm</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blk-dnm-fashion-brand-acquired-by-leading-blockchain-firm/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 13:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BLK DNM]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chroma Way]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78817</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The worlds of fashion and blockchain are coming together as luxury fashion label BLK DNM has been acquired by blockchain firm Chroma Way. The purpose? To embed digital garment IDs (undetectable microchips) into every new piece of clothing that will be issued to potential buyers. BLK DNM Will Have Chips in Its Clothing The chips [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blk-dnm-fashion-brand-acquired-by-leading-blockchain-firm/">BLK DNM Fashion Brand Acquired By Leading Blockchain Firm</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The worlds of fashion and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/blockchain/">blockchain</a> are <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/angelalei/2023/06/15/blk-dnm-to-unveil-fw23-collection-powered-by-blockchain-technology/?sh=3181f36b6ff6">coming together as luxury</a> fashion label BLK DNM has been acquired by blockchain firm Chroma Way. The purpose? To embed digital garment IDs (undetectable microchips) into every new piece of clothing that will be issued to potential buyers.</p>
<h2>BLK DNM Will Have Chips in Its Clothing</h2>
<p>The chips will permit each clothing article to have a unique identity that will be recorded on a distributed ledger. The chips will also monitor the production of the garments from the time they’re first conceived to the moment they arrive on the market. The chips will reward ethical behavior and assure owners’ brand influence.</p>
<p>Toni Collin – CEO of BLK DNM – said in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>BLK DNM’s philosophy is one of community, and our clothing is designed, through both its craftsmanship and timeless aesthetic, to be treasured and passed down through generations — the antithesis of irresponsible fast fashion. Now, with the introduction of BLK DNM Society and the first embedded hardware in our garments, we take those two pillars to a revolutionary new level. By embedding intelligence in every item, we hope we can inspire our industry to join us in using connected fashion to do better.</p></blockquote>
<p>Collin further stated that this is the perfect first step in developing a new fashion community, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>For the first time in fashion, technology is being used to engage that community in the virtual worlds that are increasingly a part of people’s lives, particularly for younger generations.</p></blockquote>
<p>Henrik Hjelte – CEO of and co-founder of Chroma Way – was also quick to throw his two cents into the mix, mentioning:</p>
<blockquote><p>Nothing like this has been attempted in fashion before. This has the potential to transform people’s relationships with the clothes they wear and brands they buy. No longer does the relationship with the customer end at the checkout. Each beautiful garment now becomes its own living, evolving piece of history.</p></blockquote>
<p>Discussing the merging of both fashion and blockchain technology, Collin added:</p>
<blockquote><p>Echoing Henrik, nothing like this has happened before. Blockchain technology offers a unique opportunity to reward responsible behaviors and to create identity and story in individual items&#8230; BLK DNM Society is bridging the gap between offline and online communities in a potentially transformative manner. The industry must begin to address the elephant in the room. The apparel industry generates an extraordinary amount of waste, even more so with the rise of fast fashion. What we’re launching here is the first step towards changing that through next-generation technology.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Rewarding the Right People</h2>
<p>The digital IDs will work to ensure all clothing is authentic while getting rid of anything that’s fake. Responsible behavior (like refurbishing clothing and second-hand purchases) will also garner positive attention and rewards.</p>
<p>BLK DNM believes adding garments to the blockchain will increase their value over time.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blk-dnm-fashion-brand-acquired-by-leading-blockchain-firm/">BLK DNM Fashion Brand Acquired By Leading Blockchain Firm</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Michael Saylor: SEC Lawsuits Are Paving the Way for BTC Dominance</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-sec-lawsuits-are-paving-the-way-to-btc-dominance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 17:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Saylor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroStrategy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78806</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Saylor, the former CEO of MicroStrategy, commented in an interview that the present SEC lawsuits against platforms like Coinbase and Binance will pave the way for bitcoin to become bigger than it’s ever been. Michael Saylor on the Future of BTC He anticipates that the bitcoin dominance in the crypto industry (which currently stands [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-sec-lawsuits-are-paving-the-way-to-btc-dominance/">Michael Saylor: SEC Lawsuits Are Paving the Way for BTC Dominance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Michael Saylor, the former CEO of MicroStrategy, <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/bitcoin-market-share-sec-regulators-cryptocurrencies-binance-microstrategy-michael-saylor-2023-6">commented in an interview</a> that the present SEC lawsuits against platforms like Coinbase and Binance will pave the way for bitcoin to become bigger than it’s ever been.</p>
<h2>Michael Saylor on the Future of BTC</h2>
<p>He anticipates that the bitcoin dominance in the crypto industry (which currently stands between 40 and 48 percent) will shoot up to a whopping 80 percent, leaving only a 20 percent margin for remaining altcoins. He thinks that with so many crypto exchanges afraid of the SEC and delisting altcoins that might be considered securities, bitcoin is going to become the ultimate force in crypto. He commented in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Now I think that the public is beginning to realize that bitcoin is the next bitcoin. The next logical step is for bitcoin to [grow] ten times from here and then ten times again.</p></blockquote>
<p>There are many crypto investors out there that have tried hard to diversify their portfolios. They have invested in multiple coins across a wide spectrum of assets as a means of ensuring that if one coin goes down, they at least have the chance of sustaining their wealth and keeping their stability.</p>
<p>However, with so many exchanges and trading platforms now getting rid of various altcoins, they’ll want to remain in the crypto space and will have no choice but to place all their money into BTC, which could wind up making it the ultimate king of digital assets.</p>
<p>Saylor has always <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-still-believes-btc-has-a-ton-of-power/">been a bitcoin bull</a>, first catching the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-microstrategy-bitcoin-bet-is-already-paying-off-big-time/">bitcoin bug back in late 2020</a> and investing some of his company’s money into the world’s number one digital currency by market cap. While things appeared promising at the start, by 2022, the currency had taken a serious turn for the worse, and Saylor wound up <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/microstrategy-dealt-heavy-blow-following-crypto-crash/">losing a bunch of</a> cash for MicroStrategy that still, largely, has not been recovered. From there, Saylor <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-btc-bull-and-microstrategy-chief-executive-steps-down/">left the CEO position</a> he worked for over 30 years and demoted himself to executive chairman.</p>
<p>Discussing the present mind frame of the SEC, Saylor mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>I mean, their view is [that] crypto exchanges should trade and hold pure digital commodities like bitcoin, and so the entire industry is kind of destined to be rationalized down to a bitcoin-focused industry, with maybe a half a dozen to a dozen other proof of work tokens.</p></blockquote>
<h2>All Exchanges Will Only Focus on BTC</h2>
<p>Eventually, he foresees a time when <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/microstrategy-founder-michael-saylor-says-bitcoin-could-grow-to-80-of-crypto-market-after-sec-suits-against-binance-and-coinbase/ar-AA1cyfwW">all crypto exchanges</a> in the world turn their backs on altcoins entirely and focus purely on bitcoin trading for their customers. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Eventually, I have confidence that the crypto exchanges will come around to realizing that bitcoin really is the dominant asset in this space, and their business models are fine when bitcoin goes up by a factor of ten.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-sec-lawsuits-are-paving-the-way-to-btc-dominance/">Michael Saylor: SEC Lawsuits Are Paving the Way for BTC Dominance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Robert Kennedy Jr. Believes Bitcoin and Blockchain Will Be Extremely &#8220;Useful&#8221;</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/robert-kennedy-jr-says-bitcoin-and-blockchain-will-be-extremely-useful/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 15:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robert Kennedy Jr.]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78803</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Democrat presidential candidate Robert Kennedy Jr. commented in an interview that he thinks bitcoin and blockchain will be very “useful” applications. Robert Kennedy Believes in the Power of Bitcoin He stated: The blockchain technology that’s coming out of bitcoin will be very useful. He was also quick to praise Elon Musk – the South African [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/robert-kennedy-jr-says-bitcoin-and-blockchain-will-be-extremely-useful/">Robert Kennedy Jr. Believes Bitcoin and Blockchain Will Be Extremely &#8220;Useful&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Democrat presidential candidate Robert Kennedy Jr. <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/robert-kennedy-jr-says-bitcoin-will-be-very-useful-praises-elon-musk-jack-dorsey-as-very-good-allies/ar-AA1cx8KY">commented in an interview</a> that he thinks bitcoin and blockchain will be very “useful” applications.</p>
<h2>Robert Kennedy Believes in the Power of Bitcoin</h2>
<p>He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>The blockchain technology that’s coming out of bitcoin will be very useful.</p></blockquote>
<p>He was also quick to praise Elon Musk – the South African billionaire behind mega companies like Tesla and SpaceX – and Jack Dorsey, the former CEO of Twitter. Continuing his discussion, Kennedy said he really admired Musk’s decision to purchase Twitter and pave the way for free speech (once again) in America. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>I find Musk and Dorsey incredibly patriotic and committed to democracy. [Musk] lost billions of dollars, but he stated that it’s worth every penny that I lose, because we need free speech in America. If we don’t have free speech in America, we don’t have democracy in America, and if we don’t have democracy in America, it’s the end of the world.</p></blockquote>
<p>He further mentioned that both men will be “good allies for him,” and that he looks forward to working with both figures to potentially improve the democratic landscape in the United States and keep America as it was prior to the far-left politics that have taken it over. Lastly, he bashed the media in the country and said it is no longer an industry designed to deliver news and keep people knowledgeable.</p>
<p>Rather, most media platforms are controlled by the far left and used instead as “instruments of totalitarian control.” He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Figuring out how to make censorship-proof social media sites… they’re doing that with Nostr.</p></blockquote>
<p>Kennedy is very big on bitcoin, saying that if he becomes president, he will ensure the U.S. government has no hand in crypto investing matters and that nothing ever blocks people from engaging in digital asset trading. Not long ago, he <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-hopeful-robert-kennedy-jr-appeared-at-this-years-miami-btc-conference/">made an appearance</a> at the Miami Bitcoin Conference and said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Monetary freedom is as important as freedom of speech. Without it, we are slaves. It’s not outlandish to imagine that even here in America, your bank account could one day be frozen because of your politics or comments you’ve made on social media.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Accepting the Asset for His Campaign</h2>
<p>He later stated that his campaign would be one of the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-candidate-robert-kennedy-jr-has-big-plans-for-the-crypto-space/">first to accept bitcoin</a> and crypto donations via the Lightning Network. He told his audience:</p>
<blockquote><p>Our campaign will be the first presidential campaign in history to accept bitcoin donations through the Lightning Network, and today, we move one step closer to the future. Today, we show the world the power, durability, and flexibility of bitcoin… You should be able to own your private keys the same as you own the keys to your car or your wallet… I don&#8217;t think the government has the right to demand access to your bitcoin key or… any of your passwords.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/robert-kennedy-jr-says-bitcoin-and-blockchain-will-be-extremely-useful/">Robert Kennedy Jr. Believes Bitcoin and Blockchain Will Be Extremely &#8220;Useful&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kevin O&#8217;Leary: It&#8217;s Time for Coinbase to Get a New CEO</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kevin-oleary-its-time-for-coinbase-to-get-a-new-ceo/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 13:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kevin O'Leary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78801</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Kevin O’Leary – a wealthy investor and the star of the show “Shark Tank” – says it’s time for the current CEO of Coinbase, Brian Armstrong, to be fired, and that a new CEO that will work hand in hand with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) should be brought aboard. Kevin O&#8217;Leary on the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kevin-oleary-its-time-for-coinbase-to-get-a-new-ceo/">Kevin O&#8217;Leary: It&#8217;s Time for Coinbase to Get a New CEO</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Kevin O’Leary – a wealthy investor and the star of the show “Shark Tank” – says it’s <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/coinbase-needs-new-ceo-after-sec-fail-kevin-oleary/ar-AA1cjguQ">time for the current</a> CEO of Coinbase, Brian Armstrong, to be fired, and that a new CEO that will work hand in hand with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) should be brought aboard.</p>
<h2>Kevin O&#8217;Leary on the Coinbase Lawsuit</h2>
<p>Not long ago, the SEC announced <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-hit-with-sec-lawsuit-says-it-operated-as-an-exchange-broker/">plans to sue Coinbase</a>, claiming it was operating as an unregistered broker. O’Leary believes it’s time to take Armstrong “behind the barn” and find someone new. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Find a new CEO that will go to SEC chairperson Gary Gensler and say, ‘You win. Let’s regulate this and call it a security.’ The move would provide Coinbase with a trillion dollars’ worth of assets for an allocation of just three percent. It is sovereign wealth.</p></blockquote>
<p>While what O’Leary suggests sounds simple enough, the situation is quite complicated, and O’Leary doesn’t seem to be taking several things into account. The first is that executives of Coinbase claim to have met with representatives of the SEC several times over a nine-year period to make sure their company followed present rules. They took issue with <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/">the Wells notice</a> they received back in April because of this, saying they had done all they could to ensure the firm was compliant.</p>
<p>Also, O’Leary appears to be suggesting that Coinbase simply “give in” to the present antics of the SEC. As we have commented in past articles, the SEC is behaving very much like a schoolyard bully. It has an attitude of, “Submit to me, or I’ll make your life a living hell.” As anybody who went to junior high knows (in other words, pretty much every person out there), you never ever give in to a bully because once you do, the abuse won’t stop.</p>
<p>The best way to deal with a bully is to stand up and fight back. It may not be comfortable, but it’s the quickest and shortest way to get a bully off your back and let them know that you can’t be messed with.</p>
<h2>You Must Always Fight Your Bullies</h2>
<p>O’Leary’s methodology is that Coinbase should try working directly with the SEC, but it’s likely he doesn’t understand that this option is not probable. You don’t try to reason with a bully; you just punch him in the face and let him know you’re tougher than you look. O’Leary continued with:</p>
<blockquote><p>Coinbase has lost 70 percent of its market cap since the initial public offering (IPO). The cryptocurrency industry has been stymied for three years and will never get capital appreciation until an institution can invest. After speaking with Sovereign Wealth and other institutions in the last 48 hours, they say this asset class is radioactive waste. We are not going to touch this.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kevin-oleary-its-time-for-coinbase-to-get-a-new-ceo/">Kevin O&#8217;Leary: It&#8217;s Time for Coinbase to Get a New CEO</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Depot Sues Texas Sheriff&#8217;s Office, Alleges Wrongful Money Seizure</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-depot-engages-in-legal-fight-against-texas-sheriffs-office/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 17:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ATMs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Depot]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lux Vending]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[McLennan County]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78791</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An 82-year-old woman in the city of Crawford, Texas has lost $15,000 to crypto scammers. The good news is that she’s gotten her money back, but the incident has sparked a serious feud between the McLennan County Sheriff’s Office and Lux Vending (operating as Bitcoin Depot), the crypto ATM company that served as the medium [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-depot-engages-in-legal-fight-against-texas-sheriffs-office/">Bitcoin Depot Sues Texas Sheriff&#8217;s Office, Alleges Wrongful Money Seizure</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An 82-year-old woman in the city of Crawford, Texas has lost $15,000 to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/crypto-scammer/">crypto scammers</a>. The good news is that she’s gotten her money back, but the <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/elderly-woman-scammed-into-converting-15k-into-bitcoin-sparks-legal-battle-between-crypto-kiosk-manager-mclennan-county-sheriff-s-office/ar-AA1cvntI">incident has sparked</a> a serious feud between the McLennan County Sheriff’s Office and Lux Vending (operating as Bitcoin Depot), the crypto ATM company that served as the medium of transfer for the potentially illicit activity.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Depot Says It&#8217;s the Victim</h2>
<p>The sheriff’s office wound up seizing cash from the machine and giving it back to the victimized person. While she’s walked away relatively unscathed from the incident, Bitcoin Depot isn’t happy about the decision made by law enforcement. It’s now suing the officers, claiming the money was wrongfully taken.</p>
<p>In a statement, Houston attorney John MacVane – who’s representing Lux Vending – explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>While the company is sympathetic to the victimized customer, as stated in the petition, the actions taken by the McLennan County Sheriff’s Office are unlawful and violate Bitcoin Depot’s rights under both the Texas and U.S. constitutions. Bitcoin Depot looks forward to making our arguments in court and seeking the return of our property.</p></blockquote>
<p>Parnell McNamara – a McLennan County sheriff – offered a rebuttal by saying that all his officers overseeing the situation did everything right and that the company can “go to hell.” Discussing the present lawsuit, he said:</p>
<blockquote><p>It’s a bunch of hogwash. As far as I am concerned, they are a bunch of vultures who want to take the money back from this person who has already been victimized. I think it is a real travesty. The money does not belong to them. It was scammed. It still belongs to the lady who put it in there, so I think it is preposterous that they have filed this lawsuit… but it will be a cold day in hell that they get this money back from our good citizen, who has already been scammed and traumatized.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Don&#8217;t Get in the Way!</h2>
<p>He also said that Bitcoin Depot did everything it could to prevent the officers from taking the machine. For example, when law enforcement agents arrived to serve a search warrant, an armored car – allegedly hired by the firm – was there to get in the way. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>While we were there with the search warrant, the armored car people came, and we served them with the search warrant. We were going to get in the machine one way or the other because we had a legal search warrant. The $15,000 she put in the machine was still in the wallet that she had put it in, so we retrieved that $15,000 and brought it back to the office. We photographed it, put it into evidence, and ultimately got it back to the victim so she wouldn’t be further traumatized by these creeps.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-depot-engages-in-legal-fight-against-texas-sheriffs-office/">Bitcoin Depot Sues Texas Sheriff&#8217;s Office, Alleges Wrongful Money Seizure</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mark Cuban Bashes the SEC for Its Actions Against Coinbase</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-bashes-the-sec-for-its-actions-against-coinbase/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 15:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mark Cuban]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78788</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Like most investors (and everyday Americans), billionaire Mark Cuban is not happy with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). In fact, he’s downright angry with the institution and says it’s abusing its power. Mark Cuban Targets the SEC in Twitter Slam In a recent interview, the owner of the Dallas Mavericks basketball team criticized the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-bashes-the-sec-for-its-actions-against-coinbase/">Mark Cuban Bashes the SEC for Its Actions Against Coinbase</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Like most investors (and everyday Americans), billionaire Mark Cuban is <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/mark-cuban-crypto-coinbase-sec-lawsuit-binance-regulation-enforcement-2023-6">not happy with the</a> Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). In fact, he’s downright angry with the institution and says it’s abusing its power.</p>
<h2>Mark Cuban Targets the SEC in Twitter Slam</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, the owner of the Dallas Mavericks basketball team criticized the agency’s decision to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-hit-with-sec-lawsuit-says-it-operated-as-an-exchange-broker/">go after Coinbase</a>, the biggest and most popular crypto exchange in the U.S. He says the SEC is doing nothing to help financial companies grow, nor is it helping to boost innovation. Instead of filing a lawsuit, he says the agency should have tried to help the company regulate itself and fall into compliance if it was disobeying present rules.</p>
<p>Cuban took to Twitter to accuse the SEC of not wanting to help crypto firms in any way, shape, or form. Rather, all it’s interested in doing is shutting the doors on them and preventing them from getting any further within America’s borders. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>They don&#8217;t want to help companies get to compliance. They want to challenge them to get to compliance. They are full of lawyers. Lawyers want to litigate.</p></blockquote>
<p>He further stated that the present Coinbase lawsuit – as well as the many other actions it’s taken over the past several weeks – is exactly why most people in the country don’t trust the agency or hold it in the brightest light. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>As it is, no one wants to talk to the SEC because no one trusts them for fear of being in the same situation as Coinbase finds itself.</p></blockquote>
<p>The SEC has long taken a road of regulation through enforcement. It hasn’t bothered to help carve out any rules or legislation pertaining to crypto agencies or new financial firms. Rather, it has an attitude of, “We’re coming after you because we think you’re smaller and weaker.” It behaves very much like a schoolyard bully and tries to pick on people rather than reason with them or get to know them better.</p>
<p>Aside from Coinbase, the SEC shocked the world a few weeks back when it announced it was charging crypto exchange platform Binance <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sues-binance-alleges-selling-of-illegal-securities/">with several crimes</a> including selling and offering unregistered securities and mixing customer and company funds. In addition, the company also went after Kraken, a popular crypto exchange in Northern California.</p>
<h2>So Many Companies Have Been Victimized</h2>
<p>Choosing to settle with the agency, Kraken <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/">was forced to part</a> with a $30 million penalty fee. It was also made to end all its staking activities and services.</p>
<p>As it turns out, the SEC’s actions are really starting to rub certain members of Congress the wrong way. Not long ago, House conservatives put <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/house-republicans-introduce-bill-to-remove-sec-chair-gary-gensler-restructure-agency/ar-AA1cs0X1">out a new bill that</a> if passed, would see the full restructuring of the SEC and the firing of Gary Gensler.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-bashes-the-sec-for-its-actions-against-coinbase/">Mark Cuban Bashes the SEC for Its Actions Against Coinbase</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will Blockchain Survive? Analysts Weigh In</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/will-blockchain-survive-analysts-weigh-in/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 13:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Luke Stokes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78786</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are bitcoin and blockchain considered practical technologies, or are they more based in fantasy? Recently, a group of analysts sat around and discussed the matter to see whether blockchain and the crypto aboard it have legitimate futures in the United States and other developed countries. What Will Happen with Blockchain? Up until this point, there [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/will-blockchain-survive-analysts-weigh-in/">Will Blockchain Survive? Analysts Weigh In</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are bitcoin and blockchain considered practical technologies, or are they more based in fantasy? Recently, a group of <a href="https://www.thestreet.com/cryptocurrency/bitcoin-and-blockchain-seeking-the-ultimate-utopia-or-a-practical-utility">analysts sat around and</a> discussed the matter to see whether blockchain and the crypto aboard it have legitimate futures in the United States and other developed countries.</p>
<h2>What Will Happen with Blockchain?</h2>
<p>Up until this point, there have been discussions about blockchain and how it could potentially serve purposes in other industries that have nothing to do with crypto or digital assets. Some of these industries include healthcare, manufacturing, and recently (as we discussed yesterday) <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/itoka-is-looking-to-register-all-ai-music-on-the-blockchain/">AI music creation</a>.</p>
<p>However, these ideas have not really been tested that much considering for the most part, blockchain is still predominantly considered the technology behind crypto assets like bitcoin. These assets have done a lot, but they are still considered part of a niche industry, and blockchain has had a very difficult time breaking out of the shackles the crypto industry has placed on its wrists.</p>
<p>For this reason, there are many experts out there that don’t believe blockchain has much of a future, though there are others that continue to advocate for it and say it’s the technology of all technologies. So, which sentiment is correct? The discussion mentioned above was hosted by Rob Nelson. As the anchor of the roundtable, he commented that bitcoin is very “utopian,” and while the ideals behind blockchain may be noble in intent, enacting them would be extremely difficult. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin&#8217;s ultimate thing was sovereignty&#8230; It&#8217;s very utopian, and one of the problems with utopianism is it&#8217;s very hard to see it enacted&#8230; Bitcoin is consensus-based, which creates a huge problem.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also said that there wasn’t much that could be considered special about bitcoin, and he said it’s about as revolutionary as Gmail. In the end, he doesn’t think BTC has much practical use, and for this reason, he doesn’t see it going far.</p>
<p>Luke Stokes – managing director at the Foundation for Inter Wallet Operability – was quick to oppose his words and challenge him on the subject. He stated that a “killer app” would be needed for blockchain to truly come full circle and be seen as the awesome technology it is. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>We know we&#8217;ve never had the ability to have network and data completely consensus across the whole world. Everyone agrees, but we just don&#8217;t really know what to do with it yet&#8230; We&#8217;re still waiting for that to happen.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Keeping the Middle Ground</h2>
<p>Max Smotritskiy – co-founder of Crypto Oracle – believes that while blockchain is indeed strong, it needs to be made stronger. In other words, there’s a lot of work to be done before it can accomplish all that everyone’s promising it will. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I&#8217;m not for hyper blockchainization of anything.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/will-blockchain-survive-analysts-weigh-in/">Will Blockchain Survive? Analysts Weigh In</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
