<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 18:50:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/cropped-fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>PayPal Steps Away from Palestine; Is Bitcoin the Answer?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paypal-steps-away-from-palestine-is-bitcoin-the-answer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 17:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Palestine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78918</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin is getting very popular in Palestine and particularly in the Gaza Strip, the big reason being that PayPal has decided not to offer its services in this corner of the world. Palestine and BTC Get Close as PayPal Drives Away The reason PayPal isn’t setting foot in Palestine is because of the alleged dangers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paypal-steps-away-from-palestine-is-bitcoin-the-answer/">PayPal Steps Away from Palestine; Is Bitcoin the Answer?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin is getting very popular in Palestine and <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/06/23/why-bitcoin-cant-replace-paypal-in-palestine/?sh=79ef60c9db4c">particularly in the Gaza Strip</a>, the big reason being that PayPal has decided not to offer its services in this corner of the world.</p>
<h2>Palestine and BTC Get Close as PayPal Drives Away</h2>
<p>The reason <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/paypal/">PayPal</a> isn’t setting foot in Palestine is because of the alleged dangers that stem from endless conflict with its geographic neighbor Israel. At least 12 congressmen, at the time of writing, have signed a proposal supporting the financial company’s decision, which is now being enforced by its CEO Dan Schulman. The proposal they’ve signed reads as follows:</p>
<blockquote><p>PayPal has a responsibility to ensure its services and operations are provided in a non-discriminatory manner and in accordance with the United Nations Guiding Principles on Business and Human Rights.</p></blockquote>
<p>Without PayPal, the people of Palestine have had to find other ways of getting the items they need to survive… The goods and services necessary for everyday life. As a result, many have turned to bitcoin.</p>
<p>One of those people – Fadi Elsalameen – is a Palestinian activist and adjunct senior fellow at the Bitcoin Policy Institute. In an interview, Elsalameen commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>I stopped sending wires to Palestine and now only make payments with bitcoin. Bitcoin solves issues of high banking or transfer fees, or extreme and invasive government overreach and unfair treatment of Palestinians by international monetary organizations as in the case of PayPal.</p></blockquote>
<p>Eric Sype of 7amleh – a digital rights group in Palestine – shares this ideology. He believes PayPal has become extremely frustrating over the years, and that bitcoin’s popularity is growing thanks to the simplicity and levels of trust that surround it. He commented that while there are several individuals who are still skeptical of using bitcoin as a method of payment, tensions are easing slowly. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The vast majority of online freelance service providers exclusively use PayPal, so that cuts off many freelance opportunities for Palestinians.</p></blockquote>
<p>This is just another example of bitcoin’s original usage intent coming into play. Initially, when first created, bitcoin was designed as a payment tool. Something that could potentially replace all fiat currencies, checks, and credit cards down the line. However, its volatility has gotten in the way.</p>
<p>Thus, there are several companies out there that refuse to accept BTC as a payment method because they could wind up losing money, and there are still many people who don’t think to use it considering its lack of mainstream appeal.</p>
<h2>Making Things Easier</h2>
<p>Elsalameen, however, has hope that all this is going to change, and he says the opportunities that arise through bitcoin payment options are endless. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>I reach the account of those I need to send bitcoin to without anyone weaponizing my transactions against me. Today, I can even buy art in Palestine with bitcoin.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paypal-steps-away-from-palestine-is-bitcoin-the-answer/">PayPal Steps Away from Palestine; Is Bitcoin the Answer?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cameron Winklevoss: Buy BTC Now Before It Explodes</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cameron-winklevoss-buy-btc-now-before-it-explodes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 15:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cameron Winklevoss]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETF]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78916</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cameron Winklevoss – one half of the Winklevoss Twins who run the Gemini crypto exchange in New York – is confident bitcoin is about to burst out of its shell and reach a new bullish peak nobody is prepared for. Cameron Winklevoss on the Future of BTC&#8217;s Price At the end of June, the price [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cameron-winklevoss-buy-btc-now-before-it-explodes/">Cameron Winklevoss: Buy BTC Now Before It Explodes</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cameron Winklevoss – one half of the Winklevoss Twins who run the Gemini crypto exchange in New York – is confident bitcoin is <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/06/23/open-the-floodgates-crypto-billionaire-warns-the-window-is-closing-fast-amid-100-billion-bitcoin-and-ethereum-price-boom/?sh=650f482f1eef">about to burst out of</a> its shell and reach a new bullish peak nobody is prepared for.</p>
<h2>Cameron Winklevoss on the Future of BTC&#8217;s Price</h2>
<p>At the end of June, the price of bitcoin rose beyond $31,000. This is the highest bitcoin’s been all year, and certainly higher than where it was for most of 2022, arguably the most bearish period on record for the world’s number one digital currency by market cap. Cameron Winklevoss believes that if people are going to take advantage of bitcoin still being somewhat low, they need to get involved now. Otherwise, they’re going to be paying a lot more for units. In an interview, he commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>The great accumulation of bitcoin has begun. Anyone watching the flurry of ETF filings understands the window to purchase pre-IPO bitcoin before ETFs go live and open the floodgates is closing fast.</p></blockquote>
<p>The warning comes after BlackRock – one of the biggest financial investment companies in the world – announced it was planning to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blackrock-etf-application-causes-btc-eth-to-surge/">submit a bitcoin-based</a> exchange-traded fund (ETF) application to the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The news came as a surprise to many people for several reasons, a big one being that in the long run, BlackRock is considered a traditional finance company, and many of these institutions won’t go anywhere near crypto.</p>
<p>Another big reason is that the SEC is going after several crypto companies right now, huge ones like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sues-binance-alleges-selling-of-illegal-securities/">Binance</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-hit-with-sec-lawsuit-says-it-operated-as-an-exchange-broker/">Coinbase</a>. It’s become clear that the SEC doesn’t care who gets victimized so long as it can follow through on its agenda of eliminating crypto from America and having complete control.</p>
<p>However, many believe that BlackRock may pave the way for a bitcoin-based ETF (<a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-delays-its-decisions-on-several-btc-etfs/">something the SEC has</a> long rejected) thanks to its high-ranking record with the financial agency. Thus far, BlackRock has enjoyed over 500 accepted proposals with the SEC and only one rejection.</p>
<h2>This New ETF Could Really Pave the Way</h2>
<p>Markus Thielen – head of research at Matrix Port – was quick to agree with Cameron Winklevoss and believes the bulls may return sooner than investors think. Discussing the new ETF, he commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>While crypto still needs more than favorable macroeconomic tailwinds and institutional inflows into bitcoin, this is a welcoming development that reminds investors that crypto is here to stay. We can imagine that this BlackRock iShares &#8216;commodity&#8217; bitcoin ETF will attract an allocation in the range of around $20 billion to $50 billion over time as ETFs that are focusing on gold alone hold around $100 billion. This BlackRock announcement has a high probability of being approved by the SEC and will drive continuous adoption from institutional investors for bitcoin.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cameron-winklevoss-buy-btc-now-before-it-explodes/">Cameron Winklevoss: Buy BTC Now Before It Explodes</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>El Salvador Continues to Make Big Bitcoin Waves</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-continues-to-make-big-bitcoin-waves/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 13:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[El Salvador]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fold]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78909</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>El Salvador is really gaining traction as a leading bitcoin haven. El Salvador was Smart to Implement Bitcoin Not long ago, professional surfer Kelly Slater commented on social media: The government has really put an emphasis on surfing (and bitcoin). A crypto winter and bear market were both responsible for bitcoin shedding quite a bit [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-continues-to-make-big-bitcoin-waves/">El Salvador Continues to Make Big Bitcoin Waves</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>El Salvador is really gaining traction as a leading bitcoin haven.</p>
<h2>El Salvador was Smart to Implement Bitcoin</h2>
<p>Not long ago, professional surfer Kelly Slater commented on social media:</p>
<blockquote><p>The government has really put an emphasis on surfing (and bitcoin).</p></blockquote>
<p>A crypto winter and bear market were both responsible for bitcoin shedding quite a bit of value in 2022, and while we’re not entirely out of the woods yet, El Salvador continues to <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/06/21/emphasis-on-surf-and-bitcoin-attracts-investments-to-el-salvador/?sh=2c37c76671dc">gain a lot of talent</a> and business in terms of bitcoin companies that want to make the Central American nation the land of their homes.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/el-salvador/">El Salvador</a> has made a partner out of Fold, for example, a bitcoin rewards app. That company is now working hand in hand with Visa to help boost crypto payment options throughout Central and South America. Will Reeves, the CEO of Fold, explained in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>El Salvador really was the shining option for us there. There was no second-best option. Bukele has announced and implemented some very serious benefits to entities operating out of El Salvador. Not only protections, but incentives that are almost unmatched and especially unmatched in North America, Central America, and South America.</p></blockquote>
<p>U.S. ambassador to El Salvador Milena Mayorga also threw her two cents into the mix, claiming that the notions of bitcoin have attracted huge investments into the country thanks to the fact that crypto is now getting integrated into the nation’s politics.</p>
<p>For example, in April of this year, a new law was developed for crypto and tech companies. These businesses become exempt from both income and capital gains taxes for 15 years granted they invest funds into the nation’s infrastructure. Mayorga said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Every day, companies are calling us here at the embassy to ask us how they can transfer their operations. We try to get rid of the bureaucracy. We try to accompany them in different meetings, according to the needs of each company.</p></blockquote>
<p>Stacy Herbert – an advisor with Bitcoin Office – further mentioned that forming crypto companies in nations like El Salvador is quite easy, and the group is considering setting up shop there as a means of avoiding all the red tape and other troubles that come with the current U.S. landscape. She stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Company formation is also a lot easier now, as is the process of returning or moving to El Salvador with the removal of red tape and taxes.</p></blockquote>
<h2>So Many People Want to Move There</h2>
<p>According to Mayorga, several Americans are also looking to make their homes in the nation she represents. She says the country can offer them a lot of benefits and mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Many North Americans are asking for Salvadoran citizenship, and it&#8217;s one of the greatest interests worldwide. How can they obtain a residence or citizenship; how can they become Salvadoran.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-continues-to-make-big-bitcoin-waves/">El Salvador Continues to Make Big Bitcoin Waves</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Denmark Territory Issues New Blockchain Stamps Commemorating Nature</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/denmark-territory-issues-new-blockchain-stamps-commemorating-nature/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 17:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Faroe Islands]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stamps]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78905</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Faroe Islands, which are part of the Kingdom of Denmark, have been issuing postage stamps for close to 50 years, but the island chain is now embracing blockchain and adding a little crypto to its postal mix. Crypto Stamps Are Now Available Known as the “Stamps of Maybe,” a stamp collection being issued by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/denmark-territory-issues-new-blockchain-stamps-commemorating-nature/">Denmark Territory Issues New Blockchain Stamps Commemorating Nature</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Faroe Islands, which are part of the Kingdom of Denmark, have been issuing postage stamps for close to 50 years, but the island chain is <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/zengernews/2023/06/22/faroe-islands-historic-postal-service-embraces-blockchain-with-weather-influenced-crypto-stamps/?sh=6a286c5c3e5a">now embracing blockchain</a> and adding a little crypto to its postal mix.</p>
<h2>Crypto Stamps Are Now Available</h2>
<p>Known as the “Stamps of Maybe,” a stamp collection being issued by the Faroe Islands is entirely digital and being released through a partnership with crypto firm Varius Systems. The stamps are unique in that not only are they considered collectible forms of art, but they also aid in the tracking of packages and other items. They’re designed by artist Heiðrik á Heygum, and they’ve been decorated with images of animals, plant life, and seasons.</p>
<p>Discussing his influence for the stamps and what he was trying to accomplish, Heygum said in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Each stamp features its own distinctive bouquet, carefully crafted to encompass the flowers, plants, birds, and animals that symbolize the essence of each season on our islands. The Faroese people have always shared a deep connection with nature and its abundant resources, which is why many of these flowers and animals have become national symbols in our music and art. In fact, our traditional national costume proudly showcases embroidered representations of these flowers, often on black or dark tones of fabric. Through these crypto stamps, I aimed to infuse the technological world with the rich tapestry of Faroese culture, uniting tradition and innovation in a visually captivating manner. It is my hope that these stamps will not only serve as a means of postage, but also as a testament to the profound connection we share with our environment and our commitment to preserving our unique traditions for generations to come.</p></blockquote>
<p>Varius Systems hasn’t always been a crypto or blockchain-themed company, but it’s always been a technology innovator. Started in the 1970s by Frank Dorner, the company is now run by his son Michael, and they take pride in the fact that Varius is family owned. Michael commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>After meeting with several leaders of postal companies around the world at the Universal Postal Union from the United Nations summit in Frankfurt earlier this week, we felt an enormous interest not only in the NFT stamps, but in blockchain technology as such. Countries from all around the globe, from Iceland to Togo, from Portugal to Singapore, are interested in how this digital revolution with decentralized blockchains can help their businesses grow and stay ahead of the curve.</p></blockquote>
<h2>They&#8217;re Like NFTs</h2>
<p>The stamps, in many ways, are like non-fungible tokens (NFTs), which have seen their popularity decrease heavily over the past 15 months or so.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/nfts/">NFTs</a> are still relatively new, having first come to the crypto scene in 2020, but interest really began sinking during the early days of last year’s crypto winter.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/denmark-territory-issues-new-blockchain-stamps-commemorating-nature/">Denmark Territory Issues New Blockchain Stamps Commemorating Nature</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trade Zing Co-Founder on How People Can Avoid Crypto Scams</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/trade-zing-co-founder-on-how-people-can-avoid-crypto-scams/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 15:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jordan Edelson]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Scams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trade Zing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78903</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Scams, scams, and more scams… Lately, it feels like all we really hear about anymore in the world of crypto are the number of scams that have been hitting the streets, but not too long ago, Roundtable anchor Rob Nelson hosted a meeting with Jordan Edelson, the co-founder of Trade Zing, and asked him what [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/trade-zing-co-founder-on-how-people-can-avoid-crypto-scams/">Trade Zing Co-Founder on How People Can Avoid Crypto Scams</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Scams, scams, and more <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/scams/">scams</a>… Lately, it feels like all we really hear about anymore in the world of crypto are the number of scams that have been hitting the streets, but not too long ago, Roundtable anchor Rob Nelson hosted a meeting with Jordan Edelson, the co-founder of Trade Zing, and asked him what <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/cryptocurrency-scams-unveiling-the-truth-with-trade-zing/ar-AA1cSkNl">people can do to prevent themselves</a> from falling victim to these ongoing issues.</p>
<h2>Trade Zing Works to Lessen Crypto Scams</h2>
<p>The event began with Nelson asking:</p>
<blockquote><p>People are hungry for information. Nobody knows what to believe anymore. There&#8217;s so much confusion about the difference between all these. How do you address that? What [are] your thoughts on addressing it and does your platform help address it?</p></blockquote>
<p>Responding, Edelson claimed that communities need to educate themselves. They need to ensure they have all the data necessary on hand to make proper decisions, and they need to check in on certain crypto investments before they get involved to make sure issuing companies have histories of transparency. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>The solution is really community and transparency, and that&#8217;s something that&#8217;s been missing. A lot of these current social networks and platforms out there were never built ground up for financial information. Because of that, a lot of people are taking advantage of the weaknesses of these platforms.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also mentioned that while crypto scams appear largely aimed at individual investors and traders, he said they do the most damage to the crypto arena in general, and that many companies are also largely affected. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>When you have these types of scams and these issues and problems, it hurts it across the board. I think adding a layer of transparency is the way to grow future tokens and digital assets and bring back truth to the sector.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Knowing the Differences Between Good and Crap Coins</h2>
<p>Lastly, he said Trade Zing is always about making sure people have what they need to make informed decisions. Trade Zing has worked hard to ensure it remains an integral part of the crypto space, and its morality is always at the highest points. He also said it’s striving to separate the good coins from the bad:</p>
<blockquote><p>We&#8217;re still kind of in that vetting process. We&#8217;re also kind of in a time right now of consolidation, where you&#8217;re seeing different projects consolidate, and ultimately, the best breed starts to bubble up to the top. Trade Zing, as a platform, is going to highlight a lot of that, amplify the messaging around it, allow a lot of that, as well as highlight the bad as well because it&#8217;s just important to be educated on the bad and the good. This way, people are properly educated about the risk involved when they get involved in these different types of assets.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/trade-zing-co-founder-on-how-people-can-avoid-crypto-scams/">Trade Zing Co-Founder on How People Can Avoid Crypto Scams</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlackRock ETF Application Caused BTC, ETH to Surge</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blackrock-etf-application-causes-btc-eth-to-surge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 13:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78901</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin and Ethereum – the world’s largest cryptocurrencies by market cap – rose to new levels in late June following several weeks of traveling through the doldrums, and the moves appear to stem from some new bitcoin-based exchange-traded fund (ETF) applications from two of the largest financial companies around: Wisdom Tree and BlackRock. BlackRock Does [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blackrock-etf-application-causes-btc-eth-to-surge/">BlackRock ETF Application Caused BTC, ETH to Surge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin and Ethereum – the world’s largest cryptocurrencies by market cap – <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/06/32966846/the-great-accumulation-of-bitcoin-etf-filings-signal-a-new-era-for-crypto-investment-say-e">rose to new levels in late</a> June following several weeks of traveling through the doldrums, and the moves appear to stem from some new bitcoin-based exchange-traded fund (ETF) applications from two of the largest financial companies around: Wisdom Tree and BlackRock.</p>
<h2>BlackRock Does Big Things for BTC</h2>
<p>Both bitcoin and Ethereum weren’t doing so hot throughout the month of June prior to this news. The assets were slipping a bit more each week, largely due to headlines that both <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sues-binance-alleges-selling-of-illegal-securities/">Binance</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-hit-with-sec-lawsuit-says-it-operated-as-an-exchange-broker/">Coinbase</a> were being sued by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). It got to the point where bitcoin, briefly, fell into the $24K range, while Ethereum itself wasn’t doing much better. Then, suddenly, the tables really turned.</p>
<p>Cameron Winklevoss – one half of the Winklevoss Twins, which run the popular Gemini crypto exchange in New York – was quick to comment on the situations surrounding the two ETFs from both BlackRock and WisdomTree. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Anyone watching the flurry of ETF filings understands the window to purchase pre-IPO bitcoin before ETFs go live and open the floodgates is closing fast. If bitcoin was the most obvious and best investment of the previous decade, this will likely be the most obvious and best trade of this decade.</p></blockquote>
<p>Michael Saylor – the former CEO of software giant and major BTC institution MicroStrategy – was also there to throw his two cents into the mix, stating:</p>
<blockquote><p>The window to front-run institutional demand for bitcoin is closing.</p></blockquote>
<p>Among the sentiments that are stemming from the news around the ETFs is that BlackRock, at least, has a chance of getting its application supported and approved by the SEC given how close it’s been with the federal financial agency. The company has had more than 500 applications approved by the SEC. To this day, it only has one rejection on its record.</p>
<p>What’s also interesting about the BlackRock application is that Coinbase – a company now getting sued by the SEC – is listed as the custody partner of the company. What this could potentially do regarding the lawsuit the agency has against the exchange remains a mystery, but it should at least throw a monkey wrench (albeit a small one) into the mix.</p>
<h2>A Huge Step Forward?</h2>
<p>The news of the price surges surrounding bitcoin and Ethereum is a huge and welcome change from what we’ve been seeing in recent days, and especially from where both assets were last year. During 2022, arguably the worst period on record for the world’s biggest cryptocurrency, the digital asset fell from about $68,000, it’s new all-time high (which it achieved in November of 2021), to around $16,600, thus constituting a near 70 percent fall from grace.</p>
<p>Ethereum and several leading altcoins were quick to follow in BTC’s footsteps.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blackrock-etf-application-causes-btc-eth-to-surge/">BlackRock ETF Application Caused BTC, ETH to Surge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Casa Bitcoin Wallet Will Now Also Hold Ethereum</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/casa-bitcoin-wallet-will-now-also-hold-ethereum/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 17:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Wallet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Casa]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[self-custody]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78888</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin wallet provider Casa has unveiled Ethereum vaults, which are designed to give Ethereum fans and holders more secure options for keeping control of their money. Casa Says &#8220;Yes&#8221; to Housing Ethereum There’s a common theme in the digital currency world. The theme is, “Not your keys, not your coins.” The statement refers to custody [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/casa-bitcoin-wallet-will-now-also-hold-ethereum/">Casa Bitcoin Wallet Will Now Also Hold Ethereum</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin wallet provider Casa has unveiled Ethereum vaults, which are designed to give Ethereum fans and holders <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-startup-casa-expands-beyond-160044845.html">more secure options for</a> keeping control of their money.</p>
<h2>Casa Says &#8220;Yes&#8221; to Housing Ethereum</h2>
<p>There’s a common theme in the digital currency world. The theme is, “Not your keys, not your coins.” The statement refers to custody practices and third parties in which custody responsibilities are trusted to figures or companies that are not the actual owners of the tokens in question. For this reason, it doesn’t matter how many units of crypto you put in your wallet. If custody is taken over by someone (or something) else, you’re not in control, and your coins could disappear whenever the company is in trouble.</p>
<p>Initially, Casa was only created for bitcoin holders. If you had bitcoin in your stash, Casa would house it for you, but now, the company is opening its doors to Ethereum, the second largest crypto by market cap and the number one competitor to bitcoin.</p>
<p>The firm is also building itself out as a self-custody outlet. In other words, while the crypto one holds can be done through a wallet provided by the firm, final ownership truly lies with whoever garnered the coins in the first place, and Casa allegedly prides itself on the fact that all its customers fully control their coins and aren’t required to forfeit their custody abilities. CEO Nick Neuman explained in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Self-custody places the control and responsibility back into the hands of the users, eliminating the risk that people’s assets will be frozen, misused, or stolen when things go wrong at an exchange. We believe that reducing reliance on third parties by taking self-custody and holding your private keys is the future of money management.</p></blockquote>
<p>Since self-custody is an entirely new route for Casa customers, the company has created new education modules to help them understand how the protocols work and what they can do to boost the safety of their coins. Neuman said one of the quickest and easiest windows to self-custody is through the company’s new app. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Our app gives Casa members a clear view of their key health and guides them through replacing a key if it is lost or stolen. It’s no more complicated than interfacing with any regular banking app, and we’re here to offer support and guidance at every step.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Making the Network Faster</h2>
<p>Ethereum is arguably becoming as big as bitcoin. The asset has already gone through two major upgrades over the last 11 months (the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/merge/">Merge</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/shapella/">Shapella</a>) that have shifted the asset over to a proof of stake module over proof of work, which it had followed since its inception.</p>
<p>Proof of stake has permitted Ethereum to move faster and lessen its gas fees.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/casa-bitcoin-wallet-will-now-also-hold-ethereum/">Casa Bitcoin Wallet Will Now Also Hold Ethereum</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vilonia, Arkansas Could Soon Be Home to a New Chinese Crypto Mining Facility</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vilonia-arkansas-could-soon-be-home-to-a-new-china-crypto-mining-facility/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 15:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[china]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vilonia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78884</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A China-owned crypto mining facility could be built in the rural town of Vilonia, Arkansas, and the residents aren’t too happy about that. Will Vilonia Be a New Crypto Mining Hub? What’s odd is that the mining facility is controlled and owned by China, a country that not long ago decided crypto mining should be [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vilonia-arkansas-could-soon-be-home-to-a-new-china-crypto-mining-facility/">Vilonia, Arkansas Could Soon Be Home to a New Chinese Crypto Mining Facility</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A China-owned crypto mining <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/chinese-owned-cryptocurrency-mining-facility-planned-in-vilonia-opposed-by-townsfolk-local-government-officials/ar-AA1cOROK">facility could be built</a> in the rural town of Vilonia, Arkansas, and the residents aren’t too happy about that.</p>
<h2>Will Vilonia Be a New Crypto Mining Hub?</h2>
<p>What’s odd is that the mining facility is controlled and owned by China, a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-crypto-mining-clampdown-in-china-is-not-over/">country that not long</a> ago decided crypto mining should be illegal due to the alleged harm it does to the atmosphere. The country announced that due to new “green” rules implemented by Beijing, all crypto mining was outlawed on Chinese lands, and miners were either going to have to close or find new places to run their businesses.</p>
<p>This shows a clear lack of regard for the U.S. Basically, China thinks mining is bad for its own air, but ours can get poisoned and destroyed? That’s basically what the nation is saying… Mining is okay so long as it doesn’t occur within its own borders.</p>
<p>Gladys Anderson is currently living in a city called Bono in Arkansas. She says there’s been a crypto mining facility near her home for a while now, and it’s caused plenty of problems for her and her family. In an interview, she stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>It&#8217;s caused a lot of headaches&#8230;I&#8217;ve been to the doctor over headaches. My son is currently in the backyard having a meltdown… They&#8217;re not going to tell you the truth. They&#8217;re not going to do what they say they&#8217;re going to do.</p></blockquote>
<p>Vilonia councilman Mike Matos stated that the high level of energy use is a big concern for him. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>It was discussed in a planning meeting that they were going to be using the equivalent of 30 schools worth of power, and one of the questions posed was, &#8216;What happens if another investor wants to come to our city and our power grid needs to be upgraded because of the massive amount of energy this thing is using?’</p></blockquote>
<p>Vilonia mayor Preston Scroggins also isn’t a big fan of what’s happening. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think foreign ownership of farmland and stuff is&#8230;at least the federal government and I understand the state government did something good. They passed a bill banning that. I wish we could do more here in our country.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Paving Space for the Business</h2>
<p>The mine hasn’t been fully approved yet, but it could potentially go through thanks to what’s known as Act 851 in Vilonia, which states:</p>
<blockquote><p>Data centers create jobs, pay taxes, and provide general economic value to local communities and this state… [The] local government shall not enact or adopt an ordinance, policy, or action that limits the sound decibels generated from home digital asset mining other than the limits set for sound pollution generally, [or] impose a different requirement for a digital asset mining business than is applicable to any requirement for a data center.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vilonia-arkansas-could-soon-be-home-to-a-new-china-crypto-mining-facility/">Vilonia, Arkansas Could Soon Be Home to a New Chinese Crypto Mining Facility</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Law Enforcement Leader on the Current State of Digital Assets</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-law-enforcement-head-on-the-current-state-of-digital-assets/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 13:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jareck Jakubcek]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78881</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance is getting a lot of heat from the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and related agencies. Not long ago, Jareck Jakubcek – the head of law enforcement at Binance APAC – sat down for an interview to explain the regulatory issues surrounding crypto and to explain that digital assets aren’t immune to criminal activity. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-law-enforcement-head-on-the-current-state-of-digital-assets/">Binance Law Enforcement Leader on the Current State of Digital Assets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance is <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sues-binance-alleges-selling-of-illegal-securities/">getting a lot of heat</a> from the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and related agencies. Not long ago, Jareck Jakubcek – the head of law enforcement at Binance APAC – <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-in/money/topstories/not-pretending-cryptocurrency-is-immune-to-criminal-activities-binance-head-of-law-enforcement-on-crypto-regulations/ar-AA1cJsbD">sat down for an</a> interview to explain the regulatory issues surrounding crypto and to explain that digital assets aren’t immune to criminal activity.</p>
<h2>What&#8217;s Going on with Binance?</h2>
<p>He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>At Binance, we welcome opportunities to actively engage with regulators, and we support clearer rules of the game, clearer regulations. We believe that there [must] be a set of defined rules by which cryptocurrencies [must] behave. So, having a regulatory framework is a step in the positive direction.</p></blockquote>
<p>Jakubcek, who conducts his work in India, says his country has set up clear steps to ensure the birth of regulation that’s clear and efficient. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>We do support criminal investigations in India and other jurisdictions. So far, we have had a very positive experience supporting the Enforcement Directorate in India, its investigations, as well as working with other law enforcement agencies in the country. An example of such a practical cooperation would be our support [for] the E-Nuggets investigation. During this investigation, we have provided extensive support to the ED that too often, under very short deadlines, allowed identification of the suspects and ultimately led to a substantial seizure of funds.</p></blockquote>
<p>Right now, Binance is facing several criminal charges from the SEC, which claims the exchange ignored securities laws and that it commingled investor funds with company funds. Gary Gensler – the head of the SEC – was also quick to dismiss any arguments that regulation is not clear in the U.S., and he said this is no excuse for companies like Binance to take chances or break present laws. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I find the talking point that there’s a lack of clarity in the securities laws unpersuasive. Some crypto companies might message that the laws are unclear rather than admitting that their platforms don’t have sufficient investor protection. Crypto intermediaries aren’t exactly lining up to register with the SEC and comply with the laws enacted by Congress.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Keep Your Head Up!</h2>
<p>Jakubcek continued by saying that bad actors litter the crypto arena, and investors always need to stay careful. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I&#8217;m not pretending that cryptocurrency is immune to criminal activities. Unfortunately, there are many criminal actors who are using the popular narrative of cryptocurrencies, and they are creating scams and different Ponzi schemes to attract naive investors. My advice is do your own research. Look at which platforms are most popular. Look at whether these platforms are used by millions of people, if these platforms were tested through time, or if these platforms can guarantee that they have billions in assets so that you will decrease your counterparty risk.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-law-enforcement-head-on-the-current-state-of-digital-assets/">Binance Law Enforcement Leader on the Current State of Digital Assets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
