<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 17:53:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>LBank Exchange Will List SHIKOKU INU (SHIK) on January 9, 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-shikoku-inu-shik-on-january-9-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-shikoku-inu-shik-on-january-9-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 17:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76399</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Jan 6, 2023 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list SHIKOKU INU (SHIK) on January 9, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the SHIK/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading at 13:00 UTC on January 9, 2023. As a decentralized memecoin experiment with far-reaching goals,<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-shikoku-inu-shik-on-january-9-2023/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-shikoku-inu-shik-on-january-9-2023/">LBank Exchange Will List SHIKOKU INU (SHIK) on January 9, 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Jan 6, 2023 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list SHIKOKU INU (SHIK) on January 9, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the SHIK/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading at 13:00 UTC on January 9, 2023.</p>
<p>As a decentralized memecoin experiment with far-reaching goals, <a href="https://etherscan.io/token/0x24da31e7bb182cb2cabfef1d88db19c2ae1f5572" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">SHIKOKU INU</a> (SHIK) is here to create a decentralized ecosystem of applications and tools, and educate investors about self-custody in an engaging way. The SHIK token will be listed on LBank Exchange at 13:00 UTC on January 9, 2023, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision.</p>
<p><strong>Introducing </strong><strong>SHIKOKU INU</strong></p>
<p>SHIKOKU INU is a decentralized experiment, launched on the 7th of November 2022, by the founder, Shikoshi, as a fresh opportunity for those who were struggling in the midst of the biggest bear market since.</p>
<p>The community of SHIKOKU INU is agile and tenacious, just like Shikoku Ken, the loyal protectors of the Japanese mountainous island of Shikoku. Born out of trials and tribulation, the SHIKOKU INU community is one of the strongest communities, supportive of one another, and pushing each other towards success.</p>
<p>Furthermore, SHIKOKU INU proposes a novel concept for community retention and engagement. That is, the publishing of the private key of the developer account for all to see and use, to harbor a truly decentralized community. SHIKOKU INU has no permanent allotted owner, instead, it is owned by all that wish to own it.</p>
<p>In addition to the main page, there’re various websites belonging to SHIKOKU INU that merge to create a complete decentralized ecosystem called SIDE (Shikoku Inu Decentralized Ecosystem). These websites include shikoku.app, a hub for decentralized applications; shikoku.space, a community blackboard space where members can collaborate on ideas and bring them to fruition; shikoku.world, an area for a world map of the SHIKOKU INU community; shikoku.life, an area for mental health checks for members of the SHIKOKU INU community, as well as tips and tricks for things in their day to day life; shikoku.store, a hub for official SHIKOKU INU merchandise; shikoku.fun, an area for all things fun such as community games, events, and get-togethers; and many more. By the development of the SIDE with SHIK being the centerpiece and store of value, it aims to create a thriving community full of creators, investors, developers, and holders.</p>
<p>SHIKOKU INU plans to assist the common investor with knowledge on how to safely custody their assets in an interesting and engaging way, while allowing them to be part of a decentralized and vibrant community of those with similar goals. SHIKOKU INU, while beginning as an experiment, plans to grow into a decentralized ecosystem, where the value will be provided by the community, for the community, and for those outside the community who are looking to learn more about decentralization and cryptocurrency as a whole.</p>
<p><strong>About SHIK Token</strong></p>
<p>SHIKOKU INU (SHIK) resides on the Ethereum blockchain. The most simplistic ERC-20 contract was used, ensuring stability in trades without outliers and efficiency in gas processing for those who wish to trade it. Although SHIK begins as a decentralized experiment, coupled with what can most succinctly be referred to as a meme coin, its goals are far-reaching, assuming the necessary community adoption and rally takes place.</p>
<p>If a user wishes to participate in SHIKOKU INU and its’ community, it is advised that an individual holds the SHIK token, as it will be used as the primary token to power all areas of the SIDE. However, if for any reason an individual wishes to participate in the community outside of the SIDE, they are welcome to do so. The token is simply a cog in the much larger wheel of mass adoption, education, and change that SHIKOKU INU plans to bring.</p>
<p>The total supply of SHIK is 1 quadrillion (i.e., 1,000,000,000,000,000) tokens, and no additional tax will be collected when buying and selling the token. It will be listed on LBank Exchange at 13:00 UTC on January 9, 2023, investors who are interested in the SHIKOKU INU investment can easily buy and sell SHIK token on LBank Exchange by then. The listing of SHIK token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p>
<p><strong>Learn More about</strong><strong> SHIK Token:</strong><br />
Official Website: <a href="https://shikoku.io" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://shikoku.io</a><br />
Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/SHIKARMY" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://t.me/SHIKARMY</a><br />
Discord: <a href="https://discord.gg/E7crTVsRXG" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://discord.gg/E7crTVsRXG</a><br />
Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/shikokuinucoin" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/shikokuinucoin</a><br />
Facebook: <a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/shikokuinu/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://www.facebook.com/groups/shikokuinu/</a><br />
YouTube: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCORRl3-7nvDy6PgvmiXTTBQ" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCORRl3-7nvDy6PgvmiXTTBQ</a><br />
Medium: <a href="https://medium.com/@shikokuinuarmy" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://medium.com/@shikokuinuarmy</a></p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media: </strong></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Facebook</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong><br />
LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
LBank Exchange<br />
<a href="mailto:marketing@lbank.info">marketing@lbank.info</a><br />
<a href="mailto:business@lbank.info">business@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-shikoku-inu-shik-on-january-9-2023/">LBank Exchange Will List SHIKOKU INU (SHIK) on January 9, 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-shikoku-inu-shik-on-january-9-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Miners Aren&#8217;t Giving Lenders Their Money Back</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-miners-arent-giving-lenders-their-money-back/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-miners-arent-giving-lenders-their-money-back/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 17:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Block Fi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celsius]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lenders]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75842</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Of all the people or companies in the crypto space, lenders likely have it worse than anyone or anything. They are the ones giving money to the crypto companies that are now failing or struggling to stay afloat. In many cases, they are not able to repay the funds they’ve utilized or borrowed, which really<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-miners-arent-giving-lenders-their-money-back/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-miners-arent-giving-lenders-their-money-back/">Crypto Miners Aren&#8217;t Giving Lenders Their Money Back</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Of all the people or companies in the crypto space, <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/crypto-lenders-woes-worsen-bitcoin-133831455.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">lenders likely have</a> it worse than anyone or anything. They are the ones giving money to the crypto companies that are now failing or struggling to stay afloat. In many cases, they are not able to repay the funds they’ve utilized or borrowed, which really puts a lot of these lending firms on edge.</p>
<h2>Lenders Are Enduring Trouble from Crypto Miners</h2>
<p>Instead of money, lenders are instead receiving machines from miners – who at one point, earned more than $4 billion through their professions – as collateral. They figure if they can’t pay their bills with cash, they can at least send these lenders the items and equipment they’re using to show that they’re “good for it.” The problem is that in this economy, cash is king, and everything else is likely to carry some degree of uselessness or risk alongside it.</p>
<p>Several firms – including New York Digital Investment Group (NYDIG), <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/celsius-network-is-next-crypto-company-to-file-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">Celsius Network</a>, Block Fi, and Galaxy Digital – have lent out machines and money to mining companies to get their jobs done. Now, with the industry being in the state it’s in, everything is coming to a crashing halt, and several of the above-named companies have been forced into bankruptcy due to liquidity issues and related concerns.</p>
<p>Ethan Vera – chief operations officer at crypto mining services firm Luxor Technologies – said in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>People were pouring dollars into the mining space. Miners ended up dictating a lot of the loan terms, so the financiers moved ahead with a lot of the deals where only the machines were collateral.</p></blockquote>
<p>Companies like Iris Energy Ltd. are expected to default on as much as $108 million in the coming months. The firm has borrowed from the NYDIG on several occasions, with its most recent loan being delivered in March of 2022. Another firm that’s borrowed from NYDIG is Core Scientific, which some are whispering could <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-firm-core-scientific-says-its-considering-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">be one of the next crypto</a> firms to file bankruptcy. NYDIG had also provided a $54 million loan to the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block-fi-is-the-latest-crypto-company-to-go-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">now bankrupt Block Fi</a>.</p>
<p>Michael Wursthorn – a spokesperson for Galaxy Digital – said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We continue to take a prudent, risk-managed approach toward financing arrangements in the mining space. In the third quarter, for example, Galaxy’s mining arm closed three existing machine leases collectively worth about $8 million at expected terms without defaults, delinquencies, or losses.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Didn&#8217;t Do Your Due Diligence, Did Ya?</h2>
<p>One of the big problems – according to Matthew Kimmel, a digital asset analyst at crypto firm Coin Shares – is that many of these lenders did not bother to really check and see if the companies they were giving money to were solid enough. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>There hasn’t necessarily been the best due diligence on whether a miner was credit worthy or not.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-miners-arent-giving-lenders-their-money-back/">Crypto Miners Aren&#8217;t Giving Lenders Their Money Back</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-miners-arent-giving-lenders-their-money-back/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>European Central Bank: Bitcoin Is Quickly Becoming Irrelevant</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/european-central-bank-bitcoin-is-quickly-becoming-irrelevant/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/european-central-bank-bitcoin-is-quickly-becoming-irrelevant/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 15:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European Central Bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75840</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The European Central Bank has issued a statement claiming that bitcoin is on its way out and closely approaching “irrelevance.” The European Central Bank Is not a Bitcoin Fan The financial institution released a blog entitled “Bitcoin’s Last Stand” that details the fall of the world’s number one digital currency. Interestingly, the bank does not<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/european-central-bank-bitcoin-is-quickly-becoming-irrelevant/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/european-central-bank-bitcoin-is-quickly-becoming-irrelevant/">European Central Bank: Bitcoin Is Quickly Becoming Irrelevant</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The European Central Bank has issued a <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/european-central-bank-says-bitcoin-is-on-the-road-to-irrelevance/ar-AA14JSOc" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">statement claiming that bitcoin</a> is on its way out and closely approaching “irrelevance.”</p>
<h2>The European Central Bank Is not a Bitcoin Fan</h2>
<p>The financial institution released a blog entitled “Bitcoin’s Last Stand” that details the fall of the world’s number one digital currency. Interestingly, the bank does <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">not refer to FTX</a> and its November collapse as the reason as to why bitcoin is doing so poorly. Rather, it hints that bitcoin was on a destructive path long before the company began sinking into oblivion.</p>
<p>When the blog was first published, the bank made note of bitcoin’s rise beyond the $17,000 mark, the first time it had done so in approximately two weeks. However, while the rise is likely to get some people excited, the bank dismissed the maneuver, claiming it wasn’t going to last. The blog says:</p>
<blockquote><p>More likely, however, it is an artificially induced last gasp before the road to irrelevance, and this was already foreseeable before FTX went bust and sent the bitcoin price to well below USD $16,000.</p></blockquote>
<p>Some of the reasons the blog speaks the way it does of bitcoin is because, it says, the digital currency does not meet the requirements of a valid investment, nor does it work as a payment method. In many ways, the currency has not proven itself to work in any way, shape, or form. It says:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin&#8217;s conceptual design and technological shortcomings make it questionable as a means of payment. Real bitcoin transactions are cumbersome, slow, and expensive. Bitcoin has never been used to any significant extent for legal real-world transactions. Bitcoin is also not suitable as an investment. It does not generate cash flow (like real estate) or dividends (like equities), cannot be used productively (like commodities) or provide social benefits (like gold). The market valuation of bitcoin is therefore based purely on speculation.</p></blockquote>
<p>With so much talk of regulation following the FTX failure, many are wondering if perhaps a few laws overseeing the space will allow bitcoin and its crypto cousins to rise through the ranks again, though the blog makes it clear that this may not happen, and that fans shouldn’t get too stuck on the idea.</p>
<h2>Regulation Won&#8217;t Help</h2>
<p>It reads:</p>
<blockquote><p>The belief that space must be given to innovation at all costs stubbornly persists. Firstly, these technologies have so far created limited value for society, no matter how great the expectations [are] for the future. Secondly, the use of a promising technology is not a sufficient condition for an added value of a product based on it.</p></blockquote>
<p>To say it has been a rough year for bitcoin would be a heavy understatement. The currency has fallen by more than 70 percent over the last 14 months since hitting a new all-time high of $68K in November 2021.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/european-central-bank-bitcoin-is-quickly-becoming-irrelevant/">European Central Bank: Bitcoin Is Quickly Becoming Irrelevant</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/european-central-bank-bitcoin-is-quickly-becoming-irrelevant/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LBank Exchange Will List Luxurion (LXRN) on January 9, 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-luxurion-lxrn-on-january-9-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-luxurion-lxrn-on-january-9-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 14:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76396</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Jan 6, 2023 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list Luxurion (LXRN) on January 9, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the LXRN/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading at 6:00 UTC on January 9, 2023. As a next-generation luxury total blockchain platform, Luxurion (LXRN)<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-luxurion-lxrn-on-january-9-2023/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-luxurion-lxrn-on-january-9-2023/">LBank Exchange Will List Luxurion (LXRN) on January 9, 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Jan 6, 2023 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list Luxurion (LXRN) on January 9, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the LXRN/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading at 6:00 UTC on January 9, 2023.</p>
<p>As a next-generation luxury total blockchain platform, <a href="https://etherscan.io/token/0x37D12e3EA2ceE077c0c97a920013Ac8920D8224F" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Luxurion</a> (LXRN) provides various benefits to users participating in the platform ecosystem. Its native token LXRN will be listed on LBank Exchange at 6:00 UTC on January 9, 2023, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision.</p>
<p><strong>Introducing </strong><strong>Luxurion</strong></p>
<p>Luxurion was developed to introduce an objective, transparent, and safe blockchain to the platform and participate in the platform ecosystem by utilizing LXRN, a key token, in order to improve the problems that have occurred in the existing luxury goods-related market.</p>
<p>Aiming to become a leading platform by providing independent solutions, Luxurion utilizes advanced technologies including blockchain and NFT to provide various functions and services that are reliable, efficient, transparent and secure. For instance, Luxurion provides a genuine authentication system using NFT. When selling luxury goods, NFT for the product is provided to enable genuine authentication and authenticity guarantee, eliminating the risk of loss and counterfeiting of existing offline authenticity certificates or guarantee cards.</p>
<p>On the Luxurion platform, ownership is divided into pieces and sold as NFTs for users who have difficulty purchasing products. The product is made with the same concept as joint purchase. With Luxurion Auction service, users can also purchase limited luxury goods released by luxury brands that have formal contracts and collaborations with Luxurion, or luxury goods sold by luxury brands through the platform.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Luxurion plans to release Blockchain Edition, a special limited edition product that records everything from product production to distribution through formal contracts and collaborations with real luxury brands. Unlike luxury items that are not officially licensed or treated as digital data that cannot actually be used in existing metaverses, Luxurion provides limited edition items and NFTs that are produced with approval from real luxury brands.</p>
<p>With the goal of providing a next-generation blockchain protocol through better environment and policies, Luxurion strives to establish itself as a next-generation platform that provides various benefits to users participating in the platform ecosystem.</p>
<p><strong>About LXRN Token</strong></p>
<p>LXRN is the native token of the Luxurion ecosystem. Users can use their existing LXRN as a key currency through the wallet provided on the Luxurion platform. LXRN can be used as a payment method, such as transactions within the platform and purchases from offline luxury goods retailers that have officially signed a contract with Luxurion.</p>
<p>Based on ERC-20, LXRN has a total supply of 1.5 billion (i.e., 1,500,000,000) tokens, of which 10% is provided for private sale, 20% is reserved, 10% will be used for marketing, 10% is allocated to the team and advisors, and the remaining 50% is provided for the ecosystem.</p>
<p>The LXRN token will be listed on LBank Exchange at 6:00 UTC on January 9, 2023, investors who are interested in the Luxurion investment can easily buy and sell LXRN token on LBank Exchange by then. The listing of LXRN token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p>
<p><strong>Learn More about</strong><strong> LXRN Token:</strong></p>
<p>Official Website: <a href="https://luxurion.io/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://luxurion.io/</a></p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media: </strong></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Facebook</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong></p>
<p>LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
LBank Exchange<br />
<a href="mailto:marketing@lbank.info">marketing@lbank.info</a><br />
<a href="mailto:business@lbank.info">business@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-luxurion-lxrn-on-january-9-2023/">LBank Exchange Will List Luxurion (LXRN) on January 9, 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-luxurion-lxrn-on-january-9-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LBank Excited About Wider Blockchain Adoption in Turkey</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-excited-about-wider-blockchain-adoption-in-turkey/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-excited-about-wider-blockchain-adoption-in-turkey/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 13:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76390</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Central Bank of Turkey (CBRT) completed CBDC tests in December 2022 and the government is currently planning to use blockchain technology for online public services. Both signal an even more welcoming embrace of blockchain technology in 2023. Why this matters: Since the Turkish government’s plan in 2019 for a national blockchain infrastructure, Turkey has<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-excited-about-wider-blockchain-adoption-in-turkey/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-excited-about-wider-blockchain-adoption-in-turkey/">LBank Excited About Wider Blockchain Adoption in Turkey</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>The Central Bank of Turkey (CBRT) completed CBDC tests in December 2022 and the government is currently planning to use blockchain technology for online public services. Both signal an even more welcoming embrace of blockchain technology in 2023. </strong></p>
<p><strong>Why this matters:</strong> Since the Turkish government’s plan in 2019 for a national blockchain infrastructure, Turkey has had many ambitious blockchain-technology-based goals. However, besides specific projects, not much was achieved. This might all change in 2023, with promising projects on the horizon.</p>
<ul>
<li>A recent <a href="https://www.tcmb.gov.tr/wps/wcm/connect/EN/TCMB+EN/Main+Menu/Announcements/Press+Releases/2022/ANO2022-55" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">statement</a> from the CBRT announced that “the first payment transactions on the Digital Turkish Lira Network were executed successfully”. It says that further advanced-stage tests will be run in the first quarter of 2023, and selected banks and financial technology companies will be chosen to be included in the expansion.</li>
<li>The <a href="https://www.tcmb.gov.tr/wps/wcm/connect/EN/TCMB+EN/Main+Menu/Announcements/Press+Releases/2021/ANO2021-40" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">official announcement</a> for a CBDC came in September of 2021. Initially, the CBRT did not commit to a digital Turkish lira. However, the most recent statement mentions that “the CBRT will continue to run tests for authentic architectural setups designed in areas such as the use of distributed ledger technologies in payment systems and the integration of these technologies with instant payment systems.”</li>
<li>“Testing and successful completion of the digital Turkish lira is seen as a big step,” Adem Özkan Özdil, Community Manager for Turkey to global crypto exchange LBank, commented.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Go deeper: </strong>Beyond Turkey’s CBDC, the government has made other commitments, such as testing and integrating blockchain technology in public services.</p>
<ul>
<li>Amid the news about the digital Turkish lira, the Vice president of Turkey, Fuat Oktay, <a href="https://tr.cointelegraph.com/news/digital-wallet-announcement-from-the-vice-president" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> plans for a blockchain-based digital identity application during the Digital Turkey 2023 Event. Many public services, including residential matters and military services, will be integrated into the E-Devlet portal, which will use a blockchain-based digital identity and login system.</li>
<li>Notably, Turkey <a href="https://www.sanayi.gov.tr/anasayfa" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">first shared</a> its vision to utilize blockchain technology in public services in 2019. In its Strategy 2023 presentation, Turkey’s Ministry of Industry and Technology put blockchain and distributed ledger technology (DLT) as one of the priorities of 2020.</li>
<li>Furthermore, the city of <a href="https://sputniknews.com.tr/20200116/konya-kendi-kripto-parasini-cikarmak-icin-calisiyor-1041035674.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Konya</a>, one of the most important cultural centers of Turkey, revealed in 2020 that they were planning to develop a “city coin” and use blockchain technology to fund social programs. Konya served as an initial test to see how blockchain technology works with public services on a large scale.</li>
<li>Efforts such as these show Turkey’s determination to push for wider blockchain integration in the country. &#8220;Turkey is an exciting market and ranks among the top 10 in crypto adoption globally. A boost for the digital Turkish lira is a positive step from the forward-looking government&#8221;, said Allen Wei Co-Founder and CEO of European licensed LBank Exchange.<strong> </strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Start Trading </strong><a href="http://lbank.com" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>Now</strong></a>!</p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media:</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>Telegram</strong></a><strong> l </strong><a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener"><strong>Twitter</strong></a><strong> l </strong><a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener"><strong>Facebook</strong></a><strong> l </strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>LinkedIn</strong></a><strong> l </strong><a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>Instagram</strong></a><strong> l </strong><a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener"><strong>YouTube</strong></a></p>
<p><strong>Press contact:</strong></p>
<p><a href="mailto:press@lbank.info">press@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
LBank Exchange<br />
<strong> </strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-excited-about-wider-blockchain-adoption-in-turkey/">LBank Excited About Wider Blockchain Adoption in Turkey</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-excited-about-wider-blockchain-adoption-in-turkey/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fame Global (FAMEG) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fame-global-fameg-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fame-global-fameg-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 13:23:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76387</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Jan 6, 2023 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed Fame Global (FAMEG) on January 6, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the FAMEG/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading. As a hyper connected fashion metaverse, FAME nourishes existing physical and digital universes where people<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fame-global-fameg-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fame-global-fameg-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">Fame Global (FAMEG) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Jan 6, 2023 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed Fame Global (FAMEG) on January 6, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the FAMEG/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading.</p>
<p>As a hyper connected fashion metaverse, FAME nourishes existing physical and digital universes where people can build, create, enjoy, play, earn and shop in a sustainable way. Its native token <a href="https://etherscan.io/token/0x526dacaaf5f4aafe2fef94b93db92c4fa1c376ba" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Fame Global</a> (FAMEG) has been listed on LBank Exchange at 12:00 UTC on January 6, 2023, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision.</p>
<p><strong>Introducing </strong><strong>FAME</strong></p>
<p>FAME is a hyper connected fashion NFTs &amp; fashion metaverse project that supports fashion designers and digital creators to create, launch, sell and produce their own digital fashion NFTs in connection with physical garments and real world productions. Participants can buy, sell, trade and play with diverse digital fashion NFTs, not to mention the real-world fashion experiences.</p>
<p>As a sustainable metaverse fashion ecosystem building platform, FAME provides a playground where the ecosystem players and stakeholders can co-create a sustainable metaverse fashion ecosystem more efficiently and effectively, and integrates the tools, solutions, knowledge, and expertise for supporting a sustainable metaverse fashion ecosystem development.</p>
<p>FAME META STUDIO &amp; LAB will be a key element of the services/platform for building sustainable fashion creator economy, supporting designers to transform their traditional designs into digital fashion garments, and transforming the physical fashion resources into 2D / 3D interactive digital fashion assets. It integrates FAME Fashion Launchpad, a key element of the self-sovereign funding and NFT management platform, to mint NFTs for the digital garments, and enables NFT based IP portfolio development for additional economic value creation.</p>
<p>In addition to above key elements, there’s also xFAME Marketplace enabling a hyper connected fashion marketplace where e-commerce is strongly connected with metaverse/NFT commerce. Furthermore, with FAME Gamification, the project enables an innovative metaverse fashion monetization.</p>
<p>With its strong management team and advisors, ever-growing list of partnerships and great designers, FAME strives to lead the “Sustainable Metaverse Fashion Ecosystem” that nourishes existing physical and digital fashion universes where people can build, create, enjoy, play, earn and shop in a sustainable way.</p>
<p><strong>About FAMEG Token</strong></p>
<p>Fame Global (FAMEG) is the native token that circulates throughout the FAME ecosystem and is a tool to activate the market. It’s the only utility token in the marketplace, and is used for NFT purchases, payment of fees and interest, and governance staking.</p>
<p>Based on ERC-20, FAMEG has a total supply of 1 billion (i.e., 1,000,000,000) tokens, of which 25% is provided for token sale, 10% is allocated to the team and advisors, 10% will be used for marketing, 10% is provided for R&amp;D, 5% is reserved, 10% will be used for operation, and the remaining 30% is allocated for the ecosystem.</p>
<p>The FAMEG token has been listed on LBank Exchange at 12:00 UTC on January 6, 2023, investors who are interested in the Fame Global investment can easily buy and sell FAMEG token on LBank Exchange right now. The listing of FAMEG token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p>
<p><strong>Learn More about</strong><strong> FAMEG Token:</strong></p>
<p>Official Website: <a href="https://www.famegroup.io" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.famegroup.io</a><br />
Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/+nSV0e2WtrXtiOGM1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://t.me/+nSV0e2WtrXtiOGM1</a><br />
Discord: <a href="https://discord.gg/N2d7gsM7dx" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://discord.gg/N2d7gsM7dx</a><br />
Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/fame_metaverse" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/fame_metaverse</a><br />
Instagram: <a href="https://www.instagram.com/x______fame/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.instagram.com/x______fame/</a><br />
Medium: <a href="https://medium.com/@fameuniverse" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://medium.com/@fameuniverse</a></p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media: </strong></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Facebook</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong><br />
LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
LBank Exchange<br />
<a href="mailto:marketing@lbank.info">marketing@lbank.info</a><br />
<a href="mailto:business@lbank.info">business@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fame-global-fameg-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">Fame Global (FAMEG) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fame-global-fameg-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>GolCoin (GOLC) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/golcoin-golc-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/golcoin-golc-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 13:12:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76384</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Oct. 25, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed GolCoin (GOLC) on October 25, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the GOLC/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading. Created to be more than just a cryptocurrency, GolCoin (GOLC) is a ticket for a successful<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/golcoin-golc-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/golcoin-golc-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">GolCoin (GOLC) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Oct. 25, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed GolCoin (GOLC) on October 25, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the GOLC/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading.</p>
<p>Created to be more than just a cryptocurrency, <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/golcoin/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">GolCoin</a> (GOLC) is a ticket for a successful investment and a way to be involved in its revolutionary projects such as Agharta, Golex.io, Golchain, NFT marketplace, and many more. Its native token GOLC has been listed on LBank Exchange at 8:00 UTC on October 25, 2022, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision.</p>
<p><strong>Introducing </strong><strong>GolCoin</strong></p>
<p>GolCoin is created to be more than just a cryptocurrency, it is a portal leading to a new futuristic world where it will be at the core of many evolutionary projects that will change many aspects of people’s life.</p>
<p>Investing in GolCoin means investing in something greater than just a cryptocurrency as it will give investor a chance to gain access into the GolCoin ecosystem which includes many projects that consist of social networking solutions, corporate applications, staking, exchange facilities where investors can reap profits by trading GolCoin and other major coins.</p>
<p>One of its revolutionary projects is called Agharta. It is a portal into a new universe in the meta world which aims to connect people in a futuristic way that has not been done yet. Agharta will contain different channels such as “Metaconnect, Metagols, and MetaNow&#8221;, all of those channels carry the same goal which is the new way of connecting with loved ones. It will help people connect with friends and family, find communities, and grow businesses.</p>
<p>In addition, there’s Golex.io that provides secure, trusted digital asset trading and asset management services, the highest quality investment, and the most rewarding experience. A 2nd generation NFT marketplace with many futuristic features is also being developed by GolCoin. NFTs bought from this marketplace will give the user virtual assist and real life benefits. In addition to that, utilities bought from the NFT marketplace can be integrated into Agharta.</p>
<p>Furthermore, to overcome the issues caused by the traditional mining process, GolCoin will be using Solar Power for its mining projects, since it is the best option for a sustainable future. This project will be one of the most important GolCoin projects giving profits on both long and short terms, boosting GolCoin presence on trading platforms and reflecting a reliable image for traders and cryptocurrency enthusiasts.</p>
<p>The team of GolCoin is constantly working on finding solutions to improve the user experience in daily used platforms and upgrading it into something unique. Its ecosystem will be a getaway from the world to a separate universe.</p>
<p><strong>About GOLC Token</strong></p>
<p>GOLC is the native token of GolCoin project. Being the core of the ecosystem, utmost importance is given to each aspect of GOLC starting from the design, supply volume, allocations, prices, and marketing to ensure long-term sustainability. The supply will be managed over time depending on the demand.</p>
<p>Based on BEP-20, GOLC has a total supply of 290 million (i.e. 290,000,000) tokens, of which 27.59% is provided for Golchain, 24.14% is allocated for Agharta, 17.24% is allocated for NFT marketplace, 15.52% is provided for mining project, 5.17% is allocated for exchange, 3.45% will be used for marketing, another 3.45% is allocated to the team, 1.72% is allocated for staking, and the remaining 1.72% is provided for airdrop.</p>
<p>The GOLC token has been listed on LBank Exchange at 8:00 UTC on October 25, 2022, investors who are interested in the GolCoin investment can easily buy and sell GOLC token on LBank Exchange right now. The listing of GOLC token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p>
<p><strong>Learn More about</strong><strong> GOLC Token:</strong></p>
<p>Official Website: <a href="https://www.golcoin.io" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.golcoin.io</a><br />
Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/GolCoin_English" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://t.me/GolCoin_English</a><br />
Discord: <a href="https://discord.com/invite/WW27yFSydP" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://discord.com/invite/WW27yFSydP</a><br />
Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/golcoin_io" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/golcoin_io</a><br />
Instagram: <a href="https://www.instagram.com/golcoin.io/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.instagram.com/golcoin.io/</a><br />
Facebook: <a href="https://www.facebook.com/GolCoin.io/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://www.facebook.com/GolCoin.io/</a></p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media: </strong></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Facebook</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong></p>
<p>LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
LBank Exchange<br />
<a href="mailto:marketing@lbank.info">marketing@lbank.info</a><br />
<a href="mailto:business@lbank.info">business@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/golcoin-golc-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">GolCoin (GOLC) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/golcoin-golc-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Gemini Exchange Has Halted Withdrawals</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-gemini-exchange-has-halted-withdrawals/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-gemini-exchange-has-halted-withdrawals/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 13:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Withdrawals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75838</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Gemini Exchange in New York – headed by the Winklevoss Twins – has halted all withdrawals, sparking rumors that the company could be next in a long line of crypto firms to file bankruptcy. Gemini Exchange Halts All Withdrawals The move is a direct result of the collapse of FTX, which came crashing down<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-gemini-exchange-has-halted-withdrawals/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-gemini-exchange-has-halted-withdrawals/">The Gemini Exchange Has Halted Withdrawals</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Gemini Exchange in New York – headed by the Winklevoss Twins – has halted all withdrawals, <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/qai/2022/11/30/gemini-crypto-pauses-withdrawals-fallout-continues-from-ftx-collapse/?sh=5f9191a64a84" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">sparking rumors that</a> the company could be next in a long line of crypto firms to file bankruptcy.</p>
<h2>Gemini Exchange Halts All Withdrawals</h2>
<p>The move is a direct <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">result of the collapse</a> of FTX, which came crashing down in mid-November. Michael Barr, an official with the Federal Reserve, is calling upon Congress to regulate crypto once and for all due to the company’s failure. In a recent statement, he hinted at possible regulation in the future, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>Over the last several years, we have seen crypto asset activity grow rapidly and experience periods of significant stress. Some financial innovations offer opportunities, but as we have recently seen, many innovations also carry risks which can include liquidity runs, the rapid collapse of asset values, misuse of customer funds, fraud, theft, manipulation, and money laundering. These risks, if not well controlled, can harm retail investors and cut against the goals of a safe and fair financial system.</p></blockquote>
<p>Gemini has close to $200 million tied up in the FTX exchange. In addition, it has reported that its outflows are significantly outdoing its inflows, and the company was forced to take quick action as a means of stabilizing itself. While withdrawals are halted, the firm issued a statement mentioning that products like Gemini staking will operate as they always have and are not affected.</p>
<p>This is a huge difference from just 12 months ago when the company garnered roughly $400 million in new funds to boost its expansion plans. The company is also working with Genesis to permit customers to redeem their money. Gemini mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>We are disappointed that the Earn program SLA will not be met, but we are encouraged by Genesis and its parent company Digital Currency Group’s commitment to doing everything in their power to fulfill their obligations to customers under the Earn program. We will continue to work with them on behalf of all Earn customers. This is our highest priority. We greatly appreciate your patience.</p></blockquote>
<p>A spokesperson for the firm is also stating that the company has no immediate plans to file bankruptcy and that it’s presently trying to work its present situation out. They said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We have no plans to file bankruptcy imminently. Our goal is to resolve the current situation consensually without the need for any bankruptcy filing.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Setting the Record Straight</h2>
<p>The enterprise has also taken to Twitter to launch what’s called the Gemini Trust Center, which seeks to provide information and answer questions about what’s going on. Gemini commented:</p>
<blockquote><p> I/We are pleased to announce the launch of the @Gemini Trust Center, a dashboard of metrics for the funds we hold in the Gemini platform and on your behalf, as well as other important data and information.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-gemini-exchange-has-halted-withdrawals/">The Gemini Exchange Has Halted Withdrawals</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-gemini-exchange-has-halted-withdrawals/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Singapore Takes Big Measures to Protect Crypto Holders</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/singapore-takes-big-measures-to-protect-crypto-holders/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/singapore-takes-big-measures-to-protect-crypto-holders/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 17:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Singapore]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75827</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When it comes to risky assets like crypto, Singapore banks are no longer required to hold 1:1 in collateral, but rather 1.25:1. What this means is that for every $1 in cryptocurrency, a financial institution needs to hold $1.25 in regular cash. This is designed to ensure there are enough reserves in place to cover<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/singapore-takes-big-measures-to-protect-crypto-holders/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/singapore-takes-big-measures-to-protect-crypto-holders/">Singapore Takes Big Measures to Protect Crypto Holders</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When it comes to risky assets like crypto, Singapore banks <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/singapore-banks-exposure-bitcoin-insignificant-163349646.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">are no longer required</a> to hold 1:1 in collateral, but rather 1.25:1. What this means is that for every $1 in cryptocurrency, a financial institution needs to hold $1.25 in regular cash. This is designed to ensure there are enough reserves in place to cover losses or other problems should the crypto industry decide to crash and burn all over again.</p>
<h2>Singapore Is Trying to Stop Future Crypto Problems</h2>
<p>2022 was one of the worst years for the crypto market. Many assets – including bitcoin, the world’s largest and most popular – fell by more than 70 percent from their all-time highs, many of which were achieved in November of 2021. During that time, it seemed like crypto was on top of the world and there was nothing that could ever bring it down.</p>
<p>We were wrong. The digital currency arena fell like it never has before. This bear market wiped away not millions or billions of dollars, but rather trillions as the crypto space fell from a valuation of about $3 trillion in early 2022 to just over $800 billion by the end of the year. It was sad, it was ugly, and above all, it was embarrassing, especially for all those who had been touting the space for several months or years and claiming it was going to bring a financial revolution to light.</p>
<p>Singapore – widely recognized for its strict financial tactics – wants to make sure it’s fully prepared for any losses or other significant damage the crypto space might seek to dole out in the coming future. Senior minister in charge of the Monetary Authority of Singapore Tharman Shanmugaratnam explained in a recent statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>Pending the finalization of the framework, MAS requires Singapore-incorporated banks to apply a 1,250 percent risk weight for exposures to riskier crypto assets such as bitcoin and ether. Based on MAS’ minimum total capital adequacy requirement of ten percent for systemically important banks incorporated in Singapore, this means that Singapore-incorporated banks are required to hold $125 of capital against an exposure of $100 to a crypto asset like bitcoin.</p></blockquote>
<p>The country has been privy to the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">rise and fall of FTX</a>, one of the world’s largest and most powerful digital currency exchanges. The company came crashing down in mid-November and has sent heavy ripples flowing through the digital currency arena. The company has caused many other firms, such as Block Fi, to be <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block-fi-is-the-latest-crypto-company-to-go-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">hit hard and file</a> bankruptcy.</p>
<h2>Lesser Measures for Other Tokens</h2>
<p>Shanmugaratnam further stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>For less risky crypto assets, such as tokenized corporate bonds that meet a set of conditions to ensure that they pose the same level of financial risks as traditional corporate bonds, the prudential treatment is similar to that applied to the traditional non-tokenized asset.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/singapore-takes-big-measures-to-protect-crypto-holders/">Singapore Takes Big Measures to Protect Crypto Holders</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/singapore-takes-big-measures-to-protect-crypto-holders/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
