<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 03:50:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Kabosu, the Dogecoin Shiba Inu Dog, Diagnosed with Serious Illness</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kabosu-the-dogecoin-shiba-inu-dog-diagnosed-with-serious-illness/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kabosu-the-dogecoin-shiba-inu-dog-diagnosed-with-serious-illness/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 17:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Atsuko Sato]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kabosu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76229</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Kabosu – the cute little Shiba Inu dog that inspired the memes of such famous digital currencies as Dogecoin – has been diagnosed with liver disease and leukemia according to her owner Atsuko Sato. Kabosu Is Very Ill The news is indeed sad for both animal lovers and crypto fans alike. Kabosu will likely never<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kabosu-the-dogecoin-shiba-inu-dog-diagnosed-with-serious-illness/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kabosu-the-dogecoin-shiba-inu-dog-diagnosed-with-serious-illness/">Kabosu, the Dogecoin Shiba Inu Dog, Diagnosed with Serious Illness</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Kabosu – the cute little Shiba Inu dog that inspired the memes of such famous digital currencies as Dogecoin – has been <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/other/the-internet-famous-shiba-inu-who-inspired-doge-memes-and-a-joke-cryptocurrency-is-seriously-ill-with-cancer/ar-AA15JVI2" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">diagnosed with liver disease</a> and leukemia according to her owner Atsuko Sato.</p>
<h2>Kabosu Is Very Ill</h2>
<p>The news is indeed sad for both animal lovers and crypto fans alike. Kabosu will likely never know how many people she has inspired with her cute little face, nor will she ever realize that her complexion and furry countenance arguably gave birth to one of the biggest bitcoin rivals to ever exist in Dogecoin.</p>
<p>Her owner made the following announcement on Twitter:</p>
<blockquote><p>Right now, the liver is very bad, and jaundice appears, but antibiotics will definitely improve.</p></blockquote>
<p>Originally a rescue pup, Kabosu voluntarily stopped eating and drinking on or around Christmas time in 2022. However, it has since been reported that she can drink water and that her appetite has come back somewhat, thus suggesting that while her condition is dangerous, hope is not completely lost yet.</p>
<p>Kabosu has already surpassed the life expectancy of her species given that she celebrated her 17th birthday in October of last year. Right now, Shiba Inu dogs are only expected to live between 12 and 15 years, so even if this is the end, one can attest to the fact that Kabosu is indeed a fighter and will go down in crypto history as a true pioneer and powerhouse of the space.</p>
<p>Her image has become synonymous with Dogecoin over the years, a currency that was initially created by computer genius Jackson Palmer. The currency was established as a way of making fun of the crypto space and its users. It was a meme coin, but it wound up becoming a major staple of the industry and has even garnered the attention of hardcore tech and crypto fans such as Elon Musk, who in all fairness, has often been kinder to Doge in the past than he has to bitcoin.</p>
<p>Musk has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-affirms-his-position-on-doge-its-the-peoples-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">referred to Dogecoin</a> as the “people’s crypto.” He has since allowed it to be used for merchandise purchases with many of his companies including <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-permits-tesla-customers-to-use-dogecoin-for-certain-merchandise/" data-wpel-link="internal">Tesla</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-permits-doge-payments-for-spacex-merchandise/" data-wpel-link="internal">SpaceX</a>.</p>
<p>Kabosu first became an <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/shiba-inu-behind-doge-meme-diagnosed-with-leukemia-and-liver-disease-owner-says/ar-AA15JmBp" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">internet sensation in 2010</a>. Her owner Sato posted her photo online and she became a quick hit on Reddit, with one user posting the word “Doge” under her photo, thus birthing the Dogecoin name.</p>
<h2>Let Us All Hope for Her Safety and Potential Recovery</h2>
<p>Three years later, the currency would emerge with her image as its major logo. This startled Sato at first, and she stated in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>When I first found out about the Kabosu memes, I was very surprised. I was terrified at the thought that just one photo I had casually posted on my blog could spread all over the world to places I didn’t know.</p></blockquote>
<p>Let us all join in praying for Kabosu’s safety.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kabosu-the-dogecoin-shiba-inu-dog-diagnosed-with-serious-illness/">Kabosu, the Dogecoin Shiba Inu Dog, Diagnosed with Serious Illness</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kabosu-the-dogecoin-shiba-inu-dog-diagnosed-with-serious-illness/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Argo Blockchain Sells Mining Facility to Galaxy Digital to Stay Afloat</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/argo-blockchain-sells-mining-facility-to-galaxy-digital-to-stay-afloat/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/argo-blockchain-sells-mining-facility-to-galaxy-digital-to-stay-afloat/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 15:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Argo Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celsius Network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Galaxy Digital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76226</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Argo Blockchain – one of the largest and most powerful digital currency mining enterprises in the world – has announced a new plan that will allow it to avoid bankruptcy and become another company that falls victim to the ongoing bear conditions of the crypto arena. Argo Blockchain Won&#8217;t Have to File Bankruptcy Argo has<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/argo-blockchain-sells-mining-facility-to-galaxy-digital-to-stay-afloat/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/argo-blockchain-sells-mining-facility-to-galaxy-digital-to-stay-afloat/">Argo Blockchain Sells Mining Facility to Galaxy Digital to Stay Afloat</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Argo Blockchain – one of the largest and most powerful digital currency mining enterprises in the world – has announced a new plan <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/bitcoin-miner-argo-to-avoid-bankruptcy-with-24100m-deal-from-galaxy-digital/ar-AA15Kx1P" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">that will allow it to avoid</a> bankruptcy and become another company that falls victim to the ongoing bear conditions of the crypto arena.</p>
<h2>Argo Blockchain Won&#8217;t Have to File Bankruptcy</h2>
<p>Argo has agreed to sell its bitcoin mining facility (called Helios) for $65 million to Galaxy Digital, the hedge fund managed by Mike Novogratz, a billionaire investor and big-time fan of bitcoin and other forms of crypto. The wealth management firm will also provide Argo with a $35 million loan to help it restructure its operations. The loan was secured through a collateral package that came in the form of Argo mining equipment.</p>
<p>In a statement, Galaxy Digital explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>The transaction will accelerate the expansion of Galaxy’s bitcoin mining operations and services, provide access to tax-efficient mining infrastructure, and reduce reliance on third-party hosting providers.</p></blockquote>
<p>The crypto space has been extremely bearish over the past 12 months. So much so, that several digital currency companies and mining facilities have entered bankruptcy proceedings as they are unable to keep up with the rising energy prices of Joe Biden’s America. They also cannot contend with the ongoing price dips being experienced by bitcoin and other mainstream forms of digital currency.</p>
<p>Some of the big names that come to mind when discussing crypto bankruptcies include the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/celsius-network-is-next-crypto-company-to-file-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">Celsius Network</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-lender-voyager-digital-files-chapter-11-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">Voyager Digital</a>, and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-hedge-fund-three-arrows-capital-is-now-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">Three Arrows Capital</a>, the latter being a crypto hedge fund. However, it is Celsius that arguably got things going in this direction. It is also one of the largest crypto companies out there and likely received the most attention when it decided to enter court proceedings as a means of shielding itself from angry customers and lenders.</p>
<p>However, it can be argued that the bankruptcies of these companies are nothing compared with the one that is currently underway for FTX, one of the largest digital currency exchanges in the history of the space. FTX first came to fruition in 2019 and rose through the ranks very quickly. It became a top-five crypto exchange by 2021 and it seemed like everything was really going well for the company, though things came crashing down in November of 2022.</p>
<h2>FTX Is the Biggest Bankruptcy Story</h2>
<p>During that month, the company’s chief executive Sam Bankman-Fried <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">announced FTX was enduring</a> a liquidity crunch and needed fast cash. Initially, it looked like the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">larger crypto firm Binance</a> was going to buy FTX out, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">though things didn’t quite</a> turn out that way, and it wasn’t long before FTX became <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">another bankrupt firm</a> and SBF was resigning from his post.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, Argo has debts exceeding $41 million. Peter Wall – CEO of the firm – says he hopes this new deal will allow it to remain functional during the bear market.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/argo-blockchain-sells-mining-facility-to-galaxy-digital-to-stay-afloat/">Argo Blockchain Sells Mining Facility to Galaxy Digital to Stay Afloat</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/argo-blockchain-sells-mining-facility-to-galaxy-digital-to-stay-afloat/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kraken Is Leaving Japan, Laying Off Several Employees</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kraken-is-leaving-japan-laying-off-several-employees/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kraken-is-leaving-japan-laying-off-several-employees/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 13:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Japan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jesse Powell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kraken]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76224</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Popular digital currency exchange Kraken has announced it is closing its Japan branch this month and laying off all its employees in the Land of the Rising Sun. Kraken Is Stepping Away from Japan The Japanese division of Kraken is called Payward Asia. In a recent blog post, the company mentioned that it’s going to<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kraken-is-leaving-japan-laying-off-several-employees/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kraken-is-leaving-japan-laying-off-several-employees/">Kraken Is Leaving Japan, Laying Off Several Employees</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Popular digital currency exchange Kraken has <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/crypto-exchange-kraken-to-shutter-its-japan-operations-after-global-layoffs/ar-AA15JTn8" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced it is closing</a> its Japan branch this month and laying off all its employees in the Land of the Rising Sun.</p>
<h2>Kraken Is Stepping Away from Japan</h2>
<p>The Japanese division of Kraken is called Payward Asia. In a recent blog post, the company mentioned that it’s going to be ceasing all its crypto trading services as of January 31, 2023. This will mark the second time Kraken has left the Japanese market, the first taking place in 2018. Up to that point, the company had been desperately trying to set up operations there for the past four years to no avail.</p>
<p>However, two years later in 2020, it made a successful attempt to establish a presence in the region after it was able to complete the necessary registration process with regulators.</p>
<p>The move is just another chalk on the ever-growing board of crypto casualties over the past several months. 2022 has been a very bad year for the digital currency industry, and while we’re only in the first month of 2023, it doesn’t look like this new era is bringing much recovery just yet. So many companies have fallen to the bearish conditions of the crypto space over the past 12 months, and analysts have no way of predicting what will happen before the year is out.</p>
<p>The news follows a long series of odd reports stemming from the Kraken exchange, a big one arriving in October of last year. It was announced during that time <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kraken-ceo-jesse-powell-is-leaving-his-post/" data-wpel-link="internal">that Kraken’s CEO Jesse Powell</a> was leaving his post following repeated allegations of semi-abusive behavior towards workers. From there, the exchange mentioned that it was going to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-exchange-kraken-is-cutting-off-russian-customers/" data-wpel-link="internal">be ceasing all relations</a> with Russian customers, and that all traders in that region would no longer gain access to the company’s services or products.</p>
<p>This news was shocking given that several months prior, the exchange stated that it would not comply with present sanctions delivered by the present U.S. <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-clarifies-everyday-russians-can-continue-to-use-our-services/" data-wpel-link="internal">administration against Russia</a> and that it would allow the country’s people to maintain their accounts and continue trading.</p>
<p>Kraken is also not the first company to announce layoffs following the start of the crypto bear market. Other big names in the “layoff department” include fellow crypto exchanges Gemini in New York (run by the Winklevoss Twins) and Coinbase in San Francisco, CA.</p>
<h2>So Many Layoffs Over the Past Year</h2>
<p>Gemini <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gemini-exchange-says-major-layoffs-are-coming/" data-wpel-link="internal">wound up releasing</a> as much as ten percent of its staff from employment. The company took flak when it was revealed that many of those who would be out of a job were informed via Zoom calls rather than in-person.</p>
<p>For Coinbase, things were even more <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-says-its-laying-off-several-employees/" data-wpel-link="internal">devastating as the company</a> ended up releasing approximately 18 percent of its staff following the announcement of huge hiring plans.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kraken-is-leaving-japan-laying-off-several-employees/">Kraken Is Leaving Japan, Laying Off Several Employees</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kraken-is-leaving-japan-laying-off-several-employees/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EOS Price Analysis: Risk of More Losses Below $0.95</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-0-95/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-0-95/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 05:38:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EOS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76590</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>EOS price started a fresh decline from the $1.08 resistance zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $1.0 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $1.04 the 4-hours chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-0-95/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-0-95/">EOS Price Analysis: Risk of More Losses Below $0.95</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>EOS price started a fresh decline from the $1.08 resistance zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $1.0 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $1.04 the 4-hours chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to decline if it stays below the $0.98 and $1.00 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>EOS price is struggling below $1.00 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-rally-could-extend-above-22k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. The price might attempt to recover if there is a clear move above $0.98.</em></p>
<h2>EOS Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, EOS price saw a fresh drop from the $1.10 zone against the US Dollar. The price traded below the $1.05 and $1.02 levels to enter a bearish zone.</p>
<p>There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $1.04 the 4-hours chart of the EOS/USD pair. The pair accelerated lower below the $0.98 support zone and settled well below the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-more-gains-possible-above-1/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>.</p>
<p>The bears pushed the price below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.8703 swing low to $1.094 high. On the downside, an immediate support is near the $0.950.</p>
<p>The 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.8703 swing low to $1.094 high is also near the $0.95 zone. The next key support is near the $0.935 level.</p>
<p>If there is a downside break below the $0.935 support, the price could test the $0.88 support in the near term. On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $0.98 level. The first major resistance is near the $1.00 level, above which the price might test the $1.080 level.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $1.08 level could start a steady increase towards the $1.15 level. Any more gains might send the price towards the $1.20 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_76591" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/EOS-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76591" class="size-full wp-image-76591" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/EOS-1.png" alt="EOS Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76591" class="wp-caption-text">EOS Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/EOSUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, EOS price is now trading below the $0.98 level and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could continue to decline if it stays below the $0.98 and $1.00 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4-hours MACD – The MACD for EOS/USD is gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4-hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $0.95 and $0.935.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $0.980 and $1.00.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-0-95/">EOS Price Analysis: Risk of More Losses Below $0.95</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-0-95/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Could Be Active Near $80</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-could-be-active-near-80/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-could-be-active-near-80/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 03:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76586</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin started a strong increase above $80 against the US Dollar. LTC price is now trading below $80 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $86.50 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair remains supported<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-could-be-active-near-80/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-could-be-active-near-80/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Could Be Active Near $80</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Litecoin started a strong increase above $80 against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>LTC price is now trading below $80 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $86.50 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair remains supported for more gains unless there is a clear move below $80.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Litecoin price is correcting gains from $92 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-rally-could-extend-above-22k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. LTC price could continue to move up if it remains well supported above the $80 level.</em></p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, there was a decent increase in bitcoin, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-rally-pauses-but-not-likely-over/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">ethereum</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-uptrend-in-place-above-0-40/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">ripple</a>, and litecoin against the US Dollar. Earlier, LTC formed a base above the $80 level and started a fresh increase.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above the $85 and $88 resistance levels. The price even climbed above the $90 level and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). However, the bears were active near the $92 zone. A high was formed near $91.14 and the price started a downside correction.</p>
<p>There was a move below the $85 level. The price traded below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $72.45 swing low to $91.14 high. There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $86.50 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>The price is now trading below $80 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). An immediate support is near the $81.80 level. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $72.45 swing low to $91.14 high.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $80 zone. A downside break below the $80 support might start a strong decline. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $84 and $85 levels. A clear move above the $85 level could pump the price towards the $92 level. The next major resistance sits near the $100 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_76587" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Litecoin-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76587" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-76587" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Litecoin-1.png" alt="Litecoin (LTC) Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76587" class="wp-caption-text">Litecoin (LTC) Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, litecoin price is clearly trading below $80 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price remains supported for more gains unless there is a clear move below $80.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LTC/USD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $80 and $75</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $85 and $92.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-could-be-active-near-80/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Could Be Active Near $80</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-could-be-active-near-80/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>More Crypto Exchanges are Verifying Reserves, is Proof of Reserves the Solution?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/more-crypto-exchanges-are-verifying-reserves-is-proof-of-reserves-the-solution/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/more-crypto-exchanges-are-verifying-reserves-is-proof-of-reserves-the-solution/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 18:53:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry and Adoption]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76565</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the wake of the FTX collapse, which happened because the now-defunct cryptocurrency exchange used customer money to cover its risks, cryptocurrency exchanges came up with proof-of-reserves to clarify transactions. Without clear rules, Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao recently pushed for a practice that gives exchanges a way to show users that they are more honest.<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/more-crypto-exchanges-are-verifying-reserves-is-proof-of-reserves-the-solution/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/more-crypto-exchanges-are-verifying-reserves-is-proof-of-reserves-the-solution/">More Crypto Exchanges are Verifying Reserves, is Proof of Reserves the Solution?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the wake of the FTX collapse, which happened because the now-defunct cryptocurrency exchange used customer money to cover its risks, cryptocurrency exchanges came up with proof-of-reserves to clarify transactions.</p>
<p>Without clear rules, Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao recently pushed for a practice that gives exchanges a way to show users that they are more honest. A <a href="https://www.okx.com/proof-of-reserves" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Proof of Reserves (PoR) audit </a>verifies that a custodian has the client funds it claims to have. The auditor takes a snapshot of all accounts and arranges together a Merkle tree to protect users&#8217; privacy. Once the snapshot has been taken, the auditor will have a <a href="https://www.okx.com/support/hc/en-us/articles/10660988139661" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Merkle root</a>, a cryptographic fingerprint specific to the sum of these accounts as of the snapshot&#8217;s creation time.</p>
<p>The auditor then compiles the digital signatures generated by the cryptocurrency exchange as evidence of who has the on-chain addresses that have balances that can be validated publicly. The final step of the audit is to verify whether or not these amounts are greater than or equal to the customer balances displayed in the Merkle tree. In that case, the client&#8217;s assets are held with a full reserve.</p>
<p>Binance Holdings Ltd. and <a href="https://www.okx.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">OKX </a>are just two examples of cryptocurrency exchanges that have turned to third-party auditors in recent months for a proof of reserves report, an increasingly popular form of attestation that can demonstrate the company&#8217;s solvency and ability to meet its debt obligations. Since most exchanges are privately owned, they don&#8217;t have to follow the rules of the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) about filing financial reports and having them audited.</p>
<p>The collapse of FTX, which had loaned billions of dollars from its clients to an affiliate, Alameda Research, and then blocked its consumers from accessing their funds, has prompted widespread worries about the financial stability of crypto platforms. Additionally, FTX went the extra mile by having its books audited by Armanino LLP and Prager Metis CPAs LLC for the previous two years, which is not something businesses in the industry typically do.</p>
<h4><strong>Is proof of reserves the solution to crypto&#8217;s trust problem?</strong></h4>
<p>Although third-party verification is a step toward greater transparency in crypto exchanges, some academics have pointed out important things that could be improved. When platforms disclose snapshots of their reserves to investors, they often conceal whether or not the platforms have pledged users&#8217; assets for loans or adjusted their assessments of assets or liabilities in the interim. The exchange may also determine the frequency of these attestations.</p>
<p>Suppose a company uses third-party verification and doesn&#8217;t give auditors information about its assets or liabilities that aren&#8217;t recorded on the blockchain. In that case, there may need for more transparency about the company&#8217;s non-digital assets.</p>
<p>These flaws highlight the limitations of on-chain platform solutions, which risk losing touch with the real world if they do not consider it. POR is insufficient to provide reliable proof against fraud or to protect against hacking.</p>
<p>An emphasis on ex-ante responsibility has resulted in more significant calls for financial regulation and control of the crypto business in the wake of FTX&#8217;s devastating death spiral. Lexology has published a paper analyzing current blockchain case law, noting that it may be difficult for the crypto business to avoid off-chain regulation. Legal mediation through the courts, backed by state authority and using existing legal concepts like fiduciary obligations and constructive trusts, will remain desirable as an ex-post method of achieving accountability for people who have suffered losses.</p>
<p>There is mounting pressure on U.S. authorities to ensure crypto businesses comply with investor protection rules. Under Chair Gary Gensler, the SEC has promised to crack down on the cryptocurrency industry. The agency has also asked for more exchanges to register but has not mentioned how platforms use proof of reserves.</p>
<p>In the coming months, cryptocurrency companies will depend more and more on proof of reserves to keep their clients&#8217; trust. However, various adjustments might be implemented to promote openness and confidence. Investors must have access to financial information regarding an exchange. This provides information about the business&#8217;s structure and income generation. As well as information about its staff and shareholders.</p>
<p>The cryptocurrency sector might greatly benefit from custodians implementing proof-of-reserves criteria, provided they communicate the dangers of this sort of self-regulation to their customers. Suppose the industry is thriving in instituting universal accountability rules,  in that case, it may avoid the setbacks that frequently accompany the collapse of centralized platforms like Mt. Gox, Cryptopia, QuadrigaCX, and FTX.</p>
<p>Users in a system where stablecoin issuers and exchanges must regularly verify their reserves would gravitate toward solutions that provide the highest level of asset safety. Therefore, more capital from institutional and individual investors would flow into the cryptocurrency market if the environment were safer.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<pre> 
<em>Image by <a href="https://pixabay.com/users/sergeitokmakov-3426571/?utm_source=link-attribution&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_campaign=image&amp;utm_content=6682491" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Sergei Tokmakov, Esq. https://Terms.Law</a> from <a href="https://pixabay.com//?utm_source=link-attribution&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_campaign=image&amp;utm_content=6682491" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Pixabay</a></em></pre>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/more-crypto-exchanges-are-verifying-reserves-is-proof-of-reserves-the-solution/">More Crypto Exchanges are Verifying Reserves, is Proof of Reserves the Solution?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/more-crypto-exchanges-are-verifying-reserves-is-proof-of-reserves-the-solution/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Paul Krugman Isn&#8217;t a Fan of Either BTC or Elon Musk</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paul-krugman-isnt-a-fan-of-either-btc-or-elon-musk/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paul-krugman-isnt-a-fan-of-either-btc-or-elon-musk/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 17:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paul Krugman]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tesla]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76222</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Paul Krugman – a Nobel Prize-winning economist – recently published a piece saying that Tesla stock is a lot like bitcoin. He also commented that the CEO of Tesla – Elon Musk, who is a big crypto fan and has since gone on to purchase Twitter – couldn’t be trusted to “feed his cat.” Paul<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paul-krugman-isnt-a-fan-of-either-btc-or-elon-musk/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paul-krugman-isnt-a-fan-of-either-btc-or-elon-musk/">Paul Krugman Isn&#8217;t a Fan of Either BTC or Elon Musk</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Paul Krugman – a Nobel Prize-winning economist – <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/nobel-laureate-paul-krugman-compares-134003901.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">recently published a piece saying</a> that Tesla stock is a lot like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. He also commented that the CEO of Tesla – Elon Musk, who is a big crypto fan and has since gone on to purchase Twitter – couldn’t be trusted to “feed his cat.”</p>
<h2>Paul Krugman Isn&#8217;t Crazy About Either Musk or BTC</h2>
<p>The bitcoin-Tesla comparisons came given that both assets have plunged heavily following solid jumps in late 2021. Bitcoin, during that time, rose to a whopping $68,000 per unit, and Tesla stock also hit a new all-time high. However, since then, Tesla has fallen by more than 73 percent, and bitcoin’s dips have also seen it lose about 70 percent of its value. In that sense, they appear to be one and the same.</p>
<p>In his piece, Krugman said that Tesla cannot compare to other big-time tech stocks such as Apple and Microsoft. He said that it doesn’t have the same network effects as those stocks as many people are turning to these latter companies for everyday use. Microsoft, for example, provides people with tools such as Word and Excel, which are pretty much used daily amongst people with 9-5 jobs.</p>
<p>Apple also provides people with their smartphones and other devices that have since become staples of everyday life. Try imaging your life without a smartphone… Not easy to picture, is it?</p>
<p>By contrast, Krugman says that at end of the day, Tesla is just another car company, and that while it has made waves in the electric and environmentally friendly auto sectors, it’s still facing heavy competition from firms such as Ford and General Motors, which have since pushed past many of their rivals to become major electric and natural gas-fueled car companies.</p>
<p>He predicts that Tesla could potentially be outdone by both these firms and similar ones in the future. He wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>It&#8217;s hard to see what would give Tesla a long-term lock on the electric vehicle business.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also said that much of the hype surrounding Tesla and the subsequent stock hikes it’s experienced have to do with the idea that Elon Musk is somehow a “cool guy.” He says this is a reputation that is not necessarily rightfully deserved, and that this reputation will fade over time as it’s allegedly been doing over the past few weeks.</p>
<h2>He Couldn&#8217;t Feed My Cat!</h2>
<p>Krugman was critical of Musk’s behavior at Twitter, claiming it was chaotic and that he was leading the social media giant down the wrong path. Musk initially <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-billionaires-think-elon-musk-will-do-well-with-twitter/" data-wpel-link="internal">completed his Twitter</a> purchase last October and has since released many leading executives of the firm. Krugman says:</p>
<blockquote><p>Given what we&#8217;ve seen of Musk&#8217;s behavior, I wouldn&#8217;t trust him to feed my cat, let alone run a major corporation.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paul-krugman-isnt-a-fan-of-either-btc-or-elon-musk/">Paul Krugman Isn&#8217;t a Fan of Either BTC or Elon Musk</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paul-krugman-isnt-a-fan-of-either-btc-or-elon-musk/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MicroStrategy Sells Some BTC&#8230; Then Turns Around and Buys More</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/microstrategy-sells-some-btc-then-turns-around-and-buys-more/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/microstrategy-sells-some-btc-then-turns-around-and-buys-more/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 15:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Saylor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroStrategy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76220</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>MicroStrategy – the famed software giant turned institutional bitcoin bull – has done something many of us thought it incapable of doing: it’s selling some of its bitcoin. MicroStrategy Sells, Then Buys, BTC MicroStrategy announced it had sold some of its BTC reserves on December 22, 2022. The company says it did so for tax<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/microstrategy-sells-some-btc-then-turns-around-and-buys-more/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/microstrategy-sells-some-btc-then-turns-around-and-buys-more/">MicroStrategy Sells Some BTC&#8230; Then Turns Around and Buys More</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MicroStrategy – the famed software giant turned institutional bitcoin bull – has done something many of us thought it incapable of doing: it’s <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/microstrategy-sells-off-bitcoin-first-162620178.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">selling some of its bitcoin</a>.</p>
<h2>MicroStrategy Sells, Then Buys, BTC</h2>
<p>MicroStrategy announced it had sold some of its BTC reserves on December 22, 2022. The company says it did so for tax purposes, but that it’s also going to use some of the proceeds to purchase additional bitcoin, suggesting that while executives are arguably trying to play everything a little straighter, they still haven’t fully grasped the lessons of the past.</p>
<p>MicroStrategy sold about 704 bitcoin units, which at the time, went for about $11.8 million. This is a huge dip in profit for the firm considering how much those units were likely purchased for. The company has been buying bitcoin for over two years, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-microstrategy-bitcoin-bet-is-already-paying-off-big-time/" data-wpel-link="internal">beginning first in August</a> of 2020. It arguably started a trend, as at that time, institutions investing in crypto just wasn’t something that really happened, and if it did, it was extremely rare.</p>
<p>MicroStrategy was the first major institution to invest in bitcoin. From there, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/square-just-bought-a-whole-lot-of-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">companies like Square</a> also took part in crypto investing. At the time of that initial purchase, MicroStrategy bought bitcoin for around $10,000 per unit, which back at the time, was considered a major number. Nobody could have anticipated that just over a year later, the currency would nearly increase its size by about six times.</p>
<p>MicroStrategy initially contended with a $2K profit gain for each unit, as the price of bitcoin instantly went from $10K to $12,000 before the month was out. Given that the company had bought over $250 million worth of the asset, it was assumed that things were moving in the right direction, though next month turned out to be particularly bearish for bitcoin, and the currency dropped in price.</p>
<p>Many other companies likely would have written their losses off and stepped away, though MicroStrategy stayed in the game. It continued <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/microstrategy-just-bought-a-whole-lot-more-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">to invest hundreds of millions</a> of dollars into BTC, and by the time BTC reached $68,000 the following November, MicroStrategy had billions of dollars in bitcoin to its name, making it one of the most successful crypto investors in history.</p>
<p>But with so many losses recorded for 2022, it’s unfortunate that those billions in profit have since turned into billions in debt. The bitcoin decision became disastrous, and Michael Saylor – the 30+ year CEO of the company – <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-btc-bull-and-microstrategy-chief-executive-steps-down/" data-wpel-link="internal">resigned from his position</a>, choosing instead to serve as the executive chairman.</p>
<h2>Trying to Grease the Tax Wheels?</h2>
<p>Regarding its recent selling and purchasing decision, MicroStrategy said in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>MicroStrategy plans to carry back the capital losses resulting from this transaction against previous capital gains, to the extent such carrybacks are available under the federal income tax laws currently in effect, which may generate a tax benefit.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/microstrategy-sells-some-btc-then-turns-around-and-buys-more/">MicroStrategy Sells Some BTC&#8230; Then Turns Around and Buys More</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/microstrategy-sells-some-btc-then-turns-around-and-buys-more/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The DOJ Is Investigating the Theft of FTX Crypto Funds</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-doj-is-investigating-the-theft-of-ftx-crypto-funds/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-doj-is-investigating-the-theft-of-ftx-crypto-funds/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 13:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76218</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The drama surrounding the fall of famed crypto exchange FTX just keeps getting bigger and bigger. FTX Will Be With Us a Long Time It has been announced that several prosecutors are looking into the disappearance of approximately $370 million in crypto funds that vanished from the exchange just hours after its head executive, Sam<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-doj-is-investigating-the-theft-of-ftx-crypto-funds/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-doj-is-investigating-the-theft-of-ftx-crypto-funds/">The DOJ Is Investigating the Theft of FTX Crypto Funds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The drama surrounding the fall of famed crypto exchange FTX just keeps getting bigger and bigger.</p>
<h2>FTX Will Be With Us a Long Time</h2>
<p>It has been <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/us-prosecutors-probing-possible-theft-150531504.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">announced that several prosecutors</a> are looking into the disappearance of approximately <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/half-a-billion-dollars-goes-missing-from-ftx-exchange/" data-wpel-link="internal">$370 million in crypto</a> funds that vanished from the exchange just hours after its head executive, Sam Bankman-Fried, filed for bankruptcy.</p>
<p>The prosecutors investigating have been hired by the Department of Justice (DOJ), which has frozen several remaining account funds to ensure they are not taken or dabbled with while the bankruptcy case proceeds or while SBF awaits his upcoming trial in California.</p>
<p>Blockchain analysis firm Elliptic announced two months ago that the funds stolen off FTX were later exchanged for ether on decentralized exchanges. Other portions went through mixers to hide the currencies’ origins and to prevent prying eyes from getting involved. In addition, the company’s new CEO John Ray III has stated that those involved with the company knew about unauthorized access taking place about 24 hours prior to the company’s bankruptcy filings, which occurred on November 11 of 2022.</p>
<p>FTX will likely go down as one of the most embarrassing blunders to ever occur within the confines of the crypto space. The exchange rose to prominence in under three years, first coming to fruition in 2019. The company was considered one of the top five crypto exchanges in the world, and Sam Bankman-Fried was lauded as a genius by many. His net worth, prior to the trading platform’s collapse, was listed at several billion dollars.</p>
<p>However, in mid-November of last year, SBF <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">began complaining of a liquidity crunch</a> on social media and made the claim that his enterprise was in fast need of cash. He initially approached his largest rival Binance about having the larger firm buy out his firm, and for a while, it <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">looked like things were</a> heading in that direction.</p>
<h2>Binance Cannot Help</h2>
<p>However, Binance eventually backed away from the deal, claiming that the problems FTX was facing were too <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">big for it to handle</a>. With too little money on hand, FTX had no <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">choice but to file bankruptcy</a>, and SBF resigned from his post as the company’s head honcho. He was later arrested and served time in a Bahamian jail before <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2022/12/19/business/sbf-extradition-bahamas/index.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">being extradited back</a> to the U.S. He is currently living at his parents’ house in the Golden State while awaiting trial.</p>
<p>The probe involving the stolen funds is separate from the charges that SBF is currently facing. It is alleged by some that the theft may have been an inside job, though significant evidence has not been uncovered to support this claim. Whoever is convicted of the theft would likely be charged with computer fraud, which presently comes with a maximum sentence of about ten years.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-doj-is-investigating-the-theft-of-ftx-crypto-funds/">The DOJ Is Investigating the Theft of FTX Crypto Funds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-doj-is-investigating-the-theft-of-ftx-crypto-funds/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
