<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 03:06:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/cropped-fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Risk of Downside Thrust Below $230</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-downside-thrust-below-230/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 03:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79475</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline below the $255 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below the $250 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $248 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-downside-thrust-below-230/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Risk of Downside Thrust Below $230</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline below the $255 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below the $250 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $248 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it stays below the $254 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin cash price is declining below the $250 zone against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. BCH/USD could extend losses if there is a close below $230.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin cash price remained in a bearish zone below the $285 and $280 resistance levels. BCH traded below the $265 support level to move further into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>There was a clear move below the $255 and $250 support levels. The pair even spiked below the $235 level. A low is formed near $231.62 and the price is now consolidating losses. It attempted a move above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $295.00 swing high to the $231.62 low.</p>
<p>However, the bears seem to be active near $254 and $255. BCH is now trading below the $250 zone and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bears-in-action-below-250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. There is also a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $248 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair.</p>
<p>The next key resistance is near $264 and the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $295.00 swing high to the $231.62 low. Any more gains above $115 could set the pace for a move toward the $285 level.</p>
<p>If there is a move above the $285 resistance, the price could rise toward the $295 zone. If not, the price might continue lower below $235. Immediate support on the downside is near the $230 zone. The next major support is near the $225 level, below which the bears might aim for $212.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79476" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79476" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-3.png"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-79476" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-3.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-3.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-3-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-3-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-3-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-3-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-3-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-3-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79476" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Cash Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BCHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, Bitcoin cash price is now trading below the $250 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $254 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for BCH/USD is losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BCH/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $230 and $225.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $254 and $264.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-downside-thrust-below-230/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Risk of Downside Thrust Below $230</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The SEC is Making Crypto Investors (and Platforms) Very Nervous</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-is-making-crypto-investors-very-nervous/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Yuya Hasegawa]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78783</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Many crypto investors are working hard to get rid of their altcoins out of fear that several of them are going to get delisted thanks to ongoing action from the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). SEC Action is Making Traders Wary The financial agency has been working hard to practically eliminate crypto altogether from the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-is-making-crypto-investors-very-nervous/">The SEC is Making Crypto Investors (and Platforms) Very Nervous</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Many crypto investors are working hard to get rid <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/06/13/crypto-braced-for-a-24-billion-earthquake-after-sec-bombshell-hit-the-price-of-bitcoin-and-ethereum/?sh=5c047d515762">of their altcoins</a> out of fear that several of them are going to get delisted thanks to ongoing action from the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<h2>SEC Action is Making Traders Wary</h2>
<p>The financial agency has been working hard to practically eliminate crypto altogether from the American monetary spectrum. There have already been multiple lawsuits filed against some of the nation’s leading digital currency companies including <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sues-binance-alleges-selling-of-illegal-securities/">Binance</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-hit-with-sec-lawsuit-says-it-operated-as-an-exchange-broker/">Coinbase</a>, and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/">Kraken</a>, and there are many traders out there that are worried about what could arrive in the coming weeks and months as the SEC potentially ramps up its efforts.</p>
<p>There are also many companies out there that don’t want to be tangled up with crypto assets that could allegedly be considered securities in the coming future. For example, trading application Robinhood announced that it will no longer be selling Cardano, Solana, and Matic. In a statement, the company said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We regularly review the crypto we offer on Robinhood.</p></blockquote>
<p>Leading exchange e-Toro also said that it’s going to end future support for Matic, Algorand, and Decentraland. All three of these tokens have market caps that come to a combined total of $24 billion, so one can assume the delisting activity is not going to produce solid results for the space. On Twitter, the company explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>We are committed to working closely with regulators around the world to shape the future of the crypto industry and champion access for the ordinary investor.</p></blockquote>
<p>Yuya Hasegawa – bitcoin and crypto market analyst at Bit Bank in Tokyo – said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The SEC’s legal battle against Binance and Coinbase has created a ripple effect where other U.S. virtual asset service providers began to halt certain services and delist some trading pairs out of concern for [the] SEC’s legal actions. Particularly, Robinhood’s decision on Friday to delist Cardano, Polygon, and Solana had a noticeable impact on the prices of those tokens and some other altcoins. Bitcoin was [also] affected, but its decline was limited compared to others, and the price has been supported by its February high. Bitcoin has been holding it together relatively well while the majority of altcoins suffered huge losses last week, but it is in for a potentially quite precarious week as more bad news could come up anytime regarding [the] SEC’s legal action, and the wider financial markets brace for [the looming Fed interest rate decision].</p></blockquote>
<h2>Gary Gensler&#8217;s Thoughts (Originally) on Crypto</h2>
<p>As discussed earlier today, the SEC has not always been after crypto like it is now. Gary Gensler – the present head of the SEC – has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gary-gensler-at-one-time-thought-differently-about-crypto-as-video-footage-shows/">commented in the past</a> that assets like BTC, ETH, and LTC don’t fall into the securities category.</p>
<p>In fact, he was convinced that roughly three quarters of the crypto assets out there don’t classify as securities.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-is-making-crypto-investors-very-nervous/">The SEC is Making Crypto Investors (and Platforms) Very Nervous</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Itoka Wants to Use Blockchain to Register All AI-Based Jingles</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/itoka-is-looking-to-register-all-ai-music-on-the-blockchain/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 15:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI-generated music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Itoka]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78778</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Itoka is a new platform that’s working to ensure all AI-generated music can be licensed and registered via the blockchain. Itoka Uses Blockchain to Register AI Songs AI-generated tunes are becoming more and more common. Who would have thought that a time would arrive when someone could literally create whatever notes they want without singing, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/itoka-is-looking-to-register-all-ai-music-on-the-blockchain/">Itoka Wants to Use Blockchain to Register All AI-Based Jingles</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Itoka is a new platform that’s working to ensure all AI-generated music <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/itoka-wants-to-license-ai-generated-music-via-the-blockchain/ar-AA1cuS43">can be licensed and registered</a> via the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/blockchain/">blockchain</a>.</p>
<h2>Itoka Uses Blockchain to Register AI Songs</h2>
<p>AI-generated tunes are becoming more and more common. Who would have thought that a time would arrive when someone could literally create whatever notes they want without singing, playing an instrument, or knowing how to read music? We’ve come so far that we’re practically reaching a day and age where nobody needs to do anything, and they could still be successful and have huge careers.</p>
<p>Not long ago, Itoka was accepted into the Allen Institute for AI”s startup incubation program. Blockchain, as we all know, is predominantly considered to be the technology behind cryptocurrency, though there are many advocates out there that seem to believe it can be applied to other industries such as healthcare and manufacturing. Perhaps music registration and licensing can be another.</p>
<p>Co-founded by Malcolm Yang and Yihao Chen, the company seeks to “tokenize” music, therefore allowing all content creators to independently license their material and receive due compensation every time their music is played or used. Itoka puts temporary holds on the ownership of songs and works to prevent plagiarism on all licensed or registered material.</p>
<p>The co-founders explained in a joint statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>Itoka is a decentralized music platform we developed to enable data self-sovereignty, the permanence of music storage, digital rights management, global music accessibility, and creator governance. We establish a new paradigm for copyright protection that doesn’t rely on the physical copyright office to enforce the legal status, but rather on code-operated smart contracts.</p></blockquote>
<p>The company also provides tools that customers can use to enhance their tunes. There are even products and programs available to individuals that have no experience whatsoever in this field, and they’re looking to create AI-generated music for the first time. The co-founders said:</p>
<blockquote><p>In the future, everyone will have the power to produce music, and there will be a massive amount of quality music produced every day for various purposes. As music production becomes democratized, the establishment of the current music industry and its monopoly will be significantly undermined. This will urge people to rethink creativity and artistry in content creation.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Working with Game Developers</h2>
<p>They completed their statement by claiming that they’re looking to target game developers as their main audience members, and the company has partnered with a firm called Canva for game content licensing purposes. They said:</p>
<blockquote><p>In the future, we will be more than happy to move on to other customer sectors and provide the most-fitting features and solutions. There are some AI-friendly musicians who’d like to help us push the boundaries of technology and music creativity, and we sincerely hope that we can achieve greatness with them together</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/itoka-is-looking-to-register-all-ai-music-on-the-blockchain/">Itoka Wants to Use Blockchain to Register All AI-Based Jingles</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gary Gensler, at One Time, Thought Differently About Crypto as Video Footage Shows</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gary-gensler-at-one-time-thought-differently-about-crypto-as-video-footage-shows/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 13:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78776</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Some interesting video footage from several years back has resurfaced that’s making people see Gary Gensler and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) a tad differently. Gary Gensler and His Original Feelings Towards Crypto In the video, Gensler – not yet in charge of the financial agency – told his audience of investors he thinks [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gary-gensler-at-one-time-thought-differently-about-crypto-as-video-footage-shows/">Gary Gensler, at One Time, Thought Differently About Crypto as Video Footage Shows</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Some interesting video footage from several years back has <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/sec-s-gensler-seen-telling-hedge-funds-that-ethereum-and-litecoin-are-not-securities-in-2018-video/ar-AA1csLWZ">resurfaced that’s making</a> people see Gary Gensler and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) a tad differently.</p>
<h2>Gary Gensler and His Original Feelings Towards Crypto</h2>
<p>In the video, Gensler – not yet in charge of the financial agency – told his audience of investors he thinks four cryptocurrencies – bitcoin, bitcoin cash, Ethereum, and Litecoin – are not securities, but things didn’t quite stop there. He also mentioned he doesn’t think about three quarters (75 percent) of the altcoins out there fall into the securities category.</p>
<p>The video is from the year 2018. Gensler explains in the footage:</p>
<blockquote><p>Over 70 percent of the crypto market is bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin, [and] bitcoin cash. Why did I name those four? They’re not securities. Three quarters of this [digital asset] market are not securities.</p></blockquote>
<p>The footage is making many crypto investors angry at the time of writing… as it should be. Gensler, like everyone in the Biden administration, has sought to end the reign of crypto in America because this is the one aspect of finance that he and his nation-hating associates cannot control. The thing about bitcoin and crypto is they were not built to be overseen the way standard or traditional banks are.</p>
<p>This time around, it’s the people (the users) who are in charge. So long as they have a digital wallet and an internet connection, a person can get engaged in crypto trading and use the assets to garner everyday items they’ll need for themselves and their families. This is the opposite of the situation surrounding banks, where literally everything you do is monitored by a third party or wandering pair of eyes.</p>
<p>Over the past several months, the SEC and Gensler have done everything in their power to take down the country’s largest crypto businesses. There have been multiple lawsuits filed against leading exchanges like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sues-binance-alleges-selling-of-illegal-securities/">Binance</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-hit-with-sec-lawsuit-says-it-operated-as-an-exchange-broker/">Coinbase</a>, and the latter is working hard to prove itself and fight back, as executives claim to have been working with representatives of the SEC over a nine-year period to ensure the company always remained compliant.</p>
<p>Other names, like Kraken, have also fallen victim. Recently, the exchange was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/">forced to part with</a> a $30 million penalty fee and end all its staking activities and practices.</p>
<h2>So Many Attempts to Shut Crypto Out</h2>
<p>When Gensler and the SEC aren’t attacking crypto, other members of this administration are. Biden, for example, has sought to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/biden-wants-to-tax-crypto-mining-companies-at-30/">impose a 30 percent</a> tax on all mining companies and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-biden-using-an-obama-era-program-to-ban-btc/">initiate an Obama-era</a> policy that would shut all crypto companies out of standard financial products.</p>
<p>It’s become clear that while Gensler may have felt one way about crypto five years ago, he’s clearly fallen into the Biden agenda of removing all individual liberties and keeping people in line with the federal (tyrannical) regime.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gary-gensler-at-one-time-thought-differently-about-crypto-as-video-footage-shows/">Gary Gensler, at One Time, Thought Differently About Crypto as Video Footage Shows</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EOS Price Analysis: Risk of More Losses Below $0.73</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-0-73/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 05:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EOS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79463</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>EOS price started a fresh decline from the $0.80 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $0.765 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $0.767 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-0-73/">EOS Price Analysis: Risk of More Losses Below $0.73</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>EOS price started a fresh decline from the $0.80 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $0.765 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $0.767 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to decline if it stays below the $0.760 and $0.780 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>EOS price is struggling below $0.760 against the US Dollar, like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. The price might attempt to recover if there is a clear move above $0.760.</em></p>
<h2>EOS Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, EOS price saw a fresh decline from the $0.80 resistance against the US Dollar. The price traded below the $0.765 and $0.750 levels to move into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>Besides, there was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $0.767 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair. The pair even spiked below the $0.730 support. A low is formed near $0.7276 and the price is now consolidating losses.</p>
<p>EOS is trading well below $0.765 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-key-uptrend-support-nearby/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $0.760 level. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.7915 swing high to the $0.7276 low.</p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $0.765 level or the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.7915 swing high to the $0.7276 low. A clear move above the $0.765 level could start a steady increase toward the $0.78 level. The next major resistance might be $0.80. Any more gains might send the price toward the $0.850 level.</p>
<p>On the downside, immediate support is near $0.735. The next key support is near the $0.730 level. If there is a downside break below the $0.730 support, the price could test the $0.705 support in the near term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79464" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79464" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-3.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-79464" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-3.png" alt="EOS Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-3.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-3-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-3-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-3-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-3-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-3-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-3-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79464" class="wp-caption-text">EOS Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/EOSUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, EOS price is now trading below the $0.765 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to decline if it stays below the $0.765 and $0.780 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for EOS/USD is losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $0.730 and $0.705.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $0.765 and $0.800.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-0-73/">EOS Price Analysis: Risk of More Losses Below $0.73</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Fresh Increase Possible Above This Resistance</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-fresh-increase-possible-above-this-resistance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 03:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79459</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin is slowly moving higher from the $88 support against the US Dollar. LTC price is now trading below $92 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $92.00 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-fresh-increase-possible-above-this-resistance/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Fresh Increase Possible Above This Resistance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Litecoin is slowly moving higher from the $88 support against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>LTC price is now trading below $92 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $92.00 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $92 and $95 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Litecoin price is recovering from the $88 zone against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. LTC price could climb again if there is a clear move above $92.</em></p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few sessions, there were mostly range moves in Bitcoin, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-shows-bearish-signs-below-1900/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a>, Ripple, and Litecoin against the US Dollar. Earlier, LTC declined heavily below the $95 pivot level.</p>
<p>The price traded below the $92 and $90 levels. However, the bulls were active near the $88 zone. The price is now attempting a recovery wave and trading above $90. There was a move above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $96.44 swing high to the $87.39 low.</p>
<p>Litecoin is now trading below $92 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $92 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $92.00 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>The trend line is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $96.44 swing high to the $87.39 low. A clear move above the $92 level could push the price toward the $95 zone.</p>
<p>The next major resistance sits near the $98.50 level. Any more gains might send the price toward the $100 level. On the downside, initial support is near the $89.50 level. The next major support is near the $88 level. If there is a downside break below the $88 support, the price could accelerate lower toward the $82 level in the near term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79460" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79460" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-3.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-79460" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-3.png" alt="Litecoin (LTC) Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-3.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-3-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-3-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-3-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-3-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-3-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-3-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79460" class="wp-caption-text">Litecoin (LTC) Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/">chart</a>, Litecoin’s price is trading below $92 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $92 and $95 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LTC/USD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $89.50 and $87.40.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $92 and $95.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-fresh-increase-possible-above-this-resistance/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Fresh Increase Possible Above This Resistance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>a16z Lands $43 Million for New Blockchain Firm Gensyn</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/a16z-lands-43-million-for-new-blockchain-firm-gensyn/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[a16z]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gensyn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[london]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78767</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Earlier today, we put out a news story talking about a16z. The venture capital firm has lots of big blockchain-related plans including opening a new crypto school aimed at garnering funds for blockchain startups, setting up a new office in London, and continuing its funding of blockchain businesses. a16z Helps Gensyn Move Forward This new [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/a16z-lands-43-million-for-new-blockchain-firm-gensyn/">a16z Lands $43 Million for New Blockchain Firm Gensyn</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Earlier today, we put out a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/a16z-announces-plans-for-new-blockchain-startups-and-divisions/">news story talking</a> about a16z. The venture capital firm has lots of big blockchain-related plans including opening a new crypto school aimed at garnering funds for blockchain startups, setting up a new office in London, and continuing its funding of blockchain businesses.</p>
<h2>a16z Helps Gensyn Move Forward</h2>
<p>This new article has to do <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/blockchain-based-ai-compute-protocol-gensyn-closes-43m-series-a-funding-round-led-by-a16z/ar-AA1cq2nF">with the latter</a>, as recently, a $43 million funding round was secured by a16z for a new blockchain company called Gensyn. The firm is a provider of blockchain computing resources for AI platforms. Gensyn co-founder Ben Fielding explained in a recent press release:</p>
<blockquote><p>The realization of its (AI’s) potential requires huge computational power. We’re harnessing the electricity of a new age and making it available to everyone at unlimited scale and fair market prices.</p></blockquote>
<p>The company is centered right in the heart of London, where a16z is planning to expand. Right now, the company’s protocol enables developers to establish new AI systems on smaller data centers, personal gaming computers, and other hardware for paying on demand. The goal is to get rid of all intermediaries, thus ensuring a fully trustless environment, keeping middlemen out of the fray, and guaranteeing that all machine-learning work is completed correctly.</p>
<p>The firm’s co-founder Harry Grieve also threw his two cents into the mix, commenting:</p>
<blockquote><p>With decentralized networks, value simply accrues to the network as a function of supply and demand. It also sharply increases the amount of compute supply by connecting previously underutilized hardware from around the world.</p></blockquote>
<p>General partner at a16z Ali Yahya said the growing number of advancements in AI are truly astounding. Thus, helping to fund Gensyn made perfect sense. Yahya said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The recent advancements in AI are incredible, but substantial computational power requirements give big technology companies an advantage over startups in the race to capture AI’s value. We believe nobody combines the knowledge and cultural understanding of both the AI and crypto cypher punk worlds better than Gensyn, and [we] look forward to partnering with them to make infrastructure for AI much more widely accessible.</p></blockquote>
<p>With this latest round, the company has garnered more than $50 million in new funding. The firm said it’s planning to use the money to grow its workforce and bring additional protocol and machine-learning engineers aboard.</p>
<p>While the funding round was led by a16z, many venture capital firms – including Coin Fund, Canonical Crypto, Protocol Labs, Eden Block, and others – were quick to take part and offer cash payments to help the growing company get what it needed.</p>
<h2>AI Keeps Getting Bigger</h2>
<p>Fielding concluded with:</p>
<blockquote><p>The key to useful, aligned AI is allowing everyone in the world to contribute to its development.</p></blockquote>
<p>The news comes just as the world of AI is expanding further than ever.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/a16z-lands-43-million-for-new-blockchain-firm-gensyn/">a16z Lands $43 Million for New Blockchain Firm Gensyn</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>a16z Releases Plans for New Blockchain Startups and Divisions</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/a16z-announces-plans-for-new-blockchain-startups-and-divisions/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 15:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[a16z]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chris Dixon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[london]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78764</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Venture capital firm Andreessen Horowitz (a16z) said it’s opening its first international space in London and it’s also starting what it’s calling the Crypto Startup School, an accelerator program designed to help digital currency startups garner the funds and resources they need to stay afloat. The company also said it wants to expand its present [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/a16z-announces-plans-for-new-blockchain-startups-and-divisions/">a16z Releases Plans for New Blockchain Startups and Divisions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Venture capital firm Andreessen Horowitz (a16z) said <a href="https://www.crowdfundinsider.com/2023/06/208600-andreessen-horowitz-a16z-announces-expansion-to-united-kingdom-looks-to-boost-blockchain-development/">it’s opening its first international</a> space in London and it’s also starting what it’s calling the Crypto Startup School, an accelerator program designed to help digital currency startups garner the funds and resources they need to stay afloat. The company also said it wants to expand its present blockchain program.</p>
<h2>a16z to Open New London Office</h2>
<p>a16z is closely working with universities throughout the London area to garner the talent and support necessary to establish blockchain clubs and curriculum throughout the region. In a statement, Chris Dixon – the founder and managing partner of a16z – said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The UK has deep pools of talent, world-leading academic institutions, and a strong entrepreneurial culture. Following a productive dialogue with the Prime Minister, and months of constructive conversations with [the] HM Treasury, U.K. policymakers, and the Financial Conduct Authority, we’re thrilled to open our first international office in a jurisdiction that welcomes blockchain technology and is committed to creating a predictable business environment by pursuing regulations that both embrace web3 and protect consumers. We look forward to helping foster the growth of the U.K. web3 ecosystem while the proper regulations come online.</p></blockquote>
<p>U.K. prime minister Rishi Sunak – a long-time blockchain and bitcoin fan – also threw his two cents into the mix, commenting:</p>
<blockquote><p> As we cement the U.K.’s place as a science and tech superpower, we must embrace new innovations like web3, powered by blockchain technology, which will enable startups to flourish here and grow the economy. That success is founded on having the right regulation and guardrails in place to protect consumers and foster innovation. While there’s still work to do, I’m determined to unlock opportunities for this technology and turn the U.K. into the world’s Web3 center… That’s why I am thrilled world-leading investor Andreessen Horowitz has decided to open their first international office in the U.K., which is testament to our world-class universities and talent and our strong competitive business environment.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Working with More Small Businesses</h2>
<p>The London office is going to be opening in late 2023 and will be run by general partner Sriram Krishnan. Thus far, the company has invested in a wide array of crypto firms including Aztec and Improbable. In a separate statement, the company mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p> We are also excited to announce our newest investment in U.K.-based Gensyn. Founded by computer science and machine-learning research veterans Ben Fielding and Harry Grieve, Gensyn’s decentralized compute protocol will enable developers to build state-of-the-art AI systems on any connected hardware. Their novel cryptographic verification system allows users to trust that the protocol’s machine-learning work was completed correctly.</p></blockquote>
<p>The relationship between blockchain and the U.K. has grown heavily in recent months given the nation was one <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-united-kingdom-announces-plans-for-new-crypto-regulations/">of the first to implement</a> hardcore crypto regulation after the fall of FTX.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/a16z-announces-plans-for-new-blockchain-startups-and-divisions/">a16z Releases Plans for New Blockchain Startups and Divisions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Texas Blockchain Council President: I Want My State to Be the Ultimate Blockchain Haven</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-blockchain-council-president-i-want-my-state-to-be-the-ultimate-blockchain-haven/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 13:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lee Bratcher]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Texas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78762</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lee Bratcher – president of the Texas Blockchain Council – said in a recent interview he wants his state to become the biggest blockchain haven in the United States. He further mentioned that he would like his Texas to become the Silicon Valley of blockchain. The Texas Mining Agenda Keeps Growing The state’s 88th legislative [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-blockchain-council-president-i-want-my-state-to-be-the-ultimate-blockchain-haven/">Texas Blockchain Council President: I Want My State to Be the Ultimate Blockchain Haven</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lee Bratcher – president of the Texas Blockchain Council – said in a <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/lone-star-state-silicon-valley-152118086.html">recent interview he wants</a> his state to become the biggest blockchain haven in the United States. He further mentioned that he would like his Texas to become the Silicon Valley of blockchain.</p>
<h2>The Texas Mining Agenda Keeps Growing</h2>
<p>The state’s 88th legislative session has been quite productive. Thus far, one crypto law has passed already, while many others are waiting in the wings (passage is expected on several). The goal is to ensure the region remains attractive to miners, which have been heading into Texas for the past two years ever since China announced the practice was illegal. Bratcher said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The microchip was invented in 1958, but that technology was monetized in California. Texas is not going to let that happen again. Texas will be the Silicon Valley of the digital asset industry.</p></blockquote>
<p>China said it would no longer <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-crypto-mining-clampdown-in-china-is-not-over/">allow digital currency</a> mining in the summer of 2021. The idea was that new rules had emerged from Beijing, and the rest of the country was seeking to comply and become greener in its energy endeavors. Many companies were forced to either shut down completely or go to other regions.</p>
<p>Several chose to focus on Texas given it has vast open spaces and low energy costs. The mining migration of the last two years allowed Texas to grow its economy, while several new jobs have opened. Overall, things have been relatively positive. However, there have been issues in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-texas-is-suffering-from-too-much-btc-mining/">that now energy usage</a> in the state has expanded tenfold, and this has prevented some residents from garnering access to the electricity they need to power their homes.</p>
<p>One of the bills designed to tackle this issue was Senate Bill 1929, which passed without much opposition. The idea is to get most mining companies to register with the Electric Reliability Council of Texas (ERCOT) so that they’re more transparent regarding their energy. Bratcher said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We did vocally support SB 1929, which requires large flexible loads over 75 megawatts to register certain details about their load with the grid operator ERCOT. This bill will prove helpful in strengthening the communication between ERCOT and bitcoin miners.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Making Things Safe for Traders</h2>
<p>Another bill, HB 1666, puts <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-passes-new-proof-of-reserves-bill-for-crypto-exchanges/">pressure on crypto exchanges</a> to be clear about how many funds they have in their reserves and to keep all customers safe. Texas director of Public Citizen Adrian Shelley explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>From our perspective, what you&#8217;re doing here is getting a new value stream to the industry that is otherwise starting to be priced out of the market… This is an industry that&#8217;s not bringing clear or tangible value into a state, [whereas] it&#8217;s got all of these exotic mechanisms for extracting value out of it.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-blockchain-council-president-i-want-my-state-to-be-the-ultimate-blockchain-haven/">Texas Blockchain Council President: I Want My State to Be the Ultimate Blockchain Haven</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
