<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 03:15:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Changpeng Zhao to Justin Sun: Don&#8217;t Try Buying My New Tokens!</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/changpeng-zhao-to-justin-sun-dont-try-buying-my-new-tokens/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/changpeng-zhao-to-justin-sun-dont-try-buying-my-new-tokens/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 17:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Justin Sun]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78156</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance head Changpeng Zhao has taken to Twitter to warn Justin Sun – the main executive behind crypto firm Tron – against using his own funds to garner the exchange’s new SUI tokens. Zhao to Sun: Your Money&#8217;s Not Welcome! Zhao has made it clear that these units are designed more for retail traders and<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/changpeng-zhao-to-justin-sun-dont-try-buying-my-new-tokens/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/changpeng-zhao-to-justin-sun-dont-try-buying-my-new-tokens/">Changpeng Zhao to Justin Sun: Don&#8217;t Try Buying My New Tokens!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance head Changpeng Zhao has taken to Twitter to warn Justin Sun – the main executive behind crypto firm Tron – against <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/binance-warns-blockchain-whale-justin-sun-of-the-consequences-over-sui-token-grab/ar-AA1aAMzd" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">using his own funds</a> to garner the exchange’s new SUI tokens.</p>
<h2>Zhao to Sun: Your Money&#8217;s Not Welcome!</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/changpeng-zhao/" data-wpel-link="internal">Zhao</a> has made it clear that these units are designed more for retail traders and that he doesn’t want “whales” (individuals with wallets stuffed to the gills with specific kinds of crypto) taking over the industry or dominating new tokens. He wants to make sure all crypto assets are distributed fairly and equally amongst users. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Our team told Justin, if he uses any of these to grab the Launch Pool Sui token, we will &#8216;take action against it.&#8217; SMH. Binance Launch Pool[s] are meant as air drops for our retail users, not just for a few whales. On the bright side, blockchains are transparent.</p></blockquote>
<p>When it first came to the scene, crypto was built to establish a degree of fairness amongst financial players that wasn’t being seen in the world of traditional finance. Many standard banks have too much control over who gains access to assets and services. Things like one’s credit history, job history, and other elements can all get in the way, and those behind crypto wanted to see a few changes thrown into the mix.</p>
<p>When it comes to crypto, your background doesn’t really matter. All you really need is a digital wallet and an internet connection and you can use, buy, trade, and sell assets as you see fit. There are no prying eyes, middlemen, or third parties involved to go against you or say what you can and cannot do. Crypto provides autonomy, independence, and a democratic financial status.</p>
<p>However, these principles haven’t always been at the forefront of trading activities, as many individuals and institutions have sought to gather up as much crypto as they can to ensure their wealth remains steadily growing. Sadly, this has cut out many smaller players who either cannot gain access to the units in question or who can no longer afford them thanks to ongoing buys.</p>
<h2>Not Interested in Exchange Promotions</h2>
<p>Sun defended his actions against Zhao, saying he is not one to blatantly take part in exchange promotions. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>As a partner market maker for TUSD, TRON DAO Venture&#8217;s primary objective in depositing TUSD is to facilitate market-making between leading TUSD exchanges, thereby enhancing liquidity and trading volume, rather than participating in any exchange promotions. In just the past few hours, our market maker has achieved a total trading volume of 40 million USD, contributing to the stability of TUSD&#8217;s price.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also stated that many of his team members who had already purchased units of the new coins weren’t aware that they were part of a specific exchange campaign.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/changpeng-zhao-to-justin-sun-dont-try-buying-my-new-tokens/">Changpeng Zhao to Justin Sun: Don&#8217;t Try Buying My New Tokens!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/changpeng-zhao-to-justin-sun-dont-try-buying-my-new-tokens/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase is Boosting Its Fight Against the SEC</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-is-boosting-its-fight-against-the-sec/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-is-boosting-its-fight-against-the-sec/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 15:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78154</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto exchange Coinbase is upping its fight against the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The company received a Wells notice from the federal agency over a month ago, and it’s not happy that Gary Gensler and his cronies are targeting its operations. Coinbase Vs. the SEC: Who Will Win? A Wells notice doesn’t necessarily mean<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-is-boosting-its-fight-against-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-is-boosting-its-fight-against-the-sec/">Coinbase is Boosting Its Fight Against the SEC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto exchange Coinbase is <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/coinbase-offers-a-fiery-response-to-the-secs-threat-of-enforcement-action/ar-AA1arecC" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">upping its fight against</a> the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The company received a Wells notice <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">from the federal agency</a> over a month ago, and it’s not happy that Gary Gensler and his cronies are targeting its operations.</p>
<h2>Coinbase Vs. the SEC: Who Will Win?</h2>
<p>A Wells notice doesn’t necessarily mean that a company is being charged with a crime. Rather, it’s a warning or indication that charges are likely coming, and thus the company may want to consult with a legal team to get itself prepared.</p>
<p>Coinbase took serious issue with the notice given it has allegedly met with the SEC over 30 times in the past nine years as a means of always familiarizing itself with present laws and trying to stay compliant.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the SEC has made it clear it does not care about which crypto companies are following rules or not. It’s simply going after any digital currency company it can as a means of making a statement. The SEC doesn’t want crypto around, and it’ll do just about anything to end the industry in America once and for all.</p>
<p>Coinbase issued a statement in May claiming that if the SEC was dumb enough to charge it with a crime or go against it in some way, it would work against the agency and pose “major programmatic risks.” The company also said that the SEC would “fail on the merits.”</p>
<p>The statement also mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Coinbase does not list, clear, or effect trading in securities.</p></blockquote>
<p>Legal compliance officer for the exchange Paul Grewal also said to separate news sources:</p>
<blockquote><p>At the time when we went public, we had detailed discussions with the SEC about the very aspects of our business that are now — two years later — the subject of the Wells notice. Nothing has changed.</p></blockquote>
<p>He stated that the SEC reviewed all forms when it went public and that it could have denied the company’s plans back in 2021.</p>
<p>The SEC had developed a reputation for being a bully when it comes to crypto, or any companies involved in the digital currency arena. Not long ago, Kraken – a popular trading platform based in Northern California – was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/" data-wpel-link="internal">the subject of SEC scrutiny</a> that saw it lose more than $30 million in penalty fees. It was also forced to cease all staking activities and services.</p>
<h2>Nothing&#8217;s Changed!</h2>
<p>Coinbase is claiming total innocence in the present matter and said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Coinbase&#8217;s retail staking services fail all four prongs of the Howey test. The SEC generally does not acknowledge the existence or non-existence of any investigation unless or until charges are filed. Coinbase has never wanted to litigate with the Commission. The Commission should not want to litigate either. Litigation will put the Commission&#8217;s own actions on trial.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-is-boosting-its-fight-against-the-sec/">Coinbase is Boosting Its Fight Against the SEC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-is-boosting-its-fight-against-the-sec/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDIC Goes After Crypto-Friendly Institution Cross River Bank</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fdic-goes-after-crypto-friendly-institution-cross-river-bank/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fdic-goes-after-crypto-friendly-institution-cross-river-bank/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 13:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[FinTech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cross River Bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FDIC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78152</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cross River Bank (CRB) – a crypto-friendly financial institution stationed in New Jersey – has angered the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC). It’s claiming that the bank hasn’t done enough to keep traders’ and customers’ assets safe. The FDIC Targets Cross River Bank The FDIC is now taking enforcement action against the bank. This action<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fdic-goes-after-crypto-friendly-institution-cross-river-bank/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fdic-goes-after-crypto-friendly-institution-cross-river-bank/">FDIC Goes After Crypto-Friendly Institution Cross River Bank</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cross River Bank (CRB) – a crypto-friendly financial institution stationed in New Jersey – has angered the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC). It’s <a href="https://www.crowdfundinsider.com/2023/04/206316-cross-river-bank-target-of-fdic-enforcement-action/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">claiming that the bank</a> hasn’t done enough to keep traders’ and customers’ assets safe.</p>
<h2>The FDIC Targets Cross River Bank</h2>
<p>The FDIC is now taking enforcement action against the bank. This action has been accepted by Cross River’s board of directors. The order was filed in early March, but for some reason, failed to make it into the news until now. The order states the following:</p>
<blockquote><p>The FDIC considered the matter and determined, and the Bank neither admits [nor] denies, that it engaged in the unsafe or unsound banking practices related to its compliance with applicable fair lending laws and regulations by failing to establish and maintain internal controls, information systems, and prudent credit underwriting practices.</p></blockquote>
<p>CRB has been ordered by the FDIC to boost the supervision of its management team. This means the institution must implement internal controls and credit underwriting to ensure all compliance measures are met through its lending program. In addition, the company must also assume all responsibility for transactions regardless of their sizes or the assets involved.</p>
<p>The FDIC is clearly worried that another crypto-based bank could wind up in the dunk tank like so many others have in recent weeks. America is in the middle of its worst banking crisis since the Great Recession of 2008, and more failed institutions could bring the U.S. to its knees.</p>
<p>Among the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-more-banks-fell-bitcoin-rose-beyond-28k/" data-wpel-link="internal">institutions that have crashed</a> and burned as of late are Silicon Valley Bank, Signature, and Silvergate. Other institutions, such as Credit Suisse, were practically on the verge of death, but were saved at the last minute through buyouts. Not long ago, problems <a href="https://thehill.com/business/3911002-what-to-know-about-first-republic-bank/#:~:text=First%20Republic%20Bank%20is%20the%20latest%20financial%20institution,two%20weeks%20as%20large%20depositors%20pulled%20their%20funds." data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">arose for companies</a> like First Republic.</p>
<h2>Working with Several Fintech Clients</h2>
<p>An anonymous spokesperson for CRB has stated that the bank has not admitted to any wrongdoing, though it’s not denying anything either. They said that the institution is looking forward to working with the FDIC and implementing appropriate safety measures. They mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>As we know, CRB is one of the foundational banks during the fintech renaissance period and partners with some of the first and biggest fintech players in existence. CRB has a very short period to answer some tough questions from the FDIC, and to do it properly with all their fintech partners. It’s [a] tall order by any measure. Every fintech partner may have to provide their individual practices with respect to Cross River’s offerings to complete the major tasks within the consent order, and it will have a large ripple effect across the industry.  One of the most difficult tasks to complete is to show to the FDIC that the bank and their partners are following fair lending laws and regulations.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fdic-goes-after-crypto-friendly-institution-cross-river-bank/">FDIC Goes After Crypto-Friendly Institution Cross River Bank</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fdic-goes-after-crypto-friendly-institution-cross-river-bank/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Faces Uphill Task Near $0.086</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-faces-uphill-task-near-0-086/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-faces-uphill-task-near-0-086/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 05:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar Lumens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78758</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stellar lumen price is struggling below the $0.0880 resistance zone against the US Dollar. XLM price is now trading below $0.0880 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0855 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could start a recovery<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-faces-uphill-task-near-0-086/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-faces-uphill-task-near-0-086/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Faces Uphill Task Near $0.086</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Stellar lumen price is struggling below the $0.0880 resistance zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>XLM price is now trading below $0.0880 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0855 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a recovery wave if it clears the $0.0855 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Stellar lumen price is trading below $0.0880 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-soon-revisit-28500/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. XLM price could extend losses if it trades below the $0.0800 support.</em></p>
<h2>Stellar Lumen Price Analysis (XLM to USD)</h2>
<p>After a sharp decline below $0.085, Stellar Lumen price struggled to gain bullish momentum against the US Dollar. The XLM/USD pair traded below the $0.0820 level to move further into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>A low was formed near $0.0786 before the price started an upside correction. There was a move above the $0.0800 and $0.0810 levels. The price climbed above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $0.0890 swing high to the $0.0786 low.</p>
<p>The price is now facing resistance near the $0.0838 level. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $0.0890 swing high to the $0.0786 low.</p>
<p>There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0855 on the 4-hour chart. XLM is now trading below $0.0850 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-eyes-fresh-increase-above-0-092/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. Initial support on the downside is near the $0.0810 level. The next major support is near the $0.0800 zone.</p>
<p>Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.0785 level in the near term, below which the price might even retest $0.07650. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $0.0855 level and the trend line.</p>
<p>A clear upside break above the $0.0855 zone might send the price toward $0.0880. Any more gains could lead the price toward the $0.0900 level or even $0.0920.</p>
<div id="attachment_78759" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78759" class="size-full wp-image-78759" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-1.png" alt="Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78759" class="wp-caption-text">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XLMUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that XLM price is now trading below $0.0880 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start a recovery wave if it clears the $0.0855 resistance.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XLM/USD is gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for XLM/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.0810 and $0.080.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.0838, $0.0850, and $0.0855.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-faces-uphill-task-near-0-086/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Faces Uphill Task Near $0.086</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-faces-uphill-task-near-0-086/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Price Analysis: Fresh Rally Possible Above $0.54</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-fresh-rally-possible-above-0-54/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-fresh-rally-possible-above-0-54/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 03:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78755</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple price started a downside correction from the $0.5450 zone against the US dollar. The price is now trading below $0.520 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.530 on the 4-hours chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Kraken). The pair<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-fresh-rally-possible-above-0-54/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-fresh-rally-possible-above-0-54/">Ripple Price Analysis: Fresh Rally Possible Above $0.54</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ripple price started a downside correction from the $0.5450 zone against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $0.520 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.530 on the 4-hours chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a major increase above the $0.530 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ripple price is consolidating near $0.520 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-soon-revisit-28500/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. XRP price must stay above the $0.4850 support to remain in a bullish zone.</em></p>
<h2>Ripple Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In recent days, Ripple price saw a strong increase above the $0.500 resistance against the US Dollar. The XRP/USD pair even climbed above the $0.52 resistance to move into a positive zone.</p>
<p>There was a steady increase and the price climbed toward the $0.532 resistance. A high was formed near $0.5411 and the price recently corrected lower. There was a move below the $0.520 and $0.500 levels. It tested the $0.4750 zone.</p>
<p>A low is formed near $0.4752 and the price is now rising. It broke the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-in-control-above-0-50/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">$0.50 resistance zone</a>. There was a move above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.5411 swing high to the $0.4752 low. XRP price is now trading below $0.52 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near $0.520 or the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.5411 swing high to the $0.4752 low. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.530 on the 4-hours chart of the XRP/USD pair.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $0.540 level. A clear move above the $0.540 resistance zone might start a strong increase. In the stated case, the price could even surpass the $0.550 resistance.</p>
<p>Any more gains might send the price toward the $0.5800 resistance. Initial support on the downside is near the $0.5010 level. The next major support is near the $0.485 level. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.4750 level, below which the price might even test $0.4500.</p>
<div id="attachment_78756" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Ripple-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78756" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78756" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Ripple-1.png" alt="Ripple Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78756" class="wp-caption-text">Ripple Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">chart</a>, Ripple’s price is now trading below the $0.52 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start a major increase above the $0.530 resistance.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XRP/USD is now losing momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for XRP/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.5010, $0.485, and $0.475.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.530 and $0.540.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-fresh-rally-possible-above-0-54/">Ripple Price Analysis: Fresh Rally Possible Above $0.54</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-fresh-rally-possible-above-0-54/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>British Columbia Resident Loses More Than $7 Million in Crypto Scam</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/british-columbia-resident-loses-more-than-7-million-in-crypto-scam/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/british-columbia-resident-loses-more-than-7-million-in-crypto-scam/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 17:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[British Columbia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[scam]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78139</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A senior citizen in British Columbia, Canada is the latest victim of a cryptocurrency scam. It’s estimated that the victim, who remains unnamed, has lost more than $7 million. British Columbia Citizen Conned Out of Tons of Crypto British Columbia authorities have stated this is arguably one of the worst digital currency scams of its<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/british-columbia-resident-loses-more-than-7-million-in-crypto-scam/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/british-columbia-resident-loses-more-than-7-million-in-crypto-scam/">British Columbia Resident Loses More Than $7 Million in Crypto Scam</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A senior citizen in British Columbia, Canada is the latest victim of a cryptocurrency <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/scam/" data-wpel-link="internal">scam</a>. It’s estimated that the victim, who remains unnamed, has lost more than $7 million.</p>
<h2>British Columbia Citizen Conned Out of Tons of Crypto</h2>
<p>British Columbia authorities have stated <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-ca/news/world/b-c-senior-defrauded-of-7-5-million-in-sophisticated-cryptocurrency-scam/ar-AA1asvry" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">this is arguably one of the</a> worst digital currency scams of its kind. The illicit actors in question pulled what they’re calling a “double barreled” approach. First, they stole the old woman’s money. From there, they stole more by claiming to be a team of people that could help her get the money back.</p>
<p>Corporal Philip Ho with the RCMP’s Economic Crime Unit in British Columbia made the following statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>Fraudsters are often changing tactics. In this case, it appears they were able to tailor the scam to target this victim in using information about her career and business history to first build trust and friendship. These scammers went to great lengths over many months to defraud this senior and convince her these were legitimate investments. These types of frauds often go unreported, but it’s important that victims come forward to police so we can investigate and help support victims, who are at a higher risk of being re-victimized once they have been defrauded by a scam.</p></blockquote>
<p>The scam began in the spring of 2022. The fraudsters reached out to the woman and said they were looking for data regarding her personal business history. To be fair, this should have been a huge red flag. When was the last time you were contacted and asked questions about this? These kinds of calls don’t normally happen unless you’re enduring a job interview, meaning it was a huge mistake to believe the questions were real.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the scammers initiated a conversation and built trust in the victim, chatting with her in Chinese via email, phone calls, and even by text. From there, they convinced her to invest millions of dollars into a new digital currency project online, and she would be able to check the ongoing balance of her account through (phony) apps the scammers provided to her.</p>
<p>Eventually, she sought to take some money out of the account when she saw she had allegedly made some returns, though this is when the scammers cut off all communication. Interestingly, a police report suggests that <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-ca/news/canada/burnaby-senior-loses-7-5-million-in-elaborate-cryptocurrency-scam-police-say/ar-AA1arJOF" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">despite being threatened multiple</a> times throughout her chats with the scammers, the woman continued to invest money in the platform. The report said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The victim, who was pressured and threatened throughout the course of the scam, invested more, but unfortunately, this was also a scam.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Even More Funds Disappear</h2>
<p>The scammers later got in touch with her again and pretended to be a team that could help her recover the lost funds.</p>
<p>This resulted in even more money being lost.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/british-columbia-resident-loses-more-than-7-million-in-crypto-scam/">British Columbia Resident Loses More Than $7 Million in Crypto Scam</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/british-columbia-resident-loses-more-than-7-million-in-crypto-scam/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Opinion: Crypto Traders Need to Realize the Government is not on Their Side</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-traders-need-to-realize-the-government-is-not-on-their-side/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-traders-need-to-realize-the-government-is-not-on-their-side/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 15:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Opinion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OpEd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Congress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78133</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto fans need to understand something once and for all: the government is not here to help you, and it is clearly incapable of accomplishing anything major within a reasonable period. Crypto Players, It&#8217;s Time to Wake Up! This warning applies to all parties and corners of the present political system, whether it&#8217;s democratic, republican,<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-traders-need-to-realize-the-government-is-not-on-their-side/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-traders-need-to-realize-the-government-is-not-on-their-side/">Opinion: Crypto Traders Need to Realize the Government is not on Their Side</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto fans need to understand something once and for all: the government is not here to help you, and it is clearly incapable of accomplishing anything major within a reasonable period.</p>
<h2>Crypto Players, It&#8217;s Time to Wake Up!</h2>
<p>This warning applies to all parties and corners of the present political system, whether it&#8217;s democratic, republican, or independent. There are so <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/republicans-arent-happy-with-the-sec-and-gary-genslers-approach-to-crypto-regulation/" data-wpel-link="internal">many committees and</a> so many organizations and so many general players taking up space in the political arena, and yet so few of them seem to finish or achieve anything of significance to the point that it’s almost humorous.</p>
<p>For example, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX</a> collapsed seven months ago. It was November of 2022 that the company fell into a heaping pile of bankruptcy and fraud. Since then, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/biden-voices-support-for-crypto-regulation/" data-wpel-link="internal">there have been ongoing</a> calls for digital currency regulation and clarity when it comes to present laws. Any reasonable person should have been working on these aspects the day the collapse occurred. We are now in June, and virtually nothing has been changed or recorded to the present rule books.</p>
<p>Despite the ongoing calls, despite people continuing to trade, and protections still (supposedly) not being in place, we cannot say that Congress or any member of America’s political system has done anything lasting or important. Instead, they are once again concerned with <a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/manhattan-grand-jury-voted-whether-indict-trump-rcna73588" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">prosecuting Donald Trump</a> for the umpteenth time and wasting everyone’s resources on phony indictments and garbage that is going to make no difference in the nation’s future.</p>
<p>If this should teach crypto fans anything, it’s that the American political system – as it presently stands – is practically useless. There really shouldn’t be any more calls for regulation or calls for political players to get involved in important matters such as where crypto goes from here. What traders and investors need to concern themselves with is keeping their assets and their practices safe and watching out for themselves and each other.</p>
<h2>So Little Done Thus Far</h2>
<p>It’s been months upon months of criticism from each side <em>for</em> each side. It’s been months of infighting and foolish arguments and childish games that have ultimately led the U.S. into a serious state of decay that will likely take years to recuperate from. The economy is tanking, <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/a-key-inflation-gauge-tracked-by-fed-remained-high-in-march/ar-AA1atuxE?OCID=ansmsnnews11" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">inflation is again reaching</a> a new high, and the ringleader of this circus – Joe Biden – is completely incapacitated both mentally and physically, and what’s scary is that nobody wants to talk about it.</p>
<p>And even if this wasn’t the case, even if Congress and other political players were proving themselves entirely capable, calls for regulation in crypto may be a bit overwrought given the industry was designed to push all regulators and prying eyes out of the picture in the first place. If crypto fans want to remain tough and resilient, they will place more focus on themselves and less on government step-ins.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-traders-need-to-realize-the-government-is-not-on-their-side/">Opinion: Crypto Traders Need to Realize the Government is not on Their Side</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-traders-need-to-realize-the-government-is-not-on-their-side/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Republicans Aren&#8217;t Happy with the SEC and Gary Gensler&#8217;s Approach to Crypto Regulation</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/republicans-arent-happy-with-the-sec-and-gary-genslers-approach-to-crypto-regulation/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/republicans-arent-happy-with-the-sec-and-gary-genslers-approach-to-crypto-regulation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 13:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[republicans]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78131</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and its head Gary Gensler are bullies. They are bullies to the crypto industry and to everyone who tries to issue digital currencies to the common public. Republicans Grill the SEC and Gary Gensler The actions of Gensler have ultimately made him the subject of wrath amongst various members<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/republicans-arent-happy-with-the-sec-and-gary-genslers-approach-to-crypto-regulation/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/republicans-arent-happy-with-the-sec-and-gary-genslers-approach-to-crypto-regulation/">Republicans Aren&#8217;t Happy with the SEC and Gary Gensler&#8217;s Approach to Crypto Regulation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and its head Gary Gensler are bullies. They are bullies to the crypto industry and to everyone who tries to issue digital currencies to the common public.</p>
<h2>Republicans Grill the SEC and Gary Gensler</h2>
<p>The actions of Gensler have ultimately <a href="https://www.pionline.com/washington/lawmakers-grill-secs-gensler-cryptocurrency-climate-rule-making" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">made him the subject of wrath</a> amongst various members of Congress who don’t like that he’s persecuting rather than regulating players in the industry. They think he’s using the power he was given through his present position in an abusive way, and Gensler was recently grilled by various members of the House of Representatives, which is currently controlled by republicans.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/gary-gensler/" data-wpel-link="internal">Gensler</a> was quick to defend himself and his actions in the hearing, claiming that members of the crypto arena have been among the most non-compliant ever. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Investors in the crypto market should benefit from the compliance with (the law). It&#8217;s the law. It&#8217;s really not a choice.</p></blockquote>
<p>Despite his conviction, many republican members of the House weren’t buying his words and were quick to point out that when it comes to regulation, the crypto arena has long been the victim of low or non-existent clarity. They also said that Gensler and the SEC have been following the path of “regulation by enforcement,” and that they haven’t done enough to make the rules understandable.</p>
<p>They stated that the SEC is working to enforce laws on companies that they, themselves, either don’t know exist, or don’t assume will apply to them. It is thus the agency’s job to ensure that these laws are clear to all players. Chairman Patrick McHenry of North Carolina said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Regulation by enforcement is not sufficient nor sustainable.</p></blockquote>
<p>Prior to the hearing, republican lawmakers sent a letter to Gensler and his team criticizing the agency for having a simple, “come in and register” attitude for all digital currency companies. The letter reads:</p>
<blockquote><p>Without clear rules of the road, your push for firms to &#8216;come in and register&#8217; is a willful misrepresentation of the SEC&#8217;s non-existent registration process. The only entity to blame for the lack of registrants is the SEC itself.</p></blockquote>
<h2>We&#8217;ve Done Well!</h2>
<p>Despite this clear distaste towards his actions, Gensler was quick to jump to his own defense and say that he and his staff have done well when it comes to keeping the crypto industry in check. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I&#8217;m very proud of what we&#8217;ve done. We put out 46 proposals to date… and on average, it&#8217;s been more than 70 days from the time we vote it out, we put it on our website, and we have a formal end to a comment period, but then we get comments after that, and we [have] meetings after that, and we engage actively with trade associations and market participants.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/republicans-arent-happy-with-the-sec-and-gary-genslers-approach-to-crypto-regulation/">Republicans Aren&#8217;t Happy with the SEC and Gary Gensler&#8217;s Approach to Crypto Regulation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/republicans-arent-happy-with-the-sec-and-gary-genslers-approach-to-crypto-regulation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Senator Ted Cruz Really Doesn&#8217;t Want a CBDC in Play</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/senator-ted-cruz-really-doesnt-want-a-cbdc-in-play/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/senator-ted-cruz-really-doesnt-want-a-cbdc-in-play/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 17:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ted Cruz]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78129</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Republican Senator from Texas Ted Cruz says he doesn’t want a digital dollar or any central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) entering the fray. He believes they’ll bring about an end to bitcoin, a cryptocurrency he has a lot of respect and admiration for. Ted Cruz Is Confident a CBDC Would Hurt BTC In a recent<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/senator-ted-cruz-really-doesnt-want-a-cbdc-in-play/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/senator-ted-cruz-really-doesnt-want-a-cbdc-in-play/">Senator Ted Cruz Really Doesn&#8217;t Want a CBDC in Play</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Republican Senator from Texas Ted Cruz says he <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/04/28/crypto-price-warning-china-biden-and-the-fed-could-be-about-to-destroy-all-value-of-bitcoin/?sh=662bc0664631" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">doesn’t want a digital</a> dollar or any central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) entering the fray. He believes they’ll bring about an end to bitcoin, a cryptocurrency he has a lot of respect and admiration for.</p>
<h2>Ted Cruz Is Confident a CBDC Would Hurt BTC</h2>
<p>In a recent statement, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ted-cruz/" data-wpel-link="internal">Cruz</a> said the following about CBDCs:</p>
<blockquote><p>We see China moving forward with the intention of using a CBDC to destroy all value of bitcoin, to destroy anonymity, to destroy decentralization. Joe Biden, early in his presidency, issued an executive order directing the Federal Reserve to study creating a CBDC, and the New York branch of the Fed is working on doing exactly that.</p></blockquote>
<p>One can understand his fear. Central bank digital currencies go against everything bitcoin and its initial altcoin counterparts are going for. Initially, they were all designed to serve as decentralized forms of payment for individuals across the globe. Those who couldn’t gain access to products and services in the traditional financial arena could gain them through bitcoin, which only needs a wallet and an internet connection to function and be transferable.</p>
<p>However, with central banks in the mix, these notions would ultimately become null and void. These banks would be the ones issuing the currencies in question, not miners or developers. They would decide who could use them and who would gain access to them. These currencies would destroy all that the first cryptocurrencies stood for and bring about an end to the crypto industry as we know it.</p>
<p>In addition, CBDCs would likely give rise to a new wave of governmental power. Regulators around the world would be able to spy on us and see what we were using our money for. They could look in on our activities and potentially get in the way anytime they wanted.</p>
<p>Cruz thinks CBDCs are wrong for a modern and free world. When discussing how a CBDC could be used against people through government protocols, he stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think that&#8217;s exceptionally dangerous. I&#8217;m very concerned about the risk of a CBDC.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Trying to Keep the Danger Out</h2>
<p>He is also very confident that a CBDC used nationally by everyone would make bitcoin less unique, and thus cause the father of all crypto to become virtually obsolete. He has no doubt that the issuance of a digital dollar or other CBDC would cause the currency to lose all its value. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The same people that want to see a CBDC, they hate bitcoin, and they hate cash. Let&#8217;s be clear: they don&#8217;t like cash for exactly the reason I like cash because it is not subjected to centralized control that is not subject to constant surveillance.</p></blockquote>
<p>In 2022, Cruz submitted legislation that if passed, would prevent the establishment of a digital dollar in America.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/senator-ted-cruz-really-doesnt-want-a-cbdc-in-play/">Senator Ted Cruz Really Doesn&#8217;t Want a CBDC in Play</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/senator-ted-cruz-really-doesnt-want-a-cbdc-in-play/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=3831 metric#misses=5 metric#hit-ratio=99.9 metric#bytes=6623244 metric#prefetches=325 metric#store-reads=64 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=405 metric#store-misses=0 metric#sql-queries=17 metric#ms-total=170.26 metric#ms-cache=16.86 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2593 metric#ms-cache-ratio=9.9 -->
