<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 08:20:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The White House Thinks BTC Has Just Boosted Crime</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-white-house-thinks-btc-has-just-boosted-crime/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-white-house-thinks-btc-has-just-boosted-crime/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 17:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[white house]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75406</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>According to White House officials, bitcoin – though it has its benefits – has increased ransomware cases across the country. The White House Isn&#8217;t Confident in BTC A White House spokesperson (who remains anonymous) recently commented in an interview: When bitcoin became more widely used, we saw a huge jump in ransomware because it was a way<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-white-house-thinks-btc-has-just-boosted-crime/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-white-house-thinks-btc-has-just-boosted-crime/">The White House Thinks BTC Has Just Boosted Crime</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to White House officials, bitcoin – <a href="https://venturebeat.com/security/the-surprising-relationship-between-bitcoin-and-ransomware-is-investigated-in-white-house-summit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://venturebeat.com/security/the-surprising-relationship-between-bitcoin-and-ransomware-is-investigated-in-white-house-summit/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537724428000&amp;usg=AOvVaw1gU-DTOvCx2jldsP-Vp96W" data-wpel-link="exclude">though it has its benefits</a> – has increased ransomware cases across the country.</p>
<h2>The White House Isn&#8217;t Confident in BTC</h2>
<p>A White House spokesperson (who remains anonymous) recently commented in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>When bitcoin became more widely used, we saw a huge jump in ransomware because it was a way to move money across borders. It’s a borderless threat, and we [need] to tackle it in a borderless way. The threat has clearly evolved.</p></blockquote>
<p>The government house is now coordinating with approximately 36 countries at the time of writing to establish a new bitcoin ransomware-fighting program that will ensure issues like this become a thing of the past. The spokesperson said:</p>
<blockquote><p>As we know, ransomware is an issue that knows no borders and affects each of the Counter Ransomware Initiative countries — our businesses, our critical infrastructure, and our citizens — and it’s only getting more challenging.</p></blockquote>
<p>Crypto has been at the forefront of American politics over the past several months. Things began in such a manner when Biden issued a new crypto <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-is-the-biden-crypto-executive-order-all-its-cracked-up-to-be/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-is-the-biden-crypto-executive-order-all-its-cracked-up-to-be/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537724428000&amp;usg=AOvVaw0R5tI8X1-9rj3v2Iv6TdaF" data-wpel-link="internal">executive order requiring</a> all financial agencies in the nation to explore digital currencies to better understand their benefits and disadvantages. The order also opened the door to a digital dollar. The Treasury has been <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-treasury-wants-to-regulate-crypto-and-fast/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-treasury-wants-to-regulate-crypto-and-fast/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537724428000&amp;usg=AOvVaw3G2o9kwMEvgbDYJn6wWYgM" data-wpel-link="internal">researching crypto hard</a> since then, though no official reports about what the White House is planning to do beyond this point have been issued.</p>
<p>The organization involving the 36 nations has come to be known as the Counter Ransomware Initiative (CRI), and it was formed during a virtual global summit designed to halt ransomware permanently. The group will also work with as many as 13 businesses in the private sector to see what information they can pass along about how to fight the growing threat.</p>
<p>The White House spokesperson said:</p>
<blockquote><p>This is just a first round of getting companies’ perspectives to ensure that we’re not doing this the traditional government way, which is government-to-government only. We’re pulling in the private sector because of their unique visibility, capability, and insights into it.</p></blockquote>
<p>Erich Kron – a security awareness advocate at KnowBe4 – offered his two cents, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>Ransomware has become a serious issue on a global scale, so it is no surprise that so many nations continue to band together to deal with the threat… The urgency to find a solution for the problem is only heightened.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Trying to Push Back</h2>
<p>Jeff Williams – co-founder and CTO of Contrast Security – mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Additionally, we must push back on the industry when it attempts to obfuscate visibility into weak security practices and technologies with claims that it will compromise intellectual property (it won’t) or make it easier for attackers (it doesn’t). We need far more insight into how the software we trust with the most important things in our lives has been secured.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-white-house-thinks-btc-has-just-boosted-crime/">The White House Thinks BTC Has Just Boosted Crime</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-white-house-thinks-btc-has-just-boosted-crime/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tim Draper Thinks Women Will Really Help BTC</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tim-draper-thinks-women-will-save-btc/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tim-draper-thinks-women-will-save-btc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 15:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tim Draper]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[women]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75403</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What will bring bitcoin back from the brink of disaster? According to famed venture capitalist and digital currency enthusiast Tim Draper, the answer is women. Tim Draper: Women Are the Answer The crypto space has been doing very poorly as of late. The industry has fallen by more than $2 trillion in valuation and some of the largest,<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tim-draper-thinks-women-will-save-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tim-draper-thinks-women-will-save-btc/">Tim Draper Thinks Women Will Really Help BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What will bring <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitcoin/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537724433000&amp;usg=AOvVaw39s3RElKOkJmQnYTjZO7ga" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a> back from the brink of disaster? According to famed venture capitalist and digital currency enthusiast Tim Draper, <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/johnkoetsier/2022/11/03/women-will-save-bitcoin-chatting-with-bitcoin-maximalist-tim-draper/?sh=306f25401183" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.forbes.com/sites/johnkoetsier/2022/11/03/women-will-save-bitcoin-chatting-with-bitcoin-maximalist-tim-draper/?sh%3D306f25401183&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537724433000&amp;usg=AOvVaw3dfaaXD53V6u_uKQmDNqMw" data-wpel-link="exclude">the answer is women</a>.</p>
<h2>Tim Draper: Women Are the Answer</h2>
<p>The crypto space has been doing very poorly as of late. The industry has fallen by more than $2 trillion in valuation and some of the largest, mainstream digital assets – including bitcoin – are down by 70 percent or more from their 2021 November highs. It’s an ugly sight to see, and many analysts are conflicted about when bitcoin and its altcoin cousins could come back.</p>
<p>Draper said the space has long been dominated by men, though he’s confident more women will be getting involved in crypto. He says they could be the ones that ultimately save the industry from crashing and burning completely. He stated in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Long-term, it’s going to be all about the women. Women control 80 percent of retail spending, and they are only one of six bitcoin wallets.</p></blockquote>
<p>He’s also confident people who engage in HODLing – those who hold on for dear life and don’t sell their crypto assets at any cost – will have their faith in BTC rewarded and that the space is going to come back like never before. Draper mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>The HODLers, the passionate people realizing bitcoin is an anthropological leap forward, they’re the ones who are buying now and hanging in there.</p></blockquote>
<p>He commented also that one of the big reasons crypto dropped so badly was spectators bought into the arena and ultimately sold BTC and other digital assets the same days that they sold their tech stocks. Draper believes women and retailers will eventually bring the arena back, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>Once the retailers realize that they can save two percent by accepting bitcoin, and once women realize they get their food, their clothing, and their shelter all in bitcoin, they’re not going to want government coins. They’re going to want bitcoin; they’re going to want something that is decentralized, open, transparent, [and] global&#8230; They’re going to want a currency that is just better, that will go up in value&#8230; versus one that you [need] to get rid of.</p></blockquote>
<p>Draper also commented that many of the people who are HODLing crypto at this time happen to be women. Instead of purchasing groceries or a new pair of shoes, they are instead buying bitcoin and other digital assets to diversify their portfolios and manage their wealth.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Can Fight Inflation</h2>
<p>Completing his discussion, he’s also sure that the inflation we’re dealing with right now will propel bitcoin to new heights. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin will start being recognized as an inflation hedge. I remember my dad giving me $1,000,000 confederate dollars. I said, ‘How much is this worth?’ and he started laughing&#8230; ‘It’s not worth anything.’</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tim-draper-thinks-women-will-save-btc/">Tim Draper Thinks Women Will Really Help BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tim-draper-thinks-women-will-save-btc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitstamp Is Bringing Its Services to Luxembourg</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitstamp-is-bringing-its-services-to-luxembourg/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitstamp-is-bringing-its-services-to-luxembourg/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 13:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitstamp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[luxembourg]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75400</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitstamp is the oldest digital currency exchange in the world. Not long ago, it announced it’s set to begin doing business in the European nation of Luxembourg, and it will soon offer its services to crypto traders in that region. Bitstamp Is Cementing Itself in Luxembourg Jean-Baptiste Graftieaux – CEO of Bitstamp – said in an interview: We<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitstamp-is-bringing-its-services-to-luxembourg/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitstamp-is-bringing-its-services-to-luxembourg/">Bitstamp Is Bringing Its Services to Luxembourg</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitstamp is the oldest digital currency exchange in the world. Not long ago, it announced it’s set to begin doing business in the <a href="https://www.computerweekly.com/feature/The-worlds-oldest-cryptocurrency-exchange-prefers-doing-business-in-Luxembourg" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.computerweekly.com/feature/The-worlds-oldest-cryptocurrency-exchange-prefers-doing-business-in-Luxembourg&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537718428000&amp;usg=AOvVaw3I-QeUNxcV8IJ7pTyzQalr" data-wpel-link="external">European nation of Luxembourg</a>, and it will soon offer its services to crypto traders in that region.</p>
<h2>Bitstamp Is Cementing Itself in Luxembourg</h2>
<p>Jean-Baptiste Graftieaux – CEO of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitstamp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitstamp/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537718428000&amp;usg=AOvVaw2eTE857d-VvCrqGv89BWMA" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitstamp</a> – said in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>We have a combination of engineers and product people who understand crypto or fintech. We also have experts in information security area and data protection. These are important for us to be best in class in terms of technology and cyber security. We also need strong customer support people. We have real human beings in our customer support instead of bots because customers want to work with real people.</p></blockquote>
<p>When talking about why his company decided to settle on Luxembourg, the CEO mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>When we looked around the European region for places to do business, the only country with the appetite to endorse this innovation was Luxembourg. It was still considered early days for cryptocurrencies, and there was virtually no regulatory framework. This meant that any company that wanted to become an established exchange had to go to each of the countries where it wanted to operate and help the government define regulations and licensing. Luxembourg is a small country, but very international and connected. It’s a good place to do business and engage with the local authorities in the sense that everyone knows each other. We worked closely with the government on how to regulate Bitstamp and to figure out what kind of license was required. In the end, we became authorized as a payment institution in Luxembourg.</p></blockquote>
<p>The firm has endured quite a bit of trouble surrounding its licensing procedures. Graftieaux also discussed that, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>Regulations and licensing are important to our business because they boost our credibility in the market. We’re looking forward to the day when it’s easier to get licensed in countries around the world.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Making Sure All Is Correct</h2>
<p>He also said that the company has worked harder to ensure audits go accordingly and that any fraudulent activity is picked up on. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>You can look at a transaction, but you don’t see all the underlying data on the sender and recipient. What you see is that there has been a transaction of one or more bitcoins from one wallet to another or from one address to another, but what you don’t know today is the owner of the wallet or address. Nevertheless, with this address, what’s happening very regularly is that if there is a fraud or an offence committed with a bitcoin address, the law enforcement agencies will reach out to the different crypto players to see if they have clients associated to that specific address, and if so, to share that information.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitstamp-is-bringing-its-services-to-luxembourg/">Bitstamp Is Bringing Its Services to Luxembourg</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitstamp-is-bringing-its-services-to-luxembourg/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SILK Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/silk-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/silk-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 08:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75947</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec. 9, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed SILK on December 9, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the SILK/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading. As the first web3 esports with earnings, Spider Tanks enables players to earn for their play through<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/silk-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/silk-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">SILK Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec. 9, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed SILK on December 9, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the SILK/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading.</p>
<p>As the first web3 esports with earnings, Spider Tanks enables players to earn for their play through its complex and brilliantly designed reward economy. Its native token <a href="https://etherscan.io/token/0xb045f7f363fe4949954811b113bd56d208c67b23" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">SILK</a> has been listed on LBank Exchange at 13:00 UTC on December 9, 2022, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision.</p>
<p><strong>Introducing </strong><strong>Spider Tanks</strong></p>
<p>Spider Tanks is a blockchain-based PVP brawler created by award-winning Netherlands based GAMEDIA and brought to players by Gala Games. Players choose between a number of Tank Bodies and Weapons in the garage, then battle it out in one of the many Spider Tanks arena maps. And since all tank parts are owned as NFTs, they can be upgraded, then sold on the secondary market at any time the player chooses.</p>
<p>Different game modes of Spider Tanks present different strategic and team-based challenges to always keep gameplay fresh. TEAM DEATHMATCH is an all-out brawl style match where the team with the most kills gets the victory. Players need to create killer destructive combinations with their teams, and let the chaos ensure. CAPTURE THE CHICKEN is a mode where player’s team&#8217;s goal is to capture as many moving chickens as possible and become a Spider Tanks chicken master. And in CAPTURE THE FLAG, the team who holds the only one flag in their possession the longest will be victorious in the match.</p>
<p>Spider Tanks is free to play, but also incorporates a variety of play-to-earn mechanics, centering around skill-based competition, resource collection, and a player-driven upgrade cycle. It builds an ecosystem where a web of participants including NFT holders, players, and game developers revolves around playing Spider Tanks matches and receiving Victory Points that can be submitted for game token reward distribution.</p>
<p>Whether the player wants to play with a small group of close friends, or tests their skills in high-stakes competition, Spider Tanks will be the worldwide play-to-earn esports for them. Players can enjoy the free to play game or compete with other players by purchasing fully tradable Weapons, Tanks and Bodies in the Spider Tanks store for advantages to the upgrade cycle, rarity head starts and more.</p>
<p><strong>About SILK Token</strong></p>
<p>Based on ERC-20, SILK is the game token of Spider Tanks ecosystem. It can be acquired by involving oneself in the Spider Tanks ecosystem through playing and winning games, as well as by operating nodes and other ecosystem products. SILK can also be spent in a number of ways, the chief of which is purchasing upgrades for a Tank Item NFT.</p>
<p>SILK will always be the only currency of the Spider Tanks ecosystem, and as that ecosystem grows in size, supply will not increase in-kind. With a soft cap of 100 million (i.e., 100,000,000) tokens, SILK&#8217;s economy is tied to the amount of players, SILK being generated, and SILK being spent and adjusts emission rates automatically.</p>
<p>The SILK token has been listed on LBank Exchange at 13:00 UTC on December 9, 2022, investors who are interested in the Spider Tanks investment can easily buy and sell SILK token on LBank Exchange now. The listing of SILK token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p>
<p><strong>Learn More about</strong> <strong>SILK Token:</strong></p>
<p>Official Website: <a href="https://www.spidertanks.game/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.spidertanks.game/</a><br />
Discord: <a href="http://galagames.chat/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://galagames.chat/</a>   &amp;  https://www.spidertanks.game/<br />
Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/GoGalaGames" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/GoGalaGames</a>   &amp;  <a href="https://twitter.com/spider_tanks" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/spider_tanks</a><br />
YouTube: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/GalaGames" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/c/GalaGames</a><br />
Facebook: <a href="https://galagames.chat/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://galagames.chat/</a><br />
Reddit: <a href="https://www.instagram.com/spidertanks/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.instagram.com/spidertanks/</a><br />
Instagram: <a href="https://www.instagram.com/spidertanks/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.instagram.com/spidertanks/</a><br />
Medium: <a href="https://medium.com/@spidertanks" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://medium.com/@spidertanks</a></p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media: </strong></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Facebook</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong></p>
<p>LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
LBank Exchange<br />
<a href="mailto:marketing@lbank.info">marketing@lbank.info</a><br />
<a href="mailto:business@lbank.info">business@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/silk-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">SILK Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/silk-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PET CASTLE PROTOCOL (PCP) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/pet-castle-protocol-pcp-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/pet-castle-protocol-pcp-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 07:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75944</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec. 9, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed PET CASTLE PROTOCOL (PCP) on December 9, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the PCP/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading. Building a blockchain-based pet community, Pet Castle Platform provides pet related online and offline<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/pet-castle-protocol-pcp-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/pet-castle-protocol-pcp-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">PET CASTLE PROTOCOL (PCP) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec. 9, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed PET CASTLE PROTOCOL (PCP) on December 9, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the PCP/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading.</p>
<p>Building a blockchain-based pet community, Pet Castle Platform provides pet related online and offline services including Pet ID Card, Pet Business Card, and Pet Castle Urban Theme Park that consists of pet hospital, pet academy, pet beauty, pet café, pet funeral, pet commodities store, and so on. Its native token <a href="https://bscscan.com/token/0x84dE7F1244B354C37a0f8a3A774062305D7006fd" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">PET CASTLE PROTOCOL</a> (PCP) has been listed on LBank Exchange at 8:00 UTC on December 9, 2022, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision.</p>
<p><strong>Introducing Pet Castle Platform</strong></p>
<p>Launched in June 2022 by PET CASTLE Ltd., a company established in March 2022, Pet Castle Platform is currently active as a blockchain-based pet community. It’s built for pets, pet owners, and pet business partners, and can be used quickly and conveniently anytime, anywhere through the mobile app or PC browser. PET CASTLE PROTOCOL (hereinafter referred to as “PCP”) is issued by PET CASTLE Ltd.</p>
<p>There are two kinds of card in the Pet Castle that one can create with free membership service. The first is the Pet ID Card, an NFT-certified ID card for companions who take care of their pets. This is to issue cards to companions so that they can use various services quickly and conveniently within the platform. Users can save their pet photos and videos in the ID card album, and they can also have pedigree analysis results and prevent disease through DNA testing provided free of charge. The platform plans to cooperate with the companion animal industries, including pet hospital, pet insurance companies and service companies that require identity verification.</p>
<p>The second is the Pet Business Card for the presidents (veterinarians) who run the pet business. Through the Pet Castle App, domestic and foreign pet hospitals, pet kindergartens, pet cafes, pet beauty shops, and pet hotel owners can create cards by themselves and do business directly with the companions (or butlers). In addition, pet helpers such as Pet Sitters can create and promote Pet Business Cards by themselves, and it is programmed so that companions can book services and purchase products through quick connection.</p>
<p>At the same time, the offline business will be launched soon. Pet Castle Urban Theme Park is the business that provides pets and the owner of pets with the service like pet hospital, pet academy, pet beauty, pet cafe, pet funeral, pet commodities store, and so on. It will be franchised with lots of franchisee in the domestic market and global one as well. PET CASTLE PROTOCOL’s ecosystem will be enlarged both through online platform and through offline franchise business in the future.</p>
<p>The Pet Castle Platform is growing as a comprehensive platform that can be a refreshing solution by identifying and analyzing the various needs and difficulties that companions are experiencing. Based on the Pet Castle Platform, PCP balances supply and demand in the changing market, and continues to grow as a payment method for Korea&#8217;s best comprehensive companion animal platform and a virtual asset that guarantees future value. Together with the owners and companion animals, PCP will become a driving force in leading an innovative society that respects companion animals.</p>
<p><strong>About PCP Token</strong></p>
<p>PET CASTLE PROTOCOL (PCP) is the native token of Pet Castle Platform. Based on BEP-20, it has a total supply of 5 billion (i.e., 5,000,000,000) tokens, of which 5% is provided for initial funding, 10% will be used for marketing, 30% goes into the exchange pool, 15% is provided for reward to users and partners, 10% is allocated to the team and advisor, 20% will be used for R&amp;D and operating, and the remaining 10% is reserved.</p>
<p>PCP token has been listed on LBank Exchange at 8:00 UTC on December 9, 2022, investors who are interested in the Pet Castel Platform investment can easily buy and sell PCP token on LBank Exchange right now. The listing of PCP token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p>
<p><strong>Learn More about</strong> <strong>PCP Token:</strong></p>
<p>Official Website: <a href="https://petcastle.io" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://petcastle.io</a></p>
<p>Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/+C5OvGVPAWyYwMjU1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://t.me/+C5OvGVPAWyYwMjU1</a></p>
<p>Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/PCP_PetCastle/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/PCP_PetCastle/</a></p>
<p>Facebook: <a href="https://www.facebook.com/Petcastleprotocol" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://www.facebook.com/Petcastleprotocol</a></p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media: </strong></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Facebook</a></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong></p>
<p>LBK Blockchain Co. Limited</p>
<p>LBank Exchange</p>
<p><a href="mailto:marketing@lbank.info">marketing@lbank.info</a></p>
<p><a href="mailto:business@lbank.info">business@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/pet-castle-protocol-pcp-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">PET CASTLE PROTOCOL (PCP) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/pet-castle-protocol-pcp-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New York Continues to Not Care About Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-continues-to-not-care-about-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-continues-to-not-care-about-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 17:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BitLicense]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kathy Hochul]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New York]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75398</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York really doesn’t care about cryptocurrency, and the re-election of Governor Kathy Hochul is proof of this. New York Just Doesn&#8217;t Get It During this year’s midterm elections, Hochul ran against Lee Zeldin, who arguably had one of the most competitive republican campaigns in the Empire State in years. Right now, New York is facing a<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-continues-to-not-care-about-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-continues-to-not-care-about-crypto/">New York Continues to Not Care About Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York really doesn’t care about cryptocurrency, and <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/the-fate-of-crypto-mining-is-back-on-the-table-in-new-york/ar-AA13VEDA" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/the-fate-of-crypto-mining-is-back-on-the-table-in-new-york/ar-AA13VEDA&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537717630000&amp;usg=AOvVaw2_mmA_Pj2tidgQjZe9z1DE" data-wpel-link="external">the re-election of</a> Governor Kathy Hochul is proof of this.</p>
<h2>New York Just Doesn&#8217;t Get It</h2>
<p>During this year’s midterm elections, Hochul ran against Lee Zeldin, who arguably had one of the most competitive republican campaigns in the Empire State in years. Right now, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-governor-hochul-facing-real-pressure-to-sign-crypto-moratorium/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-governor-hochul-facing-real-pressure-to-sign-crypto-moratorium/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537717630000&amp;usg=AOvVaw0uV_wYwq8AzATCp-4JowqA" data-wpel-link="internal">New York is facing a bill</a> that’s been passed by the state legislature. The bill would enforce a moratorium on the crypto mining space and prevent all new digital currency mining companies from setting up shop within the region’s borders.</p>
<p>Zeldin has mentioned numerous times he would end the bill and prevent its passage if he were elected governor. In his campaign against Hochul, he clearly addressed many issues New York was facing. He discussed crime and inflation, items that Hochul – in the past – has refused to acknowledge. He also clearly won the one and only debate between himself and the democrat incumbent, and it appeared he was on a solid track to make native New Yorkers view the conservative party differently.</p>
<p>Sadly, this was not meant to be. Despite being a clear winner in many areas and having some solid ideas in place for the state, New York – as usual – chose to go blue and voted Hochul in for a second term despite her clear lack of attention to the well-being of those living in her state. Now, the crypto moratorium is back on the table, and Hochul has until the end of the year to decide if she’s going to sign it into law. Clearly, the people of New York don’t care about crypto enough to get rid of her.</p>
<p>New York has developed a reputation for being a very anti-crypto state. A big contributor to this is the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitlicense/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitlicense/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537717630000&amp;usg=AOvVaw2oI0R66233KwSXukvFUFB4" data-wpel-link="internal">BitLicense</a>, which was enacted in the year 2015. Many crypto companies left New York completely or were forced to end all their services there due to the harsh regulatory tactics enforced by the BitLicense. Acquiring one also came with monster-sized fees and given that the crypto space was still very much in its infancy at that time, several of these firms couldn’t afford to hawk up the required funds.</p>
<h2>The Bill Is Damaging</h2>
<p>John Olsen – the New York state lead for the Blockchain Association – explained that the moratorium would arguably make a lot of miners leave the state. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think you would see a swift exodus. Should the governor sign the bill, I think you would see a swift exodus of any miners that aren’t almost solely reliant on renewable energy. It’s a difficult time for the industry. New York probably wouldn’t be worth it if it doesn’t have [a] strong signal to the industry that it’s welcome here&#8230; That starts with a veto of that bill.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-continues-to-not-care-about-crypto/">New York Continues to Not Care About Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-continues-to-not-care-about-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>It Appears Michael Saylor Will Never Reject BTC</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/it-appears-michael-saylor-will-never-reject-btc/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/it-appears-michael-saylor-will-never-reject-btc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 15:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Saylor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroStrategy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75396</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Despite the recent crash of the crypto space, despite everything bitcoin has cost him, Michael Saylor – the former head executive of MicroStrategy, a one-time software giant that has since transformed into one of the biggest bitcoin bulls out there – says bitcoin is going to be a winning asset in the end. Michael Saylor Will Never<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/it-appears-michael-saylor-will-never-reject-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/it-appears-michael-saylor-will-never-reject-btc/">It Appears Michael Saylor Will Never Reject BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite the recent crash of the crypto space, despite everything bitcoin has cost him, Michael Saylor – the former head executive of MicroStrategy, a one-time software giant that has since transformed into one of the biggest bitcoin bulls out there – says <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/bitcoin-will-be-the-winner-because-bitcoin-is-a-digital-commodity-and-it-s-the-least-controversial-of-everything-said-microstrategy-s-michael-saylor/ar-AA13YdF2" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/bitcoin-will-be-the-winner-because-bitcoin-is-a-digital-commodity-and-it-s-the-least-controversial-of-everything-said-microstrategy-s-michael-saylor/ar-AA13YdF2&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537717369000&amp;usg=AOvVaw2kWpmknVD2L0hrzLsUsHPc" data-wpel-link="external">bitcoin is going to</a> be a winning asset in the end.</p>
<h2>Michael Saylor Will Never Give Up on BTC</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, he commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Speaking for all bitcoiners, we feel we’re trapped in a dysfunctional relationship with crypto and we want out. Bitcoin will be the winner because bitcoin is a digital commodity and it’s the least controversial of everything.</p></blockquote>
<p>Michael Saylor first began adding bitcoin to the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-microstrategy-bitcoin-bet-is-already-paying-off-big-time/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-microstrategy-bitcoin-bet-is-already-paying-off-big-time/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537717369000&amp;usg=AOvVaw3AG2iG7mBenyTfr1ujQmvv" data-wpel-link="internal">MicroStrategy balance sheet</a> in August of 2020. At that time, the world’s number one digital currency by market cap was trading in the $11K range, which was small compared to what the price would be just 12 months later. However, at the time, the price was considered a milestone for the currency, and apparently MicroStrategy wanted in.</p>
<p>During that month, the company purchased close to $400 million in BTC. This would be the first in a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/microstrategy-just-bought-a-whole-lot-more-btc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/microstrategy-just-bought-a-whole-lot-more-btc/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537717369000&amp;usg=AOvVaw1AwNz2_6wHWQ5TVfIE8mlZ" data-wpel-link="internal">string of purchases</a> that would ultimately reach beyond the billion-dollar mark. Bitcoin, in many ways, was still considered a very risky investment given how volatile it was. Its vulnerability to price swings was often labeled as the main reason as to why so many institutions refused to get involved in crypto investing, and MicroStrategy appeared to be a risk taker in this department.</p>
<p>At first, it appeared things were paying off. Throughout 2021, bitcoin’s price reached mega highs, and MicroStrategy was indeed experiencing huge growth as a result. Unfortunately, bitcoin took a serious beating this year, and instead of backing off like it probably should have, MicroStrategy – by way of Saylor’s incessant fanaticism – chose to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-just-bought-more-btc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-just-bought-more-btc/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537717369000&amp;usg=AOvVaw1MJxnz-uv-GII1awo1yTk9" data-wpel-link="internal">continue investing</a> in the digital asset.</p>
<p>MicroStrategy is now billions of dollars in the hole, and Saylor was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-btc-bull-and-microstrategy-chief-executive-steps-down/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-btc-bull-and-microstrategy-chief-executive-steps-down/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537717369000&amp;usg=AOvVaw3_Kg0l5aLqWFI5yhoXwfR7" data-wpel-link="internal">recently pressured to relieve</a> himself of his chief executive duties, instead reverting to the lesser position of executive chairman. The company that had been run under his careful eye for more than 30 years is no longer in his hands.</p>
<h2>More Players Will Enter</h2>
<p>To say Saylor’s constant admiration of bitcoin is likely overwrought would be an understatement. Nevertheless, he continues to push the BTC agenda and claims it has properties that cannot be ignored. Continuing his interview, Saylor said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We’re moving from the entrepreneurial stage… to an institutional digital asset stage where big players… are going to enter this space and we’re all just going to grow up and the world is going to benefit from that.</p></blockquote>
<p>At the time of writing, the price of bitcoin is at its lowest point since June of this year. It is presently trading in the high $17K range, which is a slight improvement over the recent $16K it struck.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/it-appears-michael-saylor-will-never-reject-btc/">It Appears Michael Saylor Will Never Reject BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/it-appears-michael-saylor-will-never-reject-btc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ahmad Abu Daher Is a Young (and Wealthy) Crypto Miner</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ahmad-abu-daher-is-a-young-and-wealthy-crypto-miner/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ahmad-abu-daher-is-a-young-and-wealthy-crypto-miner/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 13:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ahmad Abu Daher]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lebanon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75394</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ahmad Abu Daher is only 22 years old, yet he’s already making a handsome living as a bitcoin miner in his home country of Lebanon. Ahmad Abu Daher Is Doing Well as a Miner Daher runs a whole team and has been doing so ever since he graduated from university. He entered a world that was wrought with financial<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ahmad-abu-daher-is-a-young-and-wealthy-crypto-miner/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ahmad-abu-daher-is-a-young-and-wealthy-crypto-miner/">Ahmad Abu Daher Is a Young (and Wealthy) Crypto Miner</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ahmad Abu Daher is only 22 years old, yet he’s already <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/this-22-year-old-survives-lebanon-with-a-bitcoin-mining-business-thats-been-earning-2420000-a-month/ar-AA13SM7T" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/this-22-year-old-survives-lebanon-with-a-bitcoin-mining-business-thats-been-earning-2420000-a-month/ar-AA13SM7T&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537717364000&amp;usg=AOvVaw2l8SA84MZp_qGvbbnZDxE3" data-wpel-link="external">making a handsome living</a> as a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/mining/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/mining/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668537717364000&amp;usg=AOvVaw1uvbV4ElZfU3FR1q9qsywC" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin miner</a> in his home country of Lebanon.</p>
<h2>Ahmad Abu Daher Is Doing Well as a Miner</h2>
<p>Daher runs a whole team and has been doing so ever since he graduated from university. He entered a world that was wrought with financial ruin, as Lebanon is currently dealing with the full collapse of its financial system and hyperinflation. He says he and his fellow miners work around the clock to constantly be adding new assets and units of bitcoin to the blockchain.</p>
<p>Right now, Daher runs a team of approximately 40 people from both Lebanon and Syria. In an interview, he commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>We can&#8217;t sleep. We can&#8217;t have any break. All my team is still awake. They don&#8217;t sleep. Our shift is working 16 hours per day, and sometimes, up to 18 or 19 hours.</p></blockquote>
<p>Lebanon used to be a solid financial center in the middle of the world. Sadly, the country has suffered due to years of war, bad spending decisions enforced by government regulators, and even Ponzi schemes. As a result, the banking sector in the country has become virtually non-existent in recent years, and many people struggle to remain afloat and maintain their livings.</p>
<p>Daher needed to find a way to make money fast after graduation. He started out small in the mining industry, first extracting units on just two or three outdated machines. From there, he got in touch with a friend that connected him to hydroelectric power, which ultimately allowed him to expand his business and bring more miners into the mix. He says:</p>
<blockquote><p>When we started, it was our great idea to make money while sleeping or eating.</p></blockquote>
<p>Initially, Daher went to school to study architecture, though he saw that many of his classmates were struggling to find work in that department after their studies were over. He realized he had to find a new way to make money, and crypto mining seemed like the prime way to do this. His company has now been in business for over two years and he’s not looking back.</p>
<p>Things have gotten so good that it’s not uncommon for Daher to pull in at least $20K a month through his mining efforts. He also has 400 crypto farms spread out across 42 separate villages.</p>
<h2>How Did Lebanon End Up Like It Is?</h2>
<p>Nicholas Shafer – a University of Oxford academic that’s studying Lebanon’s growing crypto mining sector – described the banking environment in the country, mentioning:</p>
<blockquote><p>Due to sanctions controls, difficulty with using cash, and specifically in Lebanon, the banking system and the inability to use dollars or wire money, USD Tether is essentially a key intermediary currency between people in the Chinese hardware market to Lebanese purchasers.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ahmad-abu-daher-is-a-young-and-wealthy-crypto-miner/">Ahmad Abu Daher Is a Young (and Wealthy) Crypto Miner</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ahmad-abu-daher-is-a-young-and-wealthy-crypto-miner/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>December 10, 2022: the biggest product launch ever planned by My NEO Group.</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/december-10-2022-the-biggest-product-launch-ever-planned-by-my-neo-group/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/december-10-2022-the-biggest-product-launch-ever-planned-by-my-neo-group/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 06:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75940</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEO X it’s the first one Super App which integrates into an all-in-one solution, fintech and crypto services, and hundreds of commonly used apps for online shopping and communication. NEO X The Super App Shift: How consumers want save, shop and spend in the connected economy, My NEO Group look at how consumer demand for<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/december-10-2022-the-biggest-product-launch-ever-planned-by-my-neo-group/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/december-10-2022-the-biggest-product-launch-ever-planned-by-my-neo-group/">December 10, 2022: the biggest product launch ever planned by My NEO Group.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEO X it’s the first one Super App which integrates into an all-in-one solution, fintech and crypto services, and hundreds of commonly used apps for online shopping and communication.</p>
<p><iframe loading="lazy" title="NEO X Super App. The all-in-one Solution powered by MY NEO GROUP" width="1778" height="1000" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/9XPTLemi-2Q?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>NEO X</em></p>
<p><strong>The Super App Shift: </strong></p>
<p><em>How consumers want save, shop and spend in the connected economy, My NEO Group look at how consumer demand for streamlined payment experiences has created widespread interest in a super app to </em><em>manage the complexity of modern life.</em></p>
<p>A broad range of recent technological changes, from advanced mobile devices to artificial intelligence (AI)powered standalone applications to new payments technologies, have changed the parameters of the possibilities for retailers, financial institutions (FIs) and consumers.</p>
<ul>
<li>Real-time connections between payment rails, retailers, essential and nonessential activities and digital identities power today&#8217;s consumer experiences.</li>
<li>We call this decentralized, evolving global infra- structure built for efficiency, security and intuitive user experience the ConnectedEconomy.</li>
</ul>
<p>Within the ConnectedEconomy, con- sumers engage in a range of core activities that power day-to-day life actions that are now fundamental interconnected. For example, shop- ping online can lead to ordering from restaurants via an app, which can nor- malize app-based grocery delivery, opening the door to many other con- nected undertakings. Though these actions are intertwined, the current infrastructure is anything but. The channels consumers use to engage in the ConnectedEconomy are disjointed, a nest of separate apps and websites from myriad providers that can clog smartphone home screens and neces- sitate the creation of overwhelming numbers of accounts (and the remem- brance and safekeeping of just as many account credentials).</p>
<p>A super app may fix this. A super app provides a user interface through which consumers can shop, order food, check social media, bank, crypto and so on — all within a single solution. It can help solve the current ecosys- tem’s decentralization problem and address consumers’ universal desire for consistent, secure and frictionless interactions throughout the pillars of their lives.</p>
<p><strong>Global consumers already want a super app: Approximately seven in 10 respondents report interest in such a solution.</strong></p>
<p>Driven by a desire for convenience and financial wellness — the latter especially among Generation Z consumers — most survey respondents have at least some interest in a solution that would allow them to manage payments and other everyday activities through a centralized tool. Overall, approx- imately onequarter are “very” or “extremely” interested in a super app, and consumers who have fully inte- grated</p>
<p>connective technology into their lives are approximately twice as likely as other respondents to exhibit this high interest.</p>
<p><strong> Consumers desire a super app, particularly for convenience and security.</strong></p>
<p>A core advantage of a super app is its elegance: such a solution takes what once was a tangled thread pile of apps, websites and channels and spools it into a single, centralized experience. Nearly four in 10 consumers who are “slightly” or “somewhat” interested in a super app highly value the benefit of minimizing the risk of losing sensitive information, and among highly interested consumers, that share rises to 57%. An equal share of highly interested consumers greatly values the convenience of coordinating different areas of life in one place.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-75942 aligncenter" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Picture64-600x385.jpg" alt="" width="600" height="385" /></p>
<p><strong>Why does Musk want to make an &#8216;everything app&#8217;?</strong></p>
<p><iframe loading="lazy" title="Could Elon Musk Turn Twitter Into a Super App?" width="1778" height="1000" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/gZqVoEKVwBk?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>Would you like to make your smartphone more efficient by managing all the main apps in a single centralized platform? From social networks, to WhatsApp, to those for online shopping, such as Amazon and many others.</p>
<p>The solution is NEO X. It&#8217;s the first “all-in-one” Super App that aggregates and makes your apps usable quickly, in a single login, freeing up storage space on your phone.</p>
<p>NEO X was conceived and built by MY NEO GROUP. This is why it is a real “Digital Ecosystem”, a versatile and scalable fintech platform, in which banking services and next-generation payment solutions are found. In the Super App you can aggregate all your current accounts, centrally manage transactions, deposit and exchange cryptocurrencies, and thanks to an innovative exchange system, use them to pay with a prepaid card, or with the integrated contactless system.</p>
<p><strong>On December 10, 2022, don&#8217;t miss the official launch of NEO X, live on the social networks of My NEO Group.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Date: December 10, 2022</strong></p>
<p>8:00 a.m. Miami</p>
<p>2:00 p.m. Italy</p>
<p>3:00 p.m. Latvia</p>
<p>6:00 p.m. Dubai</p>
<p>7:00 p.m. Mumbai</p>
<p><strong>Book your place for free now: </strong>shorturl.at/wAJL4</p>
<p><strong>More about My NEO Group: </strong><a href="https://myneo.org" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://myneo.org</a> and <a href="https://myneogroup.com" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://myneogroup.com</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/december-10-2022-the-biggest-product-launch-ever-planned-by-my-neo-group/">December 10, 2022: the biggest product launch ever planned by My NEO Group.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/december-10-2022-the-biggest-product-launch-ever-planned-by-my-neo-group/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
