<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 18:13:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Dexsport detects hack, user funds unaffected</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dexsport-detects-hack-user-funds-unaffected/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dexsport-detects-hack-user-funds-unaffected/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 18:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry and Adoption]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75971</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dexsport, a Web3 betting platform that supports cryptocurrency payment, reported a hacking incident that ended up in $400,000 in BUSD being stolen. According to the Dexsport team, on November 30, hackers exploited a vulnerability in the off-chain part related to the case-sensitive recording of unique transaction identifiers for processing deposits and improperly increased the balance<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dexsport-detects-hack-user-funds-unaffected/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dexsport-detects-hack-user-funds-unaffected/">Dexsport detects hack, user funds unaffected</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dexsport, a Web3 betting platform that supports cryptocurrency payment, reported a hacking incident that ended up in $400,000 in BUSD being stolen. According to the Dexsport team, on November 30, hackers exploited a vulnerability in the off-chain part related to the case-sensitive recording of unique transaction identifiers for processing deposits and improperly increased the balance of their wallets on the platform. After that they withdrew illicitly obtained coins.</p>
<p>The breach was quickly detected and fixed, with additional security mechanisms added. User funds were not compromised or affected.</p>
<p>“The vulnerability was not on the side of our smart contracts as they are constantly tested and audited by the leading security firms Certik and Pessimistic,” Dexsport spokesperson is quoted as saying. “We know that, in a trustless environment, the reputation is one of the main treasures, especially in a bear market. Therefore, we pay maximum attention to the high level of user experience and safety of user funds.”</p>
<p>Stolen coins were the platform&#8217;s own assets used as additional liquidity.</p>
<p>Operations were paused for a few hours, but currently all the workflow is retrieved. Withdrawals and deposits are delivered without delays.</p>
<p><a href="https://go.dexsport.io/go/f59e603e" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Dexsport</a> is a Web3 cryptocurrency-supporting betting platform. It is deployed on the Binance Smart Chain, OKX, Polygon, and Avalanche blockchains. The project provides a secure and transparent betting system via smart contracts and blockchain.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dexsport-detects-hack-user-funds-unaffected/">Dexsport detects hack, user funds unaffected</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dexsport-detects-hack-user-funds-unaffected/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Santander Is Ending All Payments to Crypto Exchanges</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/santander-is-ending-all-payments-to-crypto-exchanges/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/santander-is-ending-all-payments-to-crypto-exchanges/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 17:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto exchanges]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[payments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Santander]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75424</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Santander – a UK-based financial institution – has announced it’s not going to allow any crypto exchange payments beginning in 2023. Thus, anyone who has a crypto wallet tied to their traditional bank account that tries to wire money to an attached crypto exchange to purchase assets will instantly be blocked. Santander Clearly Doesn&#8217;t Like Crypto The<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/santander-is-ending-all-payments-to-crypto-exchanges/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/santander-is-ending-all-payments-to-crypto-exchanges/">Santander Is Ending All Payments to Crypto Exchanges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Santander – a UK-based financial institution – has <a href="https://money.usnews.com/investing/news/articles/2022-11-04/santander-to-block-uk-transfers-to-crypto-exchanges-in-2023" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://money.usnews.com/investing/news/articles/2022-11-04/santander-to-block-uk-transfers-to-crypto-exchanges-in-2023&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668540095509000&amp;usg=AOvVaw3K3hDc5vetVI30IdUNpGQ6" data-wpel-link="external">announced it’s not going</a> to allow any crypto exchange payments beginning in 2023. Thus, anyone who has a crypto wallet tied to their traditional bank account that tries to wire money to an attached crypto exchange to purchase assets will instantly be blocked.</p>
<h2>Santander Clearly Doesn&#8217;t Like Crypto</h2>
<p>The organization is taking a lot of flak for the maneuver, with many traders and investors claiming that the bank should not be allowed to decide what its customers can spend their money on. Beginning next year, all real-time payments to crypto exchanges will not be permitted through Santander accounts, and this is just another notch on the old “England hates crypto” ladder that’s been growing exponentially over the last few years.</p>
<p>A spokesperson for Santander issued the following statement regarding the company’s recent decision:</p>
<blockquote><p>Keeping our customers safe from cryptocurrency scams is a top priority. We intend to further protect customers by blocking all faster payments we identify to cryptocurrency exchanges from Santander accounts. This will be implemented during 2023.</p></blockquote>
<p>The United Kingdom has not always been the friendliest country when it comes to digital assets. Not long ago, the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) – a regulatory agency for the United Kingdom – <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fca-rules-all-crypto-atms-in-the-uk-are-operating-illegally/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fca-rules-all-crypto-atms-in-the-uk-are-operating-illegally/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668540095509000&amp;usg=AOvVaw1dxgpYbSFF-010TVxK1K6t" data-wpel-link="internal">announced that all bitcoin</a> and crypto-based ATMs would be illegal in the country. In a statement, the FCA explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>None of the crypto asset firms registered with us have been approved to offer crypto ATM services, meaning that any of them operating in the U.K. are doing so illegally and consumers should not be using them… We regularly warn consumers that crypto assets are unregulated and high-risk, which means people are very unlikely to have any protection if things go wrong, so people should be prepared to lose all their money if they choose to invest in them.</p></blockquote>
<p>The FCA and the United Kingdom regularly stand against crypto trading and all related issues claiming that as they are not regulated, they cannot be trusted. This has been the main reason both entities have taken such hard stances against this growing industry, and while to an extent we can understand where they’re coming, it can be argued that the United Kingdom is suffering from a lack of crypto innovation.</p>
<h2>The UK Isn&#8217;t Kind to Crypto</h2>
<p>While Santander is now making headlines with its decision, it’s not the first bank in the UK to limit crypto-based activity. Customers will still be able to receive payouts to their bank accounts from crypto exchanges, though sending companies money directly through Santander is another story.</p>
<p>This is still more than what the company will allow with firms like Binance, which continues to see all its transactions from Santander-based accounts blocked fully following the implementation of new regulatory tactics in July of last year.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/santander-is-ending-all-payments-to-crypto-exchanges/">Santander Is Ending All Payments to Crypto Exchanges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/santander-is-ending-all-payments-to-crypto-exchanges/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dubai Is Creating a New Crypto Regulatory Agenda</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dubai-is-creating-a-new-crypto-regulatory-agenda/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dubai-is-creating-a-new-crypto-regulatory-agenda/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 15:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto-regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dubai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UAE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75422</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dubai – which has grown exponentially over the years as a leading digital currency hub – is expanding its reputation thanks in part to the Dubai Financial Services Authority (DFSA), the regulatory entity of the region. The organization is now unveiling a new digital currency regime designed to boost crypto-based innovation and regulatory strategies. Dubai Is Growing<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dubai-is-creating-a-new-crypto-regulatory-agenda/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dubai-is-creating-a-new-crypto-regulatory-agenda/">Dubai Is Creating a New Crypto Regulatory Agenda</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dubai – which has grown exponentially over the years as a leading digital currency hub – is expanding its <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-ae/news/other/dfsa-unveils-cryptocurrency-token-regime-to-foster-innovation/ar-AA13BJG3" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.msn.com/en-ae/news/other/dfsa-unveils-cryptocurrency-token-regime-to-foster-innovation/ar-AA13BJG3&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668540095513000&amp;usg=AOvVaw3vnBNgWiJR0sEC0X3mkDJ7" data-wpel-link="external">reputation thanks in part</a> to the Dubai Financial Services Authority (DFSA), the regulatory entity of the region. The organization is now unveiling a new digital currency regime designed to boost crypto-based innovation and regulatory strategies.</p>
<h2>Dubai Is Growing Its Crypto Friendly Sector</h2>
<p>The goal is to make the crypto arena in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/dubai/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/dubai/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668540095513000&amp;usg=AOvVaw1hWF25tdcuQvIdPll98GWU" data-wpel-link="internal">Dubai</a> as transparent as possible according to a statement regarding the agency’s objectives. Chief executive of the DFSA Ian Johnston said:</p>
<blockquote><p>As a progressive regulator, the DFSA recognizes the growing interest in innovative financial products. Our work to develop a comprehensive crypto token regime has [considered] feedback from a broad range of stakeholders. It aims to strike a balance between encouraging innovation in the DIFC and protecting the consumers of these financial products.</p></blockquote>
<p>Crypto regulation has been at the forefront of several governments over the past few months, a prime example being the government of the United States. Earlier in the year, a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-is-the-biden-crypto-executive-order-all-its-cracked-up-to-be/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-is-the-biden-crypto-executive-order-all-its-cracked-up-to-be/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668540095513000&amp;usg=AOvVaw0YnZBVwOfQ-ca8JgkHNrI5" data-wpel-link="internal">crypto executive order</a> was issued asking financial companies and agencies throughout the nation to commit themselves to crypto-based research so they could better understand how crypto assets can negatively and positively impact traders in America.</p>
<p>The order also opened the door to a digital version of USD. Now, it looks like Dubai is taking a page out of this book and seeking to regulate digital asset activity to ensure all goes smoothly within its borders.</p>
<p>The idea of regulation has always been a two-sided coin (pardon the pun). On the one hand, it can be argued that regulation goes against everything the digital currency scene stands for. The goal was to ensure that there were no prying eyes in the mix. Traders and users would be free of third parties and middlemen having a say in what can and cannot be done with their hard-earned money.</p>
<p>This was all designed to give traders their financial freedom and autonomy, which in the long run, isn’t a bad idea. At the same time, the crypto space – largely due to the lack of regulation – has been subjected to various criminal incidents that have seen exchanges get hacked and many individuals victimized by fraudulent projects that steal their funds. Many argue that some degree of regulation is necessary. Otherwise, the crypto space will never attain the legitimacy and mainstream attention it deserves.</p>
<h2>Keep Players Protected</h2>
<p>In its regulatory draft, the DFSA has stated it aims to implement appropriate protection issues to ensure traders’ data and assets aren’t stolen. The framework will also seek to prevent money laundering and implement newfound market integrity to ensure all traders remain shielded against illicit actors.</p>
<p>Lastly, all crypto companies seeking to offer services in Dubai must become registered with the DFSA.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dubai-is-creating-a-new-crypto-regulatory-agenda/">Dubai Is Creating a New Crypto Regulatory Agenda</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dubai-is-creating-a-new-crypto-regulatory-agenda/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Did Binance Help Iran Avoid Financial Sanctions?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/did-binance-help-iran-avoid-financial-sanctions/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/did-binance-help-iran-avoid-financial-sanctions/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 13:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Iran]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Patrick Hillmann]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75420</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Iran is a sanctioned country. It’s not allowed to engage in certain activities unless the United States says so. Despite all this, popular digital currency exchange Binance still enabled the country to engage in crypto trades nearing $8 billion at press time. Binance Is Alleged to Have Aided Iran Almost all the trades occurred between Binance and<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/did-binance-help-iran-avoid-financial-sanctions/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/did-binance-help-iran-avoid-financial-sanctions/">Did Binance Help Iran Avoid Financial Sanctions?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Iran is a sanctioned country. It’s not allowed to engage in certain activities unless the United States says so. Despite all this, popular digital currency exchange Binance <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-ae/money/news/crypto-exchange-binance-helped-iranian-firms-trade-8-billion-despite-sanctions/ar-AA13K4nc" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.msn.com/en-ae/money/news/crypto-exchange-binance-helped-iranian-firms-trade-8-billion-despite-sanctions/ar-AA13K4nc&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668540095517000&amp;usg=AOvVaw3vuPaUp8wvJd2G130yNZpt" data-wpel-link="external">still enabled the country</a> to engage in crypto trades nearing $8 billion at press time.</p>
<h2>Binance Is Alleged to Have Aided Iran</h2>
<p>Almost all the trades occurred between Binance and Nobitex, a crypto exchange based in the Middle Eastern country. This data comes directly from blockchain analysis firm Chainalysis, which recently produced a report discussing how sanctioned countries will often use crypto to avoid financial penalties.</p>
<p>Back in July, it was stated by various media outlets that Binance knew about what was going on in Iran and did nothing about it. People working within the realms of the exchange were aware that the company was quite popular in Iran, and thus they continued to offer services to the sanctioned region. At around the same time, Binance executive and founder Changpeng Zhao issued the following tweet:</p>
<blockquote><p>Binance banned Iranian users after sanctions. Seven got missed/found a workaround. They were banned later anyways.</p></blockquote>
<p>In a statement, Binance spokesman Patrick Hillmann explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>Binance.com is not a US company, unlike other platforms that have exposure to these same US sanctioned entities. However, we have taken proactive steps to limit our exposure to the Iranian marketplace.</p></blockquote>
<p>Not long ago, Binance stated that the company was going to be implementing complete know your customer (KYC) protocols to ensure that all its customers were who they claimed to be. Hillmann continued his statement with the following:</p>
<blockquote><p>Residents of Iran are prohibited from opening or maintaining [accounts]. We are continually updating processes and technology as we learn about new risks and potential exposures. As a result of these efforts, including real-time transaction monitoring in coordination with external vendors, between June of 2021 and November of 2022, Binance&#8217;s exposure to Iranian-linked entities has seen an exponential decline.</p></blockquote>
<p>Hillmann also hinted that so long as accounts are vetted and checked for wrongdoing, Binance shouldn’t be labeled an illicit exchange. He says that the company goes through great lengths to make sure all the activity occurring through its wallets remains clean and that it is also quick to report anything unusual it might see. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>What&#8217;s important to note is not where the funds come from, as crypto deposits cannot be blocked, but what we do after the funds are deposited.</p></blockquote>
<h2>The Firm Has Been in the News a Lot</h2>
<p>Not long ago, the crypto exchange made headlines <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-hacked-nearly-600-million-in-bnb-stolen/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-hacked-nearly-600-million-in-bnb-stolen/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668540095517000&amp;usg=AOvVaw3ajQIDQlirfsM8x6mbFM26" data-wpel-link="internal">when it suffered a breach</a> that saw close to $600 million in digital funds stolen from its hot wallets. Discussing the hack, Zhao commented with:</p>
<blockquote><p>An exploit on a cross-chain bridge, BSC Token Hub, resulted in extra BNB. We have asked all validators to temporarily suspend BSC. The issue is contained now. Your funds are safe.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/did-binance-help-iran-avoid-financial-sanctions/">Did Binance Help Iran Avoid Financial Sanctions?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/did-binance-help-iran-avoid-financial-sanctions/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CloudChain (CLDC) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cloudchain-cldc-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cloudchain-cldc-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 08:20:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75963</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec. 8, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed CloudChain (CLDC) on December 8, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the CLDC/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading. Laying the foundation for an interoperable, distributed web, CloudChain (CLDC) unites and expands new web3 ecosystem<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cloudchain-cldc-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cloudchain-cldc-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">CloudChain (CLDC) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec. 8, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed CloudChain (CLDC) on December 8, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the CLDC/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading.</p>
<p>Laying the foundation for an interoperable, distributed web, <a href="https://bscscan.com/token/0x1a5afa6ecac4016aa585a5539a29e40ffb522242" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">CloudChain</a> (CLDC) unites and expands new web3 ecosystem where apps and services can communicate across chain. Its native token CLDC has been listed on LBank Exchange at 10:00 UTC on December 8, 2022, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision.</p>
<p><strong>Introducing Cloud</strong><strong>Chain</strong></p>
<p>Founded by FineVentures, an investment company specializing in distributed blockchain networks, CloudChain is a next-generation blockchain protocol that unites an entire network of purpose-built blockchains, allowing them to operate seamlessly together at scale. Because CloudChain allows any type of data to be sent between any type of blockchain, it unlocks a wide range of real-world use cases.</p>
<p>While blockchains have demonstrated great promise in several fields—Internet of Things (IoT), finance, governance, identity management, web decentralization, and asset-tracking to name a few—design limitations in previous systems have largely hindered large-scale adoption. CloudChain’s design offers several distinct advantages over existing and legacy networks, including scalability, upgradeability, transparent governance and cross-chain composability.</p>
<p>With a global team of top distributed system engineers, cryptographers, solutions architects and researchers who have developed distributed network technology for over 12 years in healthcare, law, architecture, and education, CloudChain was created as a better network by linking various virtual currencies and blockchain ecosystems. By bringing together the best features from multiple specialized blockchains, CloudChain paves the way for new decentralized marketplaces to emerge, offering fairer ways to access services through a variety of apps and providers.</p>
<p>The cross-chain composability and message passing of CloudChain allows shards to communicate, exchange value, and share functionality, opening the door to a new wave of innovation. And thanks to CloudChain’s ability to bridge blockchains, CloudChain network will also be able to interact with popular decentralized-finance protocols and crypto assets on external networks like Ethereum.</p>
<p>In addition, it’s also easy to participate in CloudChain ecosystem. Users can install mined servers to become CloudChain participants, and it doesn&#8217;t just limit participants to network users. One can also become part of the CloudChain Network in other ways and receive rewards from CloudChain foundation.</p>
<p><strong>About CLDC Token</strong></p>
<p>CLDC is the native token of the CloudChain ecosystem. It serves three distinct purposes, including distributed networking server usages, staking, and bartering. The CLDC token holder offers worldwide distributed network servers at a low cost. Users can use a distributed network to operate a more secure server. And through the staking service, users receive a certain level of compensation even if they do not use a mining server. In addition, various products can also be exchanged using CLDC.</p>
<p>Based on BEP-20, CLDC has a total supply of 10 billion (i.e., 10,000,000,000) tokens. It has been listed on LBank Exchange at 10:00 UTC on December 8, 2022, investors who are interested in the CloudChain investment can easily buy and sell CLDC token on LBank Exchange right now. The listing of CLDC token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p>
<p><strong>Learn More about</strong> <strong>CLDC Token:</strong></p>
<p>Official Website: <a href="https://www.cloudchain.network/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.cloudchain.network/</a><br />
Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/cloudchain_official" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://t.me/cloudchain_official</a><br />
Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/cldc_network" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/cldc_network</a></p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media: </strong></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Facebook</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong></p>
<p>LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
LBank Exchange<br />
<a href="mailto:marketing@lbank.info">marketing@lbank.info</a><br />
<a href="mailto:business@lbank.info">business@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cloudchain-cldc-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">CloudChain (CLDC) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cloudchain-cldc-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Risk of More Losses Below $0.30</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-0-30/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-0-30/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 06:18:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75960</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ADA price is signaling a bearish bias below the $0.32 support zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $0.320 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.308 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Bitfinex). The price could continue to<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-0-30/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-0-30/">Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Risk of More Losses Below $0.30</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>ADA price is signaling a bearish bias below the $0.32 support zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $0.320 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.308 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Bitfinex).</li>
<li>The price could continue to move down if it stays below the $0.315 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Cardano price is struggling below $0.315 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-upside-break-above-18k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. ADA price must stay above the $0.295 support to avoid more downsides.</em></p>
<h2>Cardano Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, cardano price saw a fresh decline from the $0.330 zone against the US Dollar. The ADA/USD pair declined below the $0.320 and $0.308 support levels.</p>
<p>The price even declined below the $0.305 support and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-bulls-aim-fresh-increase-above-0-335/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hour)</a>. A low was formed near $0.3008 and the price is now consolidating losses. On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $0.308 zone.</p>
<p>There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.308 on the 4-hours chart. The trend line is near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3292 swing high to $0.3008 low.</p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $0.315 level and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours) or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3292 swing high to $0.3008 low, above which the price might recover.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $0.350 zone. A clear upside break above the $0.350 level might send the price towards the $0.388 resistance. Any more gains could start a steady increase towards the $0.400 level.</p>
<p>On the downside, an immediate support is near the $0.300 level. The next major support is near the $0.295 level, below which the price may perhaps decline towards the $0.262 support level. Any more losses might call for a test of the $0.250 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_75961" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Cardano-Price-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-75961" class="size-full wp-image-75961" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Cardano-Price-1.png" alt="Cardano Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-75961" class="wp-caption-text">Cardano Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ADAUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that ADA price is now trading below $0.312 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it fails to surpass the $0.315 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ADA/USD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for ADA/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.300 and $0.295.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.315 and $0.330.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-0-30/">Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Risk of More Losses Below $0.30</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-0-30/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Analysis: Bulls Aim Upside Break above $1,300</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-bulls-aim-upside-break-above-1300/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-bulls-aim-upside-break-above-1300/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 03:28:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75956</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum price is showing positive signs above the $1,220 level against the US Dollar. ETH price is now trading above $1,230 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a major contracting triangle forming with resistance near $1,290 on the 4-hours chart (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could climb further if it clears<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-bulls-aim-upside-break-above-1300/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-bulls-aim-upside-break-above-1300/">Ethereum Price Analysis: Bulls Aim Upside Break above $1,300</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ethereum price is showing positive signs above the $1,220 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>ETH price is now trading above $1,230 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a major contracting triangle forming with resistance near $1,290 on the 4-hours chart (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could climb further if it clears the $1,290 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ethereum price is rising above the $1,220 level against the US Dollar. ETH/USD could rise further if it clears the $1,290 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Ethereum Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-rally-possible-above-this-hurdle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">ethereum saw a decent increase</a> above the $1,200 level against the US Dollar. ETH price was able to gain pace for a move above the $1,230 level and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</p>
<p>The bulls even cleared the $1,250 resistance zone. However, they struggled to clear the $1,300 and $1,310 resistance levels. There was a downside correction below the $1,260 level. The price declined below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1,151 swing low to $1,310 high.</p>
<p>On the downside, the price found support near the $1,230 zone. It remained stable above the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1,151 swing low to $1,310 high.</p>
<p>The price is now rising above $1,230 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-at-risk-of-drop-below-1k-2/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. An immediate resistance on the upside is near the $1,280 level. The next major resistance is near the $1,290 zone. Any more gains could even send the price towards the $1,400 resistance zone in the near term.</p>
<p>On the downside, an initial support is near the $1,250 level. The next major support is now near the $1,230 level and the triangle lower trend line. A break below the $1,230 support could push the price to $1,185. Any more losses could lead the price towards $1,120 or even $1,070 in the coming days.</p>
<div id="attachment_75957" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Ethereum-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-75957" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-75957" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Ethereum-1.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-75957" class="wp-caption-text">Ethereum Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Ethereum price is clearly trading above the $1,230 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, ether price could climb further if it clears the $1,290 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $1,250, followed by the $1,230 zone.</p>
<p>Key Resistance$ Levels – $1,290 and $1,310.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-bulls-aim-upside-break-above-1300/">Ethereum Price Analysis: Bulls Aim Upside Break above $1,300</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-bulls-aim-upside-break-above-1300/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tokenz Limited Is Establishing Its Own Crypto Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tokenz-limited-is-establishing-its-own-crypto-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tokenz-limited-is-establishing-its-own-crypto-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 17:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manu Prashant]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rimmi Sen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tokenz Limited]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75418</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tokenz Limited – a firm that seeks to provide blockchain-based sustainable practices – has launched its own digital currency exchange to permit customers to trade, purchase, and sell assets like bitcoin and Ethereum. The goal is to enable carbon exchanges within the free market. Tokenz Limited Is Bringing Its Own Exchange to Fruition Rimmi Sen – one<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tokenz-limited-is-establishing-its-own-crypto-exchange/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tokenz-limited-is-establishing-its-own-crypto-exchange/">Tokenz Limited Is Establishing Its Own Crypto Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tokenz Limited – a firm that seeks to provide blockchain-based sustainable practices – has launched its own digital currency <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-in/money/news/tokenz-limited-unveils-new-exchange-platform-to-permit-cryptocurrency-trading/ar-AA13Efab" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.msn.com/en-in/money/news/tokenz-limited-unveils-new-exchange-platform-to-permit-cryptocurrency-trading/ar-AA13Efab&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668540095521000&amp;usg=AOvVaw07bbzpEa2INYahM-0kWQx4" data-wpel-link="external">exchange to permit</a> customers to trade, purchase, and sell assets like bitcoin and Ethereum. The goal is to enable carbon exchanges within the free market.</p>
<h2>Tokenz Limited Is Bringing Its Own Exchange to Fruition</h2>
<p>Rimmi Sen – one of the directors of Tokenz Limited – commented in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Tokenz’s platform has arrived with the aim to empower every type of cryptocurrency user. With the launch of our exchange platform, we intend to stand behind our vision that cryptocurrency is for everyone. No other exchange offers .1 percent daily spot wallet holding APY for every trader. Cryptocurrency platforms can be both easy to use and rewarding, and we aim to prove that.</p></blockquote>
<p>Manu Prashant – co-director of the firm – also threw his two cents into the mix, commenting:</p>
<blockquote><p>Cryptocurrencies are growing, and we believe [they] will lead the market. I think efforts have been made to launch a platform that provides insurance for all accounts. Ours is the platform in the market that intends to ensure every user’s wallet is secure compared to other platforms in the market. The platform intends to not have bugs, and supports anti-money laundering.</p></blockquote>
<p>The above news is a testament to just how strong and popular digital currency remains. While the space is in one of its worst positions ever, there are still so many people interested in trading that Tokenz felt no choice but to commit itself to a whole new crypto exchange platform.</p>
<p>The digital currency arena has been failing miserably over the last several months. The space has lost more than $2 trillion in overall valuation and the price of bitcoin – the world’s number one digital currency by market cap – has incurred a 70 percent dip from its all-time high of about $68,000 per unit, which it achieved in November 2021. It’s not a pretty sight, and many have been wondering if perhaps the crypto space is coming to a standstill or reaching a full end of sorts.</p>
<h2>A Testament to the Power of Crypto</h2>
<p>This news is proof that it’s not. Tokenz is an organization that seeks to empower both companies and individuals alike through crypto trading, an industry that has always sought to provide full financial anonymity and privacy to users. They do not have to worry about third parties, middlemen, or prying eyes interfering with their financial activities. They can simply choose to do what they will with their money and not suffer any repercussions for it.</p>
<p>At the same time, Tokenz also prides itself on trying to limit the amount of carbon the space emits. The company has long sought to comply with present environmental regulations and limit the amount of damage the space can do to the planet, which <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-bitcoin-mining-may-require-more-energy-than-180-countries/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-bitcoin-mining-may-require-more-energy-than-180-countries/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668540095521000&amp;usg=AOvVaw1Ki9pQD-qeXZhW_Z0FKIDY" data-wpel-link="internal">some say is getting worse</a> by the day.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tokenz-limited-is-establishing-its-own-crypto-exchange/">Tokenz Limited Is Establishing Its Own Crypto Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tokenz-limited-is-establishing-its-own-crypto-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Freedom Convoy Is Still Waiting on Certain Crypto Funds</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-freedom-convoy-is-still-waiting-on-certain-crypto-funds/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-freedom-convoy-is-still-waiting-on-certain-crypto-funds/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 15:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chad Eros]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Freedom Convoy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75416</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Freedom Convoy made headlines earlier in the year when Canada sought to impose COVID vaccine mandates. Comprised of several Canadian truckers and others who refused to give in, the Convoy took issue with what it felt were oppressive politics, and let the world know it wasn’t going to be giving in any time soon. The Freedom<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-freedom-convoy-is-still-waiting-on-certain-crypto-funds/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-freedom-convoy-is-still-waiting-on-certain-crypto-funds/">The Freedom Convoy Is Still Waiting on Certain Crypto Funds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Freedom Convoy made headlines <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/canada-seeks-to-invoke-new-rules-preventing-truckers-from-earning-crypto-donations/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/canada-seeks-to-invoke-new-rules-preventing-truckers-from-earning-crypto-donations/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668540095791000&amp;usg=AOvVaw3nD1oeBW4ObuNSflKt6dCY" data-wpel-link="internal">earlier in the year</a> when Canada sought to impose COVID vaccine mandates. Comprised of several Canadian truckers and others who refused to give in, the Convoy took issue with what it felt were oppressive politics, and let the world know it wasn’t going to be giving in any time soon.</p>
<h2>The Freedom Convoy Is Waiting for Its Crypto Funds</h2>
<p>During that period, many people who sided with the Convoy made the decision to forward digital currency funds to those involved. This was because a lot of the fiat currencies that were being utilized to fund their efforts were being blocked by Canadian financial agencies who claimed these kinds of donations were illegal. Thus, donors felt crypto could get the job done and give these people the money they needed to purchase supplies and other items that could keep them in action.</p>
<p>Sadly, this isn’t quite the case, as <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-ca/news/canada/money-flowed-to-convoy-protesters-through-envelopes-of-cash-cryptocurrency-campaign-inquiry-hears/ar-AA13IRKQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.msn.com/en-ca/news/canada/money-flowed-to-convoy-protesters-through-envelopes-of-cash-cryptocurrency-campaign-inquiry-hears/ar-AA13IRKQ&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1668540095791000&amp;usg=AOvVaw2EiI6UsMOW_wQfhDrLpDV3" data-wpel-link="external">several of these crypto funds</a> remain fully locked up in court battles or have been returned to the donors. Still, the Convoy was able to get its hands on several million dollars’ worth of bitcoin and other mainstream altcoins through firms like Tally Coin, which allowed individuals to donate small amounts of BTC at virtually no cost.</p>
<p>The truckers and everyone else involved in the Convoy were able to access their funds by people simply passing out envelopes telling them how to gain access to them. One of the campaigns that arranged for this was called Honk Honk HODL, which through the method mentioned above, was able to distribute just over $800K to the truckers and those taking part in the Convoy. In a statement, the group said:</p>
<blockquote><p>This had been accomplished by handing out physical envelopes that contained instructions on how to access approximately $8,000 of bitcoin using a mobile phone.</p></blockquote>
<p>The Public Order Emergency Commission was able to end the Tally Coin project and prevent further crypto donations through that window, though much of the money wound up getting passed out before the Commission could take control. In a report, the Commission states:</p>
<blockquote><p>A system was later put into place whereby the money was placed into numbered envelopes with $500 in each one. People would then sign out these envelopes and distribute them to truckers. Records were kept of the identities of the individuals who were given envelopes, and this information was tracked on a spreadsheet.</p></blockquote>
<h2>How Would the Money Be Moved?</h2>
<p>Chad Eros is the man who was tasked with overseeing the collection of money in the campaign. The report continues with:</p>
<blockquote><p>Mr. Eros did not have direct knowledge of the source of their funding but understood that individuals would bring cash to the ARC hotel, which would be processed and placed into envelopes in the amount of $2,000 CAD before being distributed to protesters.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-freedom-convoy-is-still-waiting-on-certain-crypto-funds/">The Freedom Convoy Is Still Waiting on Certain Crypto Funds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-freedom-convoy-is-still-waiting-on-certain-crypto-funds/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
