<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 21:54:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/cropped-fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Crypto Winter to Blame for Miami BTC Conference Attendance Dips? Analysts Think So</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-winter-to-blame-for-miami-btc-conference-attendance-dips-analysts-think-so/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 17:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto winter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Bitcoin Conference]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robert Kennedy Jr.]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78448</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The crypto winter of 2022 may be technically over, but the effects are still being felt. This year, the Miami Bitcoin Conference saw a whopping 50 percent dip in its attendance rate. The Crypto Winter Is Still a Powerful Enemy That means roughly half of last year’s crowd showed up this year, and many are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-winter-to-blame-for-miami-btc-conference-attendance-dips-analysts-think-so/">Crypto Winter to Blame for Miami BTC Conference Attendance Dips? Analysts Think So</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto winter of 2022 may be technically over, but the <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/bitcoin-miami-conference-drop-attendance-crypto-094208644.html">effects are still being</a> felt. This year, the Miami Bitcoin Conference saw a whopping 50 percent dip in its attendance rate.</p>
<h2>The Crypto Winter Is Still a Powerful Enemy</h2>
<p>That means roughly half of last year’s crowd showed up this year, and many are blaming the crypto winter for the drops.</p>
<p>Some analysts believe the number may be lower than what’s being reported. For example, this year, roughly 15,000 people were in attendance. However, there are records suggesting last year’s attendance rate exceeded 35,000.</p>
<p>Despite this, the event still featured some relatively high-ranking individuals, one of which was democratic candidate for the White House Robert F. Kennedy Jr.</p>
<p>Kennedy is <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-candidate-robert-kennedy-jr-has-big-plans-for-the-crypto-space/">clearly a bitcoin fanatic</a>. He mentioned he is going to be accepting bitcoin and crypto donations for his campaign, and he also stated that should he become president, the government will never get in the way of investing in and holding digital assets. He commented during a speech:</p>
<blockquote><p>As president, I will make sure that your right to hold and use bitcoin is inviolable. I am an ardent defender and lifelong defender of civil liberties, and bitcoin is both an exercise and a guarantee of those freedoms.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also took serious issue with the situation involving Canadian truckers in 2022. During that time, several of these men took to protesting after their government announced they were required to take the COVID-19 vaccine. When their bank accounts and other <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-fund-set-up-for-canadian-truckers/">financial tools were shut</a> off, they sought to gain access to crypto so they could continue their actions.</p>
<p>From there, the Canadian government got in the way and sought to freeze whatever digital assets they got their hands on. Kennedy said he would make sure the government could take no action like that in the future and commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>None of these lawful and peaceful protestors had violated any law, but suddenly, they found that they could not access their money [or] their bank accounts to pay their mortgages or feed their families. When I witnessed this devastating use of government repression, I realized for the first time how free money is as important as free expression.</p></blockquote>
<h2>So Many Losses</h2>
<p>The crypto winter of 2022 was arguably the worst period for bitcoin and its digital cousins. BTC – the world’s number one digital currency by market cap – was trading at a new all-time high of $68,000 per unit during November of 2021. However, roughly one year later, the asset had lost more than 70 percent of its value and was trading in the mid-$16K range. It was a sad and ugly sight to see.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, things didn’t quite stop there, and many cryptocurrencies followed in BTC’s footsteps, thus causing the arena to lose more than $2 trillion in overall value.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-winter-to-blame-for-miami-btc-conference-attendance-dips-analysts-think-so/">Crypto Winter to Blame for Miami BTC Conference Attendance Dips? Analysts Think So</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Michael Saylor Is Still a Big Bitcoin Fan</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-bitcoin-is-the-future/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 15:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Saylor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroStrategy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78445</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Former CEO of software giant MicroStrategy Michael Saylor made an appearance at this year’s Miami Bitcoin Conference. He assured all people in attendance that bitcoin is here to stay, and that they shouldn’t worry about the prospects of a currency that, at this stage, has clearly proven itself. Michael Saylor Still Loves BTC Saylor addressed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-bitcoin-is-the-future/">Michael Saylor Is Still a Big Bitcoin Fan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Former CEO of software giant MicroStrategy Michael Saylor <a href="https://www.thestreet.com/cryptocurrency/news/michael-saylor-bitcoin-miami-thermodynamically-sound">made an appearance at this</a> year’s Miami Bitcoin Conference. He assured all people in attendance that bitcoin is here to stay, and that they shouldn’t worry about the prospects of a currency that, at this stage, has clearly proven itself.</p>
<h2>Michael Saylor Still Loves BTC</h2>
<p>Saylor addressed the 2022 bear market and tried hard to calm the investors in the room. Whether they felt concerned about the future of bitcoin is unclear at this time, but Saylor was quick to address the situation and let them know that the technology behind bitcoin is revolutionary, and that it’s going to secure the currency’s place in the financial spectrum. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>The reason that bitcoin is so sound, literally sound, is because it is thermodynamically sound. It’s this masterpiece of engineering because we’ve created a monetary asset where we’ve stripped away all the counterparty risks.</p></blockquote>
<p>He stated that one of the big reasons why bitcoin is so “special” is because it’s simple to use. Currently, individuals only need internet connections and digital wallets to appreciate bitcoin and its altcoin cousins. When one is trying to gain access to standard monetary tools and services, they’re usually stuck answering for their past histories (job histories, financial histories, etc.) The funny thing is bitcoin really doesn’t care about all that.</p>
<p>With a  digital wallet and access to the internet, one can easily start trading, buying, selling, and investing in bitcoin to their heart’s content. Saylor also said that right now, bitcoin’s “safe haven” status is growing given how shady and untrustworthy the entire rest of the industry has become following a long <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-provide-their-thoughts-on-latest-bitcoin-rally/">string of bank failures</a> that include Silicon Valley Bank, Signature Bank, and First Republic Bank. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>All of those things, which could be viewed in a negative light, are positive for bitcoin because they’re all accelerating the conclusion of the mainstream investor that bitcoin is special and ethically sound, technically sound, and economically sound. Bitcoin fixes things. Bitcoin can help everybody.</p></blockquote>
<p>He was also very positive about the Lightning Network, which is a service that enables many smaller bitcoin transactions to occur off-chain, thus freeing up space on the network and ensuring transactions move faster.</p>
<p>Saylor is a maximalist that believes bitcoin has a bright future ahead of it despite its many ups and downs of the last couple years. He finished his statements with:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin is here to stay. Bitcoin is the future.</p></blockquote>
<h2>So Much Love Led to Trouble</h2>
<p>Saylor is a man who has been investing his company’s <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-microstrategy-bitcoin-bet-is-already-paying-off-big-time/">reserves into bitcoin</a> since late 2020.</p>
<p>While things initially appeared positive, by the middle of 2022, the industry took a nasty turn, yet Saylor <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-buys-more-btc-despite-ongoing-crash/">continued to invest and ultimately</a> put his company in debt as a result.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-bitcoin-is-the-future/">Michael Saylor Is Still a Big Bitcoin Fan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How the Debt Ceiling Argument May Come Back to Hurt BTC</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-the-debt-ceiling-argument-may-come-back-to-hurt-btc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 13:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Debt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Noelle]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78442</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Right now, the U.S. government is trapped in a financial fight that has both sides of the political spectrum arguing over the debt ceiling. The Debt Ceiling Issue Could Hurt BTC Democrats and individuals like Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen want the debt ceiling raised, as they believe the U.S. is about to go bankrupt, while [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-the-debt-ceiling-argument-may-come-back-to-hurt-btc/">How the Debt Ceiling Argument May Come Back to Hurt BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Right now, the U.S. government is trapped in <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/us-debt-deal-may-weigh-over-bitcoin-observers-1032342845">a financial fight that</a> has both sides of the political spectrum arguing over the debt ceiling.</p>
<h2>The Debt Ceiling Issue Could Hurt BTC</h2>
<p>Democrats and individuals like Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen want the debt ceiling raised, as they believe the U.S. is about to go bankrupt, while the republicans and House Speaker Kevin McCarthy are saying any such hike would result in devastating financial repercussions for the standard American public.</p>
<p>Some analysts are saying that any kind of deal is likely to have a few nasty repercussions for bitcoin and other forms of crypto. One of the things they say will happen is the prices of bond yields will move up. Whenever this happens, bitcoin tends to go down, by contrast.</p>
<p>Giving her thoughts on the matter, Noelle Acheson – former head of research at Genesis Trading and the author of the “Crypto Is Macro Now” newsletter – stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>The issuance of debt to top up coffers will have the opposite effect. Money will move out of cash and risk assets into U.S. government bonds, especially as yields on these instruments rise to offset the increase in supply. This could be bad for bitcoin and gold, which in theory fall in price when yields are rising (high yield environments tend to not be great for assets that yield nothing). What&#8217;s more, the issuance of more U.S. government debt would increase public spending, which would be good for the economy, further delaying the likelihood of rate cuts.</p></blockquote>
<p>The fact remains that only assets tied to the true American economy stand to do well should a deal be reached following the debt crisis. Bitcoin and other forms of crypto aren’t tied to anything, suggesting they could suffer in the long run.</p>
<p>It is also widely believed that should the U.S. default, this would ultimately lead to panic selling and a huge desire for cash similar with what was seen during the early days of the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/coronavirus/">COVID-19 pandemic</a>. During that time, the price of bitcoin fell by more than 50 percent.</p>
<h2>What Will Happen?</h2>
<p>Satyakam Gautam – the rates trader at India-based bank ICICI – commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>What it implies is a lack of USD funding in the immediate short term post the successful ceiling negotiation, if any. Corporate bonds markets, as well as private credit, will find it hard to roll over existing maturities, and this will lead to a real crash in either commercial real estate assets funding or plain junk bond issuers. This might be the real deal crash which the U.S. rate markets have been elusively looking for. There might be then a secular fall in long-end rates, as well as massive steepening in U.S. rates. This should augur well for risk haven [forex] like JPY &amp; CHF.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-the-debt-ceiling-argument-may-come-back-to-hurt-btc/">How the Debt Ceiling Argument May Come Back to Hurt BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: More Gains Seems Likely Above $0.30</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-more-gains-seems-likely-above-0-30/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 05:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79035</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ADA price is showing positive signs above the $0.280 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above $0.285 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $0.2950 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Coinbase). The price could gain [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-more-gains-seems-likely-above-0-30/">Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: More Gains Seems Likely Above $0.30</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>ADA price is showing positive signs above the $0.280 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $0.285 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $0.2950 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Coinbase).</li>
<li>The price could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $0.300 and $0.305 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Cardano price is rising above $0.288 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-bulls-in-control-above-29500/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. ADA price could rally if there is a clear move above the $0.305 resistance.</em></p>
<h2>Cardano Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This week, Cardano price started a steady increase above the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-bulls-face-key-hurdle-near-0-305/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$0.275 resistance zone</a> against the US Dollar. The ADA/USD pair gained pace for a move above the $0.280 and $0.285 levels.</p>
<p>Besides, there was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $0.295 on the 4-hours chart. The bulls were able to pump the price toward the $0.300 resistance. However, the bears appeared near $0.300. A high is formed near $0.300 and the price is now consolidating gains.</p>
<p>It is trading well above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.2673 swing low to the $0.30 high. ADA price is still trading above $0.288 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>It is also showing positive signs above the same trend line. On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $0.300 zone. The next major resistance is near the $0.305 zone.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $0.305 resistance might start a strong increase toward $0.332. Any more gains above the $0.332 resistance might send the price toward the $0.350 resistance or even $0.365.</p>
<p>On the downside, immediate support is near the $0.292 level. The next major support is near the $0.285 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.2673 swing low to the $0.30 high. A clear move below the $0.285 level might send the price toward the $0.275 level. Any more losses might send the price toward the $0.262 support.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79036" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79036" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Cardano-Price.png"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-79036" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Cardano-Price.png" alt="Cardano (ADA) Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Cardano-Price.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Cardano-Price-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Cardano-Price-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Cardano-Price-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Cardano-Price-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Cardano-Price-750x345.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79036" class="wp-caption-text">Cardano (ADA) Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ADAUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a> indicates that ADA price is now trading above $0.285 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $0.300 and $0.305 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ADA/USD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for ADA/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.285 and $0.275.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.300 and $0.305.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-more-gains-seems-likely-above-0-30/">Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: More Gains Seems Likely Above $0.30</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Could Rally Above $2,000</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-rally-above-2000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 03:28:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79031</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum price is moving higher above the $1,880 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH price is now trading above $1,880 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $1,930 on the 4-hours chart (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could climb further if it [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-rally-above-2000/">Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Could Rally Above $2,000</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ethereum price is moving higher above the $1,880 resistance against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>ETH price is now trading above $1,880 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $1,930 on the 4-hours chart (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could climb further if it stays above the $1,900 support zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ethereum price is rising above the $1,880 level against the US Dollar. ETH/USD could rise further if it clears the $2,000 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Ethereum Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few sessions, Ethereum saw a decent increase above the $1,820 level against the US Dollar. ETH price was able to gain pace for a move above the $1,880 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>The bulls even pushed the price above the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-eyes-more-gains-above-1920/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$1,920 resistance zone</a>. A high is formed near $1,976 and the price is now consolidating gains. It is trading above the $1,950 level. It is also above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward wave from the $1,823 swing low to the $1,976 high.</p>
<p>Ether’s price is showing positive signs above $1,880 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-recover-to-1900/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support near $1,930 on the 4-hours chart.</p>
<p>Immediate resistance on the upside is near the $1,975 level. The next major resistance is near the $2,000 zone. A clear move above the $2,000 level could send the price toward $2,080. Any more gains could even send the price toward the $2,200 resistance zone or $2,250 in the near term.</p>
<p>On the downside, initial support is near the $1,930 level and the trend line. The next major support is now near the $1,900 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward wave from the $1,823 swing low to the $1,976 high.</p>
<p>A break below the $1,900 support could push the price to $1,825. Any more losses could lead the price towards $1,750.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79032" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79032" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-79032" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum-750x345.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79032" class="wp-caption-text">Ethereum Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, Ethereum’s price is trading above the $1,880 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, Ether’s price could climb further if it stays above the $1,900 support zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $1,930, followed by the $1,900 zone.</p>
<p>Key Resistance$ Levels – $2,000 and $2,080.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-rally-above-2000/">Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Could Rally Above $2,000</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Opinion: Bitcoin Could Be a Big Topic in Next Year&#8217;s Presidential Election</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-bitcoin-could-be-a-big-topic-in-next-years-presidential-election/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 17:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Opinion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OpEd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[election]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78432</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Will crypto and bitcoin be big talking points in next year’s presidential election? Everything looks like they will be, though it’s hard to say for sure. Bitcoin Could Be a Major Subject in Next Year&#8217;s White House Race For the most part, it’s not like crypto hasn’t made its way into the world of presidential [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-bitcoin-could-be-a-big-topic-in-next-years-presidential-election/">Opinion: Bitcoin Could Be a Big Topic in Next Year&#8217;s Presidential Election</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Will crypto and <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bitcoin/">bitcoin</a> be big talking points in next year’s presidential election? Everything looks like they will be, though it’s hard to say for sure.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Could Be a Major Subject in Next Year&#8217;s White House Race</h2>
<p>For the most part, it’s not like crypto hasn’t made its way into the world of presidential politics in the past. As we all remember in 2019 and 2020, there were several democratic hopefuls that sought to enhance their campaigns with crypto promises. <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/andrew-yang-the-crypto-president/">Andrew Yang</a>, for example, an entrepreneur and businessman, said one of his big plans was to make all crypto regulations easy to understand in America and rewrite them all in plain English, thus ending the many frustrations of crypto investors all over the country.</p>
<p>The same announcement came by way of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-bloomberg-proposes-clarified-bitcoin-regulation-if-he-takes-the-white-house/">Michael Bloomberg</a>, the former mayor of New York City. However, neither of these men were able to arouse much attention from voters, and it wasn’t long before they opted to suspend their campaigns and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-presidential-candidate-andrew-yang-drops-out-of-race/">step away from the</a> presidential game.</p>
<p>However, one can easily argue that that was a different time. Crypto didn’t have the reputation that it does now. Also, over the past several years, we have seen a man – Joe Biden – run America into the ground. He has employed economic tactics that have <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-fed-bitcoins-worst-enemy-right-now/">ultimately caused the Fed</a> to fall into a compromised spot. They have regularly implemented rate hikes as a means of fighting inflation, and this caused crypto prices to fall like they never had before.</p>
<p>Biden has also sought to do everything he can to make crypto investors’ lives difficult. From a phony <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-amendment-for-infrastructure-bill-leads-to-more-problems-and-infighting/">infrastructure bill</a> to an <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-biden-using-an-obama-era-program-to-ban-btc/">Obama-era policy</a> designed to shut crypto firms out of the standard monetary club, Biden has made a real name for himself as the most anti-crypto leader in history.</p>
<p>However, despite all this, we’ve also seen bitcoin’s “<a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/why-bitcoin-is-once-again-considered-a-safe-haven/">safe haven</a>” reputation grow over the past several months as banks throughout America and Europe continue to fall. Institutions like Silicon Valley Bank, Signature Bank, and First Republic Bank <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-provide-their-thoughts-on-latest-bitcoin-rally/">have all collapsed</a>, and bitcoin’s price has only shot up during the ordeals. Thus, it appears many believe bitcoin to be a solid hedge against the failures of USD and other forms of fiat.</p>
<h2>So Much Has Happened in Recent Years</h2>
<p>The circumstances have undoubtedly changed over the past three or four years, and the stage has been set for crypto to potentially be a big topic in the political spectrum next year. Its reputation has grown, there are likely more people investing in it, and thus it’s also likely that they’ve been more affected by the goings-on of 2022 and 2023.</p>
<p>Not to mention there are already several presidential candidates – from <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-candidate-robert-kennedy-jr-has-big-plans-for-the-crypto-space/">Robert Kennedy Jr.</a> to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vivek-ramaswamy-is-making-crypto-a-big-part-of-his-white-house-campaign/">Vivek Ramaswamy</a> – that have announced big bitcoin plans should they take the White House next year.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-bitcoin-could-be-a-big-topic-in-next-years-presidential-election/">Opinion: Bitcoin Could Be a Big Topic in Next Year&#8217;s Presidential Election</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dylan LeClair: BTC Can End All Financial Corruption</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dylan-leclair-btc-can-end-all-financial-corruption/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 15:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dylan LeClair]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[financial corruption]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78429</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dylan LeClair – the head of market research at media company BTC Inc., which reports on all things crypto and blockchain – is a maximalist that’s convinced bitcoin could potentially end all corruption and shortcomings in the standard financial industry. Dylan LeClair Thinks Highly of BTC In a recent interview, he commented: The money is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dylan-leclair-btc-can-end-all-financial-corruption/">Dylan LeClair: BTC Can End All Financial Corruption</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dylan LeClair – the head of market research at media company BTC Inc., which reports on all things crypto and blockchain – is a maximalist <a href="https://www.thestreet.com/cryptocurrency/news/bitcoin-2023-bitcoin-is-the-solution-to-the-corruption-of-money">that’s convinced bitcoin could</a> potentially end all corruption and shortcomings in the standard financial industry.</p>
<h2>Dylan LeClair Thinks Highly of BTC</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, he commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>The money is corrupt, and everything else is corrupted as a result.</p></blockquote>
<p>LeClair has a lot of points. Bitcoin and other digital currencies were designed as alternatives to standard finance, a space that has long been dominated by third parties, prying eyes, and middlemen saying what we can and cannot do with our money. They look at our job histories and other personal aspects of our lives and decide if we can gain access to specific products and services from there.</p>
<p>Bitcoin and crypto, however, don’t care about these things. So long as you have an internet connection and a digital wallet, that’s all you really need to concern yourself with. You can begin trading, investing in, selling, and buying digital assets as you see fit. The point of crypto was to give unbanked individuals or people that cannot gain access to traditional finance opportunities to garner the products and items they need for ordinary, day-to-day survival.</p>
<p>In regions <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/could-btc-revamp-the-financial-industry-of-africa/">such as Africa</a>, for example, which has long been hurt by the ongoing political and financial corruption of standard banks and centralized institutions, bitcoin and crypto have long been proposed as potential solutions to these problems, so the idea of crypto working as an alternate method to standard finance is not new.</p>
<p>However, LeClair went further in his statements and mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>When you dig down to the roots of government – of the money, of how power systems and society [are] structured today – you really come to understand that the base level of this whole game is corrupted. The incentives at the base layer of society [are] corrupted in the form of corrupt money. [It] got abstracted to gold receipts, gold IOUs, gold certificates of deposits, and ultimately, that was corrupted because you had to trust someone not to mess with your gold.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also mentioned that the world of standard finance has endured tons of failures, and crypto is the perfect outlet to help those that have been affected by those failures attain monetary solutions to their ongoing issues. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>The orange pill is the fact that we have an engineering solution to fix the money, and it&#8217;s this big abstract concept that people aren&#8217;t familiar with.</p></blockquote>
<h2>So Many Banks Are Crashing!</h2>
<p>Right now, many standard <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-provide-their-thoughts-on-latest-bitcoin-rally/">institutions have failed</a>. The list presently contains names such as Signature Bank, Silicon Valley Bank, and First Republic Bank.</p>
<p>As these banks have fallen, bitcoin’s price and the prices of many digital assets have shot up.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dylan-leclair-btc-can-end-all-financial-corruption/">Dylan LeClair: BTC Can End All Financial Corruption</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Presidential Hopeful Robert Kennedy Jr. Has Big Ideas Regarding the Crypto Space</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-candidate-robert-kennedy-jr-has-big-plans-for-the-crypto-space/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 13:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robert Kennedy Jr.]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78426</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Just yesterday, Live Bitcoin News published an article talking about republican presidential candidate Vivek Ramaswamy and his big plans for bitcoin should he take the White House next November. Interestingly, he’s not the only presidential hopeful that’s betting big on bitcoin. Robert F. Kennedy Jr. – a democratic candidate who’s hoping to take the nomination [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-candidate-robert-kennedy-jr-has-big-plans-for-the-crypto-space/">Presidential Hopeful Robert Kennedy Jr. Has Big Ideas Regarding the Crypto Space</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Just yesterday, <em>Live Bitcoin News</em> published an article <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vivek-ramaswamy-is-making-crypto-a-big-part-of-his-white-house-campaign/">talking about republican</a> presidential candidate Vivek Ramaswamy and his big plans for bitcoin should he take the White House next November. Interestingly, he’s not the only presidential hopeful that’s betting big on bitcoin. Robert F. Kennedy Jr. – a democratic candidate who’s hoping to take the nomination from Biden early next year – is also saying he’s going to do big things <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/presidential-candidate-robert-f-kennedy-jr-to-accept-campaign-donations-in-bitcoin-outlines-plan-for-crypto/ar-AA1bucUD">when it comes to cryptocurrency</a>.</p>
<h2>Robert Kennedy Is a BTC Fan, It Seems</h2>
<p>Not long ago, during the Miami Bitcoin Conference, Kennedy made an appearance and announced that his campaign is accepting bitcoin and crypto donations. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Our campaign will be the first presidential campaign in history to accept bitcoin donations through the Lightning Network, and today, we move one step closer to the future. Today, we show the world the power, durability, and flexibility of bitcoin.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also mentioned that as the president, he will ensure all Americans have the right to crypto holdings, and that the government will never do anything to get in the way of this. His comments are clear throwbacks to the nasty maneuvers Americans have witnessed over the past two years involving the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), its <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-wants-more-funds-to-go-after-crypto-companies/">head Gary Gensler</a>, and the many members of the Biden administration, which have done nothing positive for crypto and instead appear dead set on making their lives hard.</p>
<p>For one thing, an infrastructure bill was implemented in the summer of 2021 – the first year of Biden’s false presidency – that was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-amendment-for-infrastructure-bill-leads-to-more-problems-and-infighting/">aimed less at rebuilding</a> roads, schools, and hospitals (like the word infrastructure would imply) and more towards making crypto investors pay more come tax time starting in the year 2024.</p>
<p>In addition, Biden has implied he’s looking to instill <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-biden-using-an-obama-era-program-to-ban-btc/">an Obama-era policy</a> that will shut out all digital currency companies from standard finance, thus making it hard for them to garner access to bank accounts, credit cards, and other products that could help their operations float along.</p>
<p>Lastly, Biden’s faulty economic plans have caused the Fed to hike rates repeatedly, which really hurt crypto prices in 2022 and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-fed-bitcoins-worst-enemy-right-now/">brought them to record lows</a>. Kennedy mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>First, I will defend the right of self-custody of bitcoin and other digital assets. You should be able to own your private keys the same as you own the keys to your car or your wallet.</p></blockquote>
<h2>No Mining Tax!</h2>
<p>He also stated complete disagreement with Biden’s plans to implement <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/biden-wants-to-tax-crypto-mining-companies-at-30/">a 30 percent tax</a> on all crypto mining operations, claiming that he is an advocate for home-based crypto mining. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I don&#8217;t think the government has the right to demand access to your bitcoin key or… any of your passwords. To say otherwise is to cede essential territory to the surveillance state.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-candidate-robert-kennedy-jr-has-big-plans-for-the-crypto-space/">Presidential Hopeful Robert Kennedy Jr. Has Big Ideas Regarding the Crypto Space</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Could Rally Further above $0.12</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-rally-further-above-0-12/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 05:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar Lumens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79028</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stellar lumen price is rising toward the $0.120 resistance zone against the US Dollar. XLM price is now trading above $0.10 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.100 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could start another increase [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-rally-further-above-0-12/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Could Rally Further above $0.12</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Stellar lumen price is rising toward the $0.120 resistance zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>XLM price is now trading above $0.10 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.100 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start another increase if it clears the $0.115 and $0.120 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Stellar lumen price is trading above $0.10 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-bulls-in-control-above-29500/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. XLM price must stay above the $0.120 support to rise further.</em></p>
<h2>Stellar Lumen Price Analysis (XLM to USD)</h2>
<p>After forming a base above the $0.075 level, Stellar Lumen price started a fresh increase against the US Dollar. The XLM/USD pair broke the $0.088 resistance zone to move into a positive zone.</p>
<p>The price even cleared the $0.0950 resistance and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-extend-gains-above-0-092/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. The upward move was such that the price spike to $0.1180 before the bears appeared. A high was formed near $0.1177 and the price is now consolidating gains.</p>
<p>XLM is now trading above $0.10 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.100 on the 4-hour chart.</p>
<p>The price is also stable above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.0752 swing low to the $0.1177 high. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $0.114 zone. The next major resistance is near the $0.118 level.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $0.118 level might send the price toward the $0.120 level. Any more gains could lead the price toward the $0.1250 level or even $0.1320 in the coming sessions.</p>
<p>Initial support on the downside is near the $0.100 level and the trend line. The next major support sits near the $0.0965 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.0752 swing low to the $0.1177 high.</p>
<p>The main support is near the $0.092 zone. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.085 level in the near term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79029" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79029" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-79029" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM.png" alt="Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-750x345.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79029" class="wp-caption-text">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XLMUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a> indicates that XLM price is now trading above $0.10 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start another increase if it clears the $0.114 and $0.12 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XLM/USD is gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for XLM/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.100 and $0.0965.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.115, $0.120, and $0.132.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-rally-further-above-0-12/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Could Rally Further above $0.12</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=3338 metric#misses=67 metric#hit-ratio=98.0 metric#bytes=4413669 metric#prefetches=97 metric#store-reads=18 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=102 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=6 metric#ms-total=228.79 metric#ms-cache=11.16 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.5872 metric#ms-cache-ratio=4.9 -->
