<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 04:15:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/cropped-fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Bears Aim Breakdown Below $0.075</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bears-aim-breakdown-below-0-075/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 06:08:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79759</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tron price started a fresh decline below the $0.080 level against the US Dollar. TRX price is now trading below $0.0785 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key contracting triangle forming with resistance near $0.0775 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could continue to move down [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bears-aim-breakdown-below-0-075/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Bears Aim Breakdown Below $0.075</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Tron price started a fresh decline below the $0.080 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>TRX price is now trading below $0.0785 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key contracting triangle forming with resistance near $0.0775 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it breaks the $0.0750 support zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>TRON price started a fresh decline below the $0.0820 zone against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-at-risk-below-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. TRX price could accelerate lower if there is a move below $0.0750.</em></p>
<h2>Tron Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, Tron price started a steady decline from well above the $0.0820 resistance level against the US Dollar. TRX price struggled to gain pace for more gains and formed a top near $0.085.</p>
<p>The price started a fresh decline below the $0.0800 level. There was a clear move below the $0.0780 level. A low is formed near $0.0754 and the price is now consolidating losses. The price is now trading below $0.0785 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-indicators-suggest-fresh-rally-to-0-085/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>On the upside, TRX is facing resistance near the $0.0775 level. It is near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.0854 swing high to the $0.0754 low.</p>
<p>There is also a key contracting triangle forming with resistance near $0.0775 on the 4-hour chart. The next major resistance is near the $0.080 level. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.0854 swing high to the $0.0754 low.</p>
<p>A close above $0.0785 and $0.080 is a must for a fresh increase. In the stated case, the price could rise toward the $0.085 resistance in the near term.</p>
<p>On the downside, initial support is near the $0.0758 level. The next major support is now forming near $0.0750. If there is a downside break below the $0.075 support, the price might revisit the $0.0720 support. Any more losses might call for a move toward the $0.070 zone in the near term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79760" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79760" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/TRON-TRX.png"><img decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" class="size-full wp-image-79760" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/TRON-TRX.png" alt="Tron (TRX) Price" width="1835" height="839" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/TRON-TRX.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/TRON-TRX-600x274.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/TRON-TRX-1100x503.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/TRON-TRX-768x351.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/TRON-TRX-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/TRON-TRX-750x343.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/TRON-TRX-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79760" class="wp-caption-text">Tron (TRX) Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/TRXUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a> indicates that TRX price is now trading below $0.0785 and near the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it breaks the $0.0750 support zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for TRX/USD is slowly gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for TRX/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.0758 and $0.0750.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.0785, $0.080, and $0.085.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bears-aim-breakdown-below-0-075/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Bears Aim Breakdown Below $0.075</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC At Risk Below $30K</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-at-risk-below-30k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 04:08:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79756</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price started a fresh decline below the $29,600 level against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $29,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $29,320 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-at-risk-below-30k/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC At Risk Below $30K</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin price started a fresh decline below the $29,600 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $29,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $29,320 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could extend its decline toward the $28,650 and $28,000 levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin price is declining below $29,600 against the US Dollar. BTC might extend losses if it stays below the $29,500 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price started a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">fresh decline</a> below the $29,600 zone. A high was formed near $30,222 before the price started a steady decline. There was a clear move below the $30,000 and $29,600 support levels.</p>
<p>The price declined below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $28,660 swing low to the $30,222 high. The bears even pushed the price below the $29,320 support zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>The price is now trading below $29,500 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $29,320 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>Immediate resistance on the upside is near the $29,320 level and the trend line. The next major resistance might be near the $29,500 zone. A clear move above the $29,500 level might send the price toward $29,750, above which the price might rise toward the $30,000 level. Any more gains might push the price toward the $31,200 zone.</p>
<p>If there is no upside break, the price might decline below the $29,000 level or the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $28,660 swing low to the $30,222 high.</p>
<p>The first major support is near $28,660. The next key support is near the $28,500 level, below which the price might accelerate lower. In the stated case, the price could decline toward the $28,000 level. Any more losses might send the price toward the $27,400 level.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79757" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79757" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Bitcoin-1.png"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-79757" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Bitcoin-1.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1835" height="839" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Bitcoin-1.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Bitcoin-1-600x274.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Bitcoin-1-1100x503.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Bitcoin-1-768x351.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Bitcoin-1-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Bitcoin-1-750x343.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Bitcoin-1-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79757" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XBTUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, Bitcoin price is clearly trading below $29,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could extend its decline toward the $28,650 and $28,000 levels.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD is now losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $29,000 and $28,660.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $29,320, $29,500, and $30,000.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-at-risk-below-30k/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC At Risk Below $30K</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Germany Says &#8220;No&#8221; to Binance, Denies Company a Crypto License</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/germany-says-no-to-binance-denies-company-a-crypto-license/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 17:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BaFin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Germany]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79138</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Germany has told leading digital currency exchange Binance that its regulators will not issue a crypto custody license to the firm’s executives. Germany Denies Binance Proper Licensure The country is not pleased, allegedly, with the way Binance is handling itself. The company has been on the brink of making every financial agency angry and it [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/germany-says-no-to-binance-denies-company-a-crypto-license/">Germany Says &#8220;No&#8221; to Binance, Denies Company a Crypto License</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Germany has told leading digital currency exchange Binance that its <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-ca/money/topstories/germany-to-reject-binances-bid-for-a-cryptocurrency-licence-source/ar-AA1dd4tU">regulators will not issue</a> a crypto custody license to the firm’s executives.</p>
<h2>Germany Denies Binance Proper Licensure</h2>
<p>The country is not pleased, allegedly, with the way Binance is handling itself. The company has been on the brink of making every financial agency angry and it has already aroused the wrath of institutions such as the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cftc-sues-binance-alleging-financial-violations/">Commodity Futures Trading Commission</a> (CFTC) and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sues-binance-alleges-selling-of-illegal-securities/">Securities and Exchange Commission</a> (SEC). Both have initiated lawsuits against the firm, claiming it has ignored securities laws for many years and even commingled customer funds with those of the enterprise.</p>
<p>BaFin is the major financial regulator in Germany and is not offering further details regarding the matter for confidentiality reasons. Binance also stated that it wouldn’t offer additional information. However, it did say:</p>
<blockquote><p>We continue to work to comply with BaFin&#8217;s requirements.</p></blockquote>
<p>Binance hinted that its fight in Germany isn’t over, and it’s currently working on having “the right team and measures in place” to ensure further discussions with the country. The exchange has been encountering multiple issues throughout Europe at press time, with Belgium’s FSMA regulator recently ordering Binance to stop offering any virtual currency services within its borders.</p>
<p>In addition, France is also performing an investigation of the firm. Binance was also made to exit the Dutch crypto scene given it was allegedly unable to meet the nation’s present regulatory requirements. Furthermore, Germany’s BaFin announced in 2021 it was on the verge of fining Binance for allegedly offering certain crypto tokens to clients without proper information supporting said tokens and the company’s tactics.</p>
<h2>How Far Will This Lawsuit Go?</h2>
<p>Not long ago, many analysts weighed in on the present SEC lawsuit against the crypto company and contemplated the idea of the crypto world existing without Binance. One – Boris Povar, the general director at EYWA – was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/could-the-sec-lawsuit-end-binance-for-good-analysts-weigh-in/">rather dismissive of the</a> lawsuit and felt it was simply an attempt from the SEC to manipulate crypto into taking a route regulators saw fit. Povar mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>This, to me, looks like nothing more than market manipulation, like the ban on cryptocurrencies in China in the past market cycles. Even if Binance.US closes, it won&#8217;t close Binance. This will accelerate Binance&#8217;s transition to a fully decentralized structure, which it has been doing for a long time, since the establishment of Binance DEX on the BNB Beacon Chain and launching of the BNB Smart Chain, plus investing in infrastructure projects such as Trust Wallet, Injective Protocol, and others. That is the future pillar of a decentralized Binance. It will gradually be reborn as a decentralized exchange (DEX) and will become stronger, I think. Any closure of the American market for Binance will lead them to develop other markets in Asia and even France.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/germany-says-no-to-binance-denies-company-a-crypto-license/">Germany Says &#8220;No&#8221; to Binance, Denies Company a Crypto License</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Could This Layer-2 Network Make Ethereum Stronger Than Ever?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/could-this-layer-2-network-make-ethereum-stronger-than-ever/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 15:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quantum Leap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stark Ware]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79135</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Israeli crypto startup Stark Ware has unveiled the new layer-2 Ethereum solution it’s been working on for some time. Known as Starknet v12.0, the upgrade – which also operates under the name “Quantum Leap” – is slated to boost the digital currency network’s throughput tenfold and help Ethereum achieve a level of greatness many analysts [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/could-this-layer-2-network-make-ethereum-stronger-than-ever/">Could This Layer-2 Network Make Ethereum Stronger Than Ever?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Israeli crypto startup Stark Ware <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ethereum-scaler-starknet-launches-testnet-160952167.html">has unveiled the new</a> layer-2 Ethereum solution it’s been working on for some time. Known as Starknet v12.0, the upgrade – which also operates under the name “Quantum Leap” – is slated to boost the digital currency network’s throughput tenfold and help Ethereum achieve a level of greatness many analysts never even fathomed.</p>
<h2>Ethereum May Be on the Verge of Greatness</h2>
<p>Ethereum is the world’s second largest digital currency by market cap and the number one competitor to bitcoin. While the price of ETH may not be comparable to bitcoin, the asset has BTC beat in a big area: its network. The Ethereum network has garnered loads of attention over the year from developers who think that if they can build their coins or blockchains atop ETH, they’re in great shape.</p>
<p>This was true for a long time. Sadly, thanks to this attitude, tons of traffic was eventually brought to ETH, thus slowing it down significantly and increasing its gas fees to the umpteenth degree. This gave way to several competing blockchains – like TRON – which were dubbed “Ethereum killers” and seen as newfound competition.</p>
<p>However, since then, Ethereum endured several upgrades including <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/shapella/">Shapella</a> and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/merge/">Merge</a>, which took place roughly six months apart from each other in March of this year and September of last year, respectively. Ethereum has thus moved from a proof of work concept to a proof of stake module and alleviated some of the high fees and slow speeds that have since become synonymous with the network.</p>
<p>These upgrades have been seen as positive steps forward, but there are still many layer-2s out there that have been brought about as means of helping Ethereum push along even further. One of them is Stark Ware, and it’s now ready to unveil the latest version of itself.</p>
<p>It’s president and co-founder Eli Ben-Sasson has high hopes for the new Quantum Leap upgrade. He stated in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Starknet’s new version, Quantum Leap, is exactly what the name suggests: a leap in TPS, the likes of which nobody yet achieved in the Ethereum ecosystem.</p></blockquote>
<p>Co-founder and CEO Uri Kolodny also threw his two cents into the mix, commenting:</p>
<blockquote><p>We all discuss how Ethereum desperately needs [to] scale. We’re talking about throughput. It’s a concept we all know. How many kids can the water slide take in a minute? How many people can get through airport check-in [in] an hour? How many transactions can a blockchain accommodate in a second?</p></blockquote>
<h2>Helping Things Get Faster</h2>
<p>He continued with:</p>
<blockquote><p>Latency really impacts the feasibility of building dApps that can smoothly leverage blockchain technology. When dApps [need] to wait for 15 minutes to confirm transactions on the blockchain, it’s cumbersome and holds back the potential of defi, gaming, and other use cases.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/could-this-layer-2-network-make-ethereum-stronger-than-ever/">Could This Layer-2 Network Make Ethereum Stronger Than Ever?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blockchain in Space? Some Companies Say It&#8217;s Possible</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-in-space-some-companies-say-its-possible/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 13:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lockheed Martin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Space]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79132</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Does blockchain going to space or taking over it sound foolhardy or impossible? According to a few different crypto companies, the idea isn’t as odd as it might seem at first glance. Blockchain and Space&#8230; The Perfect Match? There are many crypto and blockchain companies out there that are very curious about the universe and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-in-space-some-companies-say-its-possible/">Blockchain in Space? Some Companies Say It&#8217;s Possible</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Does blockchain going to space or taking over it sound foolhardy or impossible? According to a few different crypto companies, the <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/technology/blockchain-to-the-moon-crypto-companies-outer-space-plans-are-less-silly-than-you-think/ar-AA1dpHyn">idea isn’t as odd</a> as it might seem at first glance.</p>
<h2>Blockchain and Space&#8230; The Perfect Match?</h2>
<p>There are many crypto and blockchain companies out there that are very curious about the universe and what distributed ledger technology can do when it comes to space. One of those companies is Lunar Crush. It recently announced plans to rover over 200,000 miles to the moon with a private key etched onto the machine that would make its way through the final frontier.</p>
<p>This is like the plan that <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-wants-to-literally-leave-dogecoin-on-the-moon/">was initiated</a> by Elon Musk. Remember when he said he literally wanted to send Doge to the moon?</p>
<p>In addition to Lunar Crush, crypto startup Cryptosat said it’s working on something called “Space Wallet,” which it said would be used to secure crypto beyond the stars. There are also several other firms – including Filecoin, Space Chain, and Blockstream – that say they want to mix outer space with blockchain.</p>
<p>Cryptosat is a company that was founded by Yan Michalevsky and Yonatan Winetraub. They are pursuing doctoral degrees at Stanford, and the company has already sent two coffee mug-sized satellites into space. They were equipped with small computers that could perform computations and safeguard crypto. Michalevsky commented in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Given the fact that they cannot be accessed physically, that can protect against very sophisticated attacks that are becoming relevant, especially in the blockchain and web3 space[s].</p></blockquote>
<p>Space Chain was founded by former BTC developer Jeff Garzik. It also has a few computers in space right now, and all are attached to satellites, a few of which have to do with the International Space Station. Talk about a big boost for blockchain! The company’s present CEO Cliff Beek said:</p>
<blockquote><p>A blockchain node or any other node in space that is off the terrestrial infrastructure creates an air gap for any access that&#8217;s unauthorized.</p></blockquote>
<p>Blocksteam was founded by Adam Back, who has close ties to Satoshi Nakamoto, the elusive founder of the bitcoin digital currency. The company has garnered more than $125 million at press time to expand its crypto mining facilities. It’s also leasing four satellites that are broadcasting to bitcoin’s blockchain. Back commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>One of the promises of bitcoin is the ability to improve global access to remittances, finance, international transfers and things like that… Entrepreneurs and businesses in different parts of the world where bandwidth is more expensive will use this infrastructure to make it economically feasible.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Securing Files with Blockchain</h2>
<p>Moreover, Lockheed Martin – a defense contractor – is using Filecoin to secure inter-satellite communications.</p>
<p>The company is also launching an interplanetary file system to test its theories regarding blockchain’s abilities to secure satellite transmissions.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-in-space-some-companies-say-its-possible/">Blockchain in Space? Some Companies Say It&#8217;s Possible</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Bears In Active Below $0.30</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-bears-in-active-below-0-30/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 05:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79751</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ADA price is gaining bearish momentum below the $0.312 support zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $0.305 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.2920 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Coinbase). The price could continue to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-bears-in-active-below-0-30/">Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Bears In Active Below $0.30</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>ADA price is gaining bearish momentum below the $0.312 support zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $0.305 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.2920 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Coinbase).</li>
<li>The price could continue to move down if it stays below the $0.300 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Cardano price is struggling below $0.300 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. ADA price could start a fresh increase if it clears the $0.300 and $0.305 resistance levels.</em></p>
<h2>Cardano Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, Cardano price saw a rejection pattern near the $0.302 zone against the US Dollar. The ADA/USD pair declined below the $0.300 and $0.292 support levels.</p>
<p>The price even declined below the $0.288 support and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-risk-of-more-downsides-below-0-30/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. It revisited the $0.2865 support zone. A low is formed near $0.2867 and the price is consolidating losses. It is now trading below $0.305 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $0.290 zone or the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3025 swing high to the $0.2865 low.</p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $0.292 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.2920 on the 4-hour chart. The next key resistance could be $0.295 or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3025 swing high to the $0.2865 low.</p>
<p>A clear upside break above the $0.295 level might send the price toward the $0.300 resistance. Any more gains could start a steady increase toward the $0.315 level or even $0.320.</p>
<p>On the downside, immediate support is near the $0.2865 level. The next major support is near the $0.282 level, below which the price may perhaps decline toward the $0.265 support level. Any more losses might call for a test of the $0.250 level.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79752" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79752" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Cardano-Price.png"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-79752" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Cardano-Price.png" alt="Cardano (ADA) Price " width="1835" height="839" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Cardano-Price.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Cardano-Price-600x274.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Cardano-Price-1100x503.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Cardano-Price-768x351.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Cardano-Price-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Cardano-Price-750x343.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Cardano-Price-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79752" class="wp-caption-text">Cardano (ADA) Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ADAUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a> indicates that ADA price is now trading below $0.305 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $0.300 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ADA/USD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for ADA/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.2865 and $0.2820.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.2920 and $0.300.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-bears-in-active-below-0-30/">Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Bears In Active Below $0.30</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Revisits Key Support</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-revisits-key-support/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 04:08:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79748</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum price is struggling to climb above the $1,880 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH price is now trading below $1,860 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,850 on the 4-hour chart (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could continue to move [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-revisits-key-support/">Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Revisits Key Support</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ethereum price is struggling to climb above the $1,880 resistance against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>ETH price is now trading below $1,860 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,850 on the 4-hour chart (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it breaks the $1,835 support zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ethereum price is declining below $1,850 against the US Dollar. ETH/USD remains at a risk of more downsides below the $1,835 support zone.</em></p>
<h2>Ethereum Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, Ethereum struggled to clear the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-resume-increase-above-1885/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$1,880 resistance zone</a> against the US Dollar. ETH price attempted a few times to clear the $1,880 level but failed.</p>
<p>A swing high was formed near $1,876 and the price started a fresh decline. There was a drop below the $1,860 and $1,850 support levels. There was a move below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1,800 swing low to the $1,876 high.</p>
<p>The pair even spiked below the $1,840 support. It is now trading below $1,850 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-shows-bearish-signs-below-1900/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. On the upside, the price is now facing resistance near the $1,850 level. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,850 on the 4-hour chart.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $1,880 level. The next major resistance is near the $1,900 zone. A clear move above the $1,880 and $1,900 resistance levels might call for a fresh move to $1,950. Any more gains could even send the price toward the $2,000 resistance zone or even $2,050 in the near term.</p>
<p>On the downside, initial support is near the $1,835 level. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1,800 swing low to the $1,876 high.</p>
<p>The next major support is now near the $1,800 level. A break below the $1,800 support could push the price to $1,720. If the bulls fail to protect the $1,720 support, the price might decline toward $1,650.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79749" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79749" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Ethereum-1.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-79749" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Ethereum-1.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1835" height="839" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Ethereum-1.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Ethereum-1-600x274.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Ethereum-1-1100x503.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Ethereum-1-768x351.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Ethereum-1-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Ethereum-1-750x343.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Ethereum-1-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79749" class="wp-caption-text">Ethereum Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, Ethereum price is clearly trading below $1,850 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, ether price could continue to move down if it breaks the $1,835 support zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for ETH/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $1,835, followed by the $1,800 zone.</p>
<p>Key Resistance$ Levels – $1,850 and $1,880.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-revisits-key-support/">Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Revisits Key Support</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BTC is Helping Victims of a War in Sudan</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/btc-is-helping-those-escaping-a-war-in-sudan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 17:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sudan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sudan Hodl]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79128</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There is a war occurring in the African nation of Sudan, and bitcoin is helping residents either survive the rough conditions or escape the nation to freedom. Sudan is in a Rough State The war in Sudan is relatively new, having only begun about four months ago (April of 2023). The conflict has been fueled [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/btc-is-helping-those-escaping-a-war-in-sudan/">BTC is Helping Victims of a War in Sudan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There is a war occurring in the African nation of Sudan, and <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/07/05/how-bitcoin-helps-civilians-escape-the-war-in-sudan/?sh=36f8f43e753e">bitcoin is helping residents</a> either survive the rough conditions or escape the nation to freedom.</p>
<h2>Sudan is in a Rough State</h2>
<p>The war in Sudan is relatively new, having only begun about four months ago (April of 2023). The conflict has been fueled by many financial issues including record-high inflation, which surged beyond the 350 percent mark in 2021. In addition, the Sudanese banking infrastructure has completely collapsed, and this has paved the way for <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitcoin/">bitcoin</a> to march in and save the day in certain cases.</p>
<p>A Sudanese expat that remains anonymous at the time of writing (and living in the country of Ireland) explained in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>It was almost impossible to send money back home. When my aunt called me about bitcoin, I understood that it could have implications beyond my own little online world.</p></blockquote>
<p>He commented that his parents and other family members who were fleeing the nation couldn’t take much with them. No cash, no gold, and it was up to him to find a way to help them start their new lives. That way involved BTC. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>They couldn’t take anything with them. No money, no gold, not even a mobile phone. Anything valuable would have been a serious threat to their life.</p></blockquote>
<p>This inspired him to start a company called Sudan Hodl, a remote crypto firm that has given way to a wide array of bitcoin-based meetups and training camps. He also runs a group called BTC Sudan, which presently houses 500 members on Discord. He says his organizations have helped hundreds of people escape the war since it began. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>There are traders, money exchangers, miners, and just regular people using bitcoin as savings. It’s an incredibly diverse community.</p></blockquote>
<p>He has also managed to raise quite a bit of money for the medical staffers in Sudan so they can help those who must remain behind for whatever reason. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>The medical situation is extremely dire. There is no humanitarian aid. Doctors are unable to purchase supplies. Some are using plastic bottles as chest drains.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Remittances Aren&#8217;t What They Once Were</h2>
<p>The war in the nation has two different caches going at it. One has large control over the government, while the other has primary control over the economy. For one side to win, they must control both sides. Sudan Hodl has put out a statement saying remittances have ultimately died in the nation over the past 17 years or so. The statement reads:</p>
<blockquote><p>Especially in the countryside, people have been working 16-18 hours a day and were still not able to make ends meet. People are desperate. When militias offered $500 to start fighting, it seemed like a good deal to them.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/btc-is-helping-those-escaping-a-war-in-sudan/">BTC is Helping Victims of a War in Sudan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why 2023 Has Been a Turnaround Year for Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/why-2023-has-been-a-turnaround-year-for-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 15:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brandon Zemp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79126</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>2023 has been a year of great turnaround for bitcoin and analysts are wondering why. Bitcoin Has Seen a Lot of Change This Year For one thing, it appears macroeconomic conditions have loosened up somewhat. While many financial experts still see an economic downturn happening towards the end of the year, talks of a recession [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/why-2023-has-been-a-turnaround-year-for-bitcoin/">Why 2023 Has Been a Turnaround Year for Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>2023 has been a year of great turnaround for bitcoin and <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-bounces-back-cryptocurrency-rebounds-after-rough-2022/ar-AA1dk1wD">analysts are wondering</a> why.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Has Seen a Lot of Change This Year</h2>
<p>For one thing, it appears macroeconomic conditions have loosened up somewhat. While many financial experts still see an economic downturn happening towards the end of the year, talks of a recession of somewhat subsided. Still, things are shaky enough (with <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-provide-their-thoughts-on-latest-bitcoin-rally/">bank failures</a> and what not) that people have looked to bitcoin and similar assets as “safe havens” through which they can funnel their money and keep their investments safe.</p>
<p>Crypto expert Brandon Zemp explained also that while some regulatory issues have arisen in the U.S., the markets around the world have eased up when it comes to crypto, thus helping the industry grow at least from an international perspective. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think most of the prior price action bitcoin has had in the past has come largely from the United States, and for the first time, I think you’re seeing a lot of that price action start to happen outside of the United States.</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition, there’s also been a lot of interest stemming from Wall Street players <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blackrock-etf-application-causes-btc-eth-to-surge/">such as BlackRock</a>, which recently filed a bitcoin ETF application with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). While the company had its application initially turned away for <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sends-blackrock-btc-etf-application-back-for-revisions/">not being comprehensive</a> enough, the firm is now looking to revamp the application and resubmit it to the financial agency for a new opinion.</p>
<p>Konstantin Shulga – CEO and co-founder of Finery Markets – said this has to do with the public still showing massive interest in BTC even though it bombed hard last year. Shulga said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The world of cryptocurrency has been facing a lot of uncertainty in the U.S. market due to regulatory issues. However, despite these challenges, institutions have still been showing interest in it as an asset class. It seems that the adoption of cryptocurrency is slowly but surely taking place.</p></blockquote>
<p>Still, Shulga thinks that the regulatory scene in the U.S. is going to be quite stringent, and thus it may take at least a few attempts from BlackRock and similar companies to get the attention of the SEC. Shulga said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Despite numerous attempts, not a single application for a spot [exchange-traded fund] has received the green light from the SEC so far. The biggest question now is whether BlackRock&#8217;s filing will meet a different fate than previous proposals from companies like Fidelity or CBOE Global Markets, which were met with rejection(s).</p></blockquote>
<h2>More Growth Coming?</h2>
<p>Zemp anticipates bitcoin will continue to grow through the rest of the year, stating:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think what will end up happening for bitcoin is we’ll see this continue to rise. Bitcoin could go to $35,000, $40,000, [or] $45,000 potentially. It will get closer and closer to its previous all-time high.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/why-2023-has-been-a-turnaround-year-for-bitcoin/">Why 2023 Has Been a Turnaround Year for Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
