<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 05:31:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>John Ray III: FTX Is the Most Mismanaged Company I&#8217;ve Ever Seen</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/john-ray-iii-ftx-is-the-most-mismanaged-company-ive-ever-seen/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/john-ray-iii-ftx-is-the-most-mismanaged-company-ive-ever-seen/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[John Ray III]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75572</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>John Ray III is an attorney that’s been in the news a lot, lately. He’s the man who cleaned up the Enron mess close to 20 years ago, and now he’s been called in to fix the problems surrounding failed digital currency exchange FTX. John Ray III Has Been Called in to Fix FTX As<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/john-ray-iii-ftx-is-the-most-mismanaged-company-ive-ever-seen/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/john-ray-iii-ftx-is-the-most-mismanaged-company-ive-ever-seen/">John Ray III: FTX Is the Most Mismanaged Company I&#8217;ve Ever Seen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>John Ray III is an attorney that’s been in the news a lot, lately. He’s the man who cleaned up the Enron mess close to 20 years ago, and <a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/sanfrancisco/news/ftx-cryptocurrency-complete-failure-sam-bankman-fried-john-ray-ceo/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">now he’s been called in</a> to fix the problems surrounding failed digital currency exchange <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX</a>.</p>
<h2>John Ray III Has Been Called in to Fix FTX</h2>
<p>As the new CEO of the now bankrupt digital currency firm, Ray commented that he has never seen such a poorly governed company in all his life, nor has ever witnessed such mismanagement of funds. He stated in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Never in my career have I seen such a complete failure of corporate controls and such a complete absence of trustworthy financial information as occurred here. From compromised systems integrity and faulty regulatory oversight abroad, to the concentration of control in the hands of a very small group of inexperienced, unsophisticated, and potentially compromised individuals, this situation is unprecedented.</p></blockquote>
<p>It is being reported that user funds stored within the digital currency exchange were used to purchase luxury homes and other items in the Bahamas for company employees. At the peak of the firm’s collapse, Ray was brought on as the new CEO, with his first day being November 11 of this year.</p>
<p>Sam Bankman-Fried has also been called out because he recently admitted in an interview that he only made appearances in Washington and spoke of regulation as a means of attracting attention to the company. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Regulators, they make everything worse.</p></blockquote>
<p>Ray furthered his discussion with:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bankman-Fried is not employed by the debtors and does not speak for them. In the Bahamas, I understand that corporate funds of the FTX Group were used to purchase homes and other personal items for employees and advisors. I understand that there does not appear to be documentation for certain of these transactions as loans, and that certain real estate was recorded in the personal name of these employees and advisors on the records of the Bahamas.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A King Has Become a Pauper</h2>
<p>The drama surrounding FTX has likely marred the crypto space on a permanent basis. At one time, FTX was considered the golden child of the crypto arena. The cryptocurrency exchange first came to fruition in the year 2019 and quickly rose to prominence as one of the largest digital currency trading platforms in the world. Sam Bankman-Fried was lauded as a genius and many felt the company had a solid and clear future in the world of crypto.</p>
<p>Sadly, this image is fading fast as the company has fallen into a hole of criminality and mistrust. Each day, more information comes out about the enterprise that puts it in a very poor light, and one must wonder if this incident is going to prevent some people from ever trusting this new financial space.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/john-ray-iii-ftx-is-the-most-mismanaged-company-ive-ever-seen/">John Ray III: FTX Is the Most Mismanaged Company I&#8217;ve Ever Seen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/john-ray-iii-ftx-is-the-most-mismanaged-company-ive-ever-seen/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Michael Saylor Gives His Thoughts on the Fall of FTX</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-gives-his-thoughts-on-the-fall-of-ftx/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-gives-his-thoughts-on-the-fall-of-ftx/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 15:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Saylor]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75570</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Former head of MicroStrategy Michael Saylor recently gave his thoughts and opinions on the digital currency scam surrounding FTX, the now fallen cryptocurrency exchange that was once labeled the ultimate golden player in the space. Michael Saylor on the FTX Collapse His conversation began with the statement that what was happening around FTX was “tragic.”<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-gives-his-thoughts-on-the-fall-of-ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-gives-his-thoughts-on-the-fall-of-ftx/">Michael Saylor Gives His Thoughts on the Fall of FTX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Former head of MicroStrategy Michael Saylor <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/michael-saylor-on-ftx-collapse-crypto-may-have-been-the-problem-but-bitcoin-is-still-the-solution/ar-AA149sCZ" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">recently gave his thoughts</a> and opinions on the digital currency scam surrounding FTX, the now fallen cryptocurrency exchange that was once labeled the ultimate golden player in the space.</p>
<h2>Michael Saylor on the FTX Collapse</h2>
<p>His conversation began with the statement that what was happening around FTX was “tragic.” It then transitioned into a discussion of FTT, the native token of the crypto exchange. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Since the supply was largely in friendly hands, they were able to manipulate the price of those tokens up through insider wash trading… Normally, the cynical bitcoiners think, ‘You know, these crypto casinos are just manipulating the price of the token up to dump it on retail,’ but [Bankman-Fried] came up with a particularly diabolical twist to the entire thing.</p></blockquote>
<p>FTX will likely go down as one of the biggest blunders in the history of crypto. First arising in the year 2019, FTX soon developed into one of the biggest and most prominent digital currency trading platforms, giving companies like Coinbase and even Binance runs for their money. The man behind the exchange, a young 30-something named Sam Bankman-Fried, was lauded as a genius by many high-ranking players in the industry, though sadly, that reputation is fading fast.</p>
<p>Mid-November saw trouble begin for the digital currency exchange after it was announced that FTX was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">experiencing a liquidity crunch</a>, and it needed fast cash to stay in business. From there, it turned to Binance for help, and it appeared that the larger company was going to buy out the smaller one, though this <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">merger never occurred</a>.</p>
<p>Within days, Binance issued a statement saying that it would not be purchasing the firm given that the problems FTX was facing were larger than what Binance felt it could handle. From there, Sam Bankman-Fried resigned from his post as the head executive of the firm and the company was forced into bankruptcy proceedings.</p>
<p>Saylor briefly described what user funds were invested in or spent on:</p>
<blockquote><p>They proceeded to spend the money on politicians and lobbying and stadium rights and advertisements and celebrity endorsements and condos in the Bahamas, and then they traded a bunch and made a bunch of bad trades, and then they lost the money.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Bitcoin Is Still a Valid Solution</h2>
<p>Despite all the issues that Saylor has experienced with bitcoin over the last year or so, he still feels that it could be a valid solution to what’s happening. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>It means you don&#8217;t have to trust the FTXs of the world, so yeah. I am a big believer because I believe that although crypto in this case may have been the problem, bitcoin is still the solution, and [Bankman-Fried] may have made a million bitcoin maximalists with this crash.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-gives-his-thoughts-on-the-fall-of-ftx/">Michael Saylor Gives His Thoughts on the Fall of FTX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-gives-his-thoughts-on-the-fall-of-ftx/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>El Salvador Vows to Buy At Least One BTC Each Day</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-vows-to-buy-at-least-one-btc-each-day/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-vows-to-buy-at-least-one-btc-each-day/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[El Salvador]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nayib Bukele]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75568</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nayib Bukele – the president of El Salvador – has issued a tweet saying he is going to be purchasing at least one bitcoin every day during the present market slump. Right now, BTC is trading in the $16K range, and the nation is looking to take advantage of the collapsing price. El Salvador Clearly<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-vows-to-buy-at-least-one-btc-each-day/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-vows-to-buy-at-least-one-btc-each-day/">El Salvador Vows to Buy At Least One BTC Each Day</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nayib Bukele – the president of El Salvador – has <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/el-salvador-plans-to-buy-more-bitcoin-every-day-despite-losing-millions-already/ar-AA14dEb9" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">issued a tweet saying he</a> is going to be purchasing at least one bitcoin every day during the present market slump. Right now, BTC is trading in the $16K range, and the nation is looking to take advantage of the collapsing price.</p>
<h2>El Salvador Clearly Still Loves BTC</h2>
<p>The maneuver is stirring mixed reactions from analysts, some of whom claim it will ensure El Salvador’s digital dominance when the market repairs itself. They believe that when things eventually come back to form, El Salvador will have so many digital reserves to its name that it will never fall into a dark financial hole again.</p>
<p>However, there are others that think El Salvador is making a big mistake. They say that the nation has lost a lot of money already, as during the present dip, the country continued to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nayib-bukele-just-bought-even-more-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">buy assets on a regular</a> basis. This hasn’t helped the nation in many ways given that the price of BTC has continued to slip deeper and deeper into oblivion. They are convinced that by the time BTC is done with its present bear market, El Salvador will have bought so much BTC and wasted so much cash that it will never rebound.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s difficult to say which outlook is correct. In any case, El Salvador has clearly shown itself to be one of the most BTC-devoted nations on the face of the Earth. The country was the first to declare bitcoin legal tender, doing so in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-fully-legal-in-el-salvador-beginning-september-7/" data-wpel-link="internal">September of last year</a>. The nation declared that all people could use BTC to purchase goods and services alongside the U.S. dollar, which up to that point, El Salvador had long been dependent on.</p>
<p>Businesses were also required to accept BTC payments and could not discriminate against those who were using it to make their everyday purchases. The nation experienced heavy resistance from organizations like the World Bank, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-world-bank-will-not-help-el-salvador-with-its-btc-plans/" data-wpel-link="internal">which stated it would</a> not be helping El Salvador with the implementation of its bitcoin agenda given that the currency was too volatile and speculative, and thus could not be taken seriously by financial regulators.</p>
<h2>A Lot of Resistance</h2>
<p>El Salvador didn’t let this little setback bring it down too much. Instead, the country went forth without help and created a new wallet system it called Chivo, which is slang for “cool” amongst the people. The wallet system would allow citizens to store their bitcoin units, and each one was gifted with an early <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/each-el-salvador-resident-could-receive-30-in-free-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">amount of $30 to help</a> them get used to how crypto worked.</p>
<p>Many were not <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-residents-protest-forced-btc-usage/" data-wpel-link="internal">happy about allegedly</a> being “forced” to play by BTC’s rules. There were riots and protests in the streets of San Salvador, the country’s capital city, amongst those who were happy simply using USD.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-vows-to-buy-at-least-one-btc-each-day/">El Salvador Vows to Buy At Least One BTC Each Day</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/el-salvador-vows-to-buy-at-least-one-btc-each-day/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Struggle Continues, Key Resistance Intact</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-struggle-continues-key-resistance-intact/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-struggle-continues-key-resistance-intact/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 06:28:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar Lumens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76175</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stellar lumen price is showing bearish signs below the $0.076 resistance zone against the US Dollar. XLM price is now trading below $0.078 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0780 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could start a<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-struggle-continues-key-resistance-intact/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-struggle-continues-key-resistance-intact/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Struggle Continues, Key Resistance Intact</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Stellar lumen price is showing bearish signs below the $0.076 resistance zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>XLM price is now trading below $0.078 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0780 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a major decline if there is a clear move below the $0.0725 support.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Stellar lumen price is trading below $0.0760 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-at-risk-of-another-crash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. XLM price must stay above the $0.0725 support to avoid more losses.</em></p>
<h2>Stellar Lumen Price Analysis (XLM to USD)</h2>
<p>After a major rejection above the $0.0900 zone, stellar lumen price started a fresh decline against the US Dollar. The XLM/USD pair traded below the $0.0850 support to move into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>There was a move below the $0.0800 and $0.0780 levels. The price even settled below the $0.078 level and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-signals-downturn-upsides-could-be-limited/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. A low was formed near $0.0725 and the price is now consolidating losses. The bears seem to be active below the $0.0760 level.</p>
<p>The price is now trading below $0.078 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $0.0770 level.</p>
<p>The 23.6% Fib retracement level of the key decline from the $0.0910 swing high to $0.0725 low is also near the $0.0769 level. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0780 on the 4-hours chart. A clear upside break above the trend line might send the price towards $0.0800.</p>
<p>Besides, the next major resistance is near the $0.0818 zone. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the key decline from the $0.0910 swing high to $0.0725 low.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $0.0818 level might send the price towards the $0.0850 level. Any more gains could lead the price towards the $0.0880 level or even $0.0910.</p>
<p>An initial support on the downside is near the $0.0738 level. The main support is near the $0.0725 zone. Any more losses could lead the price towards the $0.0700 level in the near term, below which the price might even retest $0.0680.</p>
<div id="attachment_76176" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76176" class="size-full wp-image-76176" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-3.png" alt="Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76176" class="wp-caption-text">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XLMUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that XLM price is now trading below $0.078 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could start a major decline if there is a clear move below the $0.0725 support.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XLM/USD is losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for XLM/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.0735 and $0.0725.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.0770, $0.0800 and $0.0820.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-struggle-continues-key-resistance-intact/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Struggle Continues, Key Resistance Intact</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-struggle-continues-key-resistance-intact/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Price Analysis: Bulls Struggle Below $0.36</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-struggle-below-0-36/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-struggle-below-0-36/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 04:28:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76172</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple price started a fresh decline below the $0.3900 zone against the US dollar. The price is now trading below $0.3700 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There was a break below a key contracting triangle with support near $0.3495 on the 4-hours chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Bittrex). The pair<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-struggle-below-0-36/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-struggle-below-0-36/">Ripple Price Analysis: Bulls Struggle Below $0.36</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ripple price started a fresh decline below the $0.3900 zone against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $0.3700 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There was a break below a key contracting triangle with support near $0.3495 on the 4-hours chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Bittrex).</li>
<li>The pair could extend losses if it stays below the $0.3600 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ripple price is struggling below $0.370 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-at-risk-of-another-crash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. XRP price must stay above $0.3400 to avoid more downsides in the near term.</em></p>
<h2>Ripple Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, ripple price saw a bearish reaction below the $0.3900 zone against the US Dollar. The XRP/USD pair declined below the $0.3780 support zone to move into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>The price even traded below the $0.3700 level. Finally, there was a move below the $0.3600 level. The price traded as low as $0.3350 before there was an upside correction. The price climbed above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3966 swing high to $0.3350 low.</p>
<p>However, the bears were active near the $0.3550 resistance. As a result, there was another decline below $0.3500. There was also a break below a key contracting triangle with support near $0.3495 on the 4-hours chart of the XRP/USD pair.</p>
<p>The price is now trading below $0.3700 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bears-in-action-below-0-365/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. An initial support on the downside is near the $0.3400 level. The next major support is near the $0.3350 level, below which the price could even test the $0.3200 support.</p>
<p>Any more losses could lead the price towards the $0.3120 level, below which the price might even test $0.3000. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near $0.3550.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $0.3660 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3966 swing high to $0.3350 low. The main resistance is near the $0.3740 zone. A clear move above the $0.3740 and $0.3750 resistance zones might start a fresh increase.</p>
<p>In the stated case, the price could even surpass the $0.395 resistance. Any more gains might send the price towards the $0.412 resistance.</p>
<div id="attachment_76173" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Ripple-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76173" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-76173" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Ripple-3.png" alt="Ripple Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76173" class="wp-caption-text">Ripple Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, ripple price is now trading below the $0.370 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could extend losses if it stays below the $0.3600 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XRP/USD is now gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for XRP/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.3400, $0.3350 and $0.3120.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.3550 and $0.3680.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-struggle-below-0-36/">Ripple Price Analysis: Bulls Struggle Below $0.36</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-struggle-below-0-36/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LBank Welcomes Nigeria’s Push to Recognize Crypto as Investment Capital</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-welcomes-nigerias-push-to-recognize-crypto-as-investment-capital/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-welcomes-nigerias-push-to-recognize-crypto-as-investment-capital/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 17:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76169</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nigeria has put forward a significant legislation design that will further facilitate cryptocurrency adoption in the country with over 200 million inhabitants. Why this matters: If the Investments and Securities Act, 2007 (Amendment) Bill passes, the Nigerian securities and exchange commission (SEC) will recognize cryptocurrencies and other digital assets as capital for investment. Babangida Ibrahim,<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-welcomes-nigerias-push-to-recognize-crypto-as-investment-capital/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-welcomes-nigerias-push-to-recognize-crypto-as-investment-capital/">LBank Welcomes Nigeria’s Push to Recognize Crypto as Investment Capital</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Nigeria has put forward a significant legislation design that will further facilitate cryptocurrency adoption in the country with over 200 million inhabitants.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Why this matters:</strong> If the Investments and Securities Act, 2007 (Amendment) Bill passes, the Nigerian securities and exchange commission (SEC) will recognize cryptocurrencies and other digital assets as capital for investment.</p>
<ul>
<li>Babangida Ibrahim, Chairman of the House of Representatives Committee, shared in <a href="https://punchng.com/proposed-cryptocurrency-law-to-define-cbns-roles-reps/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">an interview</a> with local media outlet <em>Punch</em>, that the proposed bill will specify the roles of the Central Bank of Nigeria and the country&#8217;s SEC in regard to cryptocurrencies.</li>
<li>Ibrahim stated that the bill is not a complete shift away from restrictive laws in place, only a review of what could be done within the current legal framework. However, he does believe that Nigeria must keep up with global economic innovations.</li>
<li>Notably, the Nigerian Export Processing Zones Authority (NEPZA) stated in a press release in September that <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/cryptocurrency/a-virtual-free-zone-in-africa-is-being-discussed-with-binance/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">it considered partnering</a> with crypto exchange Binance to create a virtual free zone to promote economic growth.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Go deeper:</strong> The legal blueprint comes at a time when Nigeria has spent almost 2 years under <a href="https://www.spglobal.com/marketintelligence/en/news-insights/latest-news-headlines/cryptocurrency-usage-soars-in-nigeria-despite-bank-ban-70497781#:~:text=This%20is%20despite%20the%20country&#039;s,laundering%20and%20and%20terrorism%20financing." data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">a cryptocurrency ban for financial institutes</a>, and the country’s CBDC, the eNaira, has failed to reach widespread adoption.</p>
<ul>
<li>Since the launch of the CBDC in October 2021, it currently sits at an adoption rate <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-10-25/shunned-digital-currency-looks-for-street-credibility-in-nigeria?sref=323RPL5z" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">of only 0.5%</a> among the population.</li>
<li>Further endorsement of the eNaira could be hampered by the legal blueprint. “This bill is basically going to create more adoption of cryptocurrencies. Through regulation of this asset class, we might start to see taxing and legal registration if you want to build something in the blockchain space,” says Anointing Aha, Community Manager for Nigeria at global crypto exchange LBank.</li>
<li>For now, Nigeria seems to be moving towards further adoption, but nothing is set in stone. “Nigeria’s presidential election is coming up early next year, and a lot will depend on the new president,” Aha adds.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-welcomes-nigerias-push-to-recognize-crypto-as-investment-capital/">LBank Welcomes Nigeria’s Push to Recognize Crypto as Investment Capital</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-welcomes-nigerias-push-to-recognize-crypto-as-investment-capital/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Citron Research: Ethereum Is the Best Crypto for Shorting</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/citron-research-ethereum-is-the-best-crypto-for-shorting/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/citron-research-ethereum-is-the-best-crypto-for-shorting/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 17:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Andrew Left]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Citron Research]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75547</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Citron Research is betting big against cryptocurrencies. In particular, the company is focusing on Ethereum, which it claims is the best digital asset to short at the time of writing. Citron Research Is Pushing Ethereum Crypto has been treated rather unfairly throughout 2022. The year has arguably been the worst for the space, with several<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/citron-research-ethereum-is-the-best-crypto-for-shorting/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/citron-research-ethereum-is-the-best-crypto-for-shorting/">Citron Research: Ethereum Is the Best Crypto for Shorting</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Citron Research is betting big against cryptocurrencies. In particular, the company is focusing on Ethereum, <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/billybambrough/2022/11/17/reignited-gamestop-short-seller-reveals-the-surprise-cryptocurrency-its-betting-against-after-ftx-crash-hits-bitcoin-and-ethereum-price/?sh=4d3c4c9773f8" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">which it claims is the best</a> digital asset to short at the time of writing.</p>
<h2>Citron Research Is Pushing Ethereum</h2>
<p>Crypto has been treated rather unfairly throughout 2022. The year has arguably been the worst for the space, with several digital currency and blockchain <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-in-the-age-of-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">firms filing bankruptcy</a> and falling off the Earth’s grid. It’s a sad and ugly sight to see, and one that has only been boosted by the falling digital currency prices traders have been forced to endure.</p>
<p>Bitcoin – the world’s largest and most powerful digital currency by market cap – has lost more than 70 percent of its value in the last 13 months. In November of last year, the asset was trading at a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit, though now, the currency is trading in the mid-$16K range. Other mainstream assets, such as Ethereum, have followed suit, and overall, the digital currency space has lost more than $2 trillion in general valuation.</p>
<p>Citron Research thinks <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ethereum/" data-wpel-link="internal">Ethereum</a> serves a unique purpose, and it&#8217;s an asset that&#8217;s loved by many investors. While not as large as bitcoin, for example, the network of Ethereum continues to attract crypto developers, who see it as the prime blockchain in which to build the new assets or projects on. The network also recently underwent an upgrade from proof of work (PoW), which relies mainly on mining as bitcoin does, to proof of stake (PoS).</p>
<p>Ethereum now operates under the name “Ethereum 2.0,” and it is allegedly faster and is less bogged down by traffic and gas fees. The switch is known as <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/merge/" data-wpel-link="internal">the Merge</a>, and it has allegedly helped Ethereum become more energy efficient.</p>
<p>Citron says that it is once again for short selling following the FTX collapse. In a statement, the company commented that the situation is a classic one where everyone got involved because they simply assumed that those in charge knew what they were doing. The company mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>It proves there are many stocks out there that are elevated on the misconception that someone else did the homework… The U.S. government should be embarrassed that they let one person get so close to the inner sanctum of government and influence without even checking a tax return.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Andrew Left Doesn&#8217;t Care for Crypto</h2>
<p>The sentiment stemming from Citron shouldn&#8217;t come as a surprise given that its founder – a man named Andrew Left – has done nothing but bash crypto over the last several years. During a recent conference, Left said to the audience:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think crypto is just [a] complete fraud over and over and over. Maybe it is time to finally [listen] to skeptics instead of vilifying them.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/citron-research-ethereum-is-the-best-crypto-for-shorting/">Citron Research: Ethereum Is the Best Crypto for Shorting</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/citron-research-ethereum-is-the-best-crypto-for-shorting/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LBank Presents TechFest International Blockchain Summit In Bombay</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-presents-techfest-international-blockchain-summit-in-bombay/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-presents-techfest-international-blockchain-summit-in-bombay/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 17:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76166</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TechFest IIT Bombay is Asia&#8217;s Largest technology festival where the world’s leading crypto influencers gather with key government delegates, media and other investors to assist the global blockchain and cryptocurrency communities. It is one of the most prestigious events of the global cryptocurrency and blockchain ecosystem. Furthermore, the festival combines young minds and blockchain enthusiasts<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-presents-techfest-international-blockchain-summit-in-bombay/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-presents-techfest-international-blockchain-summit-in-bombay/">LBank Presents TechFest International Blockchain Summit In Bombay</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TechFest IIT Bombay is Asia&#8217;s Largest technology festival where the world’s leading crypto influencers gather with key government delegates, media and other investors to assist the global blockchain and cryptocurrency communities. It is one of the most prestigious events of the global cryptocurrency and blockchain ecosystem.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the festival combines young minds and blockchain enthusiasts in one place to provide knowledge about the industry to the community. The International Blockchain Summit of TechFest IIT Bombay is sponsored by LBank, a global crypto exchange, with a primary focus on providing crypto education. This TechFest is a three day event which attracts the students, alumni, and techn geeks who are said to be the sole essence of the summit.</p>
<h4>LBank’s Live Session at TechFest</h4>
<p>Notably, the <a href="http://www.lbank.com" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">top cryptocurrency exchange</a> LBank prioritizes knowledge sharing about blockchain space. Considering the main objective to achieve educating the community, the company is taking part in the panel discussion on “Tech and the environmental impact of Blockchain”. This discussion will be held on the second day of the summit with other top mentors in the industry.</p>
<p>The whole summit is all about learning and understanding the upcoming trends and red flags of the blockchain space. Moreover, LBank believes that the festival has a significant role in giving people the chance to network with peers, mentors, and idols as well as to gain professional growth.</p>
<p>However, the exchange would also love to celebrate the community&#8217;s participation and distribute some presents to the crypto enthusiasts. With so many eager participants teaming up with LBank, the event&#8217;s first day has started off well. Participants demonstrated a keen interest in learning about the potential applications of blockchain technology.</p>
<h4>About LBank</h4>
<p><a href="http://lbank.info" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LBank</a> is a top cryptocurrency exchange founded in 2015. It provides users with a platform to securely buy, sell, receive and hold Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies. With over 7 million users, LBank offers a wide range of payment options and competitive transaction fees, lowering the entry barrier to drive more adoption.</p>
<p>The platform supports more than 800+ trading pairs and 149+ fiat currencies. It offers services around crypto trading, specialized financial derivatives, and professional asset management services. LBank’s robust ecosystem allows users to leverage and build a well-rounded financial portfolio.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.info" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.info</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media:</strong></p>
<p>l<a href="https://www.newsfilecorp.com/redirect/vR47rSkMwG" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> Telegram</a><br />
l<a href="https://www.newsfilecorp.com/redirect/JZeKvUj8Kj" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> Twitter</a><br />
l<a href="https://www.newsfilecorp.com/redirect/GOeWGSQOPx" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> Facebook</a><br />
l<a href="https://www.newsfilecorp.com/redirect/bAvmJCPwNR" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> Linkedin</a></p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong></p>
<p>LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
Downtown, Dubai<br />
<u>media@lbank.info</u></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-presents-techfest-international-blockchain-summit-in-bombay/">LBank Presents TechFest International Blockchain Summit In Bombay</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-presents-techfest-international-blockchain-summit-in-bombay/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LBank Exchange Will List DiDimCoin (DDC) on December 23, 2022</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-didimcoin-ddc-on-december-23-2022/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-didimcoin-ddc-on-december-23-2022/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 16:35:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76162</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec 22, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list DiDimCoin (DDC) on December 23, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the DDC/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading at 6:00 UTC on December 23, 2022. As a blockchain-based global social commerce platform, DiDim maximizes<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-didimcoin-ddc-on-december-23-2022/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-didimcoin-ddc-on-december-23-2022/">LBank Exchange Will List DiDimCoin (DDC) on December 23, 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec 22, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list DiDimCoin (DDC) on December 23, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the DDC/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading at 6:00 UTC on December 23, 2022.</p>
<p>As a blockchain-based global social commerce platform, DiDim maximizes the true value of all users by introducing a platform that connects e-commerce, markets, exchanges, payments, and content. Its native token <a href="https://tronscan.org/#/token20/TG8AEC18tJUefG4z4wmp1e5QbeuQuQWunV" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">DiDimCoin</a> (DDC) will be listed on LBank Exchange at 6:00 UTC on December 23, 2022, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision.</p>
<p><strong>Introducing </strong><strong>DiDim</strong></p>
<p>E-commerce global business is growing rapidly every year, its market is expected to exceed $3.453 trillion by 2025. One of the reasons e-commerce has grown rapidly is the development of cross-border e-commerce, a new market called overseas direct purchase is opening, and as it grows rapidly, platforms that reflect it are emerging. DiDim global shopping mall APP is one of them.</p>
<p>The global shopping mall service of DiDim was established in 2018. Including its own apps, it operates shopping malls through social commerce such as WeChat, Taobao, and TikTok, and has marketing channels such as Baidu, Kwai Show, and bilibili to exert influence in the Chinese and global markets. As a global shopping center for DiDimgn Co., Ltd. It is designed for commodity trading in South Korea, China, the United States, Russia and Southeast Asia.</p>
<p>Utilizing blockchain technology, DiDim not only allows users to trade securely anytime, anywhere, but also to share information and benefits. The DiDim platform was launched to maximize the true value of all blockchain users by introducing a platform that connects e-commerce, markets, exchanges, payments, and content. The payment system within the DIDIM platform will be a more secure network, providing all users with sufficient satisfaction and rewards and a blockchain platform that connects users worldwide beyond everyday transactions.</p>
<p>In addition to traditional shopping malls, DiDim is also building the best virtual department stores with metaverse technology. Creating a new shopping trend in the non-face-to-face era through a luxury store called Luxury Hall. For the MZ generation, who is leading the new consumer market, DiDim provides special content that fits the consumption pattern. This Metaverse Department Store will offer everything that can be sold in virtual reality. It will be a new shopping mall concept where users can sell and pay through any payment method.</p>
<p>With all above features, DiDim presents a decentralized commerce protocol where anyone in the world can freely sell/buy products and share profits transparently. Various services such as payment, shopping, and rewards are introduced into the ecosystem provided by DiDimCoin.</p>
<p><strong>About DDC Token</strong></p>
<p>DiDimCoin (DDC) is the utility coin and payment coin for free e-commerce based on blockchain. It presents a new vision and goal for the e-commerce market with the aim of offering users the ability to purchase products through global shopping malls, building a commerce ecosystem that all ecosystem users can trust, using blockchain technology to ensure transparency of all transaction data, and maximizing the benefits of ecosystem users and investors.</p>
<p>Based on TRC-20, DDC has a total supply of 5 billion (i.e., 5,000,000,000) tokens, of which 40% is reserved for payment, and the rest 60% is allocated for partnerships, ecosystem, marketing, company operation, the team and advisors.</p>
<p>The DDC token will be listed on LBank Exchange at 6:00 UTC on December 23, 2022, investors who are interested in the DiDim investment can easily buy and sell DDC token on LBank Exchange by then. The listing of DDC token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p>
<p><strong>Learn More about</strong><strong> DDC Token:</strong><br />
Official Website: <a href="http://didim.io/index_en.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://didim.io/index_en.html</a><br />
Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/didimcoin" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://t.me/didimcoin</a><br />
Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/DidimCoin" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/DidimCoin</a><br />
Instagram: <a href="https://www.instagram.com/didimcoin/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.instagram.com/didimcoin/</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media: </strong></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Facebook</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong></p>
<p>LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
LBank Exchange<br />
<a href="mailto:marketing@lbank.info">marketing@lbank.info</a><br />
<a href="mailto:business@lbank.info">business@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-didimcoin-ddc-on-december-23-2022/">LBank Exchange Will List DiDimCoin (DDC) on December 23, 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-didimcoin-ddc-on-december-23-2022/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
