<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 04:45:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/cropped-fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Kickstarter Decides Against Potential Blockchain Move</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kickstarter-decides-against-potential-blockchain-move/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 13:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kickstarter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[real estate]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78993</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Two Decembers ago, project funding platform Kickstarter announced it was considering a shift to blockchain, and that it was potentially looking into placing all its operations atop the same distributed ledger technology that has grown so close with digital assets. Kickstarter Says &#8220;No&#8221; to Blockchain Now, however, it appears this move is not going to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kickstarter-decides-against-potential-blockchain-move/">Kickstarter Decides Against Potential Blockchain Move</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Two Decembers ago, project funding platform Kickstarter <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/entertainment/gaming/kickstarter-s-community-advisory-council-helped-steer-it-away-from-blockchain-tech/ar-AA1ddvEi">announced it was considering</a> a shift to blockchain, and that it was potentially looking into placing all its operations atop the same distributed ledger technology that has grown so close with digital assets.</p>
<h2>Kickstarter Says &#8220;No&#8221; to Blockchain</h2>
<p>Now, however, it appears this move is not going to happen. Kickstarter recently hired a new group of board members that have decided against the blockchain switch. They’re instead committed to the “core business and needs” of the creative community using and supporting Kickstarter. A spokesperson for the company said in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>As we’ve shared with our community in previous blog posts, we’re exploring the opportunities that are in blockchain to alleviate some of the challenges that we face as a centralized crowdfunding company. However, we’re not committed to moving Kickstarter to the blockchain or doing anything specific there. We are open to exploration and experimentation but want to do it in a way that feels tested, collaborative with our community, and considerate of the experience[s] they want from Kickstarter.</p></blockquote>
<p>A situation like this shouldn’t surprise people to any great extent. Blockchain is, after all, a relatively new technology, and the situations involving it arguably have people a little confused. For example, there are likely many individuals out there who associate blockchain purely with crypto. Even though it’s now being used in industries such as manufacturing and healthcare, blockchain is still widely considered a crypto-centered platform of sorts.</p>
<p>In addition, blockchain is not exactly the easiest technology to understand, especially when you’re not used to the up-and-coming ideologies that are now influencing today’s tech world. The Kickstarter spokesperson continued with:</p>
<blockquote><p>Where we are focused and deeply committed&#8230; is on our core business and making Kickstarter better. This is why we’ve prioritized finding ways to give creators access to the pledge management and digital marketing tools they need to be successful during and after their campaign period[s]. The creation of the Community Advisory Council was born out of the feedback we received about the [blockchain] protocol. We saw a need to create another surface for feedback and conversation with our community so that they could be involved in our direction and our decision making not just about the protocol, but about all the topics that are top of mind for us and our community. We hope to continue this dialogue with our second cohort of the council this fall.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Others Still Think It&#8217;s Cool</h2>
<p>Fans of blockchain technology shouldn’t let a little setback like this bring them down.</p>
<p>Several other industries, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-how-blockchain-could-pave-the-way-for-real-estate/">including real estate</a>, have announced that they’re planning to at least look at blockchain and consider potential transitions to the technology to ease their operations and open their products and services up to more individuals.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kickstarter-decides-against-potential-blockchain-move/">Kickstarter Decides Against Potential Blockchain Move</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tom Lee Sees BTC Rising to $200K</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tom-lee-sees-btc-rising-to-200k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 17:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tom Lee]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78974</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tom Lee of Fundstrat fame is at it again. This time, he’s commenting in a recent interview that the price of bitcoin could reach a whopping $200,000 in the next few years, though he didn’t give a specific date this time around. Tom Lee: BTC is Going to $200K In the discussion, Lee said he’s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tom-lee-sees-btc-rising-to-200k/">Tom Lee Sees BTC Rising to $200K</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tom Lee of Fundstrat fame is at it again. This time, he’s <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/bitcoin-forecast-crypto-currency-sec-blackrock-gains-tom-lee-fundstrat-2023-6">commenting in a recent interview</a> that the price of bitcoin could reach a whopping $200,000 in the next few years, though he didn’t give a specific date this time around.</p>
<h2>Tom Lee: BTC is Going to $200K</h2>
<p>In the discussion, Lee said he’s been following Cathie Wood. Not long ago, the main madam behind Ark Invest said she thinks bitcoin <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-btc-will-be-priced-at-1-5-million-in-2030/">could reach a price</a> that surpasses the million-dollar mark in the next seven years or so, and Lee doesn’t think she’s that off, clearly complimenting her confidence. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think her idea of network value for bitcoin and scarcity still argues that, if this isn&#8217;t an upcycle, her numbers are correct, you know, something in the $200,000-plus range.</p></blockquote>
<p>Tom Lee has always been there to give his BTC predictions. Whether the world’s number one digital asset goes up or down, you can bet that Lee will be there in the shadows deciding or commenting about where it will go next. This would all be fine and dandy except for one thing… He hasn’t been right that often.</p>
<p>For example, at the end of 2018, Lee regularly stated that bitcoin was going to end the year on a high note. Prior to last year, 2018 was considered the worst period on record for bitcoin. During that time, BTC started at around $20K during the first few weeks of January. Over the next 12 months, it wound up in the mid-$3,000 range. It was embarrassing, it was sad, and a lot of traders lost way more than they bargained for.</p>
<p>However, while the currency continued to meander through the doldrums and show the world it wasn’t listening to what people wanted, Lee was there saying the asset was going to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fundstrats-tom-lee-sticks-by-15000-for-bitcoin-year-end-price/">end 2018 at around</a> $15,000. This didn’t occur as we all remember, and the situation was so crippling that eventually Lee commented that <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tom-lee-announces-hes-no-longer-predicting-bitcoin-prices/">he wasn’t going to be making</a> any more price predictions and would instead focus on the power and technicality behind BTC.</p>
<h2>Former Statements Clearly Mean Nothing</h2>
<p>This clearly isn’t happening, as here he is again saying bitcoin will rise out of the ashes. He says one big thing that’s happened over the past year or so is that many negative players have either gotten out of crypto or been forced to walk away, but they’ve all been replaced with compliant, positive entities. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>There&#8217;s been sort of a stage exit stage left for a lot of players, but then we&#8217;ve replaced them with, you know, some of the traditional players that have a lot of credibility, like BlackRock and the Citadels coming into bitcoin.</p></blockquote>
<p>Not long ago, bitcoin reached $31K, the highest it’s been in about <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/">four months</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tom-lee-sees-btc-rising-to-200k/">Tom Lee Sees BTC Rising to $200K</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wyoming is Becoming a Growing Crypto Haven</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/wyoming-is-becoming-a-growing-crypto-haven/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 15:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Custodia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Steve Lupien]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wyoming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78972</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Wyoming, despite its lack of a population, has been on a mission to become one of the most – if not the most – crypto-friendly regions known to man, and thus far, it’s succeeding. Wyoming Still Loves Crypto Over the past seven years, Wyoming has passed more than 30 crypto-based laws designed to regulate the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/wyoming-is-becoming-a-growing-crypto-haven/">Wyoming is Becoming a Growing Crypto Haven</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wyoming, despite its lack of a population, has been <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/wyoming-regulatory-clarity-and-crypto-friendly-banks-fuel-blockchain-revolution-1032412121">on a mission to become</a> one of the most – if not <em>the</em> most – crypto-friendly regions known to man, and thus far, it’s succeeding.</p>
<h2>Wyoming Still Loves Crypto</h2>
<p>Over the past seven years, Wyoming has passed more than 30 crypto-based laws designed to regulate the industry, grow innovation, and make things safer. Steve Lupien – director of the Center for Blockchain and Digital Innovation at the University of Wyoming – explained in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>We’re seeing a lot of companies that are moving to Wyoming. Last time I checked, there were over 3,000 companies that domiciled in Wyoming, and there are probably more now.</p></blockquote>
<p>A lot of these companies are bringing either crypto or tech-oriented jobs. Lupien has seen a lot of his students graduate and leave Wyoming over the years. It’s estimated that about 70 percent of the graduates of the University of Wyoming leave their home state for “greener pastures,” though he thinks that’s going to change very quickly in the coming months and years given all the big tech-related alterations that are happening within the region’s borders.</p>
<p>Lupien said that the new statistics should be giving a lot of his future students hope that they may not have to leave to find work if they don’t want to. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>It gives my university graduates an opportunity to work in the digital asset space and not have to leave the state. [Several] of my graduates are now working for Wyoming companies or [have] started Wyoming companies.</p></blockquote>
<p>One of the big crypto-friendly laws to be passed in the state involves one where crypto is placed on par with cash, so when one needs to file bankruptcy, for example, like the cash in their wallets, they don’t have to forfeit digital assets, meaning whatever bitcoin, Ethereum, or altcoin units they have in their pockets will stay there.</p>
<p>However, while things may look positive and clear on the horizon, Wyoming is experiencing a few problems here and there, a big one coming in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-bank-custodia-sees-its-fed-application-denied/">the form of Custodia</a>. The digital financial firm was denied access to Federal Reserve banking services not too long ago, and thus the enterprise has a cloud hovering over its operations.</p>
<h2>The Bank Can Still Win</h2>
<p>But while this may be scary at first, Lupien is confident Custodia will get its way, and all will be resolved in the end. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>When Custodia prevails, Wyoming will be ground zero for digital assets banking because there are four Wyoming SPDIs standing by ready to operate as soon as the Fed relents, [and] the court will make them.</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition to all this, the state is headed by the most crypto-friendly <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/cynthia-lummis/">senator in congressional history</a>, and her name is Cynthia Lummis.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/wyoming-is-becoming-a-growing-crypto-haven/">Wyoming is Becoming a Growing Crypto Haven</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hayden Adams on the Success of Crypto Firm Uniswap</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/hayden-adams-on-the-success-of-crypto-firm-uniswap/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 13:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hayden Adams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uniswap]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78970</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Uniswap is a crypto firm that started about five years ago. The company introduced the world to the automated market maker (AMM). The tool works to let people swap currencies on various exchanges and networks without the aid of middlemen. Uniswap Has Come a Long Way The company has grown into something nobody was expecting. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/hayden-adams-on-the-success-of-crypto-firm-uniswap/">Hayden Adams on the Success of Crypto Firm Uniswap</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Uniswap is a crypto firm that started about five years ago. The company <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/uniswaps-hayden-adams-q-a-on-weathering-the-regulatory-storm-what-s-next-for-defi/ar-AA1d4Gf7">introduced the world</a> to the automated market maker (AMM). The tool works to let people swap currencies on various exchanges and networks without the aid of middlemen.</p>
<h2>Uniswap Has Come a Long Way</h2>
<p>The company has grown into something nobody was expecting. Uniswap now processes about $1 trillion in blockchain transactions on various networks. In a recent interview, the company’s CEO Hayden Adams talks about the latest Uniswap updates and about all the public comments the company has gotten since opening itself up to critiques.</p>
<p>Uniswap is now in what’s called the V4 phase. In other words, this is “version four.” There have been enough updates to the platform that the version users see now is the fourth major adaptation. Discussing the latest example, Adams said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Historically, the way that new protocol versions have come out has been almost more like products, in the sense that they&#8217;ve been basically announced when they&#8217;re almost done, and that was sort of, I think, something that made sense at the time, but with where the Uniswap protocol is today, building in public and inviting the community to build alongside us and contribute to this decentralized protocol is a [good] thing.</p></blockquote>
<p>One of the big clinchers of the platform is that it now comes with what are called “hooks.” These are tools that expand upon the functionality of staking pools. Discussing their functions, he mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>What you find in the process of building things like Uniswap is that you make a lot of trade-offs. Hooks are essentially ways of customizing and modifying how liquidity pools work within Uniswap. These are done by the people who create pools. Anyone can create a pool and then choose how to customize it. What we wanted to do with hooks is let people basically make these trade-offs themselves and really choose how their pool works.</p></blockquote>
<p>Adams also talked a bit about the lawsuits the SEC has initiated against <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-hit-with-sec-lawsuit-says-it-operated-as-an-exchange-broker/">Coinbase</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sues-binance-alleges-selling-of-illegal-securities/">Binance</a>. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I don&#8217;t really know too much about those lawsuits. Generally, I think that DeFi and decentralized platforms are quite different from centralized ones. There are different properties, and so I don&#8217;t have a ton to add. Personally, I do think that over time I always expect to see more decentralized platforms over centralized ones. I think there are fundamental benefits of self-custody, transparency that they can offer, provable solvency, all these things.</p></blockquote>
<h2>It&#8217;s All too New</h2>
<p>When discussing the potential regulation of his own company, he mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>We have lawyers, and we make sure that everything that we do is legal and all of that. I would say that the way I think about the space, though, is DeFi is a new industry.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/hayden-adams-on-the-success-of-crypto-firm-uniswap/">Hayden Adams on the Success of Crypto Firm Uniswap</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Bears In Charge Below $250</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bears-in-charge-below-250/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 07:28:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79697</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline below the $250 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below the $240 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $234 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bears-in-charge-below-250/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Bears In Charge Below $250</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline below the $250 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below the $240 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $234 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it stays below the $242 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin cash price is declining below the $242 zone against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. BCH/USD could extend losses if there is a close below $220.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin cash price remained in a bearish zone below the $255 and $250 resistance levels. BCH traded below the $242 support level to move further into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>There was a clear move below the $235 zone. The price is now moving lower below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $217 swing low to the $249 high. The bears seem to be in control below $242 and $250.</p>
<p>Bitcoin Cash is now trading below the $240 zone and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-downside-thrust-below-230/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $234 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair.</p>
<p>Immediate resistance is near the $232 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). The next key resistance is near the trend line and $235. Any more gains above $235 could set the pace for a move toward the $242 level. If there is a move above the $242 resistance, the price could rise toward the $250 zone.</p>
<p>If not, the price might continue lower below $230. Immediate support on the downside is near the $225 zone. The next major support is near the $220 level, below which the bears might aim for $215 or even $205.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79698" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79698" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Bitcoin-Cash.png"><img decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" class="size-full wp-image-79698" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Bitcoin-Cash.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash Price" width="1835" height="839" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Bitcoin-Cash.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Bitcoin-Cash-600x274.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Bitcoin-Cash-1100x503.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Bitcoin-Cash-768x351.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Bitcoin-Cash-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Bitcoin-Cash-750x343.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Bitcoin-Cash-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79698" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Cash Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BCHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, Bitcoin cash price is now trading below the $240 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $242 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for BCH/USD is gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BCH/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $225 and $220.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $235 and $242.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bears-in-charge-below-250/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Bears In Charge Below $250</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EOS Price Analysis: Bears Aim For $0.65 or Lower</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bears-aim-for-0-65-or-lower/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 06:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EOS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79694</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>EOS price started a fresh decline from the $0.775 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $0.725 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.7190 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bears-aim-for-0-65-or-lower/">EOS Price Analysis: Bears Aim For $0.65 or Lower</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>EOS price started a fresh decline from the $0.775 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $0.725 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.7190 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to decline if it stays below the $0.720 and $0.740 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>EOS price is struggling below $0.720 against the US Dollar, unlike <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. The price might attempt to recover if there is a clear move above $0.740.</em></p>
<h2>EOS Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, EOS price saw a fresh decline from the $0.775 resistance against the US Dollar. The price traded below the $0.75 and $0.74 levels to move into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>The pair even spiked below the $0.705 support. A low is formed near $0.7014 and the price is now consolidating losses. EOS is trading well below $0.725 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-0-73/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $0.719 level.</p>
<p>There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.7190 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair. It is close to the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.7767 swing high to the $0.7014 low.</p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $0.74 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.7767 swing high to the $0.7014 low. A clear move above the $0.74 level could start a steady increase toward the $0.75 level.</p>
<p>The next major resistance might be $0.775. Any more gains might send the price toward the $0.80 level. On the downside, immediate support is near $0.705.</p>
<p>The next key support is near the $0.70 level. If there is a downside break below the $0.70 support, the price could test the $0.65 support in the near term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79695" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79695" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/EOS.png"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-79695" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/EOS.png" alt="EOS Price" width="1835" height="839" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/EOS.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/EOS-600x274.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/EOS-1100x503.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/EOS-768x351.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/EOS-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/EOS-750x343.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/EOS-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79695" class="wp-caption-text">EOS Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/EOSUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, EOS price is now trading below the $0.725 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to decline if it stays below the $0.720 and $0.740 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for EOS/USD is losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $0.705 and $0.700.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $0.720 and $0.740.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bears-aim-for-0-65-or-lower/">EOS Price Analysis: Bears Aim For $0.65 or Lower</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Risk of More Losses Below $80</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-80/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 04:18:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79691</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin is showing bearish signs and trading below $90 against the US Dollar. LTC price is now trading below $85 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $83.80 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-80/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Risk of More Losses Below $80</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Litecoin is showing bearish signs and trading below $90 against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>LTC price is now trading below $85 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $83.80 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could start a decent increase if it clears the $85 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Litecoin price is struggling below $85 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. LTC price could continue to decline if it stays below the $85 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, there was a short-lived recovery in Bitcoin, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-resume-increase-above-1885/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a>, Ripple, and Litecoin against the US Dollar. Earlier, LTC settled below the $90 resistance zone to move into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>The price broke the $85 support zone and started a fresh decline. It even traded below the $82 support. A low is formed near $79.19 and the price is now consolidating losses. It is now trading below $85 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>Immediate resistance is near the $84 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $83.80 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair. It is close to the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $99.60 swing high to the $79.19 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $89 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $99.60 swing high to the $79.19 low. A clear move above the $89 level could pump the price toward the $95 level. The next major resistance could be $100.</p>
<p>On the downside, immediate support is near the $81 level. The next key support is near the $80 level. If there is a downside break below the $80 support, the price could accelerate lower toward the $75 level in the near term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79692" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79692" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Litecoin.png"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-79692" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Litecoin.png" alt="Litecoin (LTC) Price" width="1835" height="839" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Litecoin.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Litecoin-600x274.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Litecoin-1100x503.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Litecoin-768x351.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Litecoin-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Litecoin-750x343.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Litecoin-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79692" class="wp-caption-text">Litecoin (LTC) Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/">chart</a>, Litecoin price is clearly trading below $85 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $85 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LTC/USD is now losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $81.00 and $80.00.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $84.00 and $89.00.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-80/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Risk of More Losses Below $80</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>THE9COMPANY make the partnership with Bithumb Korea subsidiary corporation ROTONDA ‘BURRITO service’.</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the9company-make-the-partnership-with-bithumb-korea-subsidiary-corporation-rotonda-burrito-service/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 17:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79674</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE9COMPANY does the strategy partnership with Bithumb Korea subsidiary corporation ROTONDA platform &#8216;BURRITO&#8217; service. Through this partnership, THE9COMPANY token &#8216;THE9&#8217; will be stored and managed in the ROTONDA platform &#8216;BURRITO wallet.&#8217; THE9COMPANYKOREA, which uses the THE9 token, will develop the platform and KIOSK system for using the BURRITO wallet. THE9COMPANYKOREA make various partnership with KT, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the9company-make-the-partnership-with-bithumb-korea-subsidiary-corporation-rotonda-burrito-service/">THE9COMPANY make the partnership with Bithumb Korea subsidiary corporation ROTONDA ‘BURRITO service’.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE9COMPANY does the strategy partnership with Bithumb Korea subsidiary corporation ROTONDA platform &#8216;BURRITO&#8217; service.</p>
<p>Through this partnership, THE9COMPANY token &#8216;THE9&#8217; will be stored and managed in the ROTONDA platform &#8216;BURRITO wallet.&#8217;</p>
<p>THE9COMPANYKOREA, which uses the THE9 token, will develop the platform and KIOSK system for using the BURRITO wallet. THE9COMPANYKOREA make various partnership with KT, the Industry of Hitejinro, etc. THE9COMPANYKOREA does business with STARTEX(which list on the KOSPI) running &#8220;Donkiotech&#8221;. STARTEX supplies the KIOSK and THE9COMPANY to run the system and related things.</p>
<p>THE9COMPANY mileage payment system is faster than the credit card payments system.</p>
<p>Utilize the token to integrate mileage system and smartphone gift cards, which expand the sales of store owners.</p>
<p>BURRITO wallet is a multi-chain platform that supports the 11 mainnet, such as Bitcoin, Ethereum, Binance chain, etc. The wallet can manage over 1,300 cryptocurrencies and make the wallet and account from a phone number. It can send the cryptocurrency and NFT to the account ID and phone number.</p>
<p>Bithumb Korea and BURRITO wallet connect by auto-connecting system, which cuts the &#8216;whitelisting process&#8217; for registration of private wallet. For now, the cryptocurrency owned by Bithumb Korea is easy to send to the BURRITO wallet because of overcoming the Travel rule process.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the9company-make-the-partnership-with-bithumb-korea-subsidiary-corporation-rotonda-burrito-service/">THE9COMPANY make the partnership with Bithumb Korea subsidiary corporation ROTONDA ‘BURRITO service’.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blockchain Discussion Focuses on Development Problems in the U.S.</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-discussion-focuses-on-development-problems-in-the-u-s/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 17:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rob Nelson]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78966</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Rob Nelson – the anchor of Roundtable – recently hosted a discussion about the impacts of global offshore blockchain companies. Is Blockchain Underused in America? The discussion primarily centered on the technology itself and on what countries stand to lose if they allow the competition regarding blockchain to become too fierce from other nations. In [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-discussion-focuses-on-development-problems-in-the-u-s/">Blockchain Discussion Focuses on Development Problems in the U.S.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Rob Nelson – the anchor of Roundtable – recently hosted a <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/the-global-impact-of-offshore-blockchain-technologies/ar-AA1d44gG">discussion about the</a> impacts of global offshore blockchain companies.</p>
<h2>Is Blockchain Underused in America?</h2>
<p>The discussion primarily centered on the technology itself and on what countries stand to lose if they allow the competition regarding blockchain to become too fierce from other nations. In his opening remarks, Nelson said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Blockchain technology is so transformative. If we lose it, it&#8217;s like we&#8217;re losing semiconductor chips in the mid to late eighties. We lose a key driver for technological growth, not just jobs, but the next generation of tech worldwide technological advancement.</p></blockquote>
<p>Jon Najarian – founder of Market Rebellion – also threw his two cents into the mix, claiming that there simply isn’t enough blockchain development happening at the time of writing. He said that this could ultimately lead to less-than-stellar growth in the arena. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>It&#8217;s still a semiconductor, but it doesn&#8217;t handle nearly the speed, the number of transactions, and all that sort of stuff. Taiwan, obviously a world leader in the space for that, has operated, and that&#8217;s one of the things that China would love to get their hands on.</p></blockquote>
<p>Among the countries that really appear to be falling behind when it comes to blockchain is the U.S. For example, the nation’s financial agencies – like the SEC – appear to be utilizing regulation-through-enforcement tactics that are causing lots of problems for crypto companies. Some, like Coinbase, have sought to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-is-now-active-in-bermuda/">open headquarters in</a> other regions to avoid the ongoing lack of regulatory clarity.</p>
<p>The SEC has made it clear it’s not interested in solidifying or stating the rules and laws surrounding crypto use and development in the United States. Rather, it’s taken on an attitude of, “Do what we say or else,” and this is not the way for companies to flourish.</p>
<p>Najarian used the Crypto Valley in Switzerland as a prime example of positive blockchain growth, and he stated that for other countries to take the lead, they need to follow the example laid out by Switzerland. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>The Crypto Valley in Switzerland flourishes because the Swiss regulators have set down the guidelines. We refuse to do that.</p></blockquote>
<p>Alex Mascioli – founder of Trade the Chain – also took part in the blockchain discussion and said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I don&#8217;t know why they&#8217;re focusing so much energy on this. You have bad actors that come into any new space. The internet, crypto, this is nothing that&#8217;s any more disproportionate than anything historically that&#8217;s happened. I don&#8217;t know where the tough guy attitude&#8217;s coming from or who it&#8217;s going to serve.</p></blockquote>
<h2>What&#8217;s the Point to Such a Bad Attitude?</h2>
<p>Nelson agreed with this and asked at the end:</p>
<blockquote><p>Is it intentional because there&#8217;s just an anti-crypto bias? Is it just misguided? But either way, what fixes it?</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-discussion-focuses-on-development-problems-in-the-u-s/">Blockchain Discussion Focuses on Development Problems in the U.S.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
