<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 03:02:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Eyes Upside Break Above $1,920</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-eyes-upside-break-above-1920/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-eyes-upside-break-above-1920/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 03:08:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78549</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum price is moving higher above the $1,880 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH price is now trading above $1,850 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $1,880 on the 4-hours chart (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could climb further if it<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-eyes-upside-break-above-1920/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-eyes-upside-break-above-1920/">Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Eyes Upside Break Above $1,920</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ethereum price is moving higher above the $1,880 resistance against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>ETH price is now trading above $1,850 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $1,880 on the 4-hours chart (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could climb further if it stays above the $1,840 support zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ethereum price is rising above the $1,850 level against the US Dollar. ETH/USD could rise further if it clears the $1,920 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Ethereum Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, Ethereum saw a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-aims-fresh-increase-above-1850/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">decent increase</a> above the $1,800 level against the US Dollar. ETH price was able to gain pace for a move above the $1,850 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>The bulls even pushed the price above the $1,880 resistance zone. A high was formed near $1,928 before the bears appeared. There was a minor downside correction below the $1,900 level. The price dipped below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1,759 swing low to the $1,928 high.</p>
<p>Ether’s price is now trading above $1,850 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-drop-below-1700/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $1,880 on the 4-hours chart.</p>
<p>Immediate resistance on the upside is near the $1,920 level. The next major resistance is near the $2,000 zone. A clear move above the $2,000 level could send the price toward $2,140. Any more gains could even send the price toward the $2,220 resistance zone or $2,280 in the near term.</p>
<p>On the downside, initial support is near the $1,880 level. The next major support is now near the $1,850 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1,759 swing low to the $1,928 high. A break below the $1,850 support could push the price to $1,800. Any more losses could lead the price towards $1,750.</p>
<div id="attachment_78550" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Ethereum-4.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78550" class="size-full wp-image-78550" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Ethereum-4.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78550" class="wp-caption-text">Ethereum Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Ethereum’s price is trading above the $1,850 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, Ether’s price could climb further if it stays above the $1,850 support zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $1,880, followed by the $1,850 zone.</p>
<p>Key Resistance$ Levels – $1,920 and $2,000.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-eyes-upside-break-above-1920/">Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Eyes Upside Break Above $1,920</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-eyes-upside-break-above-1920/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hong Kong Set to Tax Crypto as Property</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/hong-kong-set-to-tax-crypto-as-property/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/hong-kong-set-to-tax-crypto-as-property/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 17:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gatecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hong Kong]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77983</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hong Kong is looking to implement digital currency regulations. It recently took its first step in doing so by deciding (and taking a page out of the U.S. taxation book) that all crypto will be taxed as property and not money. Hong Kong Changes Its Thoughts on Crypto This is very similar to how crypto<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/hong-kong-set-to-tax-crypto-as-property/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/hong-kong-set-to-tax-crypto-as-property/">Hong Kong Set to Tax Crypto as Property</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hong Kong is looking <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/hong-kong-high-court-recognizes-cryptocurrency-as-property-for-the-first-time/ar-AA1a3o6K" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">to implement digital currency</a> regulations. It recently took its first step in doing so by deciding (and taking a page out of the U.S. taxation book) that all crypto will be taxed as property and not money.</p>
<h2>Hong Kong Changes Its Thoughts on Crypto</h2>
<p>This is very similar to how crypto is taxed in the United States. Organizations like the Internal Revenue Service (IRS) do not look at crypto transactions as exchanges of money. Rather, they are exchanges of property, meaning selling crypto ultimately subjects the person to capital gains taxes or capital losses depending on if they sell their assets higher or lower than when they first purchased or received them.</p>
<p>This is somewhat of a problem because Hong Kong, like the U.S., is refusing to see digital currency for what it is: legitimate and actual money. What many people likely forget is that while bitcoin and many of its crypto cousins have taken on either speculative or even hedge-like statuses in recent years, many of them were initially designed to serve as payment tools. They were built to push checks, credit cards, and fiat currencies to the side, but this has been a relatively slow journey given the volatility that continues to drag them down.</p>
<p>Despite this volatility, however, crypto was – and always has been – designed to serve as money, so the idea that a region as advanced and as forward-thinking as Hong Kong refuses to take such initiative is disappointing to say the least.</p>
<p>Still, some analysts are viewing this maneuver as a solid step forward given Hong Kong served as the home of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/gatecoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">Gatecoin Limited</a>, a crypto exchange that ultimately fell apart roughly four years after it was first introduced to the world in 2015.</p>
<p>The collapse of the digital currency platform and the subsequent legal matters it was involved in are what are ultimately considered to have contributed to the prevention of Hong Kong even recognizing crypto either as money or property, and many fans are lauding regulators for at least being able to step beyond their initial biases.</p>
<h2>FTX Boosted Regulatory Calls</h2>
<p>The calls for crypto regulation have been increasing over the past six months following the collapse of digital currency <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">platform FTX</a>. The company – which first rose to fame in the year 2019 – became one of the top five crypto exchanges within three years and its founder and chief executive Sam Bankman-Fried was considered a genius by many, but that reputation didn’t last long.</p>
<p>SBF is presently awaiting trial at his parents’ <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-to-await-trial-at-his-parents-house/" data-wpel-link="internal">house in Northern California</a>. It is believed that he used customer funds to potentially invest in luxury Bahamian real estate. It is also thought that he used the money to pay off loans taken out by his other company Alameda Research.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/hong-kong-set-to-tax-crypto-as-property/">Hong Kong Set to Tax Crypto as Property</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/hong-kong-set-to-tax-crypto-as-property/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>My Crypto Merchant Unveils Crypto Payment Software for Small Businesses</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/my-crypto-merchant-unveils-crypto-payment-platform-for-small-businesses/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/my-crypto-merchant-unveils-crypto-payment-platform-for-small-businesses/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 15:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto payments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[My Crypto Merchant]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77980</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Digital currency company My Crypto Merchant has announced the launch of new software designed to help both small and medium-sized businesses integrate crypto payments into their networks. The goal is to help these enterprises accept digital currency payments for goods and services from their clients. My Crypto Merchant Will Help Small Businesses Accept Crypto The<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/my-crypto-merchant-unveils-crypto-payment-platform-for-small-businesses/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/my-crypto-merchant-unveils-crypto-payment-platform-for-small-businesses/">My Crypto Merchant Unveils Crypto Payment Software for Small Businesses</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Digital currency company My Crypto Merchant has <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/pressreleases/23/04/31881307/my-crypto-merchant-launches-cryptocurrency-payment-processing-platform-for-smes" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">announced the launch of</a> new software designed to help both small and medium-sized businesses integrate crypto payments into their networks. The goal is to help these enterprises accept digital currency payments for goods and services from their clients.</p>
<h2>My Crypto Merchant Will Help Small Businesses Accept Crypto</h2>
<p>The move is pushing the goals of bitcoin and its digital counterparts closer to being achieved. What many people likely forget is that while bitcoin and many of its crypto cousins have taken on either speculative or even hedge-like statuses in recent years, many of them were initially designed to serve as payment tools. They were built to push checks, credit cards, and fiat currencies to the side, but this has been a relatively slow journey given the volatility that continues to drag them down.</p>
<p>It is extremely hard to understand when <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a> and its crypto family will go up or down when it comes to their prices. Many stores and companies have been reluctant to say “yes” when it comes to accepting crypto payments for this reason, and to a degree, we can’t blame them.</p>
<p>Consider the following scenario: someone walks into a store and buys $50 worth of merchandise with bitcoin. For one reason or another, the store doesn’t trade the BTC into fiat right away and about 24 hours go by. From there, the price of BTC goes down and that $50 becomes $40. The customer gets to keep everything he or she bought, but the store loses money in the end. Is this a fair situation? Not everyone thinks so.</p>
<p>That’s what makes enterprises like My Crypto Merchant so important. They understand the initial purposes of bitcoin and digital currencies and are trying to transform them into usable tools that everyday people can benefit from.</p>
<p>Bryant Harper – co-founder of My Crypto Merchant – expressed his enthusiasm in an interview and commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>We are excited to launch our innovative crypto services which will be a game-changer for small businesses, enabling them to accept digital payments securely and compliantly. Our user-friendly platform will help businesses seamlessly process crypto transactions, while our focus on financial inclusion will benefit SMEs across the retail industries. Our mission is to enable every business, merchant, gig worker, vendor, and contractor to receive payment in the cryptocurrency of their choice directly from their customer with no middleman, no fees, and no limits.</p></blockquote>
<h2>No Fees for Merchants!</h2>
<p>The company is built to provide direct customer-to-merchant payments with zero (you read that right) fees for the merchant. Transaction volumes are also designed to be unlimited, meaning there can be no halting in how many crypto payments a company can accept or initiate.</p>
<p>My Crypto Merchant also believes that digital currency payments can limit financial fraud and money laundering.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/my-crypto-merchant-unveils-crypto-payment-platform-for-small-businesses/">My Crypto Merchant Unveils Crypto Payment Software for Small Businesses</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/my-crypto-merchant-unveils-crypto-payment-platform-for-small-businesses/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BTC Falls Following High Inflation in the U.K.</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/btc-falls-following-high-inflation-in-the-u-k/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/btc-falls-following-high-inflation-in-the-u-k/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 13:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Inflation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[U.K.]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77977</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The prices of bitcoin, several crypto stocks, and other leading altcoins have fallen somewhat at the time of writing following fears surrounding higher-than-expected inflation figures stemming from the United Kingdom. Inflation was Much Higher Than Expected in the U.K. Inflation in the U.S. and for all its allies has been a serious problem over the<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/btc-falls-following-high-inflation-in-the-u-k/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/btc-falls-following-high-inflation-in-the-u-k/">BTC Falls Following High Inflation in the U.K.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The prices of bitcoin, several crypto stocks, and other leading altcoins have fallen somewhat at the time of writing following fears surrounding <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/stocks/panic-in-crypto-land-bitcoin-dives-ether-sinks-altcoins-crumble-%E2%80%94-4-experts-on-the-path-ahead-1032244044" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">higher-than-expected</a> inflation figures stemming from the United Kingdom.</p>
<h2>Inflation was Much Higher Than Expected in the U.K.</h2>
<p>Inflation in the U.S. and for all its allies has been a serious problem over the past two years. There were several antics taken during the days of the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/coronavirus/" data-wpel-link="internal">COVID pandemic</a>, one of which was constantly printing new money as a means of giving people the funds they needed to survive and make it out alive at the end of the day. This caused the values of the U.S. dollar and the U.K. pound to dip heavily.</p>
<p>However, there has also been a wide array of simplistic (and dumb) economic plans put in place by the likes of incompetent leaders such as Janet Yellen and Joe Biden, which have ultimately caused the problems surrounding inflation to expand well into 2022 and 2023.</p>
<p>Co-founder and CEO of Mudrex Edul Patel commented that U.K. inflation has grown by more than ten percent in just the last 12 months. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>As is typical with unexpected events, the market responded with a reaction, causing investors to move away from the riskier assets. It may take some time for investors and traders to evaluate the potential impact of the inflation data and recover from the event.</p></blockquote>
<p>Ilya Volkov – CEO and co-founder of You Hodler – says that despite the recent dips in its price, bitcoin is still in an “upward trend channel” given that roughly one-fifth of the world&#8217;s total bitcoin supply stays holed up by long-term holders that refuse to keep it on exchanges and similar platforms. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Over the last few days, the crypto market has experienced relatively high volatility while many on-chain indicators are surprisingly consistent and tell us about the potential of further growth.</p></blockquote>
<p>However, the slips for crypto are <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-and-ether-fall-as-investors-weigh-persistent-inflation-and-rising-interest-rates/ar-AA1a2Z98" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">still relatively disappointing</a> in many ways given BTC recently hit a new ten-month high by <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">striking the $30K</a> mark. In addition, Ethereum also shot beyond the $2,000 price mark after it went through the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-ethereum-shapella-upgrade-occurred-now-what/" data-wpel-link="internal">recent Shapella upgrade</a>. Joel Kruger – market strategist at LMAX Group – said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We believe the pullback we&#8217;re seeing is more a function of an overdue correction following some impressive moves and possible profit taking on broader risk-off flow in global markets than anything crypto specific.</p></blockquote>
<h2>More Rate Hikes Coming?</h2>
<p>Kruger also commented that there’s likely to be further rate hikes in the U.S. and other countries given inflation remains a pressing problem. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>There have been some signs the Fed could be more aggressive towards higher interest rate policy than what the market is pricing, which has been driving yield differentials in the U.S. dollar&#8217;s favor, while weighing on sentiment.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/btc-falls-following-high-inflation-in-the-u-k/">BTC Falls Following High Inflation in the U.K.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/btc-falls-following-high-inflation-in-the-u-k/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Could Surge If It Clears $0.090</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-surge-if-it-clears-0-090/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-surge-if-it-clears-0-090/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 05:08:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar Lumens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78545</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stellar lumen price is attempting a fresh increase from the $0.085 zone against the US Dollar. XLM price is now trading above $0.0880 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0888 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could start<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-surge-if-it-clears-0-090/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-surge-if-it-clears-0-090/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Could Surge If It Clears $0.090</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Stellar lumen price is attempting a fresh increase from the $0.085 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>XLM price is now trading above $0.0880 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0888 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a major increase if there is a clear move above the $0.0900 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Stellar lumen price is trading above $0.0850 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-another-increase-to-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. XLM price must clear $0.090 to start a major increase.</em></p>
<h2>Stellar Lumen Price Analysis (XLM to USD)</h2>
<p>This past week, Stellar lumen price saw a bearish reaction from the $0.0900 zone against the US Dollar. The XLM/USD pair traded below the $0.0850 support and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>The bears were able to push the price below the $0.0832 level. A low was formed near $0.0827 and the price is now attempting a fresh increase. It was able to rise back above the $0.0850 resistance. The price is now testing the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.0948 swing high to the $0.0827 low.</p>
<p>XLM is now trading above $0.0850 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-nosedive-below-0-087/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $0.0888 zone.</p>
<p>There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0888 on the 4-hour chart. The next major resistance is near the $0.0900 level. It is near the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.0948 swing high to the $0.0827 low.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $0.090 level might send the price toward the $0.0950 level. Any more gains could lead the price toward the $0.1000 level or even $0.1050.</p>
<p>Initial support on the downside is near the $0.0880 level. The main support is near the $0.0850 zone. Any more losses could lead the price towards the $0.0825 level in the near term, below which the price might even retest $0.080.</p>
<div id="attachment_78546" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-4.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78546" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78546" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-4.png" alt="Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78546" class="wp-caption-text">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XLMUSD/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">chart</a> indicates that XLM price is now trading above $0.0850 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start a major increase if there is a clear move above the $0.0900 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XLM/USD is gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for XLM/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.0880 and $0.0850.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.0888, $0.090, and $0.1000.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-surge-if-it-clears-0-090/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Could Surge If It Clears $0.090</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-surge-if-it-clears-0-090/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Price Analysis: Upside Break Looms At $0.485</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-upside-break-looms-at-0-485/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-upside-break-looms-at-0-485/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 03:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78542</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple price is facing resistance near the $0.485 level against the US dollar. The price is now trading above $0.470 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.4640 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Kraken). The pair could<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-upside-break-looms-at-0-485/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-upside-break-looms-at-0-485/">Ripple Price Analysis: Upside Break Looms At $0.485</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ripple price is facing resistance near the $0.485 level against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $0.470 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.4640 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a major increase above the $0.4850 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ripple price is rising above $0.4750 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-another-increase-to-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. XRP price must stay above the $0.4700 support to remain in a bullish zone.</em></p>
<h2>Ripple Price Analysis</h2>
<p>After forming a base above the $0.4120 level, Ripple price started a fresh increase against the US Dollar. The XRP/USD pair broke the $0.432 resistance to move into a positive zone.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above the $0.450 resistance and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). The bulls even pushed the price above the $0.470 resistance. A high is formed near $0.4861 and the price is now consolidating gains.</p>
<p>It is now trading above $0.470 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-more-gains-possible-above-0-47/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near $0.4850. The next major resistance is near the $0.4880 level.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $0.4880 resistance zone might start a strong increase. In the stated case, the price could even surpass the $0.4920 resistance. Any more gains might send the price toward the $0.5120 resistance. Initial support on the downside is near the $0.4760 level or the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.4433 swing low to the $0.4861 high.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $0.4700 level. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.4640 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair.</p>
<p>The trend line is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.4433 swing low to the $0.4861 high. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.4500 level, below which the price might even test $0.4320.</p>
<div id="attachment_78543" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Ripple-4.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78543" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78543" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Ripple-4.png" alt="Ripple Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78543" class="wp-caption-text">Ripple Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">chart</a>, Ripple price is now trading above the $0.47 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start a major increase above the $0.4850 resistance.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XRP/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for XRP/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.476, $0.470, and $0.450.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.4850 and $0.4880.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-upside-break-looms-at-0-485/">Ripple Price Analysis: Upside Break Looms At $0.485</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-upside-break-looms-at-0-485/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Bumps Slow After Bittrex News</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-bumps-stall-after-bittrex-news/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-bumps-stall-after-bittrex-news/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bittrex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77966</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The price of bitcoin has stalled thanks to recent news surrounding Bittrex, a popular digital currency exchange, and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Bitcoin Is Slowing Down a Bit Bitcoin has been on something of a roll since the beginning of the year. In 2022, the world’s number one cryptocurrency by market cap endured<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-bumps-stall-after-bittrex-news/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-bumps-stall-after-bittrex-news/">Bitcoin Price Bumps Slow After Bittrex News</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price of bitcoin has <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-stalls-near-30-000-after-the-token-s-biggest-drop-in-over-a-month/ar-AA19ZzZg" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stalled thanks to recent</a> news surrounding Bittrex, a popular digital currency exchange, and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Is Slowing Down a Bit</h2>
<p>Bitcoin has been on something of a roll since the beginning of the year. In 2022, the world’s number one cryptocurrency by market cap endured one of the harshest beatings it’s ever suffered and lost more than 70 percent of its value after attaining a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit in the prior November. By the end of 2022, the currency had fallen into the mid-$16K range.</p>
<p>In addition, several other digital assets decided to follow in BTC’s footsteps. This caused the entire space to come crashing to the ground and lose more than $2 trillion in valuation over the course of just ten to 12 months.</p>
<p>However, this year has offered something of a turnaround for bitcoin. The asset initially rose to $17K during the early months, and from there, it began expanding its price throughout the $20K range. Recently, it made headlines when it <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">struck the $30K</a> mark for the first time in about ten or 11 months (not since June of last year), causing many analysts to assume that the bulls were back in town and that bitcoin was going to reverse itself for good over the next few months.</p>
<p>While lasting damage arguably hasn’t been done yet, the currency has seen its growth spurt stunted a bit for the time being thanks to the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-continues-its-crypto-wrath-files-suit-against-bittrex/" data-wpel-link="internal">news surrounding Bittrex</a>, which is the latest digital currency victim of the SEC as our latest article suggests. The agency is claiming that the exchange has been breaking financial and securities rules for years, and that it took steps to avoid playing by the rules since it first came to fruition in the year 2014.</p>
<p>To be fair, it’s hard to know if these suggestions are real or not given how the SEC has just been working to crack down on every cryptocurrency company in existence as of late. Not long ago, for example, the agency went after Kraken and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/" data-wpel-link="internal">engaged in a settlement</a> with the exchange that saw the latter forced to give up more than $30 million in penalty fees. It was also required to cease all its staking services.</p>
<h2>Going After All the Companies</h2>
<p>The SEC didn’t stop there. It also recently <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">issued a Wells notice</a> to Coinbase, saying that while the company wasn’t being charged yet, it was being watched and it could expect to face charges in the coming future. The funny thing is that Coinbase claims to have met with representatives of the SEC regularly over the past nine years to ensure it always remained in compliance.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, bitcoin was trading in the low $30K range.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-bumps-stall-after-bittrex-news/">Bitcoin Price Bumps Slow After Bittrex News</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-bumps-stall-after-bittrex-news/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Continues Its Crypto Wrath; Files Suit Against Bittrex</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-continues-its-crypto-wrath-files-suit-against-bittrex/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-continues-its-crypto-wrath-files-suit-against-bittrex/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 15:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bittrex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kraken]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77963</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has laid its nasty hands into another digital currency company. This time, the victim of the agency’s wrath is Bittrex Inc., along with its former chief executive officer William Shihara. The SEC Is At It Again The agency says Bittrex broke its laws for years and that this<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-continues-its-crypto-wrath-files-suit-against-bittrex/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-continues-its-crypto-wrath-files-suit-against-bittrex/">SEC Continues Its Crypto Wrath; Files Suit Against Bittrex</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has laid its <a href="https://siliconangle.com/2023/04/17/sec-charges-cryptocurrency-exchange-bittrex-former-ceo-william-shihara/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">nasty hands into another</a> digital currency company. This time, the victim of the agency’s wrath is Bittrex Inc., along with its former chief executive officer William Shihara.</p>
<h2>The SEC Is At It Again</h2>
<p>The agency says Bittrex broke its laws for years and that this whole time, it operated as an unregistered securities exchange. This appears to be the narrative of the SEC each time it goes after a crypto firm. One wonders if these companies really and truly are engaged in such illicit behavior or if the agency is simply pulling this out of a hat as an excuse to go after whatever digital enterprise it wants.</p>
<p>The complaint was filed by the SEC in the U.S. District Court in Western Washington. The firm mentioned earlier this year that it was of the belief that many crypto companies throughout the country were selling digital currencies that, while popular, could easily be labeled securities. As a result, it said that many of these businesses were out of compliance and thus hadn’t taken part in appropriate registration protocols with the SEC, and now it looks like Bittrex has fallen into that category.</p>
<p>In a statement, SEC head Gary Gensler mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Today’s action, yet again, makes plain that the crypto markets suffer from a lack of regulatory compliance, not a lack of regulatory clarity. As alleged in our complaint, Bittrex and issuers that it worked with knew the rules that applied to them but went to great lengths to evade them by directing issuer-applicants to ‘scrub‘ offering materials of information indicating that certain crypto assets were securities.</p></blockquote>
<p>The SEC has really been going after the world’s leading crypto companies as of late. Not long ago, it engaged in a settlement with digital <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/" data-wpel-link="internal">exchange Kraken that forced</a> the firm to give up $30 million in penalties. It was also required to end all its staking services.</p>
<p>The SEC has also issued a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">Wells notice to Coinbase</a>, meaning that while the latter hasn’t been charged yet, it can likely expect to be charged with something in the coming future. A Wells notice is an indication that you are being watched.</p>
<h2>The Company&#8217;s History</h2>
<p>Bittrex initially launched in 2014 and became one of the world’s 50 largest digital currency exchanges soon after. Per the SEC, the company garnered more than $1 billion in revenue between 2017 and 2022. From its launch until the year 2019, Shihara served as the firm’s CEO.</p>
<p>Prior to today’s ruling, Bittrex had announced that it was looking into potentially shuttering its U.S. division, citing “continued regulatory uncertainty” as the reason why. In October of last year, the company was slapped with a $53 million fine by the U.S. Treasury Department due to its business engagements.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-continues-its-crypto-wrath-files-suit-against-bittrex/">SEC Continues Its Crypto Wrath; Files Suit Against Bittrex</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-continues-its-crypto-wrath-files-suit-against-bittrex/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Star Athlete Shaquille O&#8217;Neal Is Latest Defendant in FTX Suit</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/star-athlete-shaquille-oneal-served-in-ftx-lawsuit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/star-athlete-shaquille-oneal-served-in-ftx-lawsuit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 13:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lawsuit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shaquille O'Neal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77948</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Basketball superstar Shaquille O’Neal is the latest athlete to be served in a class-action lawsuit against the now defunct crypto exchange FTX, which fell apart in a heap of bankruptcy and fraud last November. Shaquille O&#8217;Neal Is the Latest FTX Defendant Adam M. Moskowitz – the attorney leading the lawsuit – made the announcement to<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/star-athlete-shaquille-oneal-served-in-ftx-lawsuit/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/star-athlete-shaquille-oneal-served-in-ftx-lawsuit/">Star Athlete Shaquille O&#8217;Neal Is Latest Defendant in FTX Suit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Basketball superstar Shaquille O’Neal is the latest athlete to be <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nba/shaquille-o-neal-served-in-ftx-lawsuit-lawyers-say/ar-AA19WzUr?OCID=ansmsnnews11" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">served in a class-action lawsuit</a> against the now defunct crypto exchange FTX, which fell apart in a heap of bankruptcy and fraud last November.</p>
<h2>Shaquille O&#8217;Neal Is the Latest FTX Defendant</h2>
<p>Adam M. Moskowitz – the attorney leading the lawsuit – made the announcement to his clients via the following statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>I wanted you to know the good news that we just served Shaquille O&#8217;Neal outside his house in Atlanta. The good news is his home video cameras recorded our service and we have made it very clear he is not to destroy and/or erase any of these security tapes because they must be preserved for our lawsuit.</p></blockquote>
<p>Moskowitz claims that he and his firm have been attempting to serve court documents to O’Neal for the past three months, but that the former Lakers and Miami Heat player has been dodging them repeatedly. Moskowitz also had a judge deny his request that the lawsuit papers be delivered electronically given the basketball legend’s (allegedly) repeated attempts to dodge those of the law firm.</p>
<p>O’Neal is now the final defendant to be served. He – along with several other professional athletes such as football <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tom-brady-named-in-new-ftx-based-lawsuit/" data-wpel-link="internal">quarterback Tom Brady</a> – is being accused of defrauding investors. Moskowitz continued his statement with:</p>
<blockquote><p>Mr. O&#8217;Neal will now be required to appear in federal court and explain to his millions of followers his &#8216;FTX: I Am All In&#8217; false advertising campaign.</p></blockquote>
<p>The NBA champion has denied he had anything to do with the fraudulent dealings of the company, claiming he only possessed a sponsorship deal with the exchange. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>A lot of people think I&#8217;m involved, but I was just a paid spokesperson for a commercial.</p></blockquote>
<p>In a recent email, Moskowitz told news sources that FTX played a false liquidity card and ultimately wound up defrauding more people than Bernie Madoff. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>FTX were geniuses at public relations and marketing and knew that such a massive Ponzi scheme — larger than the Madoff scheme — could only be successful with the help and promotion of the most famous, respected, and beloved celebrities and influencers in the world.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Terrible Occurrence for All</h2>
<p>FTX is likely to go down as one of the worst embarrassments in the history of crypto. What was once one of the world’s top five digital currency exchanges soon became a scam-ridden haven for illicit behavior that ultimately <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-the-damage-caused-by-ftx-was-worse-than-initially-thought/" data-wpel-link="internal">cost the crypto arena more</a> than $200 billion.</p>
<p>It is alleged that Sam Bankman-Fried – the man behind the digital currency trading platform – utilized customer funds to invest in luxury Bahamian real estate. It has also been reported that he used these same monies to pay off loans taken out by his other company Alameda Research, thus combining both business and customer assets (an illegal action).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/star-athlete-shaquille-oneal-served-in-ftx-lawsuit/">Star Athlete Shaquille O&#8217;Neal Is Latest Defendant in FTX Suit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/star-athlete-shaquille-oneal-served-in-ftx-lawsuit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
