<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 03:16:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Buncombe County in North Carolina Shuts Down Crypto Mining for One Year</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/buncombe-county-in-north-carolina-shuts-down-crypto-mining-for-one-year/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/buncombe-county-in-north-carolina-shuts-down-crypto-mining-for-one-year/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 17:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Moratorium]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[North Carolina]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78208</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Buncombe County commissioners in North Carolina are taking a page out of New York’s crypto playbook and are enforcing a one-year moratorium on all crypto mining operations so they can explore regulations and laws. North Carolina County Halts Crypto Mining Planning director Nate Pennington said in an interview: We don’t often bring a moratorium to<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/buncombe-county-in-north-carolina-shuts-down-crypto-mining-for-one-year/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/buncombe-county-in-north-carolina-shuts-down-crypto-mining-for-one-year/">Buncombe County in North Carolina Shuts Down Crypto Mining for One Year</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Buncombe County commissioners in North Carolina are taking a page out of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/some-want-the-crypto-moratorium-in-new-york-to-last-longer/" data-wpel-link="internal">New York’s crypto</a> playbook and are enforcing a <a href="https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/buncombe-county-oks-1-moratorium-113219118.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">one-year moratorium on all</a> crypto mining operations so they can explore regulations and laws.</p>
<h2>North Carolina County Halts Crypto Mining</h2>
<p>Planning director Nate Pennington said in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>We don’t often bring a moratorium to the table.</p></blockquote>
<p>However, he commented that because crypto mining is still relatively new and doesn’t run under any specific laws, this period will allow him and his fellow city council members to explore new ideas for ensuring the space remains safe for all who take part in it or benefit from it.</p>
<p>Chris Joyell – the healthy communities director with Mountain True – said the region’s people have been extremely helpful and “proactive” when it comes to the issue at hand. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Mountain True has seen several cryptocurrency mines operating in WNC, especially in Cherokee County, where they have proven to be a nuisance to neighbors and a threat to our environment.</p></blockquote>
<p>He said that right now, there are many concerns surrounding the potential noise of the mining machines. There is also a lot of worry regarding the pollution they allegedly emit, and he and his fellow constituents don’t want North Carolina air or water being ruined because people are looking to create blockchain careers for themselves. He continued with:</p>
<blockquote><p>There is no way to greenwash crypto mining. Let me repeat: As the value of bitcoin rebounds, the growth of cryptocurrency mining operations put North Carolina in danger of not being able to hit the goals set out by Gov. Cooper and the N.C. General Assembly with House Bill 951.</p></blockquote>
<p>Craig Deutsch has lived in Buncombe County for about ten years. He’s one of the few people who’s against the moratorium, saying that with crypto being such a revolutionary arena, he’s concerned the move could put North Carolina behind in terms of technical achievements. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I urge the county commissioners and planners to take the time to visit bitcoin mines, do research about bitcoin’s benefits to the environment&#8230; and listen to stories about the positive impacts of bitcoin for underserved and underbanked communities… At the end of the day, all bitcoin mining computers do is run code, and code is a form of constitutionally protected speech.</p></blockquote>
<p>Kimberly Stonebraker, who has lived in North Carolina since 1999, said to the commissioners:</p>
<blockquote><p>I urge you to keep an open mind.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Not Good for Residents?</h2>
<p>Finally, Ken Brame – a representative of the Sierra Club – said he fears crypto mining can do a lot of damage to residents. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We live out there for a reason. We need to take the time to figure out what regulations, what management we have in place to prevent that from happening in neighborhoods like mine.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/buncombe-county-in-north-carolina-shuts-down-crypto-mining-for-one-year/">Buncombe County in North Carolina Shuts Down Crypto Mining for One Year</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/buncombe-county-in-north-carolina-shuts-down-crypto-mining-for-one-year/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leticia James Introduces Bill That Would Birth Basic Crypto Regulation in New York</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leticia-james-introduces-bill-that-would-birth-basic-crypto-regulation-in-new-york/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leticia-james-introduces-bill-that-would-birth-basic-crypto-regulation-in-new-york/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto-regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Leticia James]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New York]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78210</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new bill proposed by New York Attorney General Leticia James would give her state a basic framework for crypto regulation. Among the provisions in the bill are exchanges being required to reimburse customers if they are the victims of fraud or theft. Leticia James Seeks to Introduce Basic Regulation New York and Leticia James<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leticia-james-introduces-bill-that-would-birth-basic-crypto-regulation-in-new-york/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leticia-james-introduces-bill-that-would-birth-basic-crypto-regulation-in-new-york/">Leticia James Introduces Bill That Would Birth Basic Crypto Regulation in New York</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new bill proposed by New York Attorney General Leticia James <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/new-york-attorney-general-seeks-new-crypto-powers-for-state-regulators/ar-AA1aMIFu" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">would give her state a basic</a> framework for crypto regulation. Among the provisions in the bill are exchanges being required to reimburse customers if they are the victims of fraud or theft.</p>
<h2>Leticia James Seeks to Introduce Basic Regulation</h2>
<p>New York and Leticia James have long held strong anti-crypto attitudes. Not long ago, the attorney general sued several digital currency companies including <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-attorney-generals-office-now-suing-ku-coin-exchange/" data-wpel-link="internal">Ku Coin</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leticia-james-sues-coin-ex-alleging-crypto-fraud/" data-wpel-link="internal">Coin Ex</a>, alleging both had taken part in various forms of fraud.</p>
<p>In addition, the state of New York has recently <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/some-want-the-crypto-moratorium-in-new-york-to-last-longer/" data-wpel-link="internal">instituted a two-year crypto</a> moratorium to ensure that no new digital currency mining companies can set up shop in the Empire State for the next 24 months. The goal is to make it so that all crypto companies run purely on clean energy and obey present environmental standards. Regarding her recent bill, James stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>We&#8217;re proposing common sense measures to protect investors and end the fraud and dysfunction that have become the hallmarks of cryptocurrency.</p></blockquote>
<p>Other provisions laid out in the bill include customers being informed of conflicts of interest amongst crypto companies. Also, they would be educated on various risks regarding their investments and the platforms they choose to work with. Lastly, crypto companies would not be permitted to borrow or lend customer assets, clearly a nod to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">the FTX debacle</a> in which customer funds were utilized to pay off loans and invest in luxury Bahamian real estate.</p>
<p>While the items laid out in the bill sound glorious, it would be a mistake to rush forward on the idea that it’s all lollipops and rainbows from here on out, the biggest reason being that James, as mentioned above, has not always liked crypto or held the most positive attitude towards it. Thus, crypto fans need to remain wary.</p>
<p>This is an idea held by many crypto analysts and legal experts including Andrew Hinkes, a partner at law firm K&amp;L Gates. In a recent tweet, Hinkes mentioned that the bill was “destined to fail” in the New York Congress given that it’s written by someone (James) who doesn’t understand crypto.</p>
<p>He explained that the provisions in the bill are virtually impossible to apply to decentralized organizations. He also mentioned that the market, as it stands, cannot provide the kinds of auditing and insurance that James would like to see initiated.</p>
<h2>Being Looked at Carefully</h2>
<p>Right now, the bill is in document form and being observed by New York regulators. They must give the “OK” on the bill for it to become law.</p>
<p>Since the fall of FTX seven months ago, crypto regulation appears to be on the minds of virtually every politician. The company <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-the-damage-caused-by-ftx-was-worse-than-initially-thought/" data-wpel-link="internal">accounted for more than</a> $200 billion in crypto funds being wiped off the digital slate permanently.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leticia-james-introduces-bill-that-would-birth-basic-crypto-regulation-in-new-york/">Leticia James Introduces Bill That Would Birth Basic Crypto Regulation in New York</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leticia-james-introduces-bill-that-would-birth-basic-crypto-regulation-in-new-york/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Opinion: Biden Will Go Down as the Most Anti-Crypto Leader in History</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-biden-will-go-down-as-the-most-anti-crypto-leader-in-history/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-biden-will-go-down-as-the-most-anti-crypto-leader-in-history/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 13:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OpEd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78213</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Between his shady infrastructure bill, attempting to shut the crypto industry out of traditional or standard financial products, and now a 30 percent tax proposal on all crypto mining operations, Joe Biden is arguably turning out to be the most anti-crypto “leader” in the history of the U.S. Biden + Crypto = Disasters! Crypto has<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-biden-will-go-down-as-the-most-anti-crypto-leader-in-history/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-biden-will-go-down-as-the-most-anti-crypto-leader-in-history/">Opinion: Biden Will Go Down as the Most Anti-Crypto Leader in History</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Between his shady <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-amendment-for-infrastructure-bill-leads-to-more-problems-and-infighting/" data-wpel-link="internal">infrastructure bill</a>, attempting to shut the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-biden-using-an-obama-era-program-to-ban-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">crypto industry out of traditional</a> or standard financial products, and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/biden-wants-to-tax-crypto-mining-companies-at-30/" data-wpel-link="internal">now a 30 percent tax</a> proposal on all crypto mining operations, Joe Biden is arguably turning out to be the most anti-crypto “leader” in the history of the U.S.</p>
<h2>Biden + Crypto = Disasters!</h2>
<p>Crypto has long been a taboo topic in American politics. As we all remember in 2019, some of the democratic hopefuls looking to make their way into the White House in 2020 built their campaigns on the ideas that crypto could be simplified. Men like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/andrew-yang-the-crypto-president/" data-wpel-link="internal">Andrew Yang</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-bloomberg-proposes-clarified-bitcoin-regulation-if-he-takes-the-white-house/" data-wpel-link="internal">Michael Bloomberg</a> said they would do all they could to make crypto laws easier to understand, and they would work to make the industry more mainstream.</p>
<p>However, neither figure was able to make waves with voters, and their plans ultimately came to immediate standstills.</p>
<p>In the end, democrats wound up with Joe Biden. The irony here is that in the beginning, Biden was touted as the man who would put <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/billybambrough/2020/11/15/why-joe-biden-could-be-big-for-bitcoin/?sh=389b95b5f688" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">crypto on the map</a>. He would make it a legitimate, mainstream asset class that could be utilized and enjoyed by all. Since then, however, he’s done the exact opposite, and his anti-crypto rhetoric has become all-too clear.</p>
<p>Things got off to a rocky start in the summer of 2021, just a few months after he was inaugurated. Biden signed a new infrastructure bill into law that instead of working to rebuild our roads, hospitals, and schools (like the word “infrastructure” would imply), contained verbiage aimed at crypto holders. They would be required to report all transactions exceeding specific numbers, and the IRS would likely come down hard on them every April 15 beginning in the year 2024.</p>
<p>Things didn’t stop there, however. Biden initiated several weak economic policies and signed multiple trillion-dollar spending bills into law that ultimately caused record inflation and brought crypto prices down to their lowest points in 2022. That period now stands as the shakiest ever for crypto.</p>
<p>Then, news spread that Biden was working to implement an Obama-era policy that would shut out all crypto businesses from traditional financial tools and services. Things like checking accounts, for example, would no longer be accessible to these firms, but just when you thought things couldn’t get any worse, America’s phony president announced he was urging Congress to consider a 30 percent tax proposal on all crypto mining businesses.</p>
<h2>Trying to Ruin the Mining Sector?</h2>
<p>This would undoubtedly bring the industry to a halt given mining’s where the money is at. It’s also what gives crypto life and brings new digital units into circulation. By defeating miners, you defeat the entire crypto arena.</p>
<p>At this stage, anyone who felt Biden would be America’s “crypto president” should be hiding in shame.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-biden-will-go-down-as-the-most-anti-crypto-leader-in-history/">Opinion: Biden Will Go Down as the Most Anti-Crypto Leader in History</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-biden-will-go-down-as-the-most-anti-crypto-leader-in-history/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Bulls Eye Recovery To $115</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bulls-eye-recovery-to-115/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bulls-eye-recovery-to-115/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 03:28:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78832</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin cash is attempting a recovery wave above the $100 resistance against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below the $110 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $105 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bulls-eye-recovery-to-115/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bulls-eye-recovery-to-115/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Bulls Eye Recovery To $115</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin cash is attempting a recovery wave above the $100 resistance against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below the $110 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $105 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair must clear $106 and $108 to continue higher in the near term.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin cash price is consolidating above $100 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-rally-above-this-resistance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. BCH/USD could start a fresh surge if it clears the $108 level.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin cash price formed a decent support base above the $95 level. BCH started a decent increase and was able to clear the $98 resistance zone.</p>
<p>The price climbed above the $100 and $102 resistance levels. There was a move above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $116.83 swing high to the $90.82 low. Besides, there was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $105 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair.</p>
<p>It is now trading below the $110 zone and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bulls-struggle-below-120/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $106 level.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $108 level or the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $116.83 swing high to the $90.82 low, above which the price may perhaps rise toward the $115 level. Any more gains above $115 could set the pace for a move toward the $120 level.</p>
<p>If not, the price might decline again. Immediate support on the downside is near the $102 level. The first major support sits near the $100 level. The next major support is near $95, below which the bears might aim for $90. The next target for them may perhaps be near the $88 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_78834" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Bitcoin-Cash-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78834" class="size-full wp-image-78834" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Bitcoin-Cash-2.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash Price" width="1835" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78834" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Cash Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BCHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Bitcoin Cash’s price is now trading below the $110 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price must clear $106 and $108 to continue higher in the near term.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for BCH/USD is gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BCH/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $102 and $100.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $108 and $115.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bulls-eye-recovery-to-115/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Bulls Eye Recovery To $115</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bulls-eye-recovery-to-115/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Shuts Down Its Borrowing and Lending Division</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-shuts-down-its-borrowing-and-lending-division/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-shuts-down-its-borrowing-and-lending-division/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase Borrow]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78200</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase Borrow – the official lending protocol of Coinbase, one of America’s largest and most popular digital currency trading platforms – has ceased all operations. Coinbase Borrow Closes Its Doors Permanently The end for Coinbase Borrow arrived on May 10. This was the last day on which customers could take out loans. Those who received<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-shuts-down-its-borrowing-and-lending-division/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-shuts-down-its-borrowing-and-lending-division/">Coinbase Shuts Down Its Borrowing and Lending Division</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase Borrow – the official lending protocol of Coinbase, one of America’s largest and most popular digital currency trading platforms – has <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/coinbase-to-stop-issuing-new-loans-via-coinbase-borrow/ar-AA1aIdBD" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">ceased all operations</a>.</p>
<h2>Coinbase Borrow Closes Its Doors Permanently</h2>
<p>The end for Coinbase Borrow arrived on May 10. This was the last day on which customers could take out loans. Those who received loans prior to the set date were told their financials wouldn’t be affected. This was simply the cut-off date for all new lending customers.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, despite the exchange being under heavy scrutiny from institutions like the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), the closing of Coinbase Borrow doesn’t appear to have anything to do with the company’s ongoing legal problems. A person allegedly familiar with the matter explained in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>We regularly evaluate our products to ensure we’re prioritizing the offerings that our customers care about most. Effective May 10, we will stop issuing new loans through Coinbase Borrow. There is no impact on customers’ outstanding loans, and no action is required from them [currently].</p></blockquote>
<p>Right now, many analysts are being forced to come up with their own conclusions and assumptions regarding the reasons for the closure. One can say, for example, that the borrowing and lending arena in the crypto world has been rather up and down over the past year, and thus Coinbase doesn’t want to take any chances.</p>
<p>For example, lending protocols such as <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/celsius-network-is-next-crypto-company-to-file-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">Celsius</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-lender-voyager-digital-files-chapter-11-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">Voyager Digital</a> have been forced to close their doors and enter bankruptcy proceedings as a means of protecting themselves against angry creditors who want their money back. <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/another-mega-bitcoin-crash-is-in-the-books/" data-wpel-link="internal">These institutions also halted</a> all withdrawals, thus cutting customers off from their hard-earned funds to ensure that they could at least remain relatively stable while they figured out their next steps.</p>
<p>The crypto industry is still reeling from the actions of 2022. While assets like bitcoin have experienced some degrees of healing since the start of 2023, there is still a lot of work to do, and a black cloud is still hanging over the heads of many crypto and blockchain institutions. It may be some time before everything is fully resolved.</p>
<p>Coinbase has been enduring several issues over the past few months. Not long ago, the company <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">received a Wells notice</a> from the SEC, informing executives that while charges hadn’t been filed against the company yet, these charges were likely to arrive relatively soon.</p>
<h2>Why Send Us This?</h2>
<p>Coinbase took serious issue with the Wells notice on account of the alleged fact that those in charge met with representatives of the SEC roughly 30 times over the course of nine years to ensure that they remained fully compliant with present securities and financial laws.</p>
<p>The SEC has arguably become one of the biggest crypto bullies around.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-shuts-down-its-borrowing-and-lending-division/">Coinbase Shuts Down Its Borrowing and Lending Division</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-shuts-down-its-borrowing-and-lending-division/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>First Republic Bank is Gone; What Will Happen to BTC?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/first-republic-bank-is-gone-what-will-happen-to-btc/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/first-republic-bank-is-gone-what-will-happen-to-btc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 15:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[banking crisis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[First Republic bank]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78198</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin endured a small dip in early May after it was revealed the drama surrounding First Republic Bank reached a new peak. Right now, the sentiment is that the bank could be the final monetary institution that crashes and burns following a long streak of banks that did the same. The streak includes names like<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/first-republic-bank-is-gone-what-will-happen-to-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/first-republic-bank-is-gone-what-will-happen-to-btc/">First Republic Bank is Gone; What Will Happen to BTC?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin endured a small dip in early May after it was <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-pulls-back-to-start-may-as-first-republic-bank-saga-comes-to-an-end/ar-AA1aBdVP" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">revealed the drama surrounding</a> First Republic Bank reached a new peak. Right now, the sentiment is that the bank could be the final monetary institution that crashes and burns following a long <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-provide-their-thoughts-on-latest-bitcoin-rally/" data-wpel-link="internal">streak of banks</a> that did the same. The streak includes names like Signature, Silvergate, and Silicon Valley.</p>
<h2>First Republic Bank Has Fallen</h2>
<p>Early last month, regulators acquired First Republic Bank and circulated most of its assets and deposits to institutions like JPMorgan Chase. This marks the third major bank failure this year, and it’s making a lot of people think the days of the 2008 Great Recession are on their way back.</p>
<p>Alex Thorn – head of firmwide research at Galaxy – commented in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>It&#8217;s unclear whether the banking crisis narrative can continue to be a boon for bitcoin. Overall, the market lacks clear positive near-term catalysts, with supply issues overhanging bitcoin… Bitcoin accumulation by small addresses is outpacing issuance, and we expect Ethereum staking to increase, each of which provides a supportive supply narrative. Outside of crypto-native factors, we expect a back-of-the-year macro environment to be characterized by tightening, recession, and an expanding multipolarity in the global economy, all of which can be supportive of gold and bitcoin.</p></blockquote>
<p>The banking crisis in America and Europe has been two-fold in many ways. On the one hand, it’s put a lot of people in a state of fear that another big financial crisis like the one we witnessed 14 or 15 years ago is coming again. At the same time, it can be argued that the current baking crisis has brought about a new “safe haven” status for bitcoin and many of its digital cronies.</p>
<p>As a result, we are seeing currencies like bitcoin rise like they never did the previous year, and there are more people backing these assets, supporting them, and investing in them as a means of keeping their wealth stable during this present period of financial and economic strife. Thorn continued with:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin and ether started 2023 inorganically cheap, allowing for plenty of room to move higher off a low-base effect. A widening banking crisis became evident in March, and the contrast with bitcoin&#8217;s transparent and decentralized nature provided a further leg up for bitcoin, while Ethereum&#8217;s successful Shanghai upgrade provided a catalyst for Ethereum.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Trouble A-Brewing for Standard Banks</h2>
<p>First Republic Bank reached a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-spikes-following-more-banking-troubles/" data-wpel-link="internal">troublesome point after</a> its stock shares fell by more than 80 percent over the course of just a few days. The dips had a lot to do with lagging deposits in Silicon Valley Bank.</p>
<p>That institution was “notoriously” tied to crypto, which is why so many regulators blamed the digital currency arena for the fall of the latter firm.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/first-republic-bank-is-gone-what-will-happen-to-btc/">First Republic Bank is Gone; What Will Happen to BTC?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/first-republic-bank-is-gone-what-will-happen-to-btc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fed Hikes Rates Again, but Analysts Think Bitcoin Will Surge Soon</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-fed-hikes-rates-again-but-analysts-think-bitcoin-will-surge-soon/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-fed-hikes-rates-again-but-analysts-think-bitcoin-will-surge-soon/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 13:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tim Draper]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78196</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Fed recently made the decision to hike rates again, but the situation appears to be quite different according to various bitcoin and crypto analysts. The Fed and Bitcoin: Working Off Each Other? This is the tenth hike instituted by the Fed over the past year or so, and many believe this could be the<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-fed-hikes-rates-again-but-analysts-think-bitcoin-will-surge-soon/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-fed-hikes-rates-again-but-analysts-think-bitcoin-will-surge-soon/">The Fed Hikes Rates Again, but Analysts Think Bitcoin Will Surge Soon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Fed recently made the decision to hike rates again, but the <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/05/04/a-new-market-regime-the-fed-may-have-just-triggered-a-100-billion-bitcoin-price-boom-as-ethereum-surges-back/?sh=44dfaa1f5417" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">situation appears to be quite</a> different according to various bitcoin and crypto analysts.</p>
<h2>The Fed and Bitcoin: Working Off Each Other?</h2>
<p>This is the tenth hike instituted by the Fed over the past year or so, and many believe this could be the last one… at least for a while. They are certain that with the agency now stepping back and allowing things to cool down for a while, bitcoin is going to endure a humongous rally, and the world’s number one digital currency by market cap could wind up spiking to unprecedented levels in the coming months or weeks.</p>
<p>Markus Thielen – head of research at crypto services provider Matrix Port – said in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>While the Fed has raised interest rates by another 25 basis points, the probability that this was the last hike for this cycle is high, which could set up the market for another strong rally.</p></blockquote>
<p>The interesting thing is <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-fed-bitcoins-worst-enemy-right-now/" data-wpel-link="internal">that 2022 was a year in</a> which rate hikes were relatively constant, and they did little to nothing positive for bitcoin and its digital cronies. These assets repeatedly fell flat on their faces after rate hikes occurred, suggesting they were not the anti-inflation tools so many analysts and advocates had touted so many times before.</p>
<p>However, the Fed has already hiked rates a few times in 2023, and interestingly, bitcoin appears to be either unaffected after they occur, or the asset endures a small price jump that makes many people wonder if perhaps the asset is gaining maturity and learning to develop a thicker and stronger skin considering the ongoing financial debauchery.</p>
<p>Thielen further said:</p>
<blockquote><p>At the same time, we continuously see bank failure, which requires liquidity injections and guarantees from the government for any acquiring party.</p></blockquote>
<p>Lewis Harland – Decentral Park Capital’s portfolio manager – was also quick to throw his two cents into the mix, stating:</p>
<blockquote><p>You see outperformance of bitcoin within the crypto market when regional bank share prices collapse. This signals that bitcoin is the high-quality, anti-dollar liquid play for investors as the crisis unfolds further. A break of 50 percent would likely signal a new market regime of prolonged bitcoin outperformance within the market.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Tim Draper Thinks BTC is Gonna Shoot Up</h2>
<p>Venture capitalist and bitcoin bull Tim Draper also <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/billionaire-investor-tim-draper-predicts-bitcoin-bull-market-says-controlling-government-is-killing-the-golden-goose-of-silicon-valley/ar-AA1aJUs4" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">believes bitcoin is going</a> to spike to new highs relatively soon. He recently commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>If the bear gets that angry to where the banks start falling apart, that actually means that bitcoin will have a bull market. It&#8217;ll be a raging bull in the middle of the bear… If they are regulating by enforcement, they&#8217;re just slapping people down and fining them and suing them. I don&#8217;t want to waste years of my life in court and trying to avoid some problem.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-fed-hikes-rates-again-but-analysts-think-bitcoin-will-surge-soon/">The Fed Hikes Rates Again, but Analysts Think Bitcoin Will Surge Soon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-fed-hikes-rates-again-but-analysts-think-bitcoin-will-surge-soon/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EOS Price Analysis: Downtrend Intact Below $0.80</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-downtrend-intact-below-0-80/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-downtrend-intact-below-0-80/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 05:08:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EOS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78814</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>EOS price started a fresh decline below the $0.80 level against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $0.750 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a short-term bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.675 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-downtrend-intact-below-0-80/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-downtrend-intact-below-0-80/">EOS Price Analysis: Downtrend Intact Below $0.80</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>EOS price started a fresh decline below the $0.80 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $0.750 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a short-term bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.675 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to decline if it stays below the $0.675 and $0.750 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>EOS price is struggling below $0.80 against the US Dollar, unlike <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-rally-above-this-resistance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. The price might attempt to recover if there is a clear move above $0.675.</em></p>
<h2>EOS Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, EOS price saw a major decline from the $0.900 resistance against the US Dollar. The price traded below the $0.85 and $0.80 levels to move into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>The decline gained pace below the $0.750 level. It even spiked below $0.700. A low is formed near $0.6048 and the price is now consolidating losses. EOS is trading well below $0.80 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-signs-of-fresh-increase-toward-0-95/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $0.675 level. There is also a short-term bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.675 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair. It is near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.9040 swing high to the $0.6048 low.</p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $0.75 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.9040 swing high to the $0.6048 low.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $0.75 level could start a steady increase toward the $0.78 level. The next major resistance might be $0.80. Any more gains might send the price toward the $0.850 level. On the downside, immediate support is near $0.620.</p>
<p>The next key support is near the $0.600 level. If there is a downside break below the $0.600 support, the price could test the $0.550 support in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_78815" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/EOS-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78815" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78815" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/EOS-2.png" alt="EOS Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78815" class="wp-caption-text">EOS Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/EOSUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, EOS price is now trading below the $0.80 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to decline if it stays below the $0.675 and $0.750 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for EOS/USD is gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $0.620 and $0.600.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $0.675 and $0.750.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-downtrend-intact-below-0-80/">EOS Price Analysis: Downtrend Intact Below $0.80</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-downtrend-intact-below-0-80/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Risk of More Losses Below $70</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-70/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-70/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 03:08:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78811</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin is showing bearish signs and trading below $80 against the US Dollar. LTC price is now trading below $78 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $80.60 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-70/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-70/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Risk of More Losses Below $70</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Litecoin is showing bearish signs and trading below $80 against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>LTC price is now trading below $78 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $80.60 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could start a decent increase if it clears the $82 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Litecoin price is struggling below $80 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-rally-above-this-resistance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. LTC price could continue to decline if it stays below the $82 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, there was a short-lived recovery in Bitcoin, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-consolidates-below-key-resistance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Ethereum</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-fresh-rally-possible-above-0-54/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Ripple</a>, and Litecoin against the US Dollar. Earlier, LTC settled below the $90 resistance zone to move into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>The price broke the $82 support zone and started a fresh decline. It even traded below the $80 support. A low is formed near $71.09 and the price is now consolidating losses. It is now trading below $78 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $80.60 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair. Immediate resistance is near the $75.60 level. It is close to the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $90.08 swing high to the $71.09 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $80 level or the trend line. The trend line is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $90.08 swing high to the $71.09 low.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $80 level could pump the price toward the $82 level or even $85. The next major resistance could be $90.</p>
<p>On the downside, immediate support is near the $72 level. The next key support is near the $70 level. If there is a downside break below the $70 support, the price could accelerate lower toward the $65 level in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_78812" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Litecoin-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78812" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78812" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Litecoin-2.png" alt="Litecoin (LTC) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78812" class="wp-caption-text">Litecoin (LTC) Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Litecoin price is clearly trading below $80 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $82 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LTC/USD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $72.00 and $70.00.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $75.60 and $80.00.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-70/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Risk of More Losses Below $70</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-70/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=3919 metric#misses=5 metric#hit-ratio=99.9 metric#bytes=6636331 metric#prefetches=398 metric#store-reads=16 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=403 metric#store-misses=0 metric#sql-queries=17 metric#ms-total=171.52 metric#ms-cache=14.19 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.8349 metric#ms-cache-ratio=8.3 -->
