<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 03:17:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Michael Saylor, the Eternal BTC Bull, Just Bought More Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-the-eternal-btc-bull-just-bought-more-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-the-eternal-btc-bull-just-bought-more-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 17:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Saylor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroStrategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Silvergate]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77675</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Saylor – the man behind software giant MicroStrategy and a major crypto bull – has paid off a $200 million+ loan obtained from the now failed crypto bank Silvergate and has purchased even more bitcoin units, thus bringing the company’s total BTC holdings to nearly $4 billion. Michael Saylor Won&#8217;t Give Up on BTC<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-the-eternal-btc-bull-just-bought-more-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-the-eternal-btc-bull-just-bought-more-crypto/">Michael Saylor, the Eternal BTC Bull, Just Bought More Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Michael Saylor – the man behind software giant MicroStrategy and a major crypto bull – has paid off a $200 million+ loan <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/michael-saylors-microstrategy-snaps-another-164250827.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">obtained from the now failed</a> crypto bank Silvergate and has purchased even more bitcoin units, thus bringing the company’s total BTC holdings to nearly $4 billion.</p>
<h2>Michael Saylor Won&#8217;t Give Up on BTC</h2>
<p>On the one hand, this is a positive story. Saylor and MicroStrategy were literally billions of dollars in debt in 2022 thanks to the ongoing bear run. The price of bitcoin was hit extremely hard and wound up losing more than 70 percent of its value over the course of 12 short months, falling from its new all-time high of $68,000 per unit (achieved in November of 2021) and dipping into the mid-$16K range by the end of 2022. It was a sad and ugly sight to see.</p>
<p>Institutional players like MicroStrategy <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/microstrategy-dealt-heavy-blow-following-crypto-crash/" data-wpel-link="internal">suffered greatly</a>. The bitcoin-related decisions made by Saylor led to his <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-btc-bull-and-microstrategy-chief-executive-steps-down/" data-wpel-link="internal">official step down from</a> the CEO position he had held with the company for over 30 years, and he switched over to the role of executive chairman. The fact that the company has managed to pull itself out of the doldrums and ultimately pay off one of its biggest loans is a good sign that things are perhaps picking up not just for the enterprise, but for the digital currency space.</p>
<p>However, as we’ve seen by now, Saylor’s love of BTC <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/it-appears-michael-saylor-will-never-reject-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">has gone a little overboard</a> at times, and he arguably rushes into things without really thinking about them as much as he should. Right now, BTC and its altcoin cousins are enduring a bit of a bull run, a solid change from 2022. It’s nice to sit back and watch, though it would be incorrect to assume that we’re fully out of the darkness and there isn’t more space to improve and heal.</p>
<p>The fact remains that BTC is nowhere near where it was a year and a half ago, and the idea that Saylor would simply jump all the way back into the bitcoin bin without allowing more time to go by is a bit concerning. It suggests that he hasn’t really learned his lesson from the past yet, and thus MicroStrategy could be in for more pain before it’s able to fully remove the bandages from its former wounds.</p>
<p>In late March, Saylor issued the following statement on Twitter:</p>
<blockquote><p>MicroStrategy repaid its $205M Silvergate loan at a 22 percent discount.</p></blockquote>
<h2>So Many Banks Are Collapsing</h2>
<p>Silvergate was one of several banks to crumble and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-crashed-following-news-of-silvergate-shutdown/" data-wpel-link="internal">collapse in recent weeks</a>, with others being Silicon Valley and Signature.</p>
<p>The financial catastrophe has also spread to Europe, with institutions <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-more-banks-fell-bitcoin-rose-beyond-28k/" data-wpel-link="internal">such as Credit Suisse</a> being on the verge of crashing and burning before it was saved by a $3 billion-bearing UBS.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-the-eternal-btc-bull-just-bought-more-crypto/">Michael Saylor, the Eternal BTC Bull, Just Bought More Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-the-eternal-btc-bull-just-bought-more-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Can Bitcoin Assist in the Tokenization of Additional Assets?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/can-bitcoin-assist-in-the-tokenization-of-additional-assets/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/can-bitcoin-assist-in-the-tokenization-of-additional-assets/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 15:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Morgan McKenney]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tokenization]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77672</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Assets like bitcoin and Ethereum have soared in recent weeks, and the sudden bull run is causing many big financial players – such as Fidelity and BlackRock – to increase their stakes in the crypto space and try to do more with digital tokens. Bitcoin Could Give Rise to Further Tokenization The bull run has<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/can-bitcoin-assist-in-the-tokenization-of-additional-assets/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/can-bitcoin-assist-in-the-tokenization-of-additional-assets/">Can Bitcoin Assist in the Tokenization of Additional Assets?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Assets like bitcoin and Ethereum have soared in recent weeks, and the <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/03/27/looming-300-trillion-crypto-earthquake-revealed-amid-huge-bitcoin-and-ethereum-price-pump/?sh=7f1da0144277" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">sudden bull run is causing</a> many big financial players – such as <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fidelity-and-black-rock-keep-expanding-their-crypto-influence/" data-wpel-link="internal">Fidelity and BlackRock</a> – to increase their stakes in the crypto space and try to do more with digital tokens.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Could Give Rise to Further Tokenization</h2>
<p>The bull run has gotten so many people excited that according to a new report issued by crypto infrastructure provider Taurus, roughly $300 trillion in private assets could be digitized in the coming future. The report reads:</p>
<blockquote><p>Tokenization could open worlds not imagined yet to private assets in a similar way to how the internet and e-commerce transformed many industries over the last two decades.</p></blockquote>
<p>2023 is, thus far, turning out to be the complete opposite of 2022. While there’s still a long way to go and an even higher degree of healing to be had before assets like bitcoin are once again at their November 2021 highs, the space appears to be turning itself around from the horrible bearish conditions it faced during the previous 12 months.</p>
<p>2022 was arguably the worst year on record for crypto. During that time, assets like bitcoin lost more than 70 percent of their value, and they crashed and burned like nobody’s business. This led to the entire space losing more than $2 trillion in overall valuation. For many, the situation was particularly dire as they had likely put more than they could afford into the space, hoping to get rich over time.</p>
<p>Now, however, the prices of assets like bitcoin appear to be turning themselves around. The currency recently reached a nine-month high of about $28,000 per unit, and while the asset has again been rocked <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cftc-sues-binance-alleging-financial-violations/" data-wpel-link="internal">due to recent</a> (and negative) news surrounding Binance, it’s unlikely the asset will stay down for the count for long.</p>
<p>In the report’s early sections, Jacques Iffland – partner at Lenz &amp; Staehelin and chair of the Capital Markets and Technology Association (CMTA) – explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>Tokenization opens the door to a broad universe of new possibilities, which the financial industry is only starting to comprehend and embrace.</p></blockquote>
<p>Morgan McKenney – chief executive of the Provenance Blockchain Foundation – also threw his two cents into the mix, commenting:</p>
<blockquote><p>Private funds are very restricted in terms of liquidity options, and by natively issuing shares on-chain, they can then open up marketplaces to give investors the opportunity to exit.</p></blockquote>
<h2>This Will Help Crypto Reach Its Ultimate Goal</h2>
<p>Furthermore, the tokenization of various assets could ultimately make them more accessible to the public and thus bring the initial dreams and goals of crypto closer to becoming realities.</p>
<p>The driving force behind crypto was that everyone should have a chance to invest and garner financial services and tools that will allow them to live applicable lives, something that standard financial institutions can often restrict.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/can-bitcoin-assist-in-the-tokenization-of-additional-assets/">Can Bitcoin Assist in the Tokenization of Additional Assets?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/can-bitcoin-assist-in-the-tokenization-of-additional-assets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zero Sync Wants to Ensure the Whole BTC Blockchain Is Verifiable</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/zero-sync-wants-to-ensure-the-whole-btc-blockchain-is-verifiable/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/zero-sync-wants-to-ensure-the-whole-btc-blockchain-is-verifiable/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 13:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robin Linus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zero Sync]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ZK-proofs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77666</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Three computer scientists in Germany have established a new crypto-based, non-profit company in Switzerland called Zero Sync Association. The goal is to help scale bitcoin using what are known as zero-knowledge proofs (ZK-proofs), which have already been hard at work through networks like ETH. Zero Sync Wants to Ensure Everything on the Blockchain Is Provable<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/zero-sync-wants-to-ensure-the-whole-btc-blockchain-is-verifiable/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/zero-sync-wants-to-ensure-the-whole-btc-blockchain-is-verifiable/">Zero Sync Wants to Ensure the Whole BTC Blockchain Is Verifiable</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Three computer scientists in Germany <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/newly-formed-zerosync-association-brings-zero-knowledge-proofs-to-bitcoin/ar-AA19aD0K" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">have established a new</a> crypto-based, non-profit company in Switzerland called Zero Sync Association. The goal is to help scale bitcoin using what are known as zero-knowledge proofs (ZK-proofs), which have already been hard at work through networks like ETH.</p>
<h2>Zero Sync Wants to Ensure Everything on the Blockchain Is Provable</h2>
<p>ZK proofs use cryptography to ensure the validity of information contained within the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/blockchain/" data-wpel-link="internal">blockchain</a> without revealing the data to outside parties or prying eyes. By using such proofs on the bitcoin network, nodes will be able to sync almost instantly rather than taking hours (or even days) like they do now. At the time of writing, the bitcoin blockchain contains roughly 500 gigabytes of data.</p>
<p>A prototype for the network is already in play. Presently, the prototype is validating things such as the ownership of various tokens and transaction histories, though the team behind it hopes things will vastly improve and expand in the coming weeks and months. Zero Sync co-founder Robin Linus explained in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>It&#8217;s very much in the prototype stage, but the grand vision is that you download that one megabyte of proof, and that is as good as if you had downloaded the 500 gigabytes.</p></blockquote>
<p>The bitcoin blockchain has always contained simple payment verification nodes, aka light clients. The concept is even mentioned in the initial BTC whitepaper that was introduced on Halloween of 2008. These nodes are limited and only work on things like mobile phones. They are not currently capable of downloading the entire blockchain. The whitepaper reads as follows:</p>
<blockquote><p>It is possible to verify payments without running a full network node. Verification is reliable as long as honest nodes control the network, but is more vulnerable if the network is overpowered by an attacker.</p></blockquote>
<p>Continuing his interview, Linus said Zero Synch doesn’t simply trust the nodes as suggested in the whitepaper. Rather, the company is set on verifying the actual transactions that occur via the network through cryptographic proof. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>You don&#8217;t have to trust. That is the entire point. The proof proves it to you. That&#8217;s the great invention.</p></blockquote>
<p>Linus has been working with his business partner Lukas George for the past ten months (they started operating the company together in July of last year). The goal was to implement a full proof of the bitcoin blockchain, a subject prominently tackled in George’s graduation thesis.</p>
<h2>How the Founders Met</h2>
<p>The duo then added another co-founder – Tino Steffens – to the mix, and the company was born from there. Linus stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>From there, I started to learn more and more about cryptography. I developed some skills over time, and then Ruben recommended me to Geometry Research. They offered me the opportunity to build STARK proofs for bitcoin, and that&#8217;s also how I got in touch with Lucas.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/zero-sync-wants-to-ensure-the-whole-btc-blockchain-is-verifiable/">Zero Sync Wants to Ensure the Whole BTC Blockchain Is Verifiable</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/zero-sync-wants-to-ensure-the-whole-btc-blockchain-is-verifiable/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Key Breakout Resistance Sits At $120</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-key-breakout-resistance-sits-at-120/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-key-breakout-resistance-sits-at-120/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 03:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78203</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin cash is attempting a recovery wave above the $115 resistance against the US Dollar. The price is now trading near the $118 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $120 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-key-breakout-resistance-sits-at-120/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-key-breakout-resistance-sits-at-120/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Key Breakout Resistance Sits At $120</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin cash is attempting a recovery wave above the $115 resistance against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading near the $118 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $120 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair must clear $120 and $124 to start a steady upward movement in the near term.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin cash price is consolidating above $115 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-extend-losses-below-27000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. BCH/USD could start a fresh surge if it clears the $120 level.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin cash price formed a decent support base above the $112 level. BCH started a decent increase and was able to clear the $115 resistance zone.</p>
<p>The price climbed above the $116.50 resistance level. There was a move above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $136.18 swing high to the $111.66 low. It is now trading near the $118 zone and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-100/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $120 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $120 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $124 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $136.18 swing high to the $111.66 low, above which the price may perhaps rise toward the $130 level. Any more gains above $130 could set the pace for a move toward the $138 level.</p>
<p>If not, the price might decline again. Immediate support on the downside is near the $115 level. The first major support sits near the $112 level. The next major support is near $110, below which the bears might aim for $102. The next target for them may perhaps be near the $100 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_78204" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Bitcoin-Cash.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78204" class="size-full wp-image-78204" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Bitcoin-Cash.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash Price " width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78204" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Cash Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BCHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Bitcoin Cash’s price is now trading near the $118 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price must clear $120 and $124 to continue higher in the near term.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for BCH/USD is gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BCH/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $115 and $112.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $120 and $124.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-key-breakout-resistance-sits-at-120/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Key Breakout Resistance Sits At $120</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-key-breakout-resistance-sits-at-120/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CFTC Sues Binance Alleging Financial Violations</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cftc-sues-binance-alleging-financial-violations/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cftc-sues-binance-alleging-financial-violations/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 17:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CFTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77664</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) is suing Binance and its founder Changpeng Zhao after the crypto exchange allegedly violated the Commodity Exchange Act and other regulations. The CFTC Is Going After Binance The agency claims Binance has had no regard for current financial laws and has been violating them for the past several<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cftc-sues-binance-alleging-financial-violations/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cftc-sues-binance-alleging-financial-violations/">CFTC Sues Binance Alleging Financial Violations</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) is suing Binance and its founder Changpeng Zhao after the crypto <a href="https://siliconangle.com/2023/03/27/cftc-sues-cryptocurrency-exchange-binance-founder-changpeng-zhao/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">exchange allegedly violated</a> the Commodity Exchange Act and other regulations.</p>
<h2>The CFTC Is Going After Binance</h2>
<p>The agency claims Binance has had no regard for current financial laws and has been violating them for the past several years. Heads of the CFTC are now seeking financial penalties and a permanent ban in the United States. CFTC chair Rostin Behnam claimed in a recent statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>For years, Binance knew they were violating CFTC rules, working actively to both keep the money flowing and avoid compliance. This should be a warning to anyone in the digital asset world that the CFTC will not tolerate willful avoidance of U.S. law.</p></blockquote>
<p>Gretchen Lowe – principal deputy director and chief counsel to the CFTC’s enforcement division – also threw her two cents into the mix, commenting:</p>
<blockquote><p>The defendants’ own emails and chats reflect that Binance’s compliance efforts have been a sham and Binance deliberately chose – over and over – to place profits over following the law.</p></blockquote>
<p>Binance is the world’s largest and most popular digital currency trading platform per its daily trading volume. In just the last few days alone, the company is alleged to have overseen roughly $9 billion in digital transactions. The company is also believed to have about 90 million users in multiple countries.</p>
<p>In its lawsuit against the exchange, the CFTC alleges that Binance is run by various corporate entities rather than a single governing body. This is designed to reportedly help it evade regulation and committee oversights. Right now, the lawsuit names three separate companies and/or divisions of Binance within its pages. They are Binance Holdings Ltd., Binance Holdings (IE) Ltd., and Finance (Services) Holdings Ltd.</p>
<p>The action has sent ripples throughout the space, with the price of bitcoin immediately descending from its nine-month high of around $28K to the high $26K range after the CFTC made the announcement. Ed Moya – an analyst at Oanda – <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-falls-after-cftc-sues-crypto-exchange-binance-for-allegedly-breaking-trading-rules/ar-AA198urA" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">commented on the situation</a>, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>Many knew Binance had a bullseye on its back, but this is still unnerving some crypto traders. Binance&#8217;s success is needed to ensure a good part of the cryptoverse can grow.</p></blockquote>
<h2>So Many Agencies Are Attacking Crypto</h2>
<p>Dessislava Aubert – an analyst at crypto data provider Kaiko – said Binance is the world’s largest crypto exchange, and thus any regulatory action against it would likely have hugely negative effects on the rest of the space.</p>
<p>It seems like lately federal agencies just want to prosecute and criminalize crypto companies as much as possible. Look at the recent track record of the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), for example. The group has nailed companies like Kraken, slapping <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/" data-wpel-link="internal">them with heavy fines</a> and ending their staking divisions, and it’s now going <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">after Coinbase</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cftc-sues-binance-alleging-financial-violations/">CFTC Sues Binance Alleging Financial Violations</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cftc-sues-binance-alleging-financial-violations/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kristi Noem Crypto Regulation Veto Remains in Place</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kristi-noem-crypto-regulation-veto-is-upheld/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kristi-noem-crypto-regulation-veto-is-upheld/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 15:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto-regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kristi Noem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Dakota]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77661</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, South Dakota Governor Kristi Noem vetoed a bill that would have paved the way for crypto regulation in her state. It was recently announced that the House of South Dakota has failed to override the veto, and thus digital currency legislation will not be making its way into the state anytime soon.<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kristi-noem-crypto-regulation-veto-is-upheld/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kristi-noem-crypto-regulation-veto-is-upheld/">Kristi Noem Crypto Regulation Veto Remains in Place</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, South Dakota Governor Kristi Noem vetoed a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/governor-kristi-noem-vetoes-central-bank-digital-currency-bill/" data-wpel-link="internal">bill that would have</a> paved the way for crypto regulation in her state. It was recently announced that the House of South Dakota has failed to override the veto, and thus digital currency legislation <a href="https://abcnews.go.com/Business/wireStory/south-dakota-govs-veto-cryptocurrency-regulations-upheld-98160004" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">will not be making its</a> way into the state anytime soon.</p>
<h2>Kristi Noem Is Getting Her Way</h2>
<p>The bill had initially passed through the legislative branch, though it failed to hold any ground after Noem initiated the veto. The new votes for the bill were 37 to 30. In a statement, Noem commented on why she felt the bill did not present a plausible future for the state of South Dakota. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>It would be imprudent to create regulations governing something that does not yet exist. More importantly, South Dakota should not open the door to a potential future overreach by the federal government.</p></blockquote>
<p>There are likely many hidden reasons for the veto, a big one being that cryptocurrency was initially designed to be ungovernable. Digital currencies were built to give the unbanked a chance and to prevent those that couldn’t gain access to standard financial products and services from being turned out in the streets. In other words, it didn’t matter what your past credit history was. So long as you had an internet connection and a digital wallet, you could begin purchasing, selling, and trading assets as you saw fit.</p>
<p>The idea of crypto regulation ultimately goes against this narrative as it would allow government heads to step in and have a say over what people could do with their money. In addition, Noem is also likely not a fan of who’s in charge of the federal government at this time, and thus doesn’t want to give Joe Biden and his nation-hating cronies the chance to have more control over people’s financial lives.</p>
<p>Ever since <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">the fall of FTX</a>, many individuals working within the federal government have renewed calls for crypto regulation. This would all be fine and dandy if you were to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-gave-a-lot-of-money-to-democrats-what-will-they-do-with-it/" data-wpel-link="internal">ignore the fact that many</a> of them accepted bribes from Sam Bankman-Fried, the man tasked with running the exchange. Now that he’s out of the picture and they’ve gotten the extra money they wanted, they suddenly want to step in and regulate the space. The whole situation feels and looks a bit fishy.</p>
<h2>Crypto Regulation&#8230; Will It Come Anyway?</h2>
<p>The bill’s sponsor – House Republican Hugh Bartels – believes crypto regulation will eventually enter the U.S. within a set period, and he’s not allowing this little setback to bring down his confidence or his mentality. He said in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>The misconception is that this bill is authorizing [a] central bank digital currency. It’s just setting up a way to do business with it.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kristi-noem-crypto-regulation-veto-is-upheld/">Kristi Noem Crypto Regulation Veto Remains in Place</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kristi-noem-crypto-regulation-veto-is-upheld/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX&#8217;s Sam Bankman-Fried Faces New Bribery Charges</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftxs-sam-bankman-fried-faces-new-bribery-charges/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftxs-sam-bankman-fried-faces-new-bribery-charges/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 13:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bribery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77658</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sam Bankman-Fried – the former crypto executive behind popular digital currency trading platform FTX – has been charged with violating the Foreign Corrupt Practices Act by allegedly attempting to bribe officials from China. Sam Bankman-Fried Is Facing New Charges Prosecutors claim that Sam Bankman-Fried attempted to send money to Chinese officials so they would unfreeze<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftxs-sam-bankman-fried-faces-new-bribery-charges/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftxs-sam-bankman-fried-faces-new-bribery-charges/">FTX&#8217;s Sam Bankman-Fried Faces New Bribery Charges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sam Bankman-Fried – the former crypto executive behind popular digital currency trading platform FTX – has been <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/sam-bankman-fried-directed-40m-cryptocurrency-bribe-to-chinese-officials-federal-prosecutors-allege/ar-AA19b1Zn" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">charged with violating</a> the Foreign Corrupt Practices Act by allegedly attempting to bribe officials from China.</p>
<h2>Sam Bankman-Fried Is Facing New Charges</h2>
<p>Prosecutors claim that Sam Bankman-Fried attempted to send money to Chinese officials so they would unfreeze roughly $1 billion under his name. The money is being held through his secondary company Alameda Research, a crypto trading hedge fund. With these new charges, Sam Bankman-Fried is now facing approximately 13 separate counts in court.</p>
<p>The indictment of the crypto executive reads as follows:</p>
<blockquote><p>In or about 2021, Samuel Bankman-Fried, a/k/a/ SBF, the defendant, authorized and directed a bribe of at least $40 million to one or more Chinese government officials. The purpose of this bribe was to influence and induce one or more Chinese government officials to unfreeze certain Alameda trading accounts containing over $1 billion in cryptocurrency, which had been frozen by Chinese authorities. Bankman-Fried and others sought to regain access to the assets to fund additional Alameda trading activity, to assist Bankman-Fried and Alameda in obtaining and retaining business.</p></blockquote>
<p>US attorney for the Southern District of New York Damian Williams – who has a knack for showing up when crypto cases like these arise – also threw his two cents into the mix, claiming:</p>
<blockquote><p>We are hard at work and will remain so until justice is done.</p></blockquote>
<p>Court documents purport that the assets held within Alameda were frozen as part of an ongoing investigation into a particular “Alameda trading counterparty,” and that SBF and several of his constituents made various attempts to get the money unlocked for private use. Some of the methods utilized – according to the indictment – included retaining attorneys to advocate in the country for the funds to be unfrozen and communicating with Chinese exchanges.</p>
<p>Sam Bankman-Fried is alleged to have tried to have the money unfrozen for months, but with no success at first. The indictment further states:</p>
<blockquote><p>As a result, in or about November 2021, Bankman-Fried caused a bribe payment of cryptocurrency then worth approximately $40 million to be transferred from Alameda’s main trading account to a private cryptocurrency wallet. At or around the time of the $40 million bribe payment, the accounts were unfrozen.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Long History of Crime?</h2>
<p>Sam Bankman-Fried is currently awaiting trial for <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-to-await-trial-at-his-parents-house/" data-wpel-link="internal">fraud at his parents’</a> Northern California home after he was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftxs-disgraced-founder-has-been-arrested/" data-wpel-link="internal">arrested in the Bahamas</a>, where FTX was initially situated. It is reported that SBF utilized customer funds to pay off loans taken out by Alameda Research and to invest in luxury real estate for himself and his fellow exchange executives.</p>
<p>FTX initially collapsed and entered <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">bankruptcy proceedings</a> in November of last year after it was reported the company was enduring <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">a harsh liquidity crunch</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftxs-sam-bankman-fried-faces-new-bribery-charges/">FTX&#8217;s Sam Bankman-Fried Faces New Bribery Charges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftxs-sam-bankman-fried-faces-new-bribery-charges/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EOS Price Analysis: Signs of Recovery Above $1.05</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-signs-of-recovery-above-1-05/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-signs-of-recovery-above-1-05/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 05:08:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EOS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78193</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>EOS price is trading in a bearish zone above the $0.98 support against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $1.05 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $1.015 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-signs-of-recovery-above-1-05/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-signs-of-recovery-above-1-05/">EOS Price Analysis: Signs of Recovery Above $1.05</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>EOS price is trading in a bearish zone above the $0.98 support against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $1.05 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $1.015 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could start a recovery wave if it clears the $1.05 and $1.08 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>EOS price is struggling below $1.08 against the US Dollar, unlike <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-extend-losses-below-27000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. The price might attempt to recover if there is a clear move above $1.050.</em></p>
<h2>EOS Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, EOS price range moves below the $1.12 resistance against the US Dollar. The price remained stable above the $0.98 and $1.00 support levels.</p>
<p>A low is formed near $0.9747 and the price is now attempting an upside correction. There was a move above the $1.015 and $1.02 resistance levels. Besides, there was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $1.015 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair.</p>
<p>The price is now trading below $1.05 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bears-in-control-below-1-10/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $1.03 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $1.05 level or the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $1.298 swing high to the $0.8747 low, above which the price might test the $1.08 level. Any more gains might send the price towards the $1.12 level.</p>
<p>The next resistance might be $1.135 or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $1.298 swing high to the $0.8747 low. On the downside, immediate support is near the $1.00 level.</p>
<p>The next key support is near the $0.98 level. If there is a downside break below the $0.980 support, the price could test the $0.95 support in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_78194" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/EOS.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78194" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78194" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/EOS.png" alt="EOS Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78194" class="wp-caption-text">EOS Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/EOSUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, EOS price is now trading below the $1.05 level and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could start a recovery wave if it clears the $1.05 and $1.08 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4-hours MACD – The MACD for EOS/USD is losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4-hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $1.00 and $0.98.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $1.05 and $1.08.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-signs-of-recovery-above-1-05/">EOS Price Analysis: Signs of Recovery Above $1.05</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-signs-of-recovery-above-1-05/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Indicators Point Fresh Increase To $100</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-indicators-point-fresh-increase-to-100/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-indicators-point-fresh-increase-to-100/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 03:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78189</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin settled below the $90 resistance zone against the US Dollar. LTC price is now trading below $90 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major contracting triangle forming with resistance near $89.20 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could start a decent<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-indicators-point-fresh-increase-to-100/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-indicators-point-fresh-increase-to-100/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Indicators Point Fresh Increase To $100</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Litecoin settled below the $90 resistance zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>LTC price is now trading below $90 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major contracting triangle forming with resistance near $89.20 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could start a decent increase if it clears the $92 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Litecoin price is struggling below $90 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-extend-losses-below-27000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. LTC price could continue to decline if it stays below the $92 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few hours, there was a minor increase in Bitcoin, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-faces-increase-in-bearish-pressure/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Ethereum</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-could-dive-below-0-44/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Ripple</a>, and Litecoin against the US Dollar. Earlier, LTC settled below the $90 resistance zone to move into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>The price broke the $88 support zone and tested the $85 support. A low is formed near $85.13 and the price is now attempting a recovery wave. There was a move above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $91.46 swing high to the $85.13 low.</p>
<p>It is now trading below $90 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $49.00 zone.</p>
<p>There is also a major contracting triangle forming with resistance near $89.20 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $91.46 swing high to the $85.13 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance sits near the $90 level. The main resistance is near the $92 level. A clear move above the $92 level could pump the price toward the $95 level or even $98. The next major resistance could be $100.</p>
<p>On the downside, immediate support is near the $86.60 level. The next key support is near the $85.00 level. If there is a downside break below the $85.00 support, the price could accelerate lower toward the $80 level in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_78190" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Litecoin.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78190" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78190" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Litecoin.png" alt="Litecoin (LTC) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78190" class="wp-caption-text">Litecoin (LTC) Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Litecoin price is clearly trading below $90 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $92 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LTC/USD is now losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $86.60 and $85.00.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $90.00 and $92.00.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-indicators-point-fresh-increase-to-100/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Indicators Point Fresh Increase To $100</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-indicators-point-fresh-increase-to-100/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
