<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 06:01:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/cropped-fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Mark Cuban Bashes the SEC for Its Actions Against Coinbase</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-bashes-the-sec-for-its-actions-against-coinbase/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 15:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mark Cuban]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78788</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Like most investors (and everyday Americans), billionaire Mark Cuban is not happy with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). In fact, he’s downright angry with the institution and says it’s abusing its power. Mark Cuban Targets the SEC in Twitter Slam In a recent interview, the owner of the Dallas Mavericks basketball team criticized the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-bashes-the-sec-for-its-actions-against-coinbase/">Mark Cuban Bashes the SEC for Its Actions Against Coinbase</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Like most investors (and everyday Americans), billionaire Mark Cuban is <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/mark-cuban-crypto-coinbase-sec-lawsuit-binance-regulation-enforcement-2023-6">not happy with the</a> Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). In fact, he’s downright angry with the institution and says it’s abusing its power.</p>
<h2>Mark Cuban Targets the SEC in Twitter Slam</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, the owner of the Dallas Mavericks basketball team criticized the agency’s decision to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-hit-with-sec-lawsuit-says-it-operated-as-an-exchange-broker/">go after Coinbase</a>, the biggest and most popular crypto exchange in the U.S. He says the SEC is doing nothing to help financial companies grow, nor is it helping to boost innovation. Instead of filing a lawsuit, he says the agency should have tried to help the company regulate itself and fall into compliance if it was disobeying present rules.</p>
<p>Cuban took to Twitter to accuse the SEC of not wanting to help crypto firms in any way, shape, or form. Rather, all it’s interested in doing is shutting the doors on them and preventing them from getting any further within America’s borders. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>They don&#8217;t want to help companies get to compliance. They want to challenge them to get to compliance. They are full of lawyers. Lawyers want to litigate.</p></blockquote>
<p>He further stated that the present Coinbase lawsuit – as well as the many other actions it’s taken over the past several weeks – is exactly why most people in the country don’t trust the agency or hold it in the brightest light. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>As it is, no one wants to talk to the SEC because no one trusts them for fear of being in the same situation as Coinbase finds itself.</p></blockquote>
<p>The SEC has long taken a road of regulation through enforcement. It hasn’t bothered to help carve out any rules or legislation pertaining to crypto agencies or new financial firms. Rather, it has an attitude of, “We’re coming after you because we think you’re smaller and weaker.” It behaves very much like a schoolyard bully and tries to pick on people rather than reason with them or get to know them better.</p>
<p>Aside from Coinbase, the SEC shocked the world a few weeks back when it announced it was charging crypto exchange platform Binance <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sues-binance-alleges-selling-of-illegal-securities/">with several crimes</a> including selling and offering unregistered securities and mixing customer and company funds. In addition, the company also went after Kraken, a popular crypto exchange in Northern California.</p>
<h2>So Many Companies Have Been Victimized</h2>
<p>Choosing to settle with the agency, Kraken <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/">was forced to part</a> with a $30 million penalty fee. It was also made to end all its staking activities and services.</p>
<p>As it turns out, the SEC’s actions are really starting to rub certain members of Congress the wrong way. Not long ago, House conservatives put <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/house-republicans-introduce-bill-to-remove-sec-chair-gary-gensler-restructure-agency/ar-AA1cs0X1">out a new bill that</a> if passed, would see the full restructuring of the SEC and the firing of Gary Gensler.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-bashes-the-sec-for-its-actions-against-coinbase/">Mark Cuban Bashes the SEC for Its Actions Against Coinbase</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will Blockchain Survive? Analysts Weigh In</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/will-blockchain-survive-analysts-weigh-in/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 13:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Luke Stokes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78786</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are bitcoin and blockchain considered practical technologies, or are they more based in fantasy? Recently, a group of analysts sat around and discussed the matter to see whether blockchain and the crypto aboard it have legitimate futures in the United States and other developed countries. What Will Happen with Blockchain? Up until this point, there [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/will-blockchain-survive-analysts-weigh-in/">Will Blockchain Survive? Analysts Weigh In</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are bitcoin and blockchain considered practical technologies, or are they more based in fantasy? Recently, a group of <a href="https://www.thestreet.com/cryptocurrency/bitcoin-and-blockchain-seeking-the-ultimate-utopia-or-a-practical-utility">analysts sat around and</a> discussed the matter to see whether blockchain and the crypto aboard it have legitimate futures in the United States and other developed countries.</p>
<h2>What Will Happen with Blockchain?</h2>
<p>Up until this point, there have been discussions about blockchain and how it could potentially serve purposes in other industries that have nothing to do with crypto or digital assets. Some of these industries include healthcare, manufacturing, and recently (as we discussed yesterday) <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/itoka-is-looking-to-register-all-ai-music-on-the-blockchain/">AI music creation</a>.</p>
<p>However, these ideas have not really been tested that much considering for the most part, blockchain is still predominantly considered the technology behind crypto assets like bitcoin. These assets have done a lot, but they are still considered part of a niche industry, and blockchain has had a very difficult time breaking out of the shackles the crypto industry has placed on its wrists.</p>
<p>For this reason, there are many experts out there that don’t believe blockchain has much of a future, though there are others that continue to advocate for it and say it’s the technology of all technologies. So, which sentiment is correct? The discussion mentioned above was hosted by Rob Nelson. As the anchor of the roundtable, he commented that bitcoin is very “utopian,” and while the ideals behind blockchain may be noble in intent, enacting them would be extremely difficult. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin&#8217;s ultimate thing was sovereignty&#8230; It&#8217;s very utopian, and one of the problems with utopianism is it&#8217;s very hard to see it enacted&#8230; Bitcoin is consensus-based, which creates a huge problem.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also said that there wasn’t much that could be considered special about bitcoin, and he said it’s about as revolutionary as Gmail. In the end, he doesn’t think BTC has much practical use, and for this reason, he doesn’t see it going far.</p>
<p>Luke Stokes – managing director at the Foundation for Inter Wallet Operability – was quick to oppose his words and challenge him on the subject. He stated that a “killer app” would be needed for blockchain to truly come full circle and be seen as the awesome technology it is. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>We know we&#8217;ve never had the ability to have network and data completely consensus across the whole world. Everyone agrees, but we just don&#8217;t really know what to do with it yet&#8230; We&#8217;re still waiting for that to happen.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Keeping the Middle Ground</h2>
<p>Max Smotritskiy – co-founder of Crypto Oracle – believes that while blockchain is indeed strong, it needs to be made stronger. In other words, there’s a lot of work to be done before it can accomplish all that everyone’s promising it will. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I&#8217;m not for hyper blockchainization of anything.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/will-blockchain-survive-analysts-weigh-in/">Will Blockchain Survive? Analysts Weigh In</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Merkeleon Introduces Cutting-Edge Crypto Derivatives Trading Software</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/merkeleon-introduces-cutting-edge-crypto-derivatives-trading-software/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 06:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79478</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Merkeleon unveils crypto derivatives trading software, introducing perpetual swaps for advanced trading opportunities Merkeleon, a leading provider of blockchain-based solutions, is proud to announce the launch of its progressive software for crypto derivatives trading platform that will enhance the digital asset trading landscape. The new software introduces the forward-thinking concept of perpetual swaps to empower [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/merkeleon-introduces-cutting-edge-crypto-derivatives-trading-software/">Merkeleon Introduces Cutting-Edge Crypto Derivatives Trading Software</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em><strong>Merkeleon unveils crypto derivatives trading software, introducing perpetual swaps for advanced trading opportunities</strong></em></p>
<p>Merkeleon, a leading provider of blockchain-based solutions, is proud to announce the launch of its progressive software for <a href="https://www.merkeleon.com/crypto-derivatives-trading-platform/">crypto derivatives trading platform</a> that will enhance the digital asset trading landscape. The new software introduces the forward-thinking concept of perpetual swaps to empower traders with innovative trading instruments and unlock a world of endless possibilities.</p>
<p>Merkeleon&#8217;s crypto derivatives trading software introduces perpetual swaps, a groundbreaking derivative product that allows traders to speculate on the price movements of cryptocurrencies without the constraints of expiration dates or roll-over costs. This novel offering opens up a new realm of opportunities for traders by providing continuous trading, enhanced liquidity, unparalleled flexibility.</p>
<p>By harnessing the power of perpetual swaps, traders can magnify trading positions, amplify potential returns and benefit from leveraged trading strategies. The software&#8217;s intuitive user interface and robust trading infrastructure enable traders of all levels to easily monitor positions and manage risk effectively.</p>
<p>‘Our team is thrilled to introduce crypto derivatives trading software, featuring the perpetual swaps,’ says Alexander Riedinger, CEO of Merkeleon. ‘We believe that our solution will galvanize existing businesses of our partners and clients. It will also reveal new opportunities for entrepreneurs who want to start a crypto trading business with advanced inventory for traders. With our state-of-the-art software, traders can explore the full potential of perpetual swaps.’</p>
<p>Merkeleon&#8217;s crypto derivatives trading software is built on a secure and reliable infrastructure that guarantees a seamless trading experience for users. The software incorporates sophisticated risk management tools for traders to control their positions and exposure. Merkeleon&#8217;s dedicated developers provide comprehensive technical support to ensure the software&#8217;s full potential for traders.</p>
<h4>About Merkeleon:</h4>
<p>Merkeleon is a leading provider of blockchain-based solutions. The company specializes in <a href="https://www.merkeleon.com/cryptocurrency-exchange-software/">cryptocurrency exchange software</a>, <a href="https://www.merkeleon.com/white-label-crypto-wallet/">white label crypto wallet software</a>, solutions for trading platforms and online auctions. With a commitment to innovation, security and user experience, Merkeleon inspires businesses worldwide to harness the power of blockchain technology.</p>
<p><strong>Press Contact</strong></p>
<p>Company: Merkeleon<br />
Contact Person: Alexander Riedinger<br />
Website: <a href="https://www.merkeleon.com">https://www.merkeleon.com</a><br />
Email: order@merkeleon.com<br />
City: Pöttelsdorf<br />
Country: Austria</p>
<p><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/merkeleon-software/">Linkedin</a><br />
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/Merkeleon/">Facebook</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/merkeleon">Twitter</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Image: <em><a href="https://www.merkeleon.com/blog/eu-crypto-regulation-mica/">Merkeleon</a></em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/merkeleon-introduces-cutting-edge-crypto-derivatives-trading-software/">Merkeleon Introduces Cutting-Edge Crypto Derivatives Trading Software</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Risk of Downside Thrust Below $230</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-downside-thrust-below-230/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 03:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79475</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline below the $255 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below the $250 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $248 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-downside-thrust-below-230/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Risk of Downside Thrust Below $230</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline below the $255 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below the $250 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $248 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it stays below the $254 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin cash price is declining below the $250 zone against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. BCH/USD could extend losses if there is a close below $230.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin cash price remained in a bearish zone below the $285 and $280 resistance levels. BCH traded below the $265 support level to move further into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>There was a clear move below the $255 and $250 support levels. The pair even spiked below the $235 level. A low is formed near $231.62 and the price is now consolidating losses. It attempted a move above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $295.00 swing high to the $231.62 low.</p>
<p>However, the bears seem to be active near $254 and $255. BCH is now trading below the $250 zone and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bears-in-action-below-250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. There is also a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $248 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair.</p>
<p>The next key resistance is near $264 and the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $295.00 swing high to the $231.62 low. Any more gains above $115 could set the pace for a move toward the $285 level.</p>
<p>If there is a move above the $285 resistance, the price could rise toward the $295 zone. If not, the price might continue lower below $235. Immediate support on the downside is near the $230 zone. The next major support is near the $225 level, below which the bears might aim for $212.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79476" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79476" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-3.png"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-79476" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-3.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-3.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-3-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-3-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-3-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-3-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-3-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-3-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79476" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Cash Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BCHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, Bitcoin cash price is now trading below the $250 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $254 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for BCH/USD is losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BCH/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $230 and $225.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $254 and $264.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-downside-thrust-below-230/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Risk of Downside Thrust Below $230</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The SEC is Making Crypto Investors (and Platforms) Very Nervous</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-is-making-crypto-investors-very-nervous/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Yuya Hasegawa]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78783</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Many crypto investors are working hard to get rid of their altcoins out of fear that several of them are going to get delisted thanks to ongoing action from the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). SEC Action is Making Traders Wary The financial agency has been working hard to practically eliminate crypto altogether from the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-is-making-crypto-investors-very-nervous/">The SEC is Making Crypto Investors (and Platforms) Very Nervous</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Many crypto investors are working hard to get rid <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/06/13/crypto-braced-for-a-24-billion-earthquake-after-sec-bombshell-hit-the-price-of-bitcoin-and-ethereum/?sh=5c047d515762">of their altcoins</a> out of fear that several of them are going to get delisted thanks to ongoing action from the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<h2>SEC Action is Making Traders Wary</h2>
<p>The financial agency has been working hard to practically eliminate crypto altogether from the American monetary spectrum. There have already been multiple lawsuits filed against some of the nation’s leading digital currency companies including <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sues-binance-alleges-selling-of-illegal-securities/">Binance</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-hit-with-sec-lawsuit-says-it-operated-as-an-exchange-broker/">Coinbase</a>, and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/">Kraken</a>, and there are many traders out there that are worried about what could arrive in the coming weeks and months as the SEC potentially ramps up its efforts.</p>
<p>There are also many companies out there that don’t want to be tangled up with crypto assets that could allegedly be considered securities in the coming future. For example, trading application Robinhood announced that it will no longer be selling Cardano, Solana, and Matic. In a statement, the company said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We regularly review the crypto we offer on Robinhood.</p></blockquote>
<p>Leading exchange e-Toro also said that it’s going to end future support for Matic, Algorand, and Decentraland. All three of these tokens have market caps that come to a combined total of $24 billion, so one can assume the delisting activity is not going to produce solid results for the space. On Twitter, the company explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>We are committed to working closely with regulators around the world to shape the future of the crypto industry and champion access for the ordinary investor.</p></blockquote>
<p>Yuya Hasegawa – bitcoin and crypto market analyst at Bit Bank in Tokyo – said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The SEC’s legal battle against Binance and Coinbase has created a ripple effect where other U.S. virtual asset service providers began to halt certain services and delist some trading pairs out of concern for [the] SEC’s legal actions. Particularly, Robinhood’s decision on Friday to delist Cardano, Polygon, and Solana had a noticeable impact on the prices of those tokens and some other altcoins. Bitcoin was [also] affected, but its decline was limited compared to others, and the price has been supported by its February high. Bitcoin has been holding it together relatively well while the majority of altcoins suffered huge losses last week, but it is in for a potentially quite precarious week as more bad news could come up anytime regarding [the] SEC’s legal action, and the wider financial markets brace for [the looming Fed interest rate decision].</p></blockquote>
<h2>Gary Gensler&#8217;s Thoughts (Originally) on Crypto</h2>
<p>As discussed earlier today, the SEC has not always been after crypto like it is now. Gary Gensler – the present head of the SEC – has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gary-gensler-at-one-time-thought-differently-about-crypto-as-video-footage-shows/">commented in the past</a> that assets like BTC, ETH, and LTC don’t fall into the securities category.</p>
<p>In fact, he was convinced that roughly three quarters of the crypto assets out there don’t classify as securities.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-is-making-crypto-investors-very-nervous/">The SEC is Making Crypto Investors (and Platforms) Very Nervous</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Itoka Wants to Use Blockchain to Register All AI-Based Jingles</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/itoka-is-looking-to-register-all-ai-music-on-the-blockchain/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 15:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI-generated music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Itoka]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78778</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Itoka is a new platform that’s working to ensure all AI-generated music can be licensed and registered via the blockchain. Itoka Uses Blockchain to Register AI Songs AI-generated tunes are becoming more and more common. Who would have thought that a time would arrive when someone could literally create whatever notes they want without singing, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/itoka-is-looking-to-register-all-ai-music-on-the-blockchain/">Itoka Wants to Use Blockchain to Register All AI-Based Jingles</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Itoka is a new platform that’s working to ensure all AI-generated music <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/itoka-wants-to-license-ai-generated-music-via-the-blockchain/ar-AA1cuS43">can be licensed and registered</a> via the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/blockchain/">blockchain</a>.</p>
<h2>Itoka Uses Blockchain to Register AI Songs</h2>
<p>AI-generated tunes are becoming more and more common. Who would have thought that a time would arrive when someone could literally create whatever notes they want without singing, playing an instrument, or knowing how to read music? We’ve come so far that we’re practically reaching a day and age where nobody needs to do anything, and they could still be successful and have huge careers.</p>
<p>Not long ago, Itoka was accepted into the Allen Institute for AI”s startup incubation program. Blockchain, as we all know, is predominantly considered to be the technology behind cryptocurrency, though there are many advocates out there that seem to believe it can be applied to other industries such as healthcare and manufacturing. Perhaps music registration and licensing can be another.</p>
<p>Co-founded by Malcolm Yang and Yihao Chen, the company seeks to “tokenize” music, therefore allowing all content creators to independently license their material and receive due compensation every time their music is played or used. Itoka puts temporary holds on the ownership of songs and works to prevent plagiarism on all licensed or registered material.</p>
<p>The co-founders explained in a joint statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>Itoka is a decentralized music platform we developed to enable data self-sovereignty, the permanence of music storage, digital rights management, global music accessibility, and creator governance. We establish a new paradigm for copyright protection that doesn’t rely on the physical copyright office to enforce the legal status, but rather on code-operated smart contracts.</p></blockquote>
<p>The company also provides tools that customers can use to enhance their tunes. There are even products and programs available to individuals that have no experience whatsoever in this field, and they’re looking to create AI-generated music for the first time. The co-founders said:</p>
<blockquote><p>In the future, everyone will have the power to produce music, and there will be a massive amount of quality music produced every day for various purposes. As music production becomes democratized, the establishment of the current music industry and its monopoly will be significantly undermined. This will urge people to rethink creativity and artistry in content creation.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Working with Game Developers</h2>
<p>They completed their statement by claiming that they’re looking to target game developers as their main audience members, and the company has partnered with a firm called Canva for game content licensing purposes. They said:</p>
<blockquote><p>In the future, we will be more than happy to move on to other customer sectors and provide the most-fitting features and solutions. There are some AI-friendly musicians who’d like to help us push the boundaries of technology and music creativity, and we sincerely hope that we can achieve greatness with them together</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/itoka-is-looking-to-register-all-ai-music-on-the-blockchain/">Itoka Wants to Use Blockchain to Register All AI-Based Jingles</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gary Gensler, at One Time, Thought Differently About Crypto as Video Footage Shows</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gary-gensler-at-one-time-thought-differently-about-crypto-as-video-footage-shows/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 13:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78776</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Some interesting video footage from several years back has resurfaced that’s making people see Gary Gensler and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) a tad differently. Gary Gensler and His Original Feelings Towards Crypto In the video, Gensler – not yet in charge of the financial agency – told his audience of investors he thinks [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gary-gensler-at-one-time-thought-differently-about-crypto-as-video-footage-shows/">Gary Gensler, at One Time, Thought Differently About Crypto as Video Footage Shows</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Some interesting video footage from several years back has <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/sec-s-gensler-seen-telling-hedge-funds-that-ethereum-and-litecoin-are-not-securities-in-2018-video/ar-AA1csLWZ">resurfaced that’s making</a> people see Gary Gensler and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) a tad differently.</p>
<h2>Gary Gensler and His Original Feelings Towards Crypto</h2>
<p>In the video, Gensler – not yet in charge of the financial agency – told his audience of investors he thinks four cryptocurrencies – bitcoin, bitcoin cash, Ethereum, and Litecoin – are not securities, but things didn’t quite stop there. He also mentioned he doesn’t think about three quarters (75 percent) of the altcoins out there fall into the securities category.</p>
<p>The video is from the year 2018. Gensler explains in the footage:</p>
<blockquote><p>Over 70 percent of the crypto market is bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin, [and] bitcoin cash. Why did I name those four? They’re not securities. Three quarters of this [digital asset] market are not securities.</p></blockquote>
<p>The footage is making many crypto investors angry at the time of writing… as it should be. Gensler, like everyone in the Biden administration, has sought to end the reign of crypto in America because this is the one aspect of finance that he and his nation-hating associates cannot control. The thing about bitcoin and crypto is they were not built to be overseen the way standard or traditional banks are.</p>
<p>This time around, it’s the people (the users) who are in charge. So long as they have a digital wallet and an internet connection, a person can get engaged in crypto trading and use the assets to garner everyday items they’ll need for themselves and their families. This is the opposite of the situation surrounding banks, where literally everything you do is monitored by a third party or wandering pair of eyes.</p>
<p>Over the past several months, the SEC and Gensler have done everything in their power to take down the country’s largest crypto businesses. There have been multiple lawsuits filed against leading exchanges like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sues-binance-alleges-selling-of-illegal-securities/">Binance</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-hit-with-sec-lawsuit-says-it-operated-as-an-exchange-broker/">Coinbase</a>, and the latter is working hard to prove itself and fight back, as executives claim to have been working with representatives of the SEC over a nine-year period to ensure the company always remained compliant.</p>
<p>Other names, like Kraken, have also fallen victim. Recently, the exchange was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/">forced to part with</a> a $30 million penalty fee and end all its staking activities and practices.</p>
<h2>So Many Attempts to Shut Crypto Out</h2>
<p>When Gensler and the SEC aren’t attacking crypto, other members of this administration are. Biden, for example, has sought to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/biden-wants-to-tax-crypto-mining-companies-at-30/">impose a 30 percent</a> tax on all mining companies and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-biden-using-an-obama-era-program-to-ban-btc/">initiate an Obama-era</a> policy that would shut all crypto companies out of standard financial products.</p>
<p>It’s become clear that while Gensler may have felt one way about crypto five years ago, he’s clearly fallen into the Biden agenda of removing all individual liberties and keeping people in line with the federal (tyrannical) regime.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gary-gensler-at-one-time-thought-differently-about-crypto-as-video-footage-shows/">Gary Gensler, at One Time, Thought Differently About Crypto as Video Footage Shows</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EOS Price Analysis: Risk of More Losses Below $0.73</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-0-73/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 05:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EOS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79463</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>EOS price started a fresh decline from the $0.80 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $0.765 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $0.767 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-0-73/">EOS Price Analysis: Risk of More Losses Below $0.73</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>EOS price started a fresh decline from the $0.80 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $0.765 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $0.767 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to decline if it stays below the $0.760 and $0.780 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>EOS price is struggling below $0.760 against the US Dollar, like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. The price might attempt to recover if there is a clear move above $0.760.</em></p>
<h2>EOS Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, EOS price saw a fresh decline from the $0.80 resistance against the US Dollar. The price traded below the $0.765 and $0.750 levels to move into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>Besides, there was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $0.767 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair. The pair even spiked below the $0.730 support. A low is formed near $0.7276 and the price is now consolidating losses.</p>
<p>EOS is trading well below $0.765 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-key-uptrend-support-nearby/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $0.760 level. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.7915 swing high to the $0.7276 low.</p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $0.765 level or the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.7915 swing high to the $0.7276 low. A clear move above the $0.765 level could start a steady increase toward the $0.78 level. The next major resistance might be $0.80. Any more gains might send the price toward the $0.850 level.</p>
<p>On the downside, immediate support is near $0.735. The next key support is near the $0.730 level. If there is a downside break below the $0.730 support, the price could test the $0.705 support in the near term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79464" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79464" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-3.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-79464" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-3.png" alt="EOS Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-3.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-3-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-3-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-3-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-3-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-3-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-3-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79464" class="wp-caption-text">EOS Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/EOSUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, EOS price is now trading below the $0.765 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to decline if it stays below the $0.765 and $0.780 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for EOS/USD is losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $0.730 and $0.705.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $0.765 and $0.800.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-risk-of-more-losses-below-0-73/">EOS Price Analysis: Risk of More Losses Below $0.73</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Fresh Increase Possible Above This Resistance</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-fresh-increase-possible-above-this-resistance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 03:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79459</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin is slowly moving higher from the $88 support against the US Dollar. LTC price is now trading below $92 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $92.00 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-fresh-increase-possible-above-this-resistance/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Fresh Increase Possible Above This Resistance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Litecoin is slowly moving higher from the $88 support against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>LTC price is now trading below $92 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $92.00 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $92 and $95 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Litecoin price is recovering from the $88 zone against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. LTC price could climb again if there is a clear move above $92.</em></p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few sessions, there were mostly range moves in Bitcoin, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-shows-bearish-signs-below-1900/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a>, Ripple, and Litecoin against the US Dollar. Earlier, LTC declined heavily below the $95 pivot level.</p>
<p>The price traded below the $92 and $90 levels. However, the bulls were active near the $88 zone. The price is now attempting a recovery wave and trading above $90. There was a move above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $96.44 swing high to the $87.39 low.</p>
<p>Litecoin is now trading below $92 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $92 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $92.00 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>The trend line is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $96.44 swing high to the $87.39 low. A clear move above the $92 level could push the price toward the $95 zone.</p>
<p>The next major resistance sits near the $98.50 level. Any more gains might send the price toward the $100 level. On the downside, initial support is near the $89.50 level. The next major support is near the $88 level. If there is a downside break below the $88 support, the price could accelerate lower toward the $82 level in the near term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79460" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79460" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-3.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-79460" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-3.png" alt="Litecoin (LTC) Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-3.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-3-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-3-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-3-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-3-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-3-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-3-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79460" class="wp-caption-text">Litecoin (LTC) Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/">chart</a>, Litecoin’s price is trading below $92 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $92 and $95 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LTC/USD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $89.50 and $87.40.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $92 and $95.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-fresh-increase-possible-above-this-resistance/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Fresh Increase Possible Above This Resistance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
