<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 02:28:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Block Fi Is the Latest Crypto Company to Go Bankrupt</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block-fi-is-the-latest-crypto-company-to-go-bankrupt/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block-fi-is-the-latest-crypto-company-to-go-bankrupt/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 17:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bankruptcy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Block Fi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75803</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It’s happened again, folks. Another digital currency company has filed for bankruptcy protection. This time, it’s Block Fi, a crypto lending platform, which was reported to be heading in this direction back in late December. Block Fi Is the Latest Crypto Firm to Crash Ironically, the company was one of the few to be “saved”<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block-fi-is-the-latest-crypto-company-to-go-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block-fi-is-the-latest-crypto-company-to-go-bankrupt/">Block Fi Is the Latest Crypto Company to Go Bankrupt</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It’s happened again, folks. Another digital currency company has filed for bankruptcy protection. This time, it’s Block Fi, a <a href="https://www.npr.org/2022/11/28/1139431115/blockfi-ftx-bankruptcy-chapter-11" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">crypto lending platform</a>, which was reported to be <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-crypto-firm-block-fi-next-in-line-to-file-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">heading in this direction</a> back in late December.</p>
<h2>Block Fi Is the Latest Crypto Firm to Crash</h2>
<p>Ironically, the company <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-discusses-his-bailout-of-crypto-firms/" data-wpel-link="internal">was one of the few</a> to be “saved” by FTX earlier in the year, though now that its savior is crashing and burning before the eyes of the public, Block Fi no longer has what it takes to remain still, and the company is going under like so many others.</p>
<p>In a letter to customers, the company wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>Rest assured, we will continue to work on recovering all obligations owed to Block Fi as promptly as practicable.</p></blockquote>
<p>Prior to the declaration, Block Fi had halted withdrawals and requested that all traders working with its platform refrain from submitting deposits.</p>
<p>The company’s co-founders Zac Prince (CEO) and Flori Marquez (COO) announced that they were troubled by the direction their company was now being forced to take as a direct response to the problems associated with FTX. They wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>We are deeply saddened to see the devastation that is cascading across an industry that we love and believe in, touching the lives of so many people.</p></blockquote>
<p>Many months ago, Block Fi – like so many crypto companies – was dealing with ongoing hardships thanks to the falling prices of the world’s most renowned coins. Bitcoin, for example, which was trading at a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit in November of 2021, has fallen into the $16K range at press time, thus losing more than 70 percent of its value. In total, the crypto space has lost more than $2.2 trillion in valuation.</p>
<p>At the time, the firm was approached by FTX, which proposed specific bailout terms that the enterprise found appropriate. Both Prince and Marquez said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Ultimately, we found a great partner in FTX US, who shares our commitment to clients.</p></blockquote>
<p>Sadly, what’s going on now with FTX is causing heavy ripples throughout the space, and the fiasco surrounding the now disgraced crypto exchange is likely to be labeled as one of the most embarrassing to occur within the borders of digital currency.</p>
<h2>FTX Has Caused Several Problems</h2>
<p>For the past three years, FTX was considered a golden player in the crypto arena, and its founder and head executive – Sam Bankman-Fried – was lauded as a genius by many, but that all faded in mid-November of last year when the exchange said it was experiencing a “<a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">liquidity crunch</a>” and needed cash.</p>
<p>The company approached its larger rival Binance for help, but when that company <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">refused to provide</a> necessary aid, FTX was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">forced into bankruptcy proceedings</a>, and its founder instantly resigned from his position. It was a sad, and altogether <em>scary</em> sight to see.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block-fi-is-the-latest-crypto-company-to-go-bankrupt/">Block Fi Is the Latest Crypto Company to Go Bankrupt</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block-fi-is-the-latest-crypto-company-to-go-bankrupt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Report: Crypto Firm DCG Is Contending with Tons of Debt</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-crypto-firm-dcg-is-contending-with-tons-of-debt/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-crypto-firm-dcg-is-contending-with-tons-of-debt/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 15:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Barry Silbert]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DCG]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75801</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>DCG (Digital Currency Group) – the crypto company that owns Grayscale – is allegedly $2 billion in debt, giving traders and crypto analysts a lot to be anxious about. DCG Is Allegedly Dealing with Tons of Debt Barry Silbert – the man who founded DCG – stated in an interview: We have weathered previous crypto<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-crypto-firm-dcg-is-contending-with-tons-of-debt/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-crypto-firm-dcg-is-contending-with-tons-of-debt/">Report: Crypto Firm DCG Is Contending with Tons of Debt</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DCG (Digital Currency Group) – the crypto company that owns Grayscale – is <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/bitcoin-teeters-grayscale-owner-dcb-reveals-debt-145958704.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">allegedly $2 billion in debt</a>, giving traders and crypto analysts a lot to be anxious about.</p>
<h2>DCG Is Allegedly Dealing with Tons of Debt</h2>
<p>Barry Silbert – the man who founded DCG – stated in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>We have weathered previous crypto winters. While this one may feel more severe, collectively we will come out of it stronger.</p></blockquote>
<p>The goal was to try and calm people’s nerves, though this is easier said than done given that this crypto bear run appears to be unlike anything the space has ever experienced or seen before. Right now, bitcoin – the world’s number one digital currency by market cap – has lost more than 70 percent of its overall value.</p>
<p>In November of 2021, for example, the currency rose to a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit. However, since then, the currency has fallen into the mid-$16K level. Many other digital currencies have followed suit and the space has lost more than $2.2 trillion in overall valuation. It’s a sad, and above all, scary sight to see; one that puts many investors in a state of harsh worry.</p>
<p>The news regarding DCG was first brought to light on Twitter by crypto commentator TradFiWhale, who reported:</p>
<blockquote><p>DCG&#8217;s Grayscale business is extremely valuable. DCG doesn&#8217;t want to fire sale this, so, they will likely let Genesis go under. Genesis likely filing for bankruptcy. I think creditors will eventually get most of [the] money back, and DCG will survive with a black eye and marred reputation.</p></blockquote>
<p>In response to the news getting out, DCG issued its own tweet trying to bring people’s concerns to a lower position. It wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>The impact lies with the lending business at Genesis and does not affect Genesis’ trading or custody businesses. Importantly, this temporary action has no impact on the business operations of DCG and our other wholly owned subsidiaries.</p></blockquote>
<p>Not long ago, Silbert went onto a podcast to try and shed light on the situation. He was asked by the podcast host if Genesis was going to take “cryptocurrency down.” Silbert responded with:</p>
<blockquote><p>Despite the difficult industry conditions, I am as excited as ever about the potential for cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology over the coming decades, and DCG is determined to remain at the forefront.</p></blockquote>
<h2>FTX to Blame?</h2>
<p>The entire crypto space has been suffering since the beginning of 2022. However, things allegedly got a lot worse when last November, golden child FTX – long considered one of the best and most popular digital currency exchanges in the world – fell into oblivion.</p>
<p>The company experienced a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">sudden liquidity crunch</a> that saw it seeking aid from rival Binance. When the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">latter refused to help</a>, the company was forced <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">into bankruptcy</a> and its head executive (Sam Bankman-Fried) resigned from his post.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-crypto-firm-dcg-is-contending-with-tons-of-debt/">Report: Crypto Firm DCG Is Contending with Tons of Debt</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-crypto-firm-dcg-is-contending-with-tons-of-debt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ben Mezrich Is Writing a Book About the NFT Craze</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ben-mezrich-is-writing-a-book-about-the-nft-craze/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ben-mezrich-is-writing-a-book-about-the-nft-craze/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 13:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ben Mezrich]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Winklevoss]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75799</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ben Mezrich is an author who wrote the book, “Bitcoin BTC Billionaires,” which talks about the rise of the Winklevoss Twins from their early days trying to develop what would eventually turn into Facebook to their adult lives as some of the biggest bitcoin bulls out there. Ben Mezrich Is Writing a New NFT Book<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ben-mezrich-is-writing-a-book-about-the-nft-craze/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ben-mezrich-is-writing-a-book-about-the-nft-craze/">Ben Mezrich Is Writing a Book About the NFT Craze</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ben Mezrich is an author who wrote the book, “Bitcoin BTC Billionaires,” which talks about the rise of the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/winklevoss/" data-wpel-link="internal">Winklevoss Twins</a> from their early days trying to develop what would eventually turn into Facebook to their adult lives as some of the biggest bitcoin bulls out there.</p>
<h2>Ben Mezrich Is Writing a New NFT Book</h2>
<p>Right now, the book is <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/personalfinance/e2-80-98bitcoin-billionaires-e2-80-99-author-ben-mezrich-takes-on-amazon-self-publishing/ar-AA14j1Hf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">being adapted into a film</a> and is in pre-production, meaning things are still being planned out and the project is in its earliest stages. Overall, Mezrich has seen many of his books adapted for the screen, and he acknowledged his position of power in a recent interview, commenting:</p>
<blockquote><p>I&#8217;m in a situation right now where I can easily sell anything simply because I have so many things under production.</p></blockquote>
<p>Now, Mezrich is working on a new book that will talk about the non-fungible token (NFT) craze. The novel will be fiction and detail the strife and troubles of an artist, a scammer, and a trader trying to get rich with NFTs. Interestingly, Mezrich has spent some time dealing with NFTs himself, having recently sold roughly 7,000 individual units of personalized (digital) art. At today’s prices, those tokens are worth nearly half a million dollars, and he gave about 2,000 other units away.</p>
<p>Anyone holding those tokens will receive screenplay royalties once his book is optioned into a movie or television program. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>My goal is that the Ben Mezrich NFT project becomes a place where other authors are going to launch book-related projects, and the goal is eventually big-name authors and brand-new authors who maybe would not have had the chance to do something like this are going to be able to rather than just try to send a manuscript off to a publisher, to take the bones of a manuscript, show it to an NFT community, and launch an NFT drop around it. If people like it, you are essentially having the community fund your ability to write a book that the community then owns or buys. I don&#8217;t really see us as competing with publishers as much as Amazon Kindle.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Writing About Very Rich People</h2>
<p>Mezrich is a graduate of Harvard and holds a degree in social studies, which he earned in 1991. He has mostly developed a writing career telling stories about billionaires or rich people that earned their keep through odd or interesting ways. In his interview, he said:</p>
<blockquote><p>As an artist – and I sometimes consider myself an artist — as a writer, we see value in the works we create. The idea that that value can translate into something digital, truly digital that you still own, is neat, and so that was the first inkling of it. They were talking to me about it, but I wasn&#8217;t going to do anything about it.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ben-mezrich-is-writing-a-book-about-the-nft-craze/">Ben Mezrich Is Writing a Book About the NFT Craze</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ben-mezrich-is-writing-a-book-about-the-nft-craze/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Fresh Increase Possible If It Clears $105</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-fresh-increase-possible-if-it-clears-105/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-fresh-increase-possible-if-it-clears-105/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 02:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76369</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin cash is facing barrier near the $105 and $108 resistance levels against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above the $100 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $100 on the 4-hours chart of the BCH/USD pair (data<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-fresh-increase-possible-if-it-clears-105/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-fresh-increase-possible-if-it-clears-105/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Fresh Increase Possible If It Clears $105</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin cash is facing barrier near the $105 and $108 resistance levels against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above the $100 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $100 on the 4-hours chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair must clear $104 and $105 to continue higher in the near term.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin cash price is climbing above $100 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-steady-increase-to-18k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. BCH/USD could start a fresh surge if it clears the $105 level.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin cash price formed a decent support base above the $95 level. BCH started a recovery wave and was able to clear the $98 resistance zone.</p>
<p>The price climbed above the $99 and $100 resistance levels. Recently, there was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $100 on the 4-hours chart of the BCH/USD pair. The pair is now trading above the $100 zone and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-downside-break-below-100-seems-real/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $104 level. The next major resistance is near the $105 level, above which the price may perhaps rise towards the $110 level. Any more gains above $110 and $112 could set the pace for a move towards the $120 level in the coming days.</p>
<p>An immediate support on the downside is near the $100 level and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $95 swing low to $104 high.</p>
<p>The first major support sits near the $98 level. It is near the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $95 swing low to $104 high. The next major support is near $95, below which the bears might aim $90. The next target for them may perhaps be near the $88 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_76370" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Bitcoin-Cash.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76370" class="size-full wp-image-76370" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Bitcoin-Cash.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76370" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Cash Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BCHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, bitcoin cash price is now trading above the $100 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price must clear $104 and $105 to continue higher in the near term.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for BCH/USD is slowly gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BCH/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $100 and $95.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $105 and $110.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-fresh-increase-possible-if-it-clears-105/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Fresh Increase Possible If It Clears $105</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-fresh-increase-possible-if-it-clears-105/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Pledges $2 Billion to &#8220;Save Crypto&#8221;</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-pledges-2-billion-to-save-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-pledges-2-billion-to-save-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 17:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75796</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Changpeng Zhao – the man behind famed digital currency exchange Binance – has pledged roughly $2 billion to help save the digital currency arena. Binance Is Looking to Save the Crypto Space The crypto space has been failing as of late. Bitcoin, for example, has lost more than 70 percent of its overall value since<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-pledges-2-billion-to-save-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-pledges-2-billion-to-save-crypto/">Binance Pledges $2 Billion to &#8220;Save Crypto&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Changpeng Zhao – the man behind famed digital currency exchange Binance – has pledged <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/billybambrough/2022/11/25/terra-luna-20-binance-ceo-reveals-huge-2-billion-fund-after-ftx-meltdown-crashed-the-bitcoin-and-crypto-price/?sh=20081532753b" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">roughly $2 billion to help</a> save the digital currency arena.</p>
<h2>Binance Is Looking to Save the Crypto Space</h2>
<p>The crypto space has been failing as of late. Bitcoin, for example, has lost more than 70 percent of its overall value since it reached its new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit in November of 2021. In general, crypto has lost more than $2.2 trillion in valuation, and many companies have either had to file for bankruptcy or have disappeared from the world of trading and digital coins for good.</p>
<p>One of the biggest fiascos to emerge from all this hype and drama was FTX, the once-glorified crypto exchange that rose through the ranks to become one of the most prominent digital currency trading companies out there. Beginning in 2019, FTX was only three years old, but was labeled the golden child of the space.</p>
<p>This all changed in mid-November when after <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">experiencing a liquidity crunch</a>, the company was forced into <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">bankruptcy rather suddenly</a>, and its head executive (Sam Bankman-Fried) resigned from his post. For a while, it <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">looked like Binance was</a> going to be the company that saved it from the darkness, but this wasn’t meant to be.</p>
<p>The money provided by Binance will allegedly go towards supporting several different companies and projects within the industry’s borders. According to a blog post issued by the exchange:</p>
<blockquote><p>The mandate of this new effort is to support the most promising and highest quality companies and projects built by the best technologists and entrepreneurs that, through no fault of their own, are facing significant, short-term, financial difficulties.</p></blockquote>
<p>Initially, Binance was saying it would only pledge $1 billion, though this quickly changed. Changpeng Zhao wrote on Twitter:</p>
<blockquote><p>Binance allocated another $1 billion [in Binance&#8217;s dollar-pegged stable coin] to the industry recovery initiative. It&#8217;s not the end of crypto. Far from it. It&#8217;s the beginning of a new chapter.</p></blockquote>
<p>Not everyone is crazy about the idea. Cory Klippensten – a known crypto skeptic – said of the situation:</p>
<blockquote><p>Obviously, a CZ-led recovery fund won&#8217;t be any better than an SBF-led effort to &#8216;save crypto.’ All it means is more money pumped into the casino to fuel greater fool gambling on inherently worthless non-bitcoin crypto tokens. If CZ succeeds in further centralizing the non-bitcoin crypto industry, it will only make it more prone to collapse or regulatory capture.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Not Everyone&#8217;s Convinced This Will Work</h2>
<p>Liron Shapira – a crypto market commentator – also expressed doubt, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>It&#8217;s hard to imagine a scenario where this particular fund does much to stop the inevitable collapse. The idea of an insurance fund against a structural, cascading collapse never works. At best, it can keep delaying by another day which is the whole way the Ponzi works in the first place. The more money they burn through, the longer they can keep it going.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-pledges-2-billion-to-save-crypto/">Binance Pledges $2 Billion to &#8220;Save Crypto&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-pledges-2-billion-to-save-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tom Lee: FTX Shouldn&#8217;t Reflect on the Crypto Space</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tom-lee-ftx-shouldnt-reflect-the-crypto-space/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tom-lee-ftx-shouldnt-reflect-the-crypto-space/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 15:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tom Lee]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75793</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tom Lee of Fundstrat fame believes that what happened with the now disgraced crypto exchange FTX should not reflect on bitcoin or the industry in general. He still believes in the power of crypto and doesn’t think the arena should suffer because of what a few bad actors have done. Tom Lee on Bitcoin and<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tom-lee-ftx-shouldnt-reflect-the-crypto-space/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tom-lee-ftx-shouldnt-reflect-the-crypto-space/">Tom Lee: FTX Shouldn&#8217;t Reflect on the Crypto Space</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tom Lee of Fundstrat fame believes that what happened with the now disgraced <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">crypto exchange FTX</a> should not reflect on bitcoin <a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/ftx-crypto-crash-bitcoin-invest-untouchable-fundstrat-tom-lee-2022-11" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">or the industry in general</a>. He still believes in the power of crypto and doesn’t think the arena should suffer because of what a few bad actors have done.</p>
<h2>Tom Lee on Bitcoin and FTX</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, Lee commented that the current bear run the crypto space is enduring is similar with the one it experienced in 2018. He said that bear run came to an end sooner than people anticipated. He commented that the space showed valid recovery in the following years, and he’s confident the same thing will happen this time around.</p>
<p>He further stated that the FTX fiasco isn’t likely to deliver a heavy-enough blow to the crypto sector given that bitcoin has historically always delivered solid returns. He further mentioned that this isn’t necessarily a bad thing in that many illicit firms and companies have now been permanently cut out.</p>
<p>Lee commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>It&#8217;s an important moment for the industry. I think it is cleaning a lot of and cleansing a lot of bad players, but do I think crypto is dead? No, I think there [are] a lot of people throwing gasoline in a crowded theatre and yelling ‘fire,’ and it&#8217;s just going to be important for those who really like what decentralization and bitcoin are doing.</p></blockquote>
<p>He further mentioned that 2022 was a horrendous year for the crypto sector. Aside from many companies filing bankruptcy or disappearing from the space, the bitcoin price has suffered heavily. In November of 2021, for example, the world’s number one digital currency by market cap rose to a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit. Now, however, the asset is trading in the mid-$16K range, meaning it’s lost more than 70 percent of its value in about 12 months.</p>
<p>Lee said:</p>
<blockquote><p>It&#8217;s been a horrific year for crypto. Nobody has made money in crypto in 2022. We first read about bitcoin in 2017, and we recommended people put one percent of their funds into bitcoin at the time. Bitcoin was under $1,000. That holding today would be 40 percent of their portfolio without rebalance.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Crypto Could Come Out Stronger</h2>
<p>Despite all the trouble the space has endured over the past year or so, he says his firm is still advising clients not to turn their backs on bitcoin and to invest in the digital asset in small doses so they can experience rewards once the market comes back. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>So, does bitcoin still make sense for someone who wants to sort of have some sort of ballast? Yes.</p></blockquote>
<p>Lastly, Lee said the crypto companies that survive the FTX drama will be like the banks that survived the 2008 financial collapse.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tom-lee-ftx-shouldnt-reflect-the-crypto-space/">Tom Lee: FTX Shouldn&#8217;t Reflect on the Crypto Space</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tom-lee-ftx-shouldnt-reflect-the-crypto-space/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Pioneer Tiantian Kullander Passes Away</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-pioneer-tiantian-kullander-passes-away/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-pioneer-tiantian-kullander-passes-away/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 13:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Amber Group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tiantian Kullander]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75791</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tiantian Kullander – the founder of digital currency firm Amber Group – is alleged to have passed away in his sleep on November 23 according to a statement from the company. Tiantian Kullander Has Passed On Kullander launched the enterprise in 2017. At the time of his death, the firm was valued at more than<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-pioneer-tiantian-kullander-passes-away/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-pioneer-tiantian-kullander-passes-away/">Crypto Pioneer Tiantian Kullander Passes Away</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tiantian Kullander – the founder of digital currency firm Amber Group – is <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/young-crypto-founder-shocks-industry-233735362.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">alleged to have passed</a> away in his sleep on November 23 according to a statement from the company.</p>
<h2>Tiantian Kullander Has Passed On</h2>
<p>Kullander launched the enterprise in 2017. At the time of his death, the firm was valued at more than $3 billion and was in the process of garnering another $100 million. The company was composed of several workers who spent time in the traditional finance sector, some of whom had even worked with giants like Morgan Stanley and Goldman Sachs Group.</p>
<p>In 2019, he was even placed on the Forbes under 30 list. He was also known as “TT” amongst those who were closest to him. In a statement, the company wrote the following about Kullander:</p>
<blockquote><p>He put his heart and soul into the company, in every stage of its growth. He led by example with his intellect, generosity, humility, diligence, and creativity… His depth of knowledge, his willingness to collaborate, and his desire to always help others benefited countless startups and individuals. His insights and creativity inspired many projects, people, and communities. We lost a great partner and a true friend in TT, and words cannot express our sorrow at this time. TT’s legacy will live on, and we will work even harder to make Amber the category-defining leader of our industry as this was TT’s ambition and dream.</p></blockquote>
<p>Aside from his work with Amber, he founded Keeper DAO prior to giving it back to the community. He also sat on the board of Fnatic, an e-sports organization. The company continued its praise of Kullander with:</p>
<blockquote><p>TT was a devoted husband, a loving father, and a fierce friend. His passing is a tragedy, and our thoughts and prayers are with his family. He is survived by his wife and their beloved son. We kindly request that you respect their privacy during this difficult time.</p></blockquote>
<p>His death marks the second in crypto over the course of just the last few weeks, the first being Nikolas Mushegian who, at 29 years of age, was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-innovator-nikolai-mushegian-dies-in-puerto-rico/" data-wpel-link="internal">discovered along the shores</a> of Puerto Rico after purportedly drowning. The circumstances surrounding his death are mysterious given that just hours before his passing, he spoke on Twitter of an alleged plot by the CIA and other agencies within the U.S. to take his life and blame him for crimes he hadn’t committed.</p>
<h2>Two Over the Course of a Few Weeks</h2>
<p>At the time of his death, an unnamed source stated the following about Mushegian:</p>
<blockquote><p>He had mental problems. He saw a psychiatrist at times. He smoked a lot of pot. A tremendous amount. Some of his paranoia was based on fact. He’d discover things. He knew things. Nikolai got bored a lot with the mundane of life.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-pioneer-tiantian-kullander-passes-away/">Crypto Pioneer Tiantian Kullander Passes Away</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-pioneer-tiantian-kullander-passes-away/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MEFLEX (MEF) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/meflex-mef-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/meflex-mef-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 09:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76357</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Jan 5, 2023 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed MEFLEX (MEF) on January 5, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the MEF/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading. As a community-based lifestyles platform, MEFLEX (MEF) carries out NFT, Metaverse and the transaction of luxurious<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/meflex-mef-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/meflex-mef-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">MEFLEX (MEF) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Jan 5, 2023 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed MEFLEX (MEF) on January 5, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the MEF/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading.</p>
<p>As a community-based lifestyles platform, <a href="https://etherscan.io/token/0x64b5a241b829bca14eb42d00097ba8fd8135841e" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">MEFLEX</a> (MEF) carries out NFT, Metaverse and the transaction of luxurious brands as a whole package. Its native token MEF has been listed on LBank Exchange at 8:00 UTC on January 5, 2023, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision.</p>
<p><strong>Introducing MEFLEX</strong></p>
<p>MEFLEX is a social NFT platform and digitopia metaverse which will bring out overall innovation and changes in entertainment, luxurious items, and furthermore any events and stocks that are still stocked and trapped in traditional customs. In short, It’s a revolution in distribution, and the perfection of lifestyle communities.</p>
<p>Unlike other existing luxury goods trading platforms, MEFLEX has lifted its reliability by providing only authentic goods supplied by proven official importers. From this, it will provide entirely different and definite advantage of its own through constant and stable supply of goods and reduction of prices at the same time, and guarantees the product affordability as well by applying BNPL as a method of payment.</p>
<p>MEFLEX also builds a social platform with influencer centered community, where influencer could constantly communicate and notify their activities and moreover each of them could make their own crews for exchanges of different lifestyles. In this comprehensive lifestyle community, current generation MZ could actively mingle and harmoniously blend in with different influencers which makes MEFLEX much more unique than other existing luxury goods trading platforms.</p>
<p>Furthermore, in MEFLEX’s NFT marketplace, people can mint and trade influencer’s NFT. Additionally, MEFLEX is also planning to develop different and various P2E games based on NFT. As the MEFLEX community grows and the blockchain ecosystem is activated, the mining difficulty increases, and the importance of influencer NFT, which greatly helps P2E games, also increases.</p>
<p>Eventually a Metaverse Digitopia, a place where dreams come true even beyond imaginary limits of reality, will be built. MEFLEX pursues and urges another metaverse digitopia that transcends the space and time, providing opportunities where the current MZ generations could freely mingle with.</p>
<p><strong>About MEF Token</strong></p>
<p>MEF, the native token of MEFLEX ecosystem, acts as the key to supporting economic activities of the platform and metaverse, and is used for NFT minting and product purchases.</p>
<p>Based on ERC-20, MEF has a total supply of 1 billion (i.e., 1,000,000,000) tokens, of which 20% is provided for public and private sale, 4% is allocated to partners, 8% is provided for R&amp;D, 4% is reserved, 2% is provided for airdrop, 5% is allocated to advisors, 15% will be used for marketing, 5% is allocated to founders, 2% is provided for the platform, 30% is provided for the ecosystem, and the remaining 5% is allocated to the team.</p>
<p>The MEF token has been listed on LBank Exchange at 8:00 UTC on January 5, 2023, investors who are interested in the MEFLEX investment can easily buy and sell MEF token on LBank Exchange right now. The listing of MEF token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p>
<p><strong>Learn More about</strong><strong> MEF Token:</strong></p>
<p>Official Website: <a href="http://www.me-flex.co.kr" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.me-flex.co.kr</a><br />
Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/meflex_official_chat" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://t.me/meflex_official_chat</a><br />
Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/meflex_official" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/meflex_official</a><br />
YouTube: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCbNmloExoKF7xO--NuKPD7Q" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCbNmloExoKF7xO&#8211;NuKPD7Q</a><br />
Medium: <a href="https://medium.com/@ME-FELX" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://medium.com/@ME-FELX</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media: </strong></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Facebook</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong><br />
LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
LBank Exchange<br />
<a href="mailto:marketing@lbank.info">marketing@lbank.info</a><br />
<a href="mailto:business@lbank.info">business@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/meflex-mef-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">MEFLEX (MEF) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/meflex-mef-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>REGENT COIN (REGENT) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/regent-coin-regent-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/regent-coin-regent-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 08:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76354</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Jan 4, 2023 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed REGENT COIN (REGENT) on January 4, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the REGENT/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading. Encompassing the entire crypto universe in one circle, Regent has simplified the whole utility token<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/regent-coin-regent-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/regent-coin-regent-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">REGENT COIN (REGENT) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Jan 4, 2023 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed REGENT COIN (REGENT) on January 4, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the REGENT/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading.</p>
<p>Encompassing the entire crypto universe in one circle, Regent has simplified the whole utility token scenario for all users with its safe transactions, faster processing, all time availability, and worldwide usage. The <a href="https://bscscan.com/token/0x4fFa143Ce16A24215e8dF96c0CEF5677a7B91EE4" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">REGENT COIN</a> (REGENT) utility token has been listed on LBank Exchange at 13:00 UTC on January 4, 2023, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision.</p>
<p><strong>Introducing </strong><strong>Regent</strong></p>
<p>The global Utility Tokens Market size in 2025 is expected to be $35 million and is expected to grow at 20% CAGR during the period till 2030. By putting across all the points and properties of basic utility tokens and compiling them all into the most profitable results of the crypto world, Regent has simplified the whole utility token scenario for all users.</p>
<p>As the name suggests, Regent encompasses the entire crypto universe in one circle. It can be used to transact directly among the users, and is available on DEX and CEX platforms. The token has been curated in such a way that it solves multi purposes in one go. The primary function being paying for different kinds of transactions flawlessly.</p>
<p>Regent will act as an internal token payment method to subscribe to more products and services, and will be needed to access and interact with its platform and to use stable currency. These tokens can be either purchased through the app or via an integrated partner. Regent is not restricted to any particular domain, it can be utilised for all sorts of online payments.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Regent will also generate value for the ecosystem stakeholder as rewards. Token holders will have real-time stable currency rewards on every transaction done through the app. In addition, users can enjoy shopping discount by using Regent. The discount will be applied directly to the listed prices at checkout.</p>
<p>Regent’s aim is to be a community governed decentralised platform that eliminates third-party platforms charges such as software as a service, transactional platforms, and high fee payment gateways. It will enable direct real-time peer-to-peer business and consumer connectivity, service delivery, and low fee stable currency and cryptocurrency payment processing at a fraction of a cost, and will enable free cross-chain asset transfer for retail payments and rewards.</p>
<p><strong>About REGENT Token</strong></p>
<p>REGENT COIN (REGENT) is designed for the convenience, cost effective solution and efficient time usage among the peer to peer community. As a utility token, REGENT enables people to make their utility bill payments using the pay app.</p>
<p>Based on BEP-20, REGENT has a total supply of 2.9 million (i.e., 2,900,000) tokens, of which 30% is provided for presale, 5% will be used for marketing, 25% is provided for staking, 20% is allocated for the community, 8% is provided for CEX listing, 8% is allocated for rewards, and the remaining 4% will be used for API development.</p>
<p>The REGENT token has been listed on LBank Exchange at 13:00 UTC on January 4, 2023, investors who are interested in the REGENT COIN investment can easily buy and sell REGENT token on LBank Exchange right now. The listing of REGENT token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p>
<p><strong>Learn More about</strong> <strong>REGENT Token:</strong></p>
<p>Official Website: <a href="https://www.regentcoin.finance" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.regentcoin.finance</a><br />
Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/RegentCoin" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://t.me/RegentCoin</a><br />
Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/regent_coin" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/regent_coin</a><br />
Instagram: <a href="https://www.instagram.com/regentcoin_/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.instagram.com/regentcoin_/</a><br />
Facebook: <a href="https://www.facebook.com/people/Regent-Coin/100087324862103/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://www.facebook.com/people/Regent-Coin/100087324862103/</a><br />
Medium: <a href="https://link.medium.com/QqfrpB8VPub" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://link.medium.com/QqfrpB8VPub</a></p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media: </strong></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Facebook</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong><br />
LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
LBank Exchange<br />
<a href="mailto:marketing@lbank.info">marketing@lbank.info</a><br />
<a href="mailto:business@lbank.info">business@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/regent-coin-regent-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">REGENT COIN (REGENT) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/regent-coin-regent-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
