<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 03:20:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/cropped-fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Binance Faces Accusations that It Mixed Customer and Company Funds</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-faces-accusations-that-it-mixed-customer-and-company-funds/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 17:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CFTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78479</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance – the largest and most popular digital currency exchange – is in hot water again after former insiders alleged that the exchange combined funds from customers with those of the company. What Did Binance Do? In what could be argued as taking a page out of the FTX playbook, Binance is accused of not [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-faces-accusations-that-it-mixed-customer-and-company-funds/">Binance Faces Accusations that It Mixed Customer and Company Funds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance – the largest and most popular digital currency exchange – is in <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/23/crypto-giant-binance-commingled-customer-funds-and-company-revenue-former-insiders-say.html">hot water again after former</a> insiders alleged that the exchange combined funds from customers with those of the company.</p>
<h2>What Did Binance Do?</h2>
<p>In what could be argued as taking a page out of the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/">FTX</a> playbook, Binance is accused of not keeping customer and company funds separate. This would be a breach of U.S. financial rules. Binance has denied any wrongdoing.</p>
<p>One of the insiders claims that the total of the commingled money is in the billions, and that this occurred almost daily through accounts the company had with the now <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-provide-their-thoughts-on-latest-bitcoin-rally/">defunct Silvergate Bank</a>. As it stands, various news platforms such as Reuters have conducted analyses of Binance’s financial transactions, yet they cannot find (at least for now) evidence suggesting that what the insiders say is true.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the claims arouse suspicion and concern in digital currency traders given this is exactly what FTX is accused of having done, and for some time, Binance and FTX <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/">were working together</a>. One needs to wonder if perhaps the latter’s bad business protocols didn’t rub off on the former.</p>
<p>In a statement, SEC commissioner Gary Gensler says many crypto exchanges are guilty of offering securities after they failed to register as broker-dealers, thus ensuring that their clients’ money would be protected and separated from all corporate assets and profit funds. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Their business models tend to be built on taking customer funds, commingling it.</p></blockquote>
<p>Binance spokesperson Brad Jaffe came out to say that Binance has not committed any crimes, nor is it guilty of what it’s being accused of. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>These accounts were not used to accept user deposits. They were used to facilitate user purchases. There was no commingling at any time because these are 100 percent corporate funds.</p></blockquote>
<p>Indeed, the situation is very reminiscent of FTX, a crypto exchange that fell into a heaping pile of bankruptcy and fraud last November. Following the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/">announcement of its bankruptcy</a>, the company’s head honcho Sam Bankman-Fried was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftxs-disgraced-founder-has-been-arrested/">arrested in the Bahamas</a> after he was accused of commingling his firm’s money with that of customers. He was also charged with using customer funds to pay off loans with his other firm Alameda Research and to invest in luxury Bahamian real estate.</p>
<p>At the present time, Binance is <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cftc-sues-binance-alleging-financial-violations/">also facing scrutiny from</a> the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), which is suing the exchange for allegedly violating the Commodity Exchange Act.</p>
<h2>Further Legal Issues</h2>
<p>CFTC chair Rostin Behnam said:</p>
<blockquote><p>For years, Binance knew they were violating CFTC rules, working actively to both keep the money flowing and avoid compliance. This should be a warning to anyone in the digital asset world that the CFTC will not tolerate willful avoidance of U.S. law.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-faces-accusations-that-it-mixed-customer-and-company-funds/">Binance Faces Accusations that It Mixed Customer and Company Funds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Michael Saylor Hints at Potential Bull Run for BTC</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-hints-at-potential-bull-run-for-btc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 15:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Saylor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroStrategy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78476</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Saylor – the former CEO of software giant MicroStrategy – is predicting big things for bitcoin. Michael Saylor Is Still a BTC Fan Not long ago, Saylor issued a separate interview that clearly showed him to be a full bitcoin maximalist. He insinuated that he would never live it down, nor would he ever [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-hints-at-potential-bull-run-for-btc/">Michael Saylor Hints at Potential Bull Run for BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Michael Saylor – the former CEO of software giant MicroStrategy – is predicting big <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-has-bottomed-and-the-worlds-biggest-cryptocurrency-is-on-a-new-bull-run-microstrategys-michael-saylor-says/ar-AA1bx3Ui">things for bitcoin</a>.</p>
<h2>Michael Saylor Is Still a BTC Fan</h2>
<p>Not long ago, Saylor issued a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-bitcoin-is-the-future/">separate interview</a> that clearly showed him to be a full bitcoin maximalist. He insinuated that he would never live it down, nor would he ever lose hope that the world’s number one digital currency by market capitalization would amount to something. In this more recent interview, he took his ideas and comments to the next level.</p>
<p>He stated that he thinks a regulatory crackdown on digital markets will ultimately work well for the asset. In addition, he said that the next halving – currently scheduled for 2024 – will help bring BTC to a new level of trading and appreciation. Saylor commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think the crypto tokens and crypto securities are going to be regulated, perhaps out of existence. Bitcoin is the most secure network. It&#8217;s the most secure asset. Everything else has got a black cloud hanging over it. You&#8217;re going to see a consistent flow of capital flowing from the rest of the crypto ecosystem [into] bitcoin.</p></blockquote>
<p>Saylor has had a very long (and up and down) history with crypto. First catching the bitcoin bug in late 2020, he began investing his company’s reserves in the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-microstrategy-bitcoin-bet-is-already-paying-off-big-time/">asset in August of that</a> year. When he first started to make profits, additional investments came, and at first, it looked like everything was going his way.</p>
<p>However, in early 2022, when the market began to crash, Saylor continued to invest in BTC even though losses were beginning to pile up, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-buys-more-btc-despite-ongoing-crash/">and this behavior continued</a> despite what has come to be known as one of the worst bear markets in the history of crypto. Before long, he had put his company into billions of dollars and debt, and the world saw him <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-btc-bull-and-microstrategy-chief-executive-steps-down/">resigning from the CEO</a> post he had held for over 30 years.</p>
<p>Despite all the issues he’s endured, Saylor still believes in BTC. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The FASB initiative to adopt fair value accounting is a very auspicious development.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Working Out the Kinks</h2>
<p>He further commented that while the industry is enduring “growing pains,” here and there, this is to be expected from something that’s still very much in an infant-like state. He mentioned that bitcoin and crypto need to go through these hindrances to be developed into lasting, strong tools that investors can truly benefit from. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Nearly all of the bad leverage has been squeezed out. Everyone in the business of shorting bitcoin, rehypothecating bitcoin, loaning bitcoin, they&#8217;ve all [gone] bankrupt. The remaining exchanges where you can short it are under a massive amount of regulatory pressure. I think bitcoin [has] found the bottom. I think the leverage is out of it. I think we&#8217;re on a bull run.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-hints-at-potential-bull-run-for-btc/">Michael Saylor Hints at Potential Bull Run for BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Powell Announces Potential Pause to Rate Hikes; BTC Slips</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/powell-announces-potential-pause-to-rate-hikes-btc-slips/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 13:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jerome Powell]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78474</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jerome Powell – the head of the Fed – has announced that due to ongoing stress endured by the American banking system, he and his cronies will likely ease their hiking of interest rates. Strangely, the news has not done great things for bitcoin or crypto. In fact, prices took a small and temporary dive [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/powell-announces-potential-pause-to-rate-hikes-btc-slips/">Powell Announces Potential Pause to Rate Hikes; BTC Slips</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jerome Powell – the head of the Fed – has <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-ethereum-dogecoin-drop-after-powells-dovish-comments-trader-predicts-king-crypto-soaring-to-300000/ar-AA1bv0No">announced that due to ongoing</a> stress endured by the American banking system, he and his cronies will likely ease their hiking of interest rates. Strangely, the news has not done great things for bitcoin or crypto. In fact, prices took a small and temporary dive following the announcement.</p>
<h2>Jerome Powell Hints at Potential Curb to Rate Hikes</h2>
<p>This is arguably the attitude Powell should have had a long time ago. When banks are failing left and right, as they’ve been doing over the past few months, one does not seek to put more financial stress on a country and its people. Rather, one steps back, assesses the damage, and tries to ease the problems as best they can.</p>
<p>This, however, is not what Powell has done. Rather, rate hikes have <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-shows-great-resilience-in-face-of-interest-rate-hikes/">continued into 2023</a>, and while the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-provide-their-thoughts-on-latest-bitcoin-rally/">banking crisis</a> has indeed allowed bitcoin and its altcoin cousins to recover somewhat from the dismal days of 2022 and the crypto winter it brought on, things are not quite where they need to be, and there’s still plenty of room to heal for the world’s number one digital asset by market cap.</p>
<p>Edward Moya – senior market analyst at OANDA – commented in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>A month ago, bitcoin was surging, passing the $30,000 level for the first time since the summer of 2022. Regional banking concerns and rising Fed rate cut bets provided a lot of support for cryptos. The bullish catalysts have now faded away, and so has roughly 30 percent of this year&#8217;s rally.  Bitcoin did not get any favor from [the] SEC’s Gensler earlier in the week, just the standard comments on how rules are already in place. The regulatory question remains the key for the crypto verse, and traders will have to remain patient.</p></blockquote>
<p>Crypto trader Tony Vays also threw his two cents in, claiming that while prices may have taken a sudden (albeit small) dip in the short term, he believes the market is turning itself around and bitcoin traders can expect a solid bull run in the coming months. Over the next few years, he’s confident bitcoin will poise itself to reach a price of $300K. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>We continue to consolidate. It’s continued to be frustrating. I&#8217;ve been a bitcoiner, and it&#8217;s very, very clear that bitcoin is choosing the purple path. I have two paths for bitcoin. One was a little more bullish with a lower top ($200,000), and the other was a little more bearish with a higher top ($300,000) a little further down in time.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Inflation Remains a Problem</h2>
<p>The rate hikes discussed above were constant throughout the year 2022 thanks to poor economic policies signed into law by Joe Biden.</p>
<p>These policies resulted in record inflation, and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-fed-bitcoins-worst-enemy-right-now/">the rate hikes became</a> the only tool for fighting this enemy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/powell-announces-potential-pause-to-rate-hikes-btc-slips/">Powell Announces Potential Pause to Rate Hikes; BTC Slips</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Fresh Rally Possible To $330</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-fresh-rally-possible-to-330/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 03:28:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79161</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin cash is eyeing a fresh rally above the $300 resistance against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above the $260 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $289 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-fresh-rally-possible-to-330/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Fresh Rally Possible To $330</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin cash is eyeing a fresh rally above the $300 resistance against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above the $260 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $289 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair must clear $290 and $300 to continue higher in the near term.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin cash price is consolidating gains above $260 against the US Dollar, unlike <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-more-upsides-above-31250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. BCH/USD could start a fresh surge if it clears the $300 level.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin cash price formed a decent support base above the $220 level. BCH started a decent increase and was able to clear the $280 resistance zone.</p>
<p>The price climbed above the $300 and $320 resistance levels. However, the bears appeared near the $328 level. There was a downside correction below the $300 level. The price declined below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $185 swing low to the $328 high.</p>
<p>However, the bulls are active above the $240 level. It is stable above the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $185 swing low to the $328 high.</p>
<p>Bitcoin cash is now trading above the $260 zone and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-rally-gains-pace-above-300/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. It is attempting a fresh rally above the $300 resistance. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $290 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $289 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $300, above which the price may perhaps rise toward the $330 level. Any more gains above $330 could set the pace for a move toward the $350 level.</p>
<p>If not, the price might decline again. Immediate support on the downside is near the $260 level. The first major support sits near the $240 level. The next major support is near $220, below which the bears might aim for $200. The next target for them may perhaps be near the $185 level.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79162" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79162" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash.png"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-79162" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79162" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Cash Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BCHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, Bitcoin Cash’s price is now trading above the $260 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price must clear $290 and $300 to continue higher in the near term.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for BCH/USD is gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BCH/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $260 and $240.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $290 and $300.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-fresh-rally-possible-to-330/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Fresh Rally Possible To $330</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Prices Rise Following Positive Sentiment from Hong Kong</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-prices-rise-following-positive-sentiment-from-hong-kong/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 17:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[china]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hong Kong]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78472</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Towards the end of May, crypto prices rose somewhat following news that Hong Kong would permit retail trading and move in the opposite direction of its mainland countrymen. Hong Kong Says &#8220;Yes&#8221; to Crypto Trading Bitcoin, for example, which had been trading in the mid-$26,000 range for several weeks, eventually shot beyond the $27K mark [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-prices-rise-following-positive-sentiment-from-hong-kong/">Crypto Prices Rise Following Positive Sentiment from Hong Kong</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Towards the end of May, crypto prices rose <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/bitcoin-climbs-back-above-27-000-after-hong-kong-greenlights-some-retail-crypto-trading/ar-AA1bzwAl">somewhat following news that</a> Hong Kong would permit retail trading and move in the opposite direction of its mainland countrymen.</p>
<h2>Hong Kong Says &#8220;Yes&#8221; to Crypto Trading</h2>
<p>Bitcoin, for example, which had been trading in the mid-$26,000 range for several weeks, eventually shot beyond the $27K mark for the first time in a while, while Ethereum – which had fallen into the $1,700 range – shot up to about $1,850.</p>
<p>The jumps arrived after the Securities and Futures Commission in Hong Kong said it would allow all retail traders interested in crypto to trade a certain number of digital assets beginning in June, though they would have to do so through registered platforms. The news is a huge step in an alternate direction given China became highly anti-crypto roughly two years ago.</p>
<p>In 2021, China shocked the world when it decided that per new regulations set forth by Beijing, all crypto and bitcoin mining would be fully illegal, and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-crypto-mining-clampdown-in-china-is-not-over/">all mining facilities</a> would have to be shut down. The move was designed to make the country less polluting and ensure stronger climate regulations were in place.</p>
<p>It was a very surprising statement given that China, at that time, was home to well over 60 percent of the world’s mining facilities. Thus, China was set to lose a lot of money within a short period, but this didn’t seem to bother regulators. In fact, they eventually took things a step further and announced that all crypto trading activities <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-traders-in-china-have-no-exchanges-to-turn-to/">would also be illegal</a>. Nobody could engage in crypto transactions, and if they were caught doing so, they would either pay a fine or go to prison for their actions.</p>
<p>Hong Kong, however, has long sought to decipher itself from the Chinese mainland. The region has worked hard to gain independence, and this is just another stick in the side of China as the area has refused to turn away from crypto the way the mainland has. Noelle Acheson – economist and author of the crypto newsletter “Crypto is Macro Now” – announced in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>This news doesn&#8217;t mean that a flood of retail buying power will enter the market at the beginning… We could see some volume uptick… however.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Trying to Be the Next Big Hub</h2>
<p>Owen Lau – an analyst at Oppenheimer – also threw his two cents into the mix, commenting that Hong Kong is being “pretty aggressive” when it comes to working towards crypto hub status. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>It will continue to capture the attention of the community and attract more firms to set up offices in Hong Kong. It is hard to gauge the exact impact, but it has a long-term effect on capital flow and talent movement.</p></blockquote>
<p>The Securities and Futures Commission has already licensed two digital currency companies.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-prices-rise-following-positive-sentiment-from-hong-kong/">Crypto Prices Rise Following Positive Sentiment from Hong Kong</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Crypto Bill in Texas Would Really Hurt Miners</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-crypto-bill-in-texas-would-really-hurt-miners/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 15:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[china]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Texas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78470</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new bill is making its way to the Texas House of Representatives that might make it hard for crypto mining companies within the state to gain access to the funds and resources they need to stay afloat and function properly. Texas Crypto Bill Is the Wrong Move The bill, for one thing, would ensure [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-crypto-bill-in-texas-would-really-hurt-miners/">New Crypto Bill in Texas Would Really Hurt Miners</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new bill is making its way to the Texas House of Representatives that <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/colinharper/2023/05/23/texas-bitcoin-bill-could-eliminate-key-source-of-funds-for-miners/?sh=5cff32c1dd06">might make it hard for</a> crypto mining companies within the state to gain access to the funds and resources they need to stay afloat and function properly.</p>
<h2>Texas Crypto Bill Is the Wrong Move</h2>
<p>The bill, for one thing, would ensure that power costs for the largest crypto miner in the state will increase by as much as $30 million each year. Also, miners would only be able to provide a limited amount of power to the Electricity Reliability Council of Texas (ERCOT), and bitcoin miners would also not be allowed to access the same property tax breaks currently available to standard industrial power consumers.</p>
<p>The situation is an odd one in that bitcoin mining profits have already shrunk by as much as 60 percent over the last year, largely due to the ongoing crypto winter and the dips many digital asset prices have incurred. Companies like Riot Blockchain – one of the most prominent crypto mining firms in the country – say the power credits that they’re currently privy to make a huge difference in how much they pay and how much they make each year. Representatives for the firm put out the following statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>These credits are recognized in power curtailment credits in the statements of operations, outside of cost of revenues, but significantly reduce the company’s overall cost to mine bitcoin. When netting the power curtailment credits with the costs of revenues, the net costs as a percentage of mining revenue were 39.7 percent and 24.7 percent for the years ended December 31, 2022, and 2021, respectively.</p></blockquote>
<p>The bill has already passed the Senate, though it would need to be signed into law by Texas Governor Greg Abbott, who has shown himself to be a bitcoin and crypto fan in the past. Thus, it’s unlikely, analysts say, that he will react favorably to the bill, though it’s impossible to assume this couldn’t happen for some reason.</p>
<h2>Helping Miners Relocate</h2>
<p>Texas has long been a major bitcoin and crypto mining hub, so it’s odd that such a bill would ever make its way through the state’s political spectrum. The state has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-is-still-a-crypto-mining-king/">highly devoted to mining</a> for about two years now, largely because so many miners have been forced to leave their native China. That country declared crypto mining illegal in 2021, and several made their way to Texas due to the state’s large, vast, and open landscapes and its cheap electricity prices.</p>
<p>While the situation hasn’t been perfect, the sudden influx of miners has given Texas’ economy a major boost. It has also created jobs and opened opportunity windows on all sides of the state, so it seems very strange that such an anti-crypto bill would garner support.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-crypto-bill-in-texas-would-really-hurt-miners/">New Crypto Bill in Texas Would Really Hurt Miners</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>America Just Celebrated Independence Day, and It&#8217;s a Reminder of What BTC Stands For</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/america-just-celebrated-independence-day-and-its-a-reminder-of-what-btc-stands-for/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 13:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[America]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Founding Fathers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78458</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It was recently the 4th of July, aka Independence Day, in America, and let this serve as just another reminder of the independence that users can gain by incorporating digital currency into their lives. America, in Many Ways, IS Bitcoin Close to 250 years ago, the Founding Fathers of America created a new nation; one [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/america-just-celebrated-independence-day-and-its-a-reminder-of-what-btc-stands-for/">America Just Celebrated Independence Day, and It&#8217;s a Reminder of What BTC Stands For</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It was recently the 4th of July, aka <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Independence_Day_(United_States)">Independence Day</a>, in America, and let this serve as just another reminder of the independence that users can gain by incorporating digital currency into their lives.</p>
<h2>America, in Many Ways, IS Bitcoin</h2>
<p>Close to 250 years ago, the Founding Fathers of America created a new nation; one where everyone was created equal. A nation where people could pursue “life, liberty, and the pursuit of happiness” without oppression, without government intervention, and without fear of persecution. This is the image they had in their heads for America, and now, over two centuries later, that image is being enhanced through assets like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitcoin/">bitcoin</a>, Ethereum, and others.</p>
<p>The big thing about digital currencies is that they are designed to improve upon financial autonomy and freedom. Right now, the standard financial industry has too much say in what people can and cannot do with their money. If you were to go to a bank, for example, and try to get your hands on a checking or savings account, there’s a good chance you’d be subjected to a background check. Those in charge at the bank will want to know what kind of jobs you’ve held, if you’ve ever gone bankrupt or defaulted on a loan, etc.</p>
<p>If there’s anything in your personal history – financial or otherwise – that these executives don’t like, there’s a good chance you won’t gain access to the institution’s services and tools, many of which will be necessary for your survival and for the care of your family or others close to you.</p>
<p>With crypto, however, none of this is ever considered, much less thrown into the mix. With crypto, if you have a digital wallet and an internet connection, you’re already off to a great start, and in many ways, these items will be all you’ll need to begin trading, buying, selling, and investing in crypto assets. It’s that simple, and nobody’s going to look at your personal history or anything like that. You won’t be told what you can do with your assets, and your finances will be fully in your control.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Enhances the Views of the Founding Fathers</h2>
<p>While bitcoin may not be as old as America (it was first mined in January of 2009 and had its whitepaper introduced to the public just a few months prior), the ideals behind it are the same. America and bitcoin both stand for freedom, and these ideals need to be taken to heart.</p>
<p>In celebrating America, one is also celebrating everything bitcoin and crypto stand for. In many ways, it’s odd that bitcoin has not been made a national currency given it stands for everything this nation stands for. With that, we say, “Happy Independence Day” to the crypto community! May your notions of freedom stay with you forever.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/america-just-celebrated-independence-day-and-its-a-reminder-of-what-btc-stands-for/">America Just Celebrated Independence Day, and It&#8217;s a Reminder of What BTC Stands For</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Enhancing Security and Privacy with AI and Blockchain: A Synergistic Approach</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/enhancing-security-and-privacy-with-ai-and-blockchain-a-synergistic-approach/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 11:09:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79147</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In today&#8217;s digital landscape, the security of applications, software, data, and systems is a paramount concern for users and developers alike. With the rise of cyber threats and data breaches, organisations are seeking innovative solutions to safeguard their valuable assets. Blockchain and artificial intelligence (AI) are two transformative technologies that offer promising avenues to enhance [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/enhancing-security-and-privacy-with-ai-and-blockchain-a-synergistic-approach/">Enhancing Security and Privacy with AI and Blockchain: A Synergistic Approach</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In today&#8217;s digital landscape, the security of applications, software, data, and systems is a paramount concern for users and developers alike. With the rise of cyber threats and data breaches, organisations are seeking innovative solutions to safeguard their valuable assets. Blockchain and artificial intelligence (AI) are two transformative technologies that offer promising avenues to enhance security measures. By leveraging the power of blockchain and AI, developers can create secure applications and fortify the protection of sensitive information. These two new technologies are at the nexus of enhancing security and privacy in the digital world.</p>
<h4>AI and blockchain intersection for digital security</h4>
<p>Blockchain technology provides a decentralised and transparent platform for storing and managing data. Its immutability and consensus mechanisms ensure the integrity of data stored on the blockchain. By leveraging blockchain&#8217;s distributed nature, sensitive information can be stored across multiple nodes, making it extremely challenging for attackers to tamper with or manipulate the data. Moreover, blockchain&#8217;s cryptographic techniques enable secure data sharing and communication, protecting the privacy of users.</p>
<p>On the other hand, AI, particularly machine learning algorithms, play a crucial role in preserving privacy and enhancing system security. Machine learning models can analyse vast amounts of data to identify patterns and anomalies that may indicate security threats. By training these models on historical data, they can effectively detect and prevent unauthorised access, ensuring the security of applications and systems.</p>
<p>Combining AI and blockchain in the development of new applications helps unlock new levels of cybersecurity and data privacy, fortifying software, applications, and systems. These technologies aid the development of robust platforms that are continually evolving to meet the emerging security and privacy challenges while maintaining integrity of the systems in the following ways:</p>
<h4>AI-Driven Secure Blockchain Applications</h4>
<p>Integrating AI with blockchain can lead to the development of intelligent applications that autonomously detect and respond to security threats. AI algorithms can continuously monitor the blockchain network, identifying suspicious activities or anomalies. These applications can initiate security protocols automatically, notifying relevant stakeholders to take immediate action and minimise potential damages. By leveraging AI capabilities, blockchain applications can adapt and evolve in real-time to counter emerging security challenges.</p>
<h4>Trust Management</h4>
<p>Establishing trust is a critical aspect of securing applications, software, data, and systems. Blockchain technology, with its decentralised and transparent nature, provides a foundation for trust management. AI algorithms can analyse data stored on the blockchain, verifying the authenticity and integrity of transactions. By combining blockchain&#8217;s trust-building capabilities with AI&#8217;s data analysis and verification techniques, organisations can enable secure and trustworthy storage and exchange of digital assets.</p>
<h4>AI-Driven Secure Computing</h4>
<p>AI models often require significant computational power to perform complex tasks. Due to the decentralised and crowdsourced nature of blockchain networks they can provide the necessary computing resources while ensuring the security and privacy of AI computations. By leveraging blockchain&#8217;s distributed computing capabilities, organisations can securely execute AI algorithms without exposing sensitive data to potential risks. This integration enables secure and efficient AI-driven computing, safeguarding applications, software, data, and systems.</p>
<p>On the other hand, smart contracts, powered by AI, can automate and secure digital interactions, minimising human errors and potential security breaches. In this way, AI-empowered secure computing on blockchain ensures the privacy and security of computations, enabling trusted execution of smart contracts.</p>
<h4>Blockchain Recovery, and Auditing using AI</h4>
<p>Ensuring the availability and recovery of data in the event of a system failure or cyber-attack is crucial. Blockchain&#8217;s decentralised architecture and AI&#8217;s predictive capabilities can be leveraged to enhance availability and recovery mechanisms. The blockchain can store backup copies of critical data, enabling efficient recovery in case of data loss. AI algorithms can analyse system logs and detect anomalies, facilitating timely response and recovery measures. Furthermore, blockchain&#8217;s transparent nature allows for efficient auditing and accountability, ensuring the integrity of system operations.</p>
<p><a href="https://aiwork.io/">AIWORK</a> is leading the development of AI-driven blockchain applications by facilitating the creation, verification and validation of AI data sets to make AI smarter for human use. Through the platform, content creators can benefit from crowd-sourced computing resources and a decentralised community to transcribe and translate their content to reach diverse audiences. AIWORK harnesses the power of blockchain technology and novel AI tools to build better content metadata to improve better search and discoverability for its users. By combining these two ground-breaking technologies, AIWORK enables improved interactions and content consumption while maintaining a high degree of security and privacy for both creators and users in the digital space.</p>
<h4>Conclusion</h4>
<p>The secure application of blockchain and artificial intelligence offers a transformative approach to fortifying the security of applications, software, data, and systems. By leveraging blockchain&#8217;s decentralised and transparent platform and integrating AI&#8217;s data analysis and predictive capabilities, applications can establish secure environments, protect sensitive information, and mitigate security risks. As the digital landscape continues to evolve, embracing the combined potential of blockchain and AI will be crucial in safeguarding valuable assets and maintaining trust in the digital realm.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/enhancing-security-and-privacy-with-ai-and-blockchain-a-synergistic-approach/">Enhancing Security and Privacy with AI and Blockchain: A Synergistic Approach</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EOS Price Analysis: Bulls Protecting Key Support at $0.70</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bulls-protecting-key-support-at-0-70/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 05:08:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EOS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79144</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>EOS price started a downside correction from the $0.808 resistance against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $0.74 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key contracting triangle forming with support near $0.715 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bulls-protecting-key-support-at-0-70/">EOS Price Analysis: Bulls Protecting Key Support at $0.70</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>EOS price started a downside correction from the $0.808 resistance against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $0.74 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key contracting triangle forming with support near $0.715 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it stays below the $0.74 and $0.75 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>EOS price is declining from $0.808 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-more-upsides-above-31250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. The price could accelerate lower if there is a clear move below the $0.70 support.</em></p>
<h2>EOS Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This week, EOS price climbed further higher above the $0.75 resistance zone against the US Dollar. The price surpassed the $0.80 level and settled above the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>A high was formed near $0.8072 before the price started a downside correction. The price declined below the $0.765 support to move into a short-term bearish zone. There was a move below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.6412 swing low to the $0.8072 high.</p>
<p>The pair even tested the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.6412 swing low to the $0.8072 high. It is now trading below $0.75 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bears-in-control-below-0-80/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>On the downside, immediate support is near the $0.705 level. There is also a key contracting triangle forming with support near $0.715 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair. The next key support is near the $0.68 level. If there is a downside break below the $0.68 support, the price could revisit the $0.62 support.</p>
<p>On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $0.74 level. The first major resistance is near the $0.75 level, above which the price could rise steadily.</p>
<p>The main resistance is still near $0.808. A clear move above the $0.808 level might call for more upsides. In the stated case, it could rise toward the $0.880 level. Any more gains might send the price toward the $0.925 level.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79145" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79145" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-79145" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS.png" alt="EOS Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79145" class="wp-caption-text">EOS Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/EOSUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, EOS price is now trading below the $0.75 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $0.74 and $0.75 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for EOS/USD is gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $0.705 and $0.700.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $0.740 and $0.808.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bulls-protecting-key-support-at-0-70/">EOS Price Analysis: Bulls Protecting Key Support at $0.70</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
