<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 02:54:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Key Breakout Resistance Sits At $118</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-key-breakout-resistance-sits-at-118/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-key-breakout-resistance-sits-at-118/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 03:08:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78614</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin cash is attempting a recovery wave above the $112 resistance against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above the $114 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $116 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-key-breakout-resistance-sits-at-118/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-key-breakout-resistance-sits-at-118/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Key Breakout Resistance Sits At $118</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin cash is attempting a recovery wave above the $112 resistance against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above the $114 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $116 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair must clear $116 and $118 to start a steady upward movement in the near term.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin cash price is rising above $114 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-key-resistance-near-28-5k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. BCH/USD could start a fresh surge if it clears the $118 level.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin cash price formed a decent support base above the $110 level. BCH started a decent increase and was able to clear the $112 resistance zone.</p>
<p>The price climbed above the $114 resistance level. There was a move above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $117.30 swing high to the $111.60 low. It is now trading above the $114 zone and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-105-2/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $116 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $116 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair.</p>
<p>The trend line is near the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $117.30 swing high to the $111.60 low. The next major resistance is near the $118 level, above which the price may perhaps rise toward the $120 level. Any more gains above $120 could set the pace for a move toward the $126 level.</p>
<p>If not, the price might decline again. Immediate support on the downside is near the $113 level. The first major support sits near the $112 level. The next major support is near $110, below which the bears might aim for $102. The next target for them may perhaps be near the $100 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_78615" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Bitcoin-Cash.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78615" class="size-full wp-image-78615" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Bitcoin-Cash.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash Price " width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78615" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Cash Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BCHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Bitcoin Cash’s price is now trading above the $114 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price must clear $116 and $118 to continue higher in the near term.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for BCH/USD is gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BCH/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $113 and $110.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $116 and $118.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-key-breakout-resistance-sits-at-118/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Key Breakout Resistance Sits At $118</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-key-breakout-resistance-sits-at-118/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Texas Passes New Proof of Reserves Bill for Crypto Exchanges</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-passes-new-proof-of-reserves-bill-for-crypto-exchanges/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-passes-new-proof-of-reserves-bill-for-crypto-exchanges/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 17:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[proof of reserves]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Texas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78020</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Texas House of Representatives has passed a bill saying that all crypto exchanges and related platforms must provide proof of reserves. This means that all trading companies must give regular proof that they have enough assets and currency in play to keep themselves afloat and to ensure all customers get their due funds should<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-passes-new-proof-of-reserves-bill-for-crypto-exchanges/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-passes-new-proof-of-reserves-bill-for-crypto-exchanges/">Texas Passes New Proof of Reserves Bill for Crypto Exchanges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Texas House of Representatives has passed a bill <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/savingandinvesting/texas-house-passes-cryptocurrency-bill-requiring-proof-of-reserves/ar-AA1a8Guv" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">saying that all crypto exchanges</a> and related platforms must provide proof of reserves. This means that all trading companies must give regular proof that they have enough assets and currency in play to keep themselves afloat and to ensure all customers get their due funds should problems arise.</p>
<h2>Texas Pushes for Stronger Crypto Regulations</h2>
<p>The move is clearly a reaction to the FTX debacle, which occurred last November. FTX will likely go down as one of the biggest debacles of the digital currency space. The exchange – which first opened its doors for business in 2019 – rose to prominence three years later to become one of the top five digital currency trading platforms in the world. Its founder and chief executive Sam Bankman-Fried was lauded as a genius by many, and his net worth was in the billions towards the end of 2022.</p>
<p>Sadly, this reputation was short-lived as in mid-November, SBF complained of a liquidity crunch on social media. He said he <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>needed fast cash</strong></a> to keep his business in operation, and he eventually turned to his biggest rival Binance about a possible buyout. While things <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>appeared to be moving</strong></a> in that direction for some time, Binance eventually backed <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>away from the deal</strong></a>, claiming the problems FTX was facing were simply too big for it to handle.</p>
<p>From there, the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>company filed bankruptcy</strong></a> and SBF resigned from his post. Things would have been bad enough if they had stopped there, but the trash meter kept rising. It was later discovered that SBF had utilized customer funds to invest in luxury Bahamian real estate and to pay off loans taken out by his other company Alameda Research. He <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftxs-disgraced-founder-has-been-arrested/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>was eventually arrested</strong></a> and extradited back to the United States. He has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-ftx-exec-sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-fraud/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>entered a not guilty plea</strong></a> and is awaiting trial at his <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-to-await-trial-at-his-parents-house/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>parents’ California home</strong></a>.</p>
<p>Texas is a state that <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-is-still-a-major-crypto-mining-hub/" data-wpel-link="internal">clearly takes crypto seriously</a>. The state opened itself to all the digital currency miners that had to flee their native <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-crypto-mining-clampdown-in-china-is-not-over/" data-wpel-link="internal">China after the country</a> implemented rules that outlawed all digital currency mining. Texas is known for low-priced electricity and vast open regions, thus making it the perfect place for extraction operations.</p>
<h2>Keeping Traders Safe</h2>
<p>But it’s precisely because it takes crypto so seriously that it doesn’t want to see anyone get hurt, nor does it want to see investors lose their hard-earned money due to a few faulty or fraudulent activities from those in charge. Thus, all crypto exchanges that do business within Texas or with customers in the state must submit reports no later than 90 days after the start of each fiscal year showing what reserves they have in place.</p>
<p>Many believe the move will lead to more adoption of crypto and stronger legitimacy in the industry.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-passes-new-proof-of-reserves-bill-for-crypto-exchanges/">Texas Passes New Proof of Reserves Bill for Crypto Exchanges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-passes-new-proof-of-reserves-bill-for-crypto-exchanges/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Firm Unchained Capital Has Made a Ton of Money</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-firm-unchained-capital-has-made-a-ton-of-money/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-firm-unchained-capital-has-made-a-ton-of-money/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 15:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HODLing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Unchained Capital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78010</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Unchained Capital – a crypto firm based in Austin, Texas – has garnered more than $60 million through a new funding round. Unchained Capital Garners $60 Million The news is positive for many reasons, a big one being that the crypto space appears to be returning to form, and confidence is once again making its<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-firm-unchained-capital-has-made-a-ton-of-money/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-firm-unchained-capital-has-made-a-ton-of-money/">Crypto Firm Unchained Capital Has Made a Ton of Money</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Unchained Capital – a crypto firm based in Austin, Texas – has <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/austin-based-bitcoin-financial-services-110140047.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">garnered more than $60 million</a> through a new funding round.</p>
<h2>Unchained Capital Garners $60 Million</h2>
<p>The news is positive for many reasons, a big one being that the crypto space appears to be returning to form, and confidence is once again making its way into the arena. All throughout 2022, the crypto space appeared to suffer from an apparent lack of interest due to ongoing price dips and other problems.</p>
<p>Bitcoin, for example, lost more than 70 percent of its value and fell into the mid-$16K range by the time the year was over. This was a huge step down from the new all-time high it achieved in November of 2021 (at that time, it was trading for about $68K per unit).</p>
<p>Many other digital assets chose to follow in BTC’s footsteps, and the crypto world lost more than $2 trillion in valuation in just under a year. This caused many investors to step away, and the industry lost a lot of the funding it was so prone to receiving over the past few years.</p>
<p>But with a new drop of happiness in the form of $60 million for Unchained Capital, it appears things are once again turning around. Not long ago, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin rose to $30K</a>, a ten-month high for the world’s number one digital currency by market cap, and while the price <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-falls-to-28k-analysts-are-wondering-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">has once again fallen</a> into the high $20K range, things are still in a powerful-enough position that crypto companies, right and left, are attracting institutional investors and new funding to help the industry expand and become more mature.</p>
<p>Vivek Pattipati – a partner at Vali that will soon be on Unchained Capital’s board of directors – said that while the crypto arena is enduring many challenges, he believes the company will serve as a primary leader and lift the industry out of its present doldrums. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>In the midst of market chaos, Unchained has emerged as a highly trusted provider of bitcoin custody and financial services through superior technology, risk management, regulatory compliance, and client service. Particularly in lending, the company has differentiated itself by minimizing risk to both the lender and the borrower, leading to resilience and an extraordinary opportunity to capture market share.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Working for Long-Term HODLers and Investors</h2>
<p>The company was founded seven years ago in 2016 and seeks to develop long-term technology for both individuals and enterprises looking to heighten their private key ownership. These figures are not interested in short-term gains and are instead looking to HODL their funds for a long while.</p>
<p>Unchained has also commented that the individuals it works with can maximize and secure their bitcoin holdings over “multiple generations.” Right now, the enterprise has more than $2 billion in bitcoin under its management.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-firm-unchained-capital-has-made-a-ton-of-money/">Crypto Firm Unchained Capital Has Made a Ton of Money</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-firm-unchained-capital-has-made-a-ton-of-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Moon Blocks to Permit Crypto-Based Payments</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/moon-blocks-to-permit-crypto-based-payments/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/moon-blocks-to-permit-crypto-based-payments/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 13:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bit Pay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto payments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Moon Blocks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78015</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Web3 and fintech company Moon Blocks has joined hands with payment processor Bit Pay to allow for cryptocurrency-based payments on its platform. Moon Blocks and Bit Pay Are Partners The move is pushing the goals of bitcoin and its digital counterparts closer to being achieved. What many people likely forget is that while bitcoin and many<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/moon-blocks-to-permit-crypto-based-payments/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/moon-blocks-to-permit-crypto-based-payments/">Moon Blocks to Permit Crypto-Based Payments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Web3 and fintech company Moon Blocks has <a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/press-release/moonblocks-selects-bitpay-to-accept-cryptocurrency-payments-2023-04-21" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">joined hands with payment</a> processor Bit Pay to allow for cryptocurrency-based payments on its platform.</p>
<h2>Moon Blocks and Bit Pay Are Partners</h2>
<p>The move is pushing the goals of bitcoin and its digital counterparts closer to being achieved. What many people likely forget is that while bitcoin and many of its crypto cousins have taken on either speculative or even hedge-like statuses in recent years, many of them were initially designed to serve as payment tools. They were built to push checks, credit cards, and fiat currencies to the side, but this has been a relatively slow journey given the volatility that continues to drag them down.</p>
<p>It is extremely hard to understand when <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a> and its crypto family will go up or down when it comes to their prices. Many stores and companies have been reluctant to say “yes” when it comes to accepting crypto payments for this reason, and to a degree, we can’t blame them.</p>
<p>Consider the following scenario: someone walks into a store and buys $50 worth of merchandise with bitcoin. For one reason or another, the store doesn’t trade the BTC into fiat right away and about 24 hours go by. From there, the price of BTC goes down and that $50 becomes $40. The customer gets to keep everything he or she bought, but the store loses money in the end. Is this a fair situation? Not everyone thinks so.</p>
<p>That’s what makes enterprises like Moon Blocks so important. They understand the initial purposes of bitcoin and digital currencies and are trying to transform them into usable tools that everyday people can benefit from.</p>
<p>Giuseppe – CEO at Moon Blocks – said in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>We decided to accept crypto because of [many] reasons. Firstly, we want to show that we understand and cater to a crypto-savvy audience to build trust with potential clients. Secondly, by accepting cryptocurrency payments, we can avoid high transaction fees associated with traditional payment methods and potentially offer lower prices to our clients. Additionally, embracing decentralization is at the heart of our philosophy, and accepting cryptocurrency payments can help us to position ourselves as a leader in the [industry]. To that end, by offering more payment options and flexibility, we can attract and retain clients who prefer to pay in cryptocurrency for various reasons, such as privacy concerns or a belief in the long-term value of certain cryptocurrencies. Bit Pay manages the entire process and makes it easy to receive crypto from the customer and deposits cash into our account.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Keeping Things Modern</h2>
<p>Merrick Theobald – vice president of marketing at Bit Pay – said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Moon Blocks realizes the potential for crypto to transform the Web3, fintech, SAAS, and gaming marketing industries, making payments faster, more secure, and less expensive on a global scale.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/moon-blocks-to-permit-crypto-based-payments/">Moon Blocks to Permit Crypto-Based Payments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/moon-blocks-to-permit-crypto-based-payments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EOS Price Analysis: Key Support Intact Near But Bearish Signs Emerge</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-key-support-intact-near-but-bearish-signs-emerge/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-key-support-intact-near-but-bearish-signs-emerge/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 05:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EOS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78601</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>EOS price started a downside correction from the $0.930 resistance against the US Dollar. The price is now trading near $0.875 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $0.9020 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-key-support-intact-near-but-bearish-signs-emerge/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-key-support-intact-near-but-bearish-signs-emerge/">EOS Price Analysis: Key Support Intact Near But Bearish Signs Emerge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>EOS price started a downside correction from the $0.930 resistance against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading near $0.875 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $0.9020 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it stays below the $0.90 and $0.92 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>EOS price is declining from $0.930 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-key-resistance-near-28-5k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. The price could accelerate lower if there is a clear move below the $0.875 support.</em></p>
<h2>EOS Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This week, EOS price climbed further higher above the $0.86 resistance zone against the US Dollar. The price surpassed the $0.875 level and settled above the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bears-in-control-below-0-90/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>A high was formed near $0.930 before the price started a downside correction. The price declined below the $0.90 support to move into a short-term bearish zone. Besides, there was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $0.902 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair.</p>
<p>The pair even tested the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.8170 swing low to the $0.9300 high. It is now trading near $0.875 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>On the downside, immediate support is near the $0.875 level. The next key support is near the $0.86 level. It is near the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.8170 swing low to the $0.9300 high. If there is a downside break below the $0.86 support, the price could revisit the $0.82 support.</p>
<p>On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $0.90 level. The first major resistance is near the $0.93 level, above which the price could rise steadily.</p>
<p>The main resistance is still near $0.976. A clear move above the $0.976 level might call for more upsides. In the stated case, it could rise toward the $1.00 level. Any more gains might send the price toward the $1.05 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_78602" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/EOS.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78602" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78602" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/EOS.png" alt="EOS Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78602" class="wp-caption-text">EOS Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/EOSUSD/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">chart</a>, EOS price is now trading near the $0.875 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $0.90 and $0.92 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for EOS/USD is gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $0.875 and $0.860.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $0.90 and $0.93.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-key-support-intact-near-but-bearish-signs-emerge/">EOS Price Analysis: Key Support Intact Near But Bearish Signs Emerge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-key-support-intact-near-but-bearish-signs-emerge/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Face Uphill Task Near $94</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-face-uphill-task-near-94/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-face-uphill-task-near-94/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 03:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78598</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin started a downside correction from the $95 zone against the US Dollar. LTC price is now trading above $88 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $92 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-face-uphill-task-near-94/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-face-uphill-task-near-94/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Face Uphill Task Near $94</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Litecoin started a downside correction from the $95 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>LTC price is now trading above $88 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $92 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair remains supported for a fresh increase unless there is a clear move below $86.50.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Litecoin price is correcting gains from $95 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-key-resistance-near-28-5k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. LTC price could resume its increase if it remains well supported above the $86.50 level.</em></p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, there was a decent increase in Bitcoin, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-eyes-upside-break-above-1920/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Ethereum</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-upside-break-looms-at-0-485/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Ripple</a>, and Litecoin against the US Dollar. Earlier, LTC formed a base above the $82.50 level and started a fresh increase.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above the $88 and $90 resistance levels. The price even climbed above the $92 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). However, the bears were active near the $94 zone. The recent high was formed near $93.32 and the price started a downside correction.</p>
<p>There was a move below the $92 level. The price traded below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $82.52 swing low to the $93.32 high. Besides, there was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $92 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>It is now trading above $88 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $92 level.</p>
<p>The next major resistance sits near the $94 level. A clear move above the $94 level could pump the price toward the $95 level. Any more gains might call for a test of $100. Immediate support is near the $88.00 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $82.52 swing low to the $93.32 high`.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $86.50 zone. A downside break below the $86.50 support might start a strong decline.</p>
<div id="attachment_78599" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Litecoin.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78599" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78599" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Litecoin.png" alt="Litecoin (LTC) Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78599" class="wp-caption-text">Litecoin (LTC) Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">chart</a>, Litecoin price is trading above $88 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price remains supported for a fresh increase unless there is a clear move below $86.50.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LTC/USD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $88.00 and $86.50</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $92 and $94.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-face-uphill-task-near-94/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Face Uphill Task Near $94</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-face-uphill-task-near-94/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Texas Startup My E Listing Lets You Buy Real Estate with BTC or ETH</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-startup-my-e-listing-lets-you-buy-real-estate-with-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-startup-my-e-listing-lets-you-buy-real-estate-with-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 17:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[My E Listing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[real estate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Texas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78017</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Texas startup My E Listing is launching a website that will allow users to purchase real estate in the Lone Star State with digital currency. Right now, properties can only be purchased with either bitcoin or Ethereum, but the company says it plans to extend its digital currency capabilities in the coming months. My E<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-startup-my-e-listing-lets-you-buy-real-estate-with-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-startup-my-e-listing-lets-you-buy-real-estate-with-crypto/">Texas Startup My E Listing Lets You Buy Real Estate with BTC or ETH</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Texas startup My E Listing is launching a <a href="https://www.chron.com/news/article/texas-startup-real-estate-cryptocurrency-17912708.php" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">website that will allow users</a> to purchase real estate in the Lone Star State with digital currency. Right now, properties can only be purchased with either bitcoin or Ethereum, but the company says it plans to extend its digital currency capabilities in the coming months.</p>
<h2>My E Listing Lets You Buy Your Dream Home with BTC</h2>
<p>My E Listing CEO Caleb Richter stated in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>This initiative will drive innovation in the crypto and real estate industries. Real estate commerce needs to be changed. It’s hard enough as it is to buy property in your local neighborhood, let alone in another state or country.</p></blockquote>
<p>The move is pushing the goals of bitcoin and its digital counterparts closer to being achieved. What many people likely forget is that while bitcoin and many of its crypto cousins have taken on either speculative or even hedge-like statuses in recent years, many of them were initially designed to serve as payment tools. They were built to push checks, credit cards, and fiat currencies to the side, but this has been a relatively slow journey given the volatility that continues to drag them down.</p>
<p>It is extremely hard to understand when bitcoin and its crypto family will go up or down when it comes to their prices. Many stores and companies have been reluctant to say “yes” when it comes to accepting crypto payments for this reason, and to a degree, we can’t blame them.</p>
<p>Consider the following scenario: someone walks into a store and buys $50 worth of merchandise with bitcoin. For one reason or another, the store doesn’t trade the BTC into fiat right away and about 24 hours go by. From there, the price of BTC goes down and that $50 becomes $40. The customer gets to keep everything he or she bought, but the store loses money in the end. Is this a fair situation? Not everyone thinks so.</p>
<p>That’s what makes enterprises like My E Listing so important. They understand the initial purposes of bitcoin and digital currencies and are trying to transform them into usable tools that everyday people can benefit from.</p>
<h2>A Lot of Crypto Love</h2>
<p>Texas has long been a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-is-still-a-major-crypto-mining-hub/" data-wpel-link="internal">major hub for crypto</a> activity and businesses. The state opened its borders to the many crypto miners in China after their native <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-crypto-mining-clampdown-in-china-is-not-over/" data-wpel-link="internal">country disallowed the practice</a> of extracting new units of digital currency from the blockchain. Many went to Texas so that they could continue their operations and take advantage of the region’s vast open spaces and cheap electricity prices.</p>
<p>The company has also announced a partnership with Coinbase. The leading digital currency exchange will aid the firm by converting cash into BTC or ETH and vice versa, thus allowing transactions to occur with ease.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-startup-my-e-listing-lets-you-buy-real-estate-with-crypto/">Texas Startup My E Listing Lets You Buy Real Estate with BTC or ETH</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-startup-my-e-listing-lets-you-buy-real-estate-with-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elderly Woman Loses Lots of Money to Crypto Scam</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elderly-woman-loses-lots-of-money-to-crypto-scam/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elderly-woman-loses-lots-of-money-to-crypto-scam/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 15:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scam]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[woman]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78008</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An elderly woman – who’s choosing not to be named at the time of writing – has been scammed out of $20K through the illicit use of a bitcoin ATM. Woman Loses $20K to Bitcoin Fraud The woman recalled in an interview how the situation came about. She received a call from someone claiming to<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elderly-woman-loses-lots-of-money-to-crypto-scam/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elderly-woman-loses-lots-of-money-to-crypto-scam/">Elderly Woman Loses Lots of Money to Crypto Scam</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An elderly woman – who’s choosing not to be named at the time of writing – has been scammed out of $20K through <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/newton-grandmother-scammed-out-of-20000-used-bitcoin-atms-to-send-money/ar-AA1a4XM7" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">the illicit use of a bitcoin</a> ATM.</p>
<h2>Woman Loses $20K to Bitcoin Fraud</h2>
<p>The woman recalled in an interview how the situation came about. She received a call from someone claiming to be a federal agent, and he mentioned she had potentially been the subject of identity theft. She commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>He said, &#8216;Alright, are you ready to go to the bank?&#8217; I said yes.” He spelled his name for me. He had me put his phone number into Google. It took me directly to the US Marshals Service website.</p></blockquote>
<p>On the site is a distinct warning claiming events like these are becoming very common. Nevertheless, the woman either didn’t see it or wasn’t aware that the situation was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/scam/" data-wpel-link="internal">scam-ridden</a>. She said there was no threatening tone from her caller, and thus she had no choice but to take things seriously.</p>
<p>She said she was instructed to go to her local bank and withdraw some money. From there, she was told to go to a bitcoin ATM and purchase the asset. She was told, in her own words:</p>
<blockquote><p>Then, you&#8217;re going to go and use that money to buy bitcoin. It&#8217;ll go into a wallet that is strictly yours. Your name is on it. It&#8217;s your money.</p></blockquote>
<p>When she went to the bank to withdraw the necessary funds (which turned out to be around $30K), she said she wasn’t questioned by any of the tellers, and nobody hinted that things may not be what they seemed. She mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>The teller said, &#8216;We don&#8217;t carry that kind of money. The best we can do is give you $9,000 and small bills.’ He called over and found out the branch in Needham could give me $10,000.</p></blockquote>
<p>After she had sent about $20K to the person she spoke with on the phone, she stopped at her attorney’s office and asked him for advice about what to do regarding the situation. She wasn’t two sentences in when her attorney said she was being victimized.</p>
<p>Her bank – Citizens Bank – has put out a statement concerning her situation. It reads:</p>
<blockquote><p>We are sorry to hear that one of our customers may have been the victim of a scam&#8230; We do work closely with law enforcement when incidents occur and provide training for our colleagues in order to help detect such incidents.</p></blockquote>
<h2>The Money May Have Disappeared</h2>
<p>Police in her town are investigating the matter, but it’s likely her money is gone. The woman said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I&#8217;m just pulling myself together now. It was just a terrible ordeal. This can happen to you. It doesn&#8217;t matter how smart you are. It doesn&#8217;t matter how skeptical you are. You can be had. They&#8217;re very good at what they do.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elderly-woman-loses-lots-of-money-to-crypto-scam/">Elderly Woman Loses Lots of Money to Crypto Scam</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elderly-woman-loses-lots-of-money-to-crypto-scam/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Slumps, and Analysts Are Wondering Why</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-falls-to-28k-analysts-are-wondering-why/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-falls-to-28k-analysts-are-wondering-why/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 13:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78005</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At the time of writing, the price of bitcoin – the world’s number one digital currency by market cap – has fallen towards $28K, about $2,000 less from where it was just a few weeks ago. During that period, the currency rose to about $30K for the first time in about ten or 11 months,<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-falls-to-28k-analysts-are-wondering-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-falls-to-28k-analysts-are-wondering-why/">Bitcoin Slumps, and Analysts Are Wondering Why</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>At the time of writing, the price of bitcoin – the world’s number one digital currency by market cap – has fallen towards $28K, about $2,000 less <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/04/20/bitcoin-moves-toward-28000-as-worlds-largest-crypto-extends-losses/?sh=6b23c6965b2f" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">from where it was just a few</a> weeks ago. During that period, the currency rose to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">about $30K for the</a> first time in about ten or 11 months, giving everyone the feeling that it was somehow stepping onto an entirely new bullish path.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Has Fallen Back a Bit</h2>
<p>Crypto analyst Tim Enneking recently blamed rising <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/federal-reserve-hikes-rates-again-what-will-happen-to-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">federal interest rates</a> for why the price of bitcoin continues to endure small periods of suffering. In an interview, he said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The entire world (crypto and fiat) is basically on tenterhooks waiting for the May 3 FOMC decision… Although the correlation between crypto and fiat has generally weakened this year, major events still cause correlation, and the pending FOMC decision has halted the upward movement of crypto. That, plus regulatory uncertainty (the SEC and Bittrex, MICA), banking difficulties (Silvergate, Signature), and contagion fears (banking, commercial real estate) are all conspiring to create a retracement after what, for BTC especially, has been a major move up.</p></blockquote>
<p>The price of bitcoin also appears to have been hit by the news of Coinbase potentially looking into relocating to Bermuda. The top crypto exchange has applied for a license in that part of the world and will allegedly investigate leaving the U.S. While customers in America will still be serviced, Coinbase is not likely to remain within the nation’s borders. The company has cited ongoing regulatory concerns as the reason for the move.</p>
<p>Not long ago, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">Coinbase was hit with a Wells</a> notice by the SEC, who said that while the exchange had not yet been charged with a crime, charges were likely coming. Coinbase took issue with this and said it met with the SEC several times over the course of the last nine years to ensure it remained compliant.</p>
<p>Scott Melker – a crypto writer and investor – said the latest bitcoin slide is nothing to worry about, commenting:</p>
<blockquote><p>For now, this is nothing more than a healthy retracement after an overextended move to the upside.</p></blockquote>
<p>Marc Bernegger – co-founder of crypto fund Alt Alpha Digital – also threw his two cents into the mix, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>I personally think that the massive gains in recent weeks made investors take some profits from the table, which might have been a trigger for this long squeeze.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Rises May Still Occur</h2>
<p>Some analysts believe the price of bitcoin is going to do quite well in the future. Robert Kiyosaki – author of “Rich Dad Poor Dad” – for example, has <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/stocks/rich-dad-poor-dad-author-says-people-s-money-bitcoin-on-its-way-to-100k-1032249559" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">commented that bitcoin</a> will soon hit $100K. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>People support [bitcoin], not Fed or gov. [Bitcoin] did not need Fed or gov bailout because [bitcoin] people&#8217;s money. [Bitcoin] to $100k. Long live [bitcoin].</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-falls-to-28k-analysts-are-wondering-why/">Bitcoin Slumps, and Analysts Are Wondering Why</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-falls-to-28k-analysts-are-wondering-why/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
