<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 04:02:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/cropped-fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Law Professor Yuliya Guseva on the Binance, Ripple, and Coinbase Lawsuits</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/law-professor-yuliya-guseva-on-the-binance-ripple-and-coinbase-lawsuits/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 17:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Yuliya Guseva]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78741</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Do the present lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase raise any red flags? A law professor at Rutgers University named Yuliya Guseva believes they do, and she thinks it’s highly unlikely nations like the U.S. will be able to dole out proper regulation before financial agencies do irreparable damage. Yuliya Guseva on the State of Crypto [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/law-professor-yuliya-guseva-on-the-binance-ripple-and-coinbase-lawsuits/">Law Professor Yuliya Guseva on the Binance, Ripple, and Coinbase Lawsuits</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do the present lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase <a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/as-sec-brings-charges-against-binance-and-coinbase-watch-out-for-three-red-flags-before-investing-in-crypto-1a63e554">raise any red flags</a>? A law professor at Rutgers University named Yuliya Guseva believes they do, and she thinks it’s highly unlikely nations like the U.S. will be able to dole out proper regulation before financial agencies do irreparable damage.</p>
<h2>Yuliya Guseva on the State of Crypto in America</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, Guseva said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The future of crypto-asset regulation in the U.S. is not fully predictable.</p></blockquote>
<p>Right now, the crypto industry in the United States appears to be more up in the air than it’s ever been. Besides both <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-hit-with-sec-lawsuit-says-it-operated-as-an-exchange-broker/">Coinbase</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sues-binance-alleges-selling-of-illegal-securities/">Binance</a>, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has another lawsuit <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-secs-case-against-ripple-could-result-in-a-massive-win-for-the-crypto-company/">with Ripple</a>, one of the world’s leading crypto companies. Stuart Alderoty – chief legal officer for the firm – recently stated in an interview regarding the charges against his firm:</p>
<blockquote><p>Even if true, this only shows that the SEC’s unelected bureaucrats believe they have unchecked power to issue indiscriminate, closed-door edicts under pain of punishment to those who don’t blindly obey. We have crossed from regulation by enforcement to hubris most foul.</p></blockquote>
<p>In a recent blog post, Binance said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The SEC’s real intent here, instead, appears to be to make headlines. All user assets on Binance and Binance-affiliate platforms, including Binance.US, are safe and secure, and we will vigorously defend against any allegations to the contrary.</p></blockquote>
<p>Paul Grewal – the chief legal officer and general counsel for Coinbase – also threw his two cents into the mix, stating:</p>
<blockquote><p>The SEC’s reliance on an enforcement-only approach in the absence of clear rules for the digital asset industry is hurting America’s economic competitiveness and companies like Coinbase that have a demonstrated commitment to compliance. In the meantime, we’ll continue to operate our business as usual.</p></blockquote>
<p>Guseva says the outcome of the Ripple lawsuit could prove huge for the future of crypto in America. She mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>There is a progression of SEC enforcement actions. The SEC started with primary markets, namely unregistered [initial coin offerings]. Ripple is one of the last cases of this generation. The primary question in these cases is whether crypto assets are securities. The outcome of the Ripple litigation, therefore, will be a major win or loss for the SEC.</p></blockquote>
<p>Brian Armstrong – the CEO of Coinbase – said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I always tell people the same thing. Don’t invest money you are unwilling to lose. This is a new field of technology. It’s one of the most important technological fields in the world, but don’t speculate with assets that you are unwilling to lose.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Customer Funds Are Safe</h2>
<p>However, Oleg Elkhunovich – a partner at Susman Godfrey – says the SEC is not after customers’ funds. He explained that this is primarily against the companies:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Disgorgement is a remedy that goes after improperly [obtained] gains. Those would not be user assets. User assets should be separated.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/law-professor-yuliya-guseva-on-the-binance-ripple-and-coinbase-lawsuits/">Law Professor Yuliya Guseva on the Binance, Ripple, and Coinbase Lawsuits</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nicholas Taleb Still Doesn&#8217;t Think Much of BTC</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nicholas-taleb-still-doesnt-think-much-of-btc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 15:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nicholas Taleb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warren Buffett]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78739</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin is a big asset. It’s got legions of fans all over the world, and it appears to be taking a higher level of precedence in U.S. national politics and similar arenas. However, it’s become clear over time that the world’s biggest and most popular digital asset isn’t going to attract positive attention from everyone, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nicholas-taleb-still-doesnt-think-much-of-btc/">Nicholas Taleb Still Doesn&#8217;t Think Much of BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin is a big asset. It’s got legions of fans all over the world, and it appears to be taking a higher level of precedence in U.S. national politics and similar arenas. However, it’s become clear over time that the world’s biggest and most popular digital asset isn’t going to attract positive attention from everyone, and one of its biggest haters – Nassim Nicholas Taleb, the author of the novel “Black Swan” – <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nicholas-taleb-still-aint-crazy-about-crypto/">has consistently</a> made it clear he’s not a fan.</p>
<h2>Nicholas Taleb Doesn&#8217;t Care for BTC</h2>
<p>Not long ago, Taleb came out <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-is-a-cult-offers-no-refuge-and-doesnt-help-even-the-bad-guys-black-swan-author-nassim-taleb-says/ar-AA1ckig7">to do another interview</a> about how bad and weak he considers bitcoin to be. He stated that not only does it not help anyone accomplish anything good, but it also doesn’t even do much for those with illicit intent. He says it’s not a “safe haven” like everyone thinks, and he doesn’t even think it’s good for money laundering or similar crimes. Taleb stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I actually have been a critic of bitcoin for reasons like my principal reason. Well, guess what? It&#8217;s not even good for money laundering. It is too traceable. Bitcoin is a book entry somewhere that anyone with basic knowledge and statistics can triangularize. The second one is that it was transformed into a cult. The first time in history, probably, we&#8217;re mixing money and [a] cult. Here&#8217;s a cult with a financial product. These things don&#8217;t go together very well.</p></blockquote>
<p>In past discussions, Taleb has referred to bitcoin as a “tumor.” In other words, he doesn’t think highly of it, and unfortunately, he’s not the only one. Rich men like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/warren-buffett/">Warren Buffett</a> – the CEO and founder of Berkshire Hathaway, one of America’s largest real estate giants – has commented in the past that he thinks bitcoin is “rat poison squared,” and it’s likely he’ll never get involved in the crypto arena.</p>
<p>Over the past several years, bitcoin has had something of a mixed run. One of the biggest problems surrounding the bitcoin space is the fact that the currency remains as volatile as ever. One can never truly predict when (or where) it’s going to move, and this has become a major issue for skilled, eager investors looking to do well.</p>
<h2>Up and Down, Up and Down</h2>
<p>There have been instances, such as in 2018 and 2022 (the years of two huge crypto crashes), in which investors lose everything they have. Instances like these don’t paint the industry in the cleanest light.</p>
<p>Still, one can make the argument that the arena has come a long way in very little time. When one considers the fact that bitcoin is only 14 years old (it was first mined in January of 2009), it can’t help but be admired, and the technology behind it has given rise to several new financial fads.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nicholas-taleb-still-doesnt-think-much-of-btc/">Nicholas Taleb Still Doesn&#8217;t Think Much of BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DA Alvin Bragg Targets Crypto Firm Coin Dispute Network</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/da-alvin-bragg-targets-crypto-firm-coin-dispute-network/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 13:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alvin Bragg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coin Dispute Network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trump]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78735</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coin Dispute Network – a company that claims to help customers retrieve their lost or stolen crypto – is currently under investigation by the Manhattan District Attorney’s office run by the allegedly corrupt Alvin Bragg. Bragg and Coin Dispute Network Are in a War Bragg has said the company is “fraudulent,” and he’s attempting to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/da-alvin-bragg-targets-crypto-firm-coin-dispute-network/">DA Alvin Bragg Targets Crypto Firm Coin Dispute Network</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coin Dispute Network – a company that claims to help <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/manhattan-da-slams-cryptocurrency-recovery-company-as-fraudulent/ar-AA1ciIPN">customers retrieve their</a> lost or stolen crypto – is currently under investigation by the Manhattan District Attorney’s office run by the allegedly corrupt Alvin Bragg.</p>
<h2>Bragg and Coin Dispute Network Are in a War</h2>
<p>Bragg has said the company is “fraudulent,” and he’s attempting to seize the domain name. The gist of Coin Dispute Network is that customers must pay a fee to get the company involved, which then begins tracing whatever crypto units are gone and reports its findings to law enforcement so they can freeze and retrieve the digital currency.</p>
<p>Granted the money is found and returned, Coin Dispute Network takes a further cut, which seems rather straightforward. However, per a statement issued by Bragg, the company went further than that and not only kept fees, but also stole additional Ethereum units from the wallets of their customers by “making false promises of asset recovery and [generating] inaccurate blockchain tracing reports to victims.”</p>
<p>Bragg has been after the company since November of last year. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>We want victims of the Coin Dispute Network, no matter where you are, to come forward as we work to hold these bad actors accountable and prevent future fraud.</p></blockquote>
<p>From the sound of things, it looks like Bragg is a man who’s doing his job. A person who cares about justice and is worried about the unregulated state of digital currency, but this would be deceiving, and for him to call anything “fraudulent” would be equivalent to a pig calling something “sloppy.” Let’s not forget that this is the same man <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-fans-see-joe-biden-for-the-destructive-force-he-is/">who recently indicted</a> President Donald Trump over a non-disclosure agreement from seven years ago while letting committers of domestic violence off the hook.</p>
<p>Trump’s case was examined by larger institutions like the Federal Election Committee (FEC) and the federal government, both of which said no crime had been committed and there was nothing to prosecute. Bragg, however, ran his campaign on the idea that he would bring Trump down, and he’s now taking on a case that’s not even within his jurisdiction.</p>
<p>We’re also well beyond the statute of limitations, so it&#8217;s become clear that Bragg is probably a Biden puppet looking to take the most powerful republican candidate out of the 2024 race before things get too hairy for democrats.</p>
<h2>A Compromised DA?</h2>
<p>Furthermore, Bragg is reportedly funded by American enemy George Soros, so it’s clear this man’s morals may not be intact. He’s got a demon on his shoulder telling him what to do, and so long as that demon exists, ugly things are going to happen.</p>
<p>Many people in law enforcement claim companies like Coin Dispute Network don’t work, and that it’s very hard to recover stolen crypto funds.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/da-alvin-bragg-targets-crypto-firm-coin-dispute-network/">DA Alvin Bragg Targets Crypto Firm Coin Dispute Network</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Remains Supported For Fresh Rally Above $0.18</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-remains-supported-for-fresh-rally-above-0-18/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 05:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar Lumens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79408</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stellar lumen price started a downside correction from the $0.180 zone against the US Dollar. XLM price is now trading above $0.1450 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.160 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could start another [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-remains-supported-for-fresh-rally-above-0-18/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Remains Supported For Fresh Rally Above $0.18</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Stellar lumen price started a downside correction from the $0.180 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>XLM price is now trading above $0.1450 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.160 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start another increase if it clears the $0.160 and $0.1675 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Stellar lumen price is trading above $0.150 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-regain-strength-above-this-hurdle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bitcoin</a>. XLM’s price must stay above the $0.145 support to rise again.</em></p>
<h2>Stellar Lumen Price Analysis (XLM to USD)</h2>
<p>After forming a base above the $0.120 level, Stellar lumen price started a fresh increase against the US Dollar. The XLM/USD pair broke the $0.150 resistance zone to move into a positive zone.</p>
<p>The price even cleared the $0.1650 resistance and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-restart-increase-above-0-142/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. The upward move was such that the price spiked to $0.180 before it corrected lower. There was a drop below the $0.175 support level.</p>
<p>The price is now testing the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.1244 swing low to the $0.1807 high. XLM is now trading above $0.1450 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $0.160 zone. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.160 on the 4-hour chart. The next major resistance is near the $0.1675 level. A clear move above the $0.1670 level might send the price toward the $0.1800 level.</p>
<p>Any more gains could lead the price toward the $0.1920 level or even $0.20. Initial support on the downside is near the $0.150 level.</p>
<p>The next major support sits near the $0.1450 level or the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.1244 swing low to the $0.1807 high. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.1250 level in the near term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79409" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79409" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-3.png"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-79409" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-3.png" alt="Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-3.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-3-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-3-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-3-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-3-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-3-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-3-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79409" class="wp-caption-text">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XLMUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a> indicates that XLM’s price is now trading above $0.145 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start another increase if it clears the $0.160 and $0.1675 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XLM/USD is losing momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for XLM/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.150 and $0.145.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.160, $0.1675, and $0.180.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-remains-supported-for-fresh-rally-above-0-18/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Remains Supported For Fresh Rally Above $0.18</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Price Analysis: Bulls Protect Uptrend Support, Aims Fresh Rally</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-protect-uptrend-support-aims-fresh-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 03:58:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79405</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple price started a downside correction below the $0.820 zone against the US dollar. The price is now trading below $0.80 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.738 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Kraken). The pair [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-protect-uptrend-support-aims-fresh-rally/">Ripple Price Analysis: Bulls Protect Uptrend Support, Aims Fresh Rally</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ripple price started a downside correction below the $0.820 zone against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $0.80 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.738 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a fresh increase above the $0.750 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ripple price is consolidating near $0.720 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-regain-strength-above-this-hurdle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. XRP price must stay above the $0.70 support to start a fresh increase.</em></p>
<h2>Ripple Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, Ripple price made another attempt to clear the $0.850 resistance against the US Dollar. The XRP/USD pair struggled to clear $0.850 and started a downside correction.</p>
<p>There was a move below the $0.820 and $0.800 support levels. However, the bulls were active above the $0.70 support. A low is formed near $0.715 and the price is now consolidating losses. XRP is now trading below $0.80 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-aim-fresh-rally-to-0-85/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near $0.735. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.738 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair.</p>
<p>The trend line is near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.8525 swing high to the $0.7156 low. The next major resistance is near the $0.750 level. A clear move above the $0.750 resistance zone might start a strong increase.</p>
<p>In the stated case, the price could even surpass the $0.785 resistance or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.8525 swing high to the $0.7156 low. Any more gains might send the price toward the $0.850 resistance.</p>
<p>Initial support on the downside is near the $0.715 level. The next major support is near the $0.70 level. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.650 level, below which the price might even test the $0.620 support zone in the near term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79406" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79406" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple-3.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-79406" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple-3.png" alt="Ripple Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple-3.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple-3-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple-3-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple-3-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple-3-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple-3-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple-3-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79406" class="wp-caption-text">Ripple Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/">chart</a>, Ripple’s price is now trading below the $0.80 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start a fresh increase above the $0.75 resistance.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XRP/USD is now losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for XRP/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.715, $0.700, and $0.650.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.735 and $0.750.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-protect-uptrend-support-aims-fresh-rally/">Ripple Price Analysis: Bulls Protect Uptrend Support, Aims Fresh Rally</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Charges Laid Out Against Two Men in Mt. Gox Case</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/charges-laid-out-against-two-men-in-mt-gox-case/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 17:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alexander Vinnik]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[conspiracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mt Gox]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78733</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Has justice arrived in the Mt. Gox case? Perhaps that’s the scenario as after nearly ten years, two Russian men have been charged with conspiring to steal more than 600,000 bitcoin units. Is the Mt. Gox Case Coming to an End? The federal government has laid charges out against Alexey Bilyuchenko and Aleksandr Verner. They’re [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/charges-laid-out-against-two-men-in-mt-gox-case/">Charges Laid Out Against Two Men in Mt. Gox Case</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Has justice arrived in the Mt. Gox case? Perhaps that’s the scenario as after nearly ten years, two Russian men have been <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/feds-charge-two-men-for-the-400-million-bitcoin-hack-that-took-down-mt-gox/ar-AA1clqdf">charged with conspiring</a> to steal more than 600,000 bitcoin units.</p>
<h2>Is the Mt. Gox Case Coming to an End?</h2>
<p>The federal government has laid charges out against Alexey Bilyuchenko and Aleksandr Verner. They’re accused of conspiring to launder as much as 647,000 BTC funds stolen from the exchange. At the time of the theft, these units would have been worth around $400 million, a figure that would be up tenfold today.</p>
<p>Also, Bilychenko is charged separately for trying to launder the money through BTC-e – a fraudulent exchange – run by Alexander Vinnik, a notorious Russian crypto criminal that <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/alleged-crypto-thief-alexander-vinnik-extradited-to-u-s/">was recently extradited</a> to the U.S. for financial crimes. Assistant attorney general Kenneth A. Polite, Jr. commented in a recent statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>As alleged in the indictments, starting in 2011, Bilyuchenko and Verner stole a massive amount of cryptocurrency from Mt. Gox, contributing to the exchange’s ultimate insolvency. Armed with the ill-gotten gains from Mt. Gox, Bilyuchenko allegedly went on to help set up the notorious BTC-e virtual currency exchange, which laundered funds for cyber criminals worldwide.</p></blockquote>
<p>If the end of the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/mt-gox/">Mt. Gox</a> debacle is finally and truly coming to an end, then congratulations to those at the top of the justice ladder… It only took them nine years to get things in order. Mt. Gox was one of the first major bitcoin exchange hacks to occur in the industry. Happening in February of 2014, the exchange saw more than $400 million (the sum listed above) vanish into thin air from one night to the next.</p>
<p>For years, it was assumed that the CEO of the exchange Mark Karpeles was guilty of having something to do with the money’s disappearance, and he was close <a href="https://apnews.com/article/bitcoin-tokyo-embezzlement-business-financial-markets-4cb64156038a48c1abbedfa64982537c">to spending time</a> in a Japanese jail after he was arrested for crimes relating to the platform’s end. However, this situation takes things in a whole new direction, and it’s hard to know who’s truly at fault.</p>
<p>The circumstances surrounding Mt. Gox have always been mysterious. They have also led to a string of related crimes over the years to the point that it’s now no longer the largest crypto theft to have ever occurred… Not by a long shot.</p>
<h2>Hacks Keeps Happening</h2>
<p>An even bigger “mishap” took place roughly four years later in early 2018. Also occurring in Japan (where Mt. Gox was situated), the victim this time around was crypto exchange <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/coincheck/">Coincheck</a>, and the platform wound up losing more than half a billion in assorted crypto funds.</p>
<p>The cycle has only continued since then, and many crypto exchanges over the years have worked hard to implement know your customer (KYC) tactics to ensure that their clients (and their reserves) remain safe.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/charges-laid-out-against-two-men-in-mt-gox-case/">Charges Laid Out Against Two Men in Mt. Gox Case</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cathie Wood on the Coinbase-SEC Lawsuit and BTC&#8217;s Price</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-on-the-coinbase-sec-lawsuit-and-btcs-price/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 15:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cathie Wood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78730</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ark Investment Management founder and CEO Cathie Wood – a longtime bitcoin bull – has thrown herself into the Coinbase mess involving the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and is defending the exchange. She also believes bitcoin could jump into $600K territory within the next seven years. Cathie Wood on Where Bitcoin Will Go Wood [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-on-the-coinbase-sec-lawsuit-and-btcs-price/">Cathie Wood on the Coinbase-SEC Lawsuit and BTC&#8217;s Price</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ark Investment Management founder and CEO Cathie Wood – a longtime bitcoin bull – has thrown <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/cathie-wood-maintains-600000-bitcoin-forecast-defends-coinbase-shares-purchase-amid-sec-battle/ar-AA1cljnn">herself into the</a> Coinbase <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-hit-with-sec-lawsuit-says-it-operated-as-an-exchange-broker/">mess involving the</a> Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and is defending the exchange. She also believes bitcoin could jump into $600K territory within the next seven years.</p>
<h2>Cathie Wood on Where Bitcoin Will Go</h2>
<p>Wood mentioned she thinks the SEC is going about the situation all wrong. All the agency wants to do is persecute when the rules are either nonexistent or difficult to understand. She believes there’s a checks and balances system in the United States that will come to full effect following the culmination of the lawsuit. She also believes that Coinbase is likely to come out on top when this is all over.</p>
<p>Lastly, she mentioned that issues like this keep arising in recent weeks, and she’s confident that these sorts of situations are going to hold serious sway in the 2024 presidential election. She commented that people are tired of the government simply going after people or entities that don’t fall in line with its beliefs, and that people are likely to do something about this with their votes. She commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>No, we’re actually betting on the checks and balances inherent in our government. The SEC and uncertainty around [cryptocurrencies] are chasing digital asset business away from this country. I think the legislative branch understands it. This will be an election year issue.</p></blockquote>
<p>Her conversation then transitioned from Coinbase to the price of bitcoin. Wood has constantly made comments that bitcoin could reach <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-btc-will-be-priced-at-1-5-million-in-2030/">more than $1 million</a> by the year 2030, and while she’s backtracking on that a bit in this recent interview, she did mention that the world’s number one digital currency by market cap will at least stand beyond $600,000 over the next seven years. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>This is the first global private, no government oversight, digital rule-based monetary system, and there’s a lot of discipline here.</p></blockquote>
<p>She commented that bitcoin is also gaining a lot more respect given <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-provide-their-thoughts-on-latest-bitcoin-rally/">the banking debacle</a> that happened in America early in the year. She said the currency’s price rose several times while banks crashed, and she believes people see bitcoin as more of a “safe haven” than ever.</p>
<h2>The Banks Have Helped BTC</h2>
<p>She commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>If you all notice, the regional bank stocks were imploding, and bitcoin went from $19,000 up to roughly $30,000, so what was that? That was a flight to safety. A flight to safety, think about that. We think all innovation is going to be a flight to safety.</p></blockquote>
<p>If Wood is right and bitcoin is indeed on a fast track to $600K, this would mark a huge difference from where it was just last year, when the currency crashed and fell into the mid-$16K range.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-on-the-coinbase-sec-lawsuit-and-btcs-price/">Cathie Wood on the Coinbase-SEC Lawsuit and BTC&#8217;s Price</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gary Gensler of the SEC Suffers Freudian Slip, and His Crypto Agenda Couldn&#8217;t Be Clearer</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gary-gensler-of-the-sec-suffers-freudian-slip-and-his-crypto-agenda-couldnt-be-clearer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 13:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78704</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Merely hours after the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filed lawsuits against both Binance and Coinbase – two of the biggest and most popular digital currency trading platforms in the world – the agency’s head Gary Gensler made comments that the entire crypto industry is “built on non-compliance” and that the U.S. doesn’t “need more [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gary-gensler-of-the-sec-suffers-freudian-slip-and-his-crypto-agenda-couldnt-be-clearer/">Gary Gensler of the SEC Suffers Freudian Slip, and His Crypto Agenda Couldn&#8217;t Be Clearer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Merely hours after the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filed lawsuits against both <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sues-binance-alleges-selling-of-illegal-securities/">Binance</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-hit-with-sec-lawsuit-says-it-operated-as-an-exchange-broker/">Coinbase</a> – two of the biggest and most popular digital currency trading platforms in the world – the agency’s head Gary Gensler <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/sec-chair-gary-gensler-us-184347676.html">made comments that the</a> entire crypto industry is “built on non-compliance” and that the U.S. doesn’t “need more digital currency.”</p>
<h2>The SEC Is Mixed Up</h2>
<p>With that latter comment, it truly becomes clear what Gensler is all about… Getting rid of crypto in America for good. He doesn’t care about rules or regulation or financial growth. He has an agenda to dismantle crypto 100 percent, and he’s clearly not going to stop until he gets what he wants.</p>
<p>This makes sense given how many companies his agency has been going after. It can’t be that <em>all</em> these firms have committed crimes or gone against present rules. <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-the-problems-between-the-sec-and-crypto-go-deep/">It’s simply impossible</a>. Coinbase executives, for example, after getting <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/">a Wells notice</a> last April that informed them of impending charges from the SEC, even commented that they had met with several representatives of the financial agency over a nine-year period to ensure they always remained compliant.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s simply out of the question that during those nine years and all those meetings, the SEC didn’t catch onto crimes Coinbase was engaged in. The idea that it’s taken this long suggests that Coinbase has done nothing wrong, and it’s simply the next big victim to be added to Gensler’s ongoing financial death list. It’s not fair, it’s not right, and it goes in tandem with what we’re seeing in America today.</p>
<p>Gensler has yet to have any say in the officiation of the crypto industry. He has never worked towards any regulatory matters, and now we know why… He’s not interested in the regulation of the space; he’s interested in the <em>death</em> of the space. Following his comments that the U.S. doesn’t need crypto, he mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>We already have digital currency. It’s called the U.S. dollar. It’s called [the] euro. It’s called the yen. They’re all digital now.</p></blockquote>
<p>This tells us that not only is Gensler probably a nasty person, but he’s also completely out of it. He refers to fiat assets like the U.S. dollar, the yen, and what have you as “digital.” <em>How</em>, Gary? <em>How</em> are they digital? The last time we checked, $1 was still printed out in paper form. <em>What are you talking about?</em></p>
<h2>Fiat and Digital Currency Are Very Different</h2>
<p>Is he referring to credit cards? While they may be centered around digital forms of fiat, the money in question doesn’t come from the plastic card that’s used to make purchases. Thus, the money itself is not digital. <em>What does he mean?</em></p>
<p>You know there’s a problem when the head of a financial agency doesn’t understand or comprehend the differences between financial entities or tools.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gary-gensler-of-the-sec-suffers-freudian-slip-and-his-crypto-agenda-couldnt-be-clearer/">Gary Gensler of the SEC Suffers Freudian Slip, and His Crypto Agenda Couldn&#8217;t Be Clearer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>It&#8217;s a Win for Coinbase as SEC Made to Answer Year-Old Regulatory Petition</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/its-a-win-for-coinbase-as-sec-made-to-answer-year-old-regulatory-petition/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 17:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78707</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Just yesterday, it was announced that popular digital currency trading platform Coinbase was being sued by the SEC. The news came as a shock to many, and it’s clearly another step in the agency’s agenda to rid the country of crypto for good. Coinbase Gets Its Way Against the SEC The good news is that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/its-a-win-for-coinbase-as-sec-made-to-answer-year-old-regulatory-petition/">It&#8217;s a Win for Coinbase as SEC Made to Answer Year-Old Regulatory Petition</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Just yesterday, it was announced that popular digital currency trading platform Coinbase <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-hit-with-sec-lawsuit-says-it-operated-as-an-exchange-broker/">was being sued</a> by the SEC. The news came as a shock to many, and it’s clearly another step in the agency’s agenda to rid the country of crypto for good.</p>
<h2>Coinbase Gets Its Way Against the SEC</h2>
<p>The good news is that Coinbase doesn’t appear to be <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/06/07/crypto-now-braced-for-another-sec-bombshell-that-could-create-chaos-for-the-price-of-bitcoin-ethereum-bnb-and-xrp/?sh=38adebb43ec3">taking the abuse sitting</a> down, and it recently got a legal win in its corner. Not long ago, the exchange made headlines when it <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-sues-sec-demands-answers-regarding-months-old-petition/">filed suit against the</a> SEC for not answering a now year-old survey regarding regulatory statutes in the U.S. that could potentially surround crypto.</p>
<p>A federal judge has since ruled in favor of the exchange and says the Securities and Exchange Commission must respond to the survey within a seven-day period and provide the insight the trading company has been seeking since July of 2022.</p>
<p>While this isn’t likely to put any serious dents in the lawsuit the SEC has against Coinbase, it could hold things up for a while. In fact, it may even force the circumstances of the lawsuit to change so that things can be easier on Coinbase in the future. The idea is to garner information from the SEC about how present securities laws would or should apply to assets like BTC and ETH.</p>
<p>Paul Grewal – chief legal officer for Coinbase – said on social media:</p>
<blockquote><p>Rules of the road, from legislation or rulemaking or both, must come before enforcement actions. That is why we petitioned the SEC for rulemaking nearly a year ago in the first place. We continue to believe that the SEC could not be proceeding with litigation against our industry, like the case filed against us… if the SEC had not already decided to deny our petition for rulemaking… If the SEC’s answer to our petition for rulemaking is &#8216;no,&#8217; then they are required by law to tell us, because we have the legal right to question that &#8216;no&#8217; in court, and there are serious questions to be asked.</p></blockquote>
<p>The SEC has taken on a pattern of “regulation by enforcement” according to many crypto fans and analysts. This pertains to the idea that the SEC has not put out any rules regarding crypto, nor has it worked to clarify present regulations. All it’s done is attack and sue.</p>
<h2>Bringing Down Big Names</h2>
<p>SEC head Gary Gensler has defended this approach on several occasions. In a recent interview, he said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The investing public has the benefit of U.S. securities laws. Crypto should be no different, and these platforms, these intermediaries need to come into compliance.</p></blockquote>
<p>Among the many other crypto firms to fall victim to the SEC’s antics are Kraken – which was forced to part <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/">with a $30 million fee</a> and end all staking services – and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sues-binance-alleges-selling-of-illegal-securities/">Binance</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/its-a-win-for-coinbase-as-sec-made-to-answer-year-old-regulatory-petition/">It&#8217;s a Win for Coinbase as SEC Made to Answer Year-Old Regulatory Petition</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
