<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 16:54:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Jim Chanos: Crypto Is Like the Dotcom Era All Over Again</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jim-chanos-crypto-is-like-the-dotcom-era-all-over-again/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jim-chanos-crypto-is-like-the-dotcom-era-all-over-again/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 17:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dotcom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jim Chanos]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75727</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Renowned short-seller Jim Chanos has stated that the current crypto environment is like the “dotcom era on steroids,” and he thinks the recent collapse of popular digital currency exchange FTX is the start of a long and negative era for digital currency. Jim Chanos: Crypto&#8217;s Future Looks Bleak Chanos predicted that Texas energy company Enron<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jim-chanos-crypto-is-like-the-dotcom-era-all-over-again/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jim-chanos-crypto-is-like-the-dotcom-era-all-over-again/">Jim Chanos: Crypto Is Like the Dotcom Era All Over Again</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Renowned short-seller Jim Chanos has stated <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/billybambrough/2022/11/23/dot-com-era-on-steroids-heres-how-bad-the-22-trillion-bitcoin-and-crypto-ftx-price-crash-could-get/?sh=1067d9615cc8" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">that the current crypto</a> environment is like the “dotcom era on steroids,” and he thinks the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">recent collapse of</a> popular digital currency exchange FTX is the start of a long and negative era for digital currency.</p>
<h2>Jim Chanos: Crypto&#8217;s Future Looks Bleak</h2>
<p>Chanos predicted that Texas energy company Enron would collapse in 2001, and he was right. How ironic that the man tasked with cleaning up the Enron mess, John Ray III, is <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/john-ray-iii-ftx-is-the-most-mismanaged-company-ive-ever-seen/" data-wpel-link="internal">now tasked with cleaning</a> up what’s left of FTX. Chanos is taking this to heart and sees the crypto space enduring a long and hard voyage following the crash of what many players thought was the industry’s golden child.</p>
<p>In a recent interview, he stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Asset prices are the staunchest defense attorney and harshest prosecutor for financial fraud. It&#8217;s only when people begin losing money that you begin to get a public outcry.</p></blockquote>
<p>In the late 90s and early 2000s, the dotcom era was in full force. With the birth of the internet arriving just years prior, many websites were being built, domains were being bought, and tech companies (several of which failed down the line) came to fruition. Anyone who invested during those years were likely seeing heavy returns, but they had no idea what was to come.</p>
<p>Not long after, the Nasdaq wound up losing close to 80 percent of its overall value given how poorly the space performed in later years. Today, the dotcom era has become a staple of economic downfall, and Chanos thinks this is the beginning of the end for crypto. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>People were losing money in the dotcom era for about a year, but it wasn&#8217;t until the Enron and WorldCom scandals hit that the federal government really geared up its efforts to look at corporate wrongdoing. This will be the same thing. People have lost a lot of money in crypto, and there&#8217;s going to be a political outcry now to regulate this system and bring people to justice.</p></blockquote>
<p>The good news is that he doesn’t think the crypto meltdown that’s likely to occur will spread to other aspects of America’s monetary system. He claimed:</p>
<blockquote><p>I don&#8217;t think this is contagion through the credit markets.</p></blockquote>
<h2>So Many Bad Things in 2022</h2>
<p>To say that 2022 was a bad year for crypto would be an understatement, and it’s not like things began with the collapse of FTX. Since the beginning of the year, bitcoin appeared set on bringing its own price down every chance it got. Despite hitting a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit prior to the start of 2022, it finished the year out trading in the $16K range. That’s a loss surpassing 70 percent.</p>
<p>Several <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-in-the-age-of-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">digital currency companies</a> – like Celsius and (of course) FTX – were also forced to file bankruptcy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jim-chanos-crypto-is-like-the-dotcom-era-all-over-again/">Jim Chanos: Crypto Is Like the Dotcom Era All Over Again</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jim-chanos-crypto-is-like-the-dotcom-era-all-over-again/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Deviants the Most Diverse and Upcoming NFT collection of 2023 Offers Discounted NFT Prices and Guaranteed Airdrop Rewards</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/deviants-the-most-diverse-and-upcoming-nft-collection-of-2023-offers-discounted-nft-prices-and-guaranteed-airdrop-rewards/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/deviants-the-most-diverse-and-upcoming-nft-collection-of-2023-offers-discounted-nft-prices-and-guaranteed-airdrop-rewards/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 16:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76281</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Users in the mint pass allowlist can purchase for only 0.06 ETH instead of 0.08 ETH Public Mint Pass price and will receive guaranteed $RVV token airdrop rewards. A maximum of 8,000 Deviants Mint Pass NFTs will be sold starting from Jan 3, 2023 1pm UTC. Are you ready for the biggest NFT collection of<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/deviants-the-most-diverse-and-upcoming-nft-collection-of-2023-offers-discounted-nft-prices-and-guaranteed-airdrop-rewards/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/deviants-the-most-diverse-and-upcoming-nft-collection-of-2023-offers-discounted-nft-prices-and-guaranteed-airdrop-rewards/">Deviants the Most Diverse and Upcoming NFT collection of 2023 Offers Discounted NFT Prices and Guaranteed Airdrop Rewards</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Users in the mint pass allowlist can purchase for only 0.06 ETH instead of 0.08 ETH Public Mint Pass price and will receive guaranteed $RVV token airdrop rewards.</li>
<li>A maximum of 8,000 Deviants Mint Pass NFTs will be sold starting from Jan 3, 2023 1pm UTC.</li>
</ul>
<p>Are you ready for the biggest NFT collection of 2023?</p>
<p>Well, the <a href="https://twitter.com/TheDeviantsNFT?s=09" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Deviants</a> from the <a href="https://twitter.com/Astra__Nova?s=09" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Astra Nova</a> MetaRPG game are dropping their <a href="https://astranovaofficial.medium.com/everything-you-need-to-know-about-deviants-mint-pass-how-you-can-get-involved-5757c4129d2c" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Deviants Mint Pass NFTs</a> in January.</p>
<p>Delve into the immersive, adventurous gameplay backed up with the most beneficial perks, web3 gaming has ever seen through the Deviants NFTs. These 10,000 fully animated VFX enabled in-game characters will open a door to the exciting interstellar journey of the Astra Nova game on <a href="https://astranovaofficial.medium.com/the-deviants-of-astra-nova-will-be-on-hedera-ethereum-let-us-explain-ee9c1eaaf3b5" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Hedera</a>.</p>
<p>These characters have 15 different species and have over 520 traits making them one of the most diverse NFT collections of all time. The Astra Nova team has spent over a year and vast resources perfecting the Deviants and they&#8217;re no joke in terms of production quality! The Deviants NFT also has its own dedicated <a href="https://astranovaofficial.medium.com/deviants-nft-roadmap-and-the-team-behind-it-862946e7c868" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Roadmap</a> and has a very detailed plan for its in-game characters.</p>
<p>Holders of the Deviants Mint Pass will be able to claim their Deviants NFT on the launch date towards the end of January. The <a href="https://astranovaofficial.medium.com/the-deviants-mint-pass-event-explained-jan-3rd-jan-20th-6b65b76aca7b" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Deviants Mint Pass Event</a> enables early users to buy into the Deviants’ collection at a discounted price and guarantees Airdrop Rewards for whitelisted users.</p>
<p>The public mint pass price of the Deviants NFT is 0.08 ETH, but Allowlisted users will be able to mint them for just 0.06 ETH. The Airdrop rewards, which is a total of 30 million $RVV or approximately $240,000 USD worth awaits the users.</p>
<p><strong>What are the Deviants?</strong></p>
<p>The game’s post-apocalyptic theme spotlights the <a href="https://astranovaofficial.medium.com/deviant-art-the-terrorizing-tikes-who-call-astra-nova-home-175519d1c003" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">original inhabitants of Astra Nova</a> – the Deviants. Players will encounter these 3D collectible characters as they step into the Astra Nova macrocosm. Each Deviant has its unique design and story, and owning one unlocks many aspects of Astra Nova’s game world, and secret quests.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Deviants are the key to unpacking the hidden history of Astra Nova. Beyond the game, Deviant NFTs offer holders early access to game development, concept art previews, and lore distribution with its own dedicated webcomic series. You can read more about their utility over <a href="https://astranovaofficial.medium.com/astra-novas-deviants-to-launch-with-extensive-utility-and-rewards-for-holders-df2c2b1b7ca6" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p><strong>How to Sign Up for the Allowlist and Airdrop?</strong></p>
<p>Users who want to qualify for the allowlist and get the guaranteed airdrop and the lowest cost for minting Deviants need to follow the required actions on this <a href="https://heymint.xyz/astranova" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">page</a>. The mint pass event lasts until January 20. Users should have a wallet for Ethereum, like Metamask,to mint the Deviants Mint Pass NFT and a Hedera-based wallet, such as <a href="https://www.bladewallet.io/astranova/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Blade Wallet</a>, to receive the Airdrop rewards.</p>
<p><strong>Deviants Mint Pass Supply Allocation</strong></p>
<p>Deviants are a collection of 10,000 NFTs. The exact launch of the Deviants NFT would be announced after the Deviants Mint Pass Event gets over.</p>
<p>There is a maximum of 8,000 Deviants Mint Pass NFTs up for grabs from Jan 3rd &#8211; Jan 20th 2023. However, only half, or 4,000, of that will go to an “allowlist,” a list of users who qualify for the token airdrop and mint pass. A total of 3,500 will be allocated to a public mint pass, letting users mint Deviants for a lower price but slightly higher than those in the allowlist at 0.08 ETH. Lastly, 500 will go to a free mint pass list, allowing users to mint Deviants for zero costs.</p>
<ul>
<li>Max Deviants Mint Pass supply: 8,000</li>
<li>Allowlist Deviants Mint Pass: 4,000</li>
<li>Public Deviants Mint Pass: 3,500</li>
<li>Free Mint Pass supply: 500</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Where to buy the Deviants Mint Pass NFT?</strong></p>
<p>Go to <a href="http://mint.deviantsnft.com" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Deviants Mint Portal</a> to mint your Deviants Mint Pass NFTs. Mint will be live from January 3rd,2023 1 pm UTC.</p>
<h4><strong>About Astra Nova</strong></h4>
<p>Astra Nova is a free-to-play Web3 MetaRPG on Hedera. It features AAA graphics and is built on Unreal Engine 5. The game stretches gaming experiences with its ever-evolving storyline, unique action adventure quests, multiplayer battle royales, stealth missions, speed runs, special quests tailored to NFTs, solo missions, customizable RPG character races, and a lot more. Astra Nova has several partners and backers, including Hedera Hashgraph, Microsoft Founder&#8217;s Hub, Nvidia inception program, Polygon DAO, BTS Ventures, Wise Crypto, Blade Wallet, GameEon, and several Indie Game Studios.</p>
<p><strong>Follow us on:</strong></p>
<p>Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/TheDeviantsNFT" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/TheDeviantsNFT</a><br />
Discord: <a href="https://discord.gg/astranova" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://discord.gg/astranova</a><br />
Medium: <a href="https://astranovaofficial.medium.com" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://astranovaofficial.medium.com</a><br />
Website: <a href="https://astranova.world/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://astranova.world/</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/deviants-the-most-diverse-and-upcoming-nft-collection-of-2023-offers-discounted-nft-prices-and-guaranteed-airdrop-rewards/">Deviants the Most Diverse and Upcoming NFT collection of 2023 Offers Discounted NFT Prices and Guaranteed Airdrop Rewards</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/deviants-the-most-diverse-and-upcoming-nft-collection-of-2023-offers-discounted-nft-prices-and-guaranteed-airdrop-rewards/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cathie Wood: BTC Will Reach $1 Million in 2030</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-btc-will-reach-1-million-in-2030/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-btc-will-reach-1-million-in-2030/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 15:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cathie Wood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75724</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cathie Wood – who’s always been the crypto bull of crypto bulls – isn’t giving up on the world’s number one digital currency by market cap. In fact, she’s reiterating her love of the coin and claiming that 2030 will be the year in which BTC reaches the long-awaited $1 million price. Cathie Wood Thinks<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-btc-will-reach-1-million-in-2030/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-btc-will-reach-1-million-in-2030/">Cathie Wood: BTC Will Reach $1 Million in 2030</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cathie Wood – who’s always been the crypto bull of crypto bulls – isn’t giving up on the world’s number one digital currency by market cap. In fact, she’s reiterating her love of the coin and claiming that 2030 will be the year in <a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/bitcoin-outlook-million-2030-crypto-cathie-wood-ark-ftx-collapse-2022-11" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">which BTC reaches</a> the long-awaited $1 million price.</p>
<h2>Cathie Wood Thinks Bitcoin Will Be Huge in Seven Years</h2>
<p>Bitcoin had a very hard year in 2022. Just a few months prior to 2022’s start, the world’s primary cryptocurrency reached a new all-time high of $68,000 per unit. This was achieved in November of 2021.</p>
<p>As soon as the new year rang in, a series of losses began. At first, bitcoin fell into the $40K range. Then, a few months later, it was at $30K. From there, it fell to $20K and before long, the currency was trading in the $15K &#8211; $16K range. This is where it ended the year, and it’s also the window that 2023 is getting its start on. There’s a lot of work to do and recovery to be had, and many are hoping the next 12 months will offer something in the form of a quick (or at least steady) fix.</p>
<p>2022 also saw the collapse of many crypto companies, some of which were alleged bad actors. FTX, the once golden player of the industry, is believed to have used customer <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/evan-luthra-a-victim-of-crypto-exchange-ftx-shares-his-story/" data-wpel-link="internal">funds to purchase luxury</a> condominiums and other items for its employees before crashing in ugly fashion. There are billions of dollars lost at the time of writing, and Wood has stated that the incident is likely to turn many institutional investors <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-ftx-has-done-harsh-damage-to-the-crypto-space/" data-wpel-link="internal">off to crypto trading</a> for good.</p>
<p>Still, she believes bitcoin and many of its altcoin cousins will recover from everything that’s happened in recent days. While things may take a while, she says there’s a good side to everything that’s happened in that it’s weeded out all the weak players, ensuring only the strong survive to keep the crypto space lasting and on sturdy legs. She commented in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Sometimes you need to battle test. You need to go through crises&#8230; to see the survivors.</p></blockquote>
<p>Wood further stated that some institutional investors could end up liking bitcoin and crypto even more if they’re willing to study the situation appropriately and do their homework regarding what happened. She mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Once they actually do the homework and see what&#8217;s happened here, I think they might actually be more comfortable moving into bitcoin, and perhaps ether, as a first stop because they&#8217;ll understand it more.</p></blockquote>
<h2>The Asset Could Still Be on Top</h2>
<p>She believes, in the long run, that bitcoin is going to come out on top following this incident, especially because inflation continues to run high, and the economy is looking weaker by the second. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We think bitcoin is coming out of this smelling like a rose.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-btc-will-reach-1-million-in-2030/">Cathie Wood: BTC Will Reach $1 Million in 2030</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-btc-will-reach-1-million-in-2030/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New York Signs Crypto Moratorium into Law</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-signs-crypto-moratorium-into-law/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-signs-crypto-moratorium-into-law/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 13:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kathy Hochul]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New York]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75722</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It’s happened, folks. We’ve always known New York wasn’t crazy about cryptocurrency, but this new law its governor has recently passed clearly takes its dislike of the industry to a whole new level. The law will limit crypto mining within the state and guarantees safe passage only to firms that utilize green energy. New York<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-signs-crypto-moratorium-into-law/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-signs-crypto-moratorium-into-law/">New York Signs Crypto Moratorium into Law</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It’s happened, folks. We’ve always known New York wasn’t crazy about cryptocurrency, but this new law its governor <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/other/new-law-requires-new-york-cryptocurrency-mining-to-use-renewable-energy/ar-AA14sXLA" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">has recently passed</a> clearly takes its dislike of the industry to a whole new level. The law will limit crypto mining within the state and guarantees safe passage only to firms that utilize green energy.</p>
<h2>New York Puts Limits on Crypto Mining</h2>
<p>The bill <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-new-york-crypto-moratorium-is-still-causing-a-big-fight/" data-wpel-link="internal">has been on the table</a> for many weeks, though New York Governor Kathy Hochul has been slow to make a clear decision on it. She’s now <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-governor-hochul-facing-real-pressure-to-sign-crypto-moratorium/" data-wpel-link="internal">facing extensive pressure</a> from legislators and eco-friendly advocates alike. Hochul has signed the bill into law, meaning the Empire State is getting off on a much stricter foot now that 2023 has been rung in.</p>
<p>In a statement, Hochul defended her signing of the bill. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I am signing this legislation into law to build on New York&#8217;s nation-leading Climate Leadership and Community Protection Act, the most aggressive climate and clean energy law in the nation, while also continuing our steadfast efforts to support economic development and job creation in upstate New York.</p></blockquote>
<p>Verbiage of the new law states the following:</p>
<blockquote><p>The continued and expanded operation of cryptocurrency mining operations running proof of work authentication methods to validate blockchain transactions will greatly increase the amount of energy usage in the state of New York and impact compliance with the Climate Leadership and Community Protection Act.</p></blockquote>
<p>The maneuver is earning a lot of criticism from crypto fans <a href="https://nypost.com/2022/11/22/kathy-hochul-signs-crypto-moratorium-bill-despite-veto-push-by-eric-adams/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">across the board including</a> New York City Mayor Eric Adams. In the past, Adams has stated that he’s very passionate about crypto and even wants it <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eric-adams-wants-crypto-taught-in-nyc-schools/" data-wpel-link="internal">taught in New York</a> City public schools. This is certainly going to get in the way of that.</p>
<p>Last June, Adams said he was going to talk to Hochul about vetoing the bill. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>I’m going to ask the governor to consider vetoing the bill that is going to get in the way of cryptocurrency upstate. When you look at the billions of dollars that are spent on cryptocurrency, New York is the leader. We can’t continue to put barriers in place.</p></blockquote>
<p>Clearly, his words meant nothing to Hochul, who took over for the disgraced Andrew Cuomo in 2021. Her signing of the bill has also garnered criticism from the Chamber of Digital Commerce, which said in a press release:</p>
<blockquote><p>The approval will set a dangerous precedent in determining who may or may not use power in New York State.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Bad Thing for the State?</h2>
<p>John Warren – CEO of bitcoin mining firm GEM Mining – also threw his two cents in, saying:</p>
<blockquote>
<p data-t="{&quot;n&quot;:&quot;blueLinks&quot;}">The regulatory environment in New York will not only halt their target (carbon-based fuel proof of work mining), but will also likely discourage new, renewable-based miners from doing business with the state due to the possibility of more regulatory creep.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-signs-crypto-moratorium-into-law/">New York Signs Crypto Moratorium into Law</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-signs-crypto-moratorium-into-law/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LBank’s 2022: A year of Challenge and Perseverance</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbanks-2022-a-year-of-challenge-and-perseverance/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbanks-2022-a-year-of-challenge-and-perseverance/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 11:52:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76278</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec. 30, 2022 – With 2022 almost over, it’s safe to say that we are all glad to leave it behind and face a fresh new year. 2022 has been a year of turmoil and tribulations for the crypto industry. For LBank, a top 20 global crypto exchange, it certainly has been<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbanks-2022-a-year-of-challenge-and-perseverance/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbanks-2022-a-year-of-challenge-and-perseverance/">LBank’s 2022: A year of Challenge and Perseverance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec. 30, 2022 – <strong>With </strong><strong>2022 almost over, it’s safe to say that we are all glad to leave it behind and face a fresh new year. 2022 has been a year of turmoil and tribulations for the crypto industry. </strong></p>
<p>For <a href="https://www.lbank.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LBank</a>, a top 20 global crypto exchange, it certainly has been a significant year of both challenges and opportunities. More importantly, LBank is ready to turn the page and see what is in store for the coming year.</p>
<p>Since its establishment in 2015, LBank has been ever-changing to fit with market trends and has been going strong for more than 7 years. 2022 was no different. Two of LBank’s major goals in the past year were globalization and localization, which refers to expanding to new locations around the world and working with a local team to connect with local users and create regional communities. 2022 was a major year of growth for LBank, which has led to the exchange currently having team members located in more than 20 countries and community managers in more than 15 countries.</p>
<p>LBank has also exhibited in many of the top industry conferences such as Consensus 2022, Bitcoin Miami 2022, <a href="https://beincrypto.com/lbank-at-token-2049-successful-exhibition-and-afterparty/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Token 2049</a>, and Web Summit Lisbon. “It was a busy year, event-wise. We were so honored to be a part of these conferences. In the first part of the year, cities were starting to open up, and we had some of the first offline crypto events in years. We were so thrilled to meet our users in person,” global event director Stojan Siljanovski told us.</p>
<p>LBank’s <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uw6Wc3mv--8&amp;t=47s" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Brand update</a> in September 2022 showed a new and improved version of the exchange and gave us a glimpse of LBank’s plans for the following years. LBank’s new logo symbolizes its determination to push for crypto education in emerging markets and bring a new generation of young crypto users to the main stage. LBank also posted its long-awaited <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y_Gaqyi1nCY&amp;t=12s" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">diversity video</a> showcasing members of their global team and how much they value workplace diversity and inclusivity.</p>
<p>LBank Labs, an independent crypto investment institution under LBank, was glad to welcome CZhang as a new member of their investment committee. LBank Labs also established a blockchain and crypto fund for Web3 development in Africa, which will be part of a series of funds dedicated to regional crypto and blockchain development. 2023 certainly will see more from LBank Labs.</p>
<p>“For LBank, 2022 certainly was full of challenges,” CMO Kaia Wang said. “But despite everything, we have to keep on moving. As an exchange that has to cater to more than 7 million users worldwide, we simply can’t afford to slow down. We are a rapidly growing company and we are expanding our team and hiring vigorously for new talent. 2022 was a good year for us, but we are ready for the next chapter. We are thrilled to move into this new exciting year with our users, and hope that we can meet new friends along our way.”</p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers its users specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions worldwide. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute to the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading </strong><a href="http://lbank.com" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>Now</strong></a>!</p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media:</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>Telegram</strong></a><strong> l </strong><a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener"><strong>Twitter</strong></a><strong> l </strong><a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener"><strong>Facebook</strong></a><strong> l </strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>LinkedIn</strong></a><strong> l </strong><a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>Instagram</strong></a><strong> l </strong><a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener"><strong>YouTube</strong></a></p>
<p><strong>Press contact:</strong><br />
<a href="mailto:press@lbank.info">press@lbank.info</a><br />
LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
LBank Exchange</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbanks-2022-a-year-of-challenge-and-perseverance/">LBank’s 2022: A year of Challenge and Perseverance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbanks-2022-a-year-of-challenge-and-perseverance/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Keeps Moving Lower, Bears Remain Active</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-keeps-moving-lower-bears-remain-active/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-keeps-moving-lower-bears-remain-active/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 06:28:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blogs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar Lumens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76275</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stellar lumen price is showing bearish signs below the $0.075 resistance zone against the US Dollar. XLM price is now trading below $0.075 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0740 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could start another<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-keeps-moving-lower-bears-remain-active/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-keeps-moving-lower-bears-remain-active/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Keeps Moving Lower, Bears Remain Active</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Stellar lumen price is showing bearish signs below the $0.075 resistance zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>XLM price is now trading below $0.075 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0740 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start another decline if there is a clear move below the $0.070 support.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Stellar lumen price is trading below $0.0750 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-drop-to-new-2022-lows/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. XLM price must stay above the $0.070 support to avoid more losses.</em></p>
<h2>Stellar Lumen Price Analysis (XLM to USD)</h2>
<p>After a failed attempt near the $0.078 zone, stellar lumen price started a fresh decline against the US Dollar. The XLM/USD pair traded below the $0.0765 support to move into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>There was a move below the $0.0750 and $0.0740 levels. The price even settled below the $0.075 level and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-struggle-continues-key-resistance-intact/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. A low was formed near $0.0704 and the price is now consolidating losses. The bears seem to be active below the $0.0740 level.</p>
<p>The price is now trading below $0.075 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). It is also near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $0.0772 swing high to $0.0704 low.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $0.0730 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0740 on the 4-hours chart. The trend line is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $0.0772 swing high to $0.0704 low.</p>
<p>A clear upside break above the trend line might send the price towards $0.0750. The next major resistance is near the $0.078 zone. Any more gains could lead the price towards the $0.0800 level or even $0.0820.</p>
<p>An initial support on the downside is near the $0.0712 level. The main support is near the $0.070 zone. Any more losses could lead the price towards the $0.0665 level in the near term, below which the price might even retest $0.0650.</p>
<div id="attachment_76276" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Stellar-Lumen-XLM.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76276" class="size-full wp-image-76276" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Stellar-Lumen-XLM.png" alt="Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76276" class="wp-caption-text">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XLMUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that XLM price is now trading below $0.076 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could start a major decline if there is a clear move below the $0.070 support.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XLM/USD is losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for XLM/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.0705 and $0.0700.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.0740, $0.0750 and $0.0780.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-keeps-moving-lower-bears-remain-active/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Keeps Moving Lower, Bears Remain Active</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-keeps-moving-lower-bears-remain-active/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Price Analysis: Risk of A Drop Below $0.30</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-risk-of-a-drop-below-0-30/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-risk-of-a-drop-below-0-30/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 03:48:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76272</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple price started a fresh decline below the $0.3800 zone against the US dollar. The price is now trading below $0.3550 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.3400 on the 4-hours chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Bittrex). The pair could<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-risk-of-a-drop-below-0-30/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-risk-of-a-drop-below-0-30/">Ripple Price Analysis: Risk of A Drop Below $0.30</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ripple price started a fresh decline below the $0.3800 zone against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $0.3550 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.3400 on the 4-hours chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Bittrex).</li>
<li>The pair could extend losses if it stays below the $0.3500 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ripple price is struggling below $0.3550 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-drop-to-new-2022-lows/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. XRP price must stay above $0.3000 to avoid more downsides in the near term.</em></p>
<h2>Ripple Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, ripple price saw a bearish reaction below the $0.3800 zone against the US Dollar. The XRP/USD pair declined below the $0.3720 support zone to move into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>The price even traded below the $0.3550 level. Finally, there was a move below the $0.3200 level. The price traded as low as $0.3159 and is currently attempting an upside correction. The price is now trading below $0.3550 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-struggle-below-0-36/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near $0.3300. It is near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3800 swing high to $0.3159 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $0.3400 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.3400 on the 4-hours chart of the XRP/USD pair. The main resistance is near the $0.3500 zone. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3800 swing high to $0.3159 low.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $0.3480 and $0.3500 resistance zones might start a fresh increase. In the stated case, the price could even surpass the $0.3740 resistance. Any more gains might send the price towards the $0.400 resistance.</p>
<p>An initial support on the downside is near the $0.3200 level. The next major support is near the $0.3150 level, below which the price could even test the $0.300 support. Any more losses could lead the price towards the $0.2800 level, below which the price might even test $0.2650.</p>
<div id="attachment_76273" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Ripple.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76273" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-76273" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Ripple.png" alt="Ripple Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76273" class="wp-caption-text">Ripple Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, ripple price is now trading below the $0.355 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could extend losses if it stays below the $0.3000 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XRP/USD is now gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for XRP/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.3200, $0.3150 and $0.300.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.3400 and $0.3500.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-risk-of-a-drop-below-0-30/">Ripple Price Analysis: Risk of A Drop Below $0.30</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-risk-of-a-drop-below-0-30/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cathie Wood: FTX Has Done Harsh Damage to the Crypto Space</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-ftx-has-done-harsh-damage-to-the-crypto-space/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-ftx-has-done-harsh-damage-to-the-crypto-space/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cathie Wood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75714</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin bull and crypto investor Cathie Wood thinks the FTX debacle may have done irreparable damage to the crypto space, and she says the incident will likely make many institutional investors stay away for a long time. Cathie Wood Thinks the Damage Done by FTX Is Severe The FTX fiasco will go down as one<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-ftx-has-done-harsh-damage-to-the-crypto-space/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-ftx-has-done-harsh-damage-to-the-crypto-space/">Cathie Wood: FTX Has Done Harsh Damage to the Crypto Space</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin bull and crypto investor Cathie Wood <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/savingandinvesting/ark-invest-says-ftx-collapse-could-delay-institutional-crypto-adoption-by-years/ar-AA146Ma1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">thinks the</a> FTX debacle may have done irreparable damage to the crypto space, and she says the incident will likely make many institutional investors stay away for a long time.</p>
<h2>Cathie Wood Thinks the Damage Done by FTX Is Severe</h2>
<p>The FTX fiasco will go down as one of the biggest embarrassments of the arena. Long considered one of the greatest players in crypto, the company first came to fruition in 2019. It rose through the ranks and was one of the top digital currency trading platforms in the world. Its founder, Sam Bankman-Fried, was labeled a genius by many, though that reputation faded quickly in mid-November of last year.</p>
<p>FTX began <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">experiencing what it referred</a> to as a “liquidity crunch” during that time. It approached Binance as a means of staying afloat and tried to work out a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">deal where the larger</a> company purchased the smaller one. Sadly, things didn’t quite work out that way, and before long, FTX was filing bankruptcy <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">and its head executive</a> was resigning from his post. It was an ugly sight to watch.</p>
<p>Cathie Wood believes what’s happening with FTX will be the final nail in the coffin. She thinks this event will make several institutional traders turn away for good. She is also confident that this is going to pave the way for hardcore regulation that will make the crypto industry almost unrecognizable.</p>
<p>Wood stated in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>In our view, FTX’s insolvency is one of the most damaging events in crypto history. It could delay institutional crypto adoption by years and perhaps give regulators license to take draconian measures… ARK’s conviction in the long-term promise of public blockchains across money, finance, and the internet is not wavering. While the crypto asset market could labor under selling pressure and liquidity crunches in the short term, we believe this crisis is purging bad actors and will enhance the health of the crypto ecosystem with more transparency and decentralization in the longer term.</p></blockquote>
<p>There already appears to be some truth to what Wood is suggesting. Indeed, there have been huge and newfound calls for <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/biden-voices-support-for-crypto-regulation/" data-wpel-link="internal">crypto regulation following</a> what occurred with FTX. Many politicians and lawmakers claim that what happened with the exchange cannot happen again, and the only way to ensure this is by putting certain laws in place to keep users protected.</p>
<p>One of the people who is unsurprisingly calling for more regulation is democrat Massachusetts senator Elizabeth Warren. She’s <a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/senators-press-fidelity-to-reconsider-allowing-bitcoin-access-in-401k-plans-2022-11-21" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">even asking Fidelity to</a> go back on its 401K and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fidelity-is-still-taking-flak-for-its-crypto-offerings/" data-wpel-link="internal">crypto retirement propositions</a> following the exchange’s collapse.</p>
<h2>Congress Needs to Get Its Act Together</h2>
<p>She mentioned in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>The implosion of FTX must be a wake-up call for Congress and financial regulators to hold this industry and its executives accountable. Too much of the crypto industry is smoke and mirrors.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-ftx-has-done-harsh-damage-to-the-crypto-space/">Cathie Wood: FTX Has Done Harsh Damage to the Crypto Space</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-ftx-has-done-harsh-damage-to-the-crypto-space/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Customers May Say Bye to Their Money for Good</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-customers-may-be-saying-bye-to-their-money-forever/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-customers-may-be-saying-bye-to-their-money-forever/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 15:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bankruptcy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mt Gox]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75710</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FTX caused a lot of nasty spillage and other problems in late 2022. Here we are in 2023, and unfortunately, the final remnants of what will likely be labeled a huge bad actor and very poor player in the crypto economy continues to wreak havoc on the space and on customers. FTX Customers May Not<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-customers-may-be-saying-bye-to-their-money-forever/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-customers-may-be-saying-bye-to-their-money-forever/">FTX Customers May Say Bye to Their Money for Good</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FTX caused a lot of nasty spillage and other problems in late 2022. Here we are in 2023, and unfortunately, the final remnants of what will likely be labeled a huge bad actor and very poor player in the crypto economy continues to <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/customers-of-bankrupt-ftx-may-never-get-their-crypto-back/ar-AA145SEK" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wreak havoc on the space</a> and on customers.</p>
<h2>FTX Customers May Not Get Their Funds Back</h2>
<p>It has been suggested by many analysts and traders that the company’s users will not get their money back. That’s right… Whatever funds they lost due to the firm’s mismanagement of their funds are potentially gone forever.</p>
<p>While this isn’t necessarily set in stone yet, it’s being suggested based on information from the infamous <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/mt-gox/" data-wpel-link="internal">Mt. Gox</a> fiasco that took place in 2014. At nearly nine years old (the incident occurred in February of 2014), Mt. Gox filed bankruptcy after allegedly losing more than $400 million in BTC funds, and those bankruptcy proceedings are still ongoing today.</p>
<p>This suggests that filing bankruptcy in the crypto space is a complicated matter. Thus, many industry heads believe that it will be a long time before FTX players ever see a dime of their money, and that’s assuming they ever see anything at all.</p>
<p>St. Johns University law professor Anthony Sabino is confident that while these customers will get some of their money back, they will never see their full stashes again. He also said that many of the assets they stored on the platform are likely to experience further price dips as the FTX drama continues to take hold of the space. In an interview, he commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>People are going to be waiting on the sidelines for a very long time, and only heaven knows what it&#8217;s going to be worth. It does not look good at all.</p></blockquote>
<p>One of the more unique aspects of FTX is that while its bankruptcy proceedings are occurring, the company is being investigated by agencies like the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Joshua Peck – an alleged expert on crypto risk – says that while these investigations won’t delay the bankruptcy, the judge overseeing the cases is going to pay very close attention to what’s uncovered.</p>
<p>He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I expect the FTX bankruptcy to take a decade or more for the process to sort out what assets remain and who owns them.</p></blockquote>
<p>Referring to the Mt. Gox debacle to support his argument, Peck stated that that company exists all over again in something like FTX. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>The Mt. Gox bankruptcy is the precedent here. That bankruptcy started in 2014 and is still ongoing.</p></blockquote>
<h2>The Trouble Began Two Months Ago</h2>
<p>FTX first began encountering difficulties in mid-November. This caused the company to seek aid from Binance, who <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">appeared to be on the verge</a> of buying the enterprise.</p>
<p>This <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">didn’t happen however</a>, and FTX has since fallen into oblivion.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-customers-may-be-saying-bye-to-their-money-forever/">FTX Customers May Say Bye to Their Money for Good</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-customers-may-be-saying-bye-to-their-money-forever/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
