<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 04:04:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/cropped-fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Grayscale Feels It&#8217;s Being Treated Unfairly by the SEC</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/grayscale-feels-its-being-treated-unfairly-by-the-sec/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 17:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grayscale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79229</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) approved a different kind of bitcoin-based exchange-traded fund (ETF), and crypto conglomerate Grayscale isn’t happy about that. Grayscale is Seeing Red The ETF that garnered approval is called 2X Volatility Shares, and it became open for public trading on June 23. For many players out there, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/grayscale-feels-its-being-treated-unfairly-by-the-sec/">Grayscale Feels It&#8217;s Being Treated Unfairly by the SEC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/grayscale-cries-foul-over-sec-000239686.html">approved a different</a> kind of bitcoin-based exchange-traded fund (ETF), and crypto conglomerate Grayscale isn’t happy about that.</p>
<h2>Grayscale is Seeing Red</h2>
<p>The ETF that garnered approval is called 2X Volatility Shares, and it became open for public trading on June 23. For many players out there, the move was the right one and a big step in a powerful new direction that’s likely to make crypto mainstream and legitimate in many traders’ eyes, but Grayscale is a little ticked off that the SEC would allow such a product to be made available while going quite far to say “no” to its own application.</p>
<p>2X Volatility is not a bitcoin spot ETF, but even still, Grayscale says it went through hell and high water to ensure its application was fully compliant with all SEC laws. As usual, the financial agency was quick to issue a stamp of disapproval on the company’s application form, and Grayscale has now engaged in a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/could-grayscale-actually-defeat-the-sec-in-court/">lawsuit against the SEC</a>.</p>
<p>One of the crypto company’s lawyers, Donald Verilli, said the SEC broke its own rules to permit the trading of 2X Volatility, thus giving the product an unfair advantage and creating harsher competition for Grayscale. He commented in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>The fact that the Commission has allowed a leveraged bitcoin futures ETP to begin trading demonstrates that the Commission continues to arbitrarily treat spot bitcoin ETPs differently than bitcoin futures ETPs… While the Commission could theoretically correct its discriminatory treatment of spot bitcoin ETPs by rescinding its approval of all bitcoin ETPs, the Commission&#8217;s apparent willingness to permit even a leveraged bitcoin futures ETP, a particularly high-risk version of a bitcoin futures product, makes clear [it] has no intention of doing so.</p></blockquote>
<p>Bitcoin ETFs have been all the rage over the past few years, though steam has really picked up in recent months following the introduction of a new bitcoin ETF application <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blackrock-etf-application-causes-btc-eth-to-surge/">from standard financial</a> firm BlackRock. The company has a solid track record with the SEC, with more than 500 applications approved in the past by the financial agency.</p>
<p>While the SEC was quick to reject BlackRock’s initial documentation, the papers <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sends-blackrock-btc-etf-application-back-for-revisions/">were swiftly revised</a> per the agency’s advice and they’re now awaiting further evaluation.</p>
<p>The Grayscale ETF founder Justin Young threw his two cents into the mix by commenting on the double standards and hypocrisy the SEC appears to exhibit. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think it brings to a lot of people&#8217;s attention the thought that if the SEC has let a leveraged bitcoin-linked product through, why on Earth wouldn&#8217;t they allow spot bitcoin through?</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Stronger Desire for BTC</h2>
<p>On Twitter, Grayscale wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>Investors are eager for $BTC exposure with the protections of the ETF wrapper.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/grayscale-feels-its-being-treated-unfairly-by-the-sec/">Grayscale Feels It&#8217;s Being Treated Unfairly by the SEC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gaming Company Sega Wants Nothing to Do with Blockchain</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gaming-company-sega-wants-nothing-to-do-with-blockchain/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 15:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sega]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79226</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There are many gaming companies out there that have joined hands with blockchain technology as a means of enhancing experiences for many players, but Sega is not (and likely will not be) one of them. Sega Doesn&#8217;t Think Much of Blockchain Sega, as we all know, is a major competitor to Nintendo and has produced [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gaming-company-sega-wants-nothing-to-do-with-blockchain/">Gaming Company Sega Wants Nothing to Do with Blockchain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are many gaming companies out there that have joined hands with <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/blockchain/">blockchain</a> technology as a means of enhancing experiences for many players, but Sega is not (and likely <em>will not</em> be) one of them.</p>
<h2>Sega Doesn&#8217;t Think Much of Blockchain</h2>
<p>Sega, as we all know, is a major competitor to Nintendo and has produced some of the world’s most recognized titles such as the “Sonic the Hedgehog” series, “Golden Axe,” and many others. In several ways, Sega has been ahead of its time and has introduced us to playable characters and stories that much of the population (particularly younger people) still enjoy talking about today.</p>
<p>However, in a recent interview, the company’s co-COO Shuji Utsumi said <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/sega-coo-backs-away-from-blockchain/ar-AA1dHuUB">he doesn’t know</a> what blockchain is good for, and it’s not likely the company will ever utilize the technology or the services that come with it in future product releases. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>We are trying to figure out what is the best way to entertain the audience. [We are] evaluating, searching, [and] learning.</p></blockquote>
<p>To be fair, the company is not shutting the door completely on blockchain. It even put out a statement saying that it has some potential. However, there are some issues with it given that several players have said they do not care for the play-to-earn outlets that other gaming companies have offered, and Sega clearly doesn’t want to diminish its returns by disappointing its players. Utsumi said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We are very careful because we understand that especially western gamers are not big fans of our web3 initiative.</p></blockquote>
<p>At the time of writing, Sega is announcing the introduction of what it’s calling a “super game,” which will be brought to the public in the year 2026. There are very few details available about the product, though according to the company, the release is going to be unlike anything any gamer has ever seen or experienced before.</p>
<h2>A Huge Change of Pace?</h2>
<p>However, things are not fully set in stone, and Sega is still not sure if blockchain will be a valid part of the so-called “super game” it plans to establish. This marks a whole change of pace for the game company, as back in 2022, Utsumi said Sega was eagerly “focusing on new areas such as [the] metaverse and web3.” He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Sega has invested in several web3 and metaverse startups as part of its open innovation efforts. Through these companies, we are accumulating various know-how, and we are researching every day what we can achieve by combining web3 technology and Sega&#8217;s resources, and what kind of business we can build.</p></blockquote>
<p>Many analyst companies – such as Gartner – feel Sega would be making a mistake by turning its back on blockchain entirely, as the firm still labels gaming as a top arena for metaverses.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gaming-company-sega-wants-nothing-to-do-with-blockchain/">Gaming Company Sega Wants Nothing to Do with Blockchain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Didi Taihuttu Creates &#8220;Moon&#8221; Algorithm to Help Read BTC Trends</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/didi-taihuttu-creates-moon-algorithm-to-help-read-btc-trends/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 13:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Didi Taihuttu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[moon algorithm]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79223</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin Family – run by patriarch Didi Taihuttu, who has been discussed several times on Live Bitcoin News – has made a real name for itself in the crypto community. Six years ago, they sold everything they had and traded everything in for bitcoin so they could enjoy a life of travel and exploring [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/didi-taihuttu-creates-moon-algorithm-to-help-read-btc-trends/">Didi Taihuttu Creates &#8220;Moon&#8221; Algorithm to Help Read BTC Trends</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin Family – run by patriarch Didi Taihuttu, who has been discussed several times on <em>Live Bitcoin News</em> – has made a real name for itself in the crypto community. Six years ago, they sold everything they had and traded <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/didi-taihuttu-and-his-family-are-putting-everything-they-have-into-btc/">everything in for bitcoin</a> so they could enjoy a life of travel and exploring exotic places.</p>
<h2>Didi Taihuttu Has Created a New Way to Predict BTC&#8217;s Price</h2>
<p>Not long ago, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/didi-taihuttu-opens-bitcoin-bar-in-portugal/">the family settled</a> in Lagos, Portugal, which is considered one of the most crypto-friendly places in Europe. Taihuttu is also adding to his bitcoin legacy and influence after having developed a new algorithm that helps him <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/the-bitcoin-family-has-a-special-algorithm-that-tracks-moon-cycles-and-its-helped-them-gain-50-since-the-bear-market-bottom/ar-AA1dJ3Sk">determine the cycles</a> of the moon, which he believes helps his bitcoin decisions and to determine where the asset’s price will go next.</p>
<p>Discussing his family’s long journey with crypto, Taihuttu said in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>We just need a few thousand per month to live on, so our performance is not really important to us.</p></blockquote>
<p>He and his family enjoy relatively moderate living conditions, though to be fair, they sound relatively luxurious in many ways. For example, Taihuttu resides in a villa on the coast that overlooks the Atlantic Ocean. You can’t exactly say this is “moderate.” Most people in the U.S. would kill to have such a view.</p>
<p>Regarding his new “moon” algorithm, he says he developed it prior to the COVID pandemic, and it has aided all his crypto investing decisions from that day on. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>From mid-November to the start of December 2022, we saw the first signs the bear market was completely over. It was confirmed in January 2023 when the long flag appeared in the model. People should have been buying bitcoin already because every bitcoin you bought at $16K, it&#8217;s at $30K now, so that&#8217;s almost 90 percent upside.</p></blockquote>
<p>Since last year’s bottom, he says his BTC investments are up roughly 50 percent. He also says being in Portugal has really helped his family maintain their wealth and status and keep up appearances in the crypto arena. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>You don&#8217;t pay any capital gains tax or anything else in Portugal on cryptocurrency. [So] long as you don&#8217;t earn cryptocurrency for providing services in Portugal, you&#8217;re in the clear. That&#8217;s a very beautiful bitcoin heaven.</p></blockquote>
<h2>How Does It Work?</h2>
<p>Taihuttu created the “moon” algorithm because he said there wasn’t much out there that could truly help him the way he wanted. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>It&#8217;s not just enough to know which indicators go into a formula. What you can&#8217;t see is the calculus and the code that [are implemented] over the stock conditions. Those calculations [are displayed] in charts… It&#8217;s a combination of Bollinger bands, lower and upper bands, NMA, red/green ribbon, Norm Stoch, RSI, price oscillator, plot, MACD, cross, Chande momentum oscillator, RSI-EMA, full moon, and new moon.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/didi-taihuttu-creates-moon-algorithm-to-help-read-btc-trends/">Didi Taihuttu Creates &#8220;Moon&#8221; Algorithm to Help Read BTC Trends</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Could Fail To Recover Above $0.135</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-fail-to-recover-above-0-135/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 05:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar Lumens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79783</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stellar lumen price is struggling below the $0.135 resistance zone against the US Dollar. XLM price is now trading below $0.130 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.131 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could start a fresh [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-fail-to-recover-above-0-135/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Could Fail To Recover Above $0.135</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Stellar lumen price is struggling below the $0.135 resistance zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>XLM price is now trading below $0.130 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.131 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a fresh increase if it clears the $0.135 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Stellar lumen price is trading below $0.135 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-at-risk-below-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. XLM price could extend losses if it trades below the $0.120 support.</em></p>
<h2>Stellar Lumen Price Analysis (XLM to USD)</h2>
<p>After a sharp decline below $0.135, Stellar Lumen price moved into a bearish zone against the US Dollar. The XLM/USD pair traded below the $0.120 level.</p>
<p>There was also a spike below the $0.105 support zone. A low was formed near $0.100 and the price is now attempting a recovery wave. There was a move above the $0.105 and $0.120 levels. The price climbed above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.1460 swing high to the $0.1000 low.</p>
<p>However, the bears were active near the $0.13 zone. XLM is now trading below $0.130 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-faces-uphill-task-near-0-145/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.131 on the 4-hour chart.</p>
<p>The next key resistance is seen near the $0.135 level. It is close to the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.1460 swing high to the $0.1000 low. A clear upside break above the $0.135 zone might send the price toward $0.144.</p>
<p>Any more gains could lead the price toward the $0.1525 level. Initial support on the downside is near the $0.124 level. The next major support is near the $0.120 zone.</p>
<p>Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.1120 level in the near term, below which the price might even retest $0.1050. The next major support is near $0.10.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79784" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79784" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-1.png"><img decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" class="size-full wp-image-79784" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-1.png" alt="Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price" width="1835" height="839" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-1.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-1-600x274.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-1-1100x503.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-1-768x351.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-1-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-1-750x343.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-1-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79784" class="wp-caption-text">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XLMUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a> indicates that XLM price is now trading below $0.135 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start a fresh increase if it clears the $0.135 resistance.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XLM/USD is gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for XLM/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.124 and $0.120.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.131, $0.1350, and $0.145.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-fail-to-recover-above-0-135/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Could Fail To Recover Above $0.135</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Price Analysis: Upsides Could Be Limited Above $0.58</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-upsides-could-be-limited-above-0-58/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 03:38:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79780</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple price is facing resistance near the $0.580 level against the US dollar. The price is now trading below $0.565 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.580 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Kraken). The pair could [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-upsides-could-be-limited-above-0-58/">Ripple Price Analysis: Upsides Could Be Limited Above $0.58</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ripple price is facing resistance near the $0.580 level against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $0.565 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.580 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start another decline if it stays below $0.565 and $0.580.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ripple price is struggling below $0.580 against the US Dollar, unlike <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-at-risk-below-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. XRP price must stay above the $0.50 support to start a recovery wave.</em></p>
<h2>Ripple Price Analysis</h2>
<p>After struggling to clear the $0.680 resistance, Ripple price started a fresh decline against the US Dollar. The XRP/USD pair gained bearish momentum below the 0.625 support zone.</p>
<p>The bears were able to push the price below the $0.50 support. A low was formed near $0.3994 and the pair is now attempting a recovery wave. There was a move above the $0.50 pivot level. The price climbed above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.6362 swing high to the $0.3994 low.</p>
<p>The price is now trading below $0.565 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-key-barrier-sits-at-0-68/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.580 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near $0.545. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.6362 swing high to the $0.3994 low. The next major resistance is near the $0.580 level.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $0.580 resistance zone might start a steady increase. In the stated case, the price could test the $0.600 resistance. Any more gains might send the price toward the $0.625 resistance.</p>
<p>Initial support on the downside is near the $0.515 level. The next major support is near the $0.500 level, below which the price could accelerate lower toward the $0.450 support. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.420 level.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79781" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79781" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Ripple-2.png"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-79781" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Ripple-2.png" alt="Ripple Price" width="1835" height="839" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Ripple-2.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Ripple-2-600x274.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Ripple-2-1100x503.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Ripple-2-768x351.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Ripple-2-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Ripple-2-750x343.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Ripple-2-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79781" class="wp-caption-text">Ripple Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, Ripple price is now trading below the $0.580 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start another decline if it stays below $0.565 and $0.580.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XRP/USD is now losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for XRP/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.515, $0.500, and $0.450.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.545 and $0.580.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-upsides-could-be-limited-above-0-58/">Ripple Price Analysis: Upsides Could Be Limited Above $0.58</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitstamp is Paving the Way for Crypto Payments</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitstamp-is-paving-the-way-for-crypto-payments/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 17:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitstamp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto payments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Qi Digital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79220</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto exchange Bitstamp has formed a new partnership with Qi Digital to ensure that all companies, banks, and payment providers that work with it can accept crypto as a method of payment. Bitstamp is Making It Easy to Pay with Crypto The move is pushing the goals of bitcoin and its digital counterparts closer to being [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitstamp-is-paving-the-way-for-crypto-payments/">Bitstamp is Paving the Way for Crypto Payments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto exchange Bitstamp has formed <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/bitstamp-and-qi-digital-team-up-over-cryptocurrency-payments/ar-AA1dHwyJ">a new partnership</a> with Qi Digital to ensure that all companies, banks, and payment providers that work with it can accept crypto as a method of payment.</p>
<h2>Bitstamp is Making It Easy to Pay with Crypto</h2>
<p>The move is pushing the goals of bitcoin and its digital counterparts closer to being achieved. What many people likely forget is that while bitcoin and many of its crypto cousins have taken on either speculative or even hedge-like statuses in recent years, many of them were initially designed to serve as payment tools. They were built to push checks, credit cards, and fiat currencies to the side, but this has been a relatively slow journey given the volatility that continues to drag them down.</p>
<p>It is extremely hard to understand when bitcoin and its crypto family will go up or down when it comes to their prices. Many stores and companies have been reluctant to say “yes” when it comes to accepting crypto payments for this reason, and to a degree, we can’t blame them.</p>
<p>Consider the following scenario: someone walks into a store and buys $50 worth of merchandise with bitcoin. For one reason or another, the store doesn’t trade the BTC into fiat right away and about 24 hours go by. From there, the price of BTC goes down and that $50 becomes $40. The customer gets to keep everything he or she bought, but the store loses money in the end. Is this a fair situation? Not everyone thinks so.</p>
<p>That’s what makes enterprises like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitstamp/">Bitstamp</a> so important. They understand the initial purposes of bitcoin and digital currencies and are trying to transform them into usable tools that everyday people can benefit from.</p>
<p>Jean-Baptiste Graftieaux – the CEO of Bitstamp – explained in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>As crypto continues to evolve and we get closer to our goal of mainstream adoption, this partnership with Qi Digital signals the next step in helping mainstream audiences confidently approach digital assets by providing seamless crypto transactions for businesses and their customers. As we work to grow the market for everyone, partnerships such as these ensure that we continue to provide a compliant and regulated service to our customers and make crypto accessible to all.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Big Step Foward?</h2>
<p>Mann Matharu – CEO at Qi Digital – also threw his two cents into the mix, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>This is an important milestone for the crypto industry. By partnering with Bitstamp, we’re able to respond positively to provide a secure, more robust crypto payment solution. We can help shape the crypto landscape by future-proofing businesses to meet the demands of a growing global consumer market. PSPs can now add a trusted, blockchain-connected payment proposition for their merchants and consumers worldwide. Our aim is to provide choice for the everyday consumer as crypto adoption rises.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitstamp-is-paving-the-way-for-crypto-payments/">Bitstamp is Paving the Way for Crypto Payments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shoe Company Community Made Will Use Blockchain to Guarantee Transparency</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/shoe-company-community-made-will-use-blockchain-to-guarantee-transparency/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 15:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Community Made]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shoes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79217</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Community Made is a Los Angeles footwear company. The firm wants to use blockchain to build out its supply chain and ensure the transparency of all its products and transactions. Community Made is Intrigued by Blockchain The company is now joining hands with Chroma Way in Stockholm, Sweden. Chroma Way is a blockchain firm that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/shoe-company-community-made-will-use-blockchain-to-guarantee-transparency/">Shoe Company Community Made Will Use Blockchain to Guarantee Transparency</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Community Made is a Los Angeles footwear company. The <a href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/building-made-usa-footwear-blockchain-130000952.html">firm wants to use blockchain</a> to build out its supply chain and ensure the transparency of all its products and transactions.</p>
<h2>Community Made is Intrigued by Blockchain</h2>
<p>The company is now joining hands with Chroma Way in Stockholm, Sweden. Chroma Way is a blockchain firm that will develop the blockchain technology Community Made needs to make its products as viable and as trustworthy as possible.</p>
<p>Community Made was founded by Sean and Shannon Scott, a duo with plenty of experience in the field of developing shoes and related footwear at companies like Asics, Toms, and Nike. The firm was launched in the year 2017 and develops shoes, foam midsoles, outsoles, and knit uppers.</p>
<p>In an interview, Sean Scott said he believes in the power of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/blockchain/">blockchain</a>, and he thinks the transparency he’s looking to achieve is necessary for all companies to survive. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>The supply chain has long been a great place to apply decentralized ledger technology. You’ve got a complicated business with a lot of stakeholders and a lot of documentation, and at the same time, you have a demand for clarity about that documentation… It may take some time, some cajoling, some education, but it’s doable.</p></blockquote>
<p>Shannon Scott, another blockchain believer, also threw her two cents into the mix, commenting:</p>
<blockquote><p>We’re at that stage in the business where we’ve got people coming in who want to do private label business, and we want to expand because we see that as a really viable thing. It took us a long time to figure out the steps and the pitfalls, and other brands are now going through the same thing.</p></blockquote>
<p>Sean also says that many consumers have become fully aware of blockchain over the years, and they’re ready to interact with it as much as possible. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>They have this ability to get educated with this computer in the palm of their hands. We all do… If the only heel counters we’ve found for our shoes are from China, and we can’t vouch for the source, we want to bring the customer along and let them know that we’re working on it. I think it shows them respect, and they’re going to hold us accountable.</p></blockquote>
<p>Chroma Way says it will spend the next year or so developing the blockchain the shoe company needs. Shannon says the firm is on the verge of hitting new milestones by having its new chain in place. She stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I felt like we were on this island alone for the longest time. Now, it kind of feels like it’s grown into a resort.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Inch by Inch</h2>
<p>Sean concluded with:</p>
<blockquote><p>This nearshoring shift, it’s not a sea change just yet, but we’re moving the needle.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/shoe-company-community-made-will-use-blockchain-to-guarantee-transparency/">Shoe Company Community Made Will Use Blockchain to Guarantee Transparency</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mighty Bear Games and Treasure Bring New Game to Arbitrum Blockchain</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mighty-bear-games-and-treasure-bring-new-game-to-arbitrum-blockchain/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 13:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitrum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mighty Bear Games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Treasure]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79214</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mighty Bear Games has joined hands with web3 game developer Treasure to move its “Mighty Action Heroes” series to the Arbitrum blockchain. Mighty Bear Games and Treasure&#8230; A Perfect Match? CEO of Mighty Bear Simon Davis explained in an interview: The Treasure ecosystem is built on Arbitrum, and this creates a positive reinforcing dynamic between [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mighty-bear-games-and-treasure-bring-new-game-to-arbitrum-blockchain/">Mighty Bear Games and Treasure Bring New Game to Arbitrum Blockchain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mighty Bear Games has joined hands with web3 game developer Treasure to move its “Mighty Action Heroes” series <a href="https://venturebeat.com/games/mighty-bear-games-will-publish-mighty-action-heroes-on-arbitrum-blockchain/">to the Arbitrum blockchain</a>.</p>
<h2>Mighty Bear Games and Treasure&#8230; A Perfect Match?</h2>
<p>CEO of Mighty Bear Simon Davis explained in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>The Treasure ecosystem is built on Arbitrum, and this creates a positive reinforcing dynamic between the chain and Treasure’s own ecosystem. The fact the two are closely intertwined is mutually beneficial and helped make the case for working with both.</p></blockquote>
<p>He further commented that <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/arbitrum/">Arbitrum</a> was chosen given it has a huge and active community and a “vibrant” development ecosystem. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>These two factors were a huge draw alongside Arbitrum’s responsiveness, openness, speed, and low fees. We had early conversations with David at Arbitrum and the founders at Treasure, and it very quickly became clear that they fully understood what we were trying to achieve (they’d all played the game which is more unusual than you’d think). We had a shared vision, and they were partners we knew we could rely upon. I spent a few days in Australia with some of the team from Treasure and that really cemented our decision. There’s a lot of mutual admiration.</p></blockquote>
<p>The company says it’s also interested in user feedback prior to the series’ general release. Thus, all games will be available for a short while through an open beta period. Davis said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The release of the open beta marks the first time that anyone can play Mighty Action Heroes and test both our on-chain and off-chain features. Joining the Treasure community and switching to Arbitrum provides a valuable opportunity for us to work alongside a thriving ecosystem of passionate gamers to develop our first-ever web3 title. Equally, we will be sharing our extensive game development expertise with Treasure. Ultimately, as a player-first studio, our main goal is to build an enjoyable game that is accessible to everyone. This is then augmented by a thriving community and a sustainable economy. Treasure plus Arbitrum is the perfect home for building a game aligned with this core vision.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A New Series for a New Audience</h2>
<p>Karel Vuong – co-founder at Treasure – also threw his two cents in, stating:</p>
<blockquote><p>We are delighted to have Mighty Bear Games bring their innovative and incredibly fun web3 battle royale to Treasure. As the decentralized game publisher building the ‘world’s game console,’ Treasure has always been community-driven and strives to build a thriving gaming ecosystem alongside values-aligned game studios, creators, and players. The Mighty Bear Games team embraces many of the principles that we hold dear as like-minded, seasoned builders who put the magic of play, as well as the player first. We couldn’t be more excited for our community to get their hands on Mighty Action Heroes on its path to becoming a household game title in the years to come.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mighty-bear-games-and-treasure-bring-new-game-to-arbitrum-blockchain/">Mighty Bear Games and Treasure Bring New Game to Arbitrum Blockchain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bluzelle (BLZ) Fires “Super” Signal Suggesting An Uptrend Is Starting</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bluzelle-blz-fires-super-signal-suggesting-an-uptrend-is-starting/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 10:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry and Adoption]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79777</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bluzelle saw a massive more than 100% price explosion this week. The move up, while already significant, started a “super” uptrend signal to turn upward for the first time in over a year. Keep reading to find out exactly what this signal means, and learn more about the BLZ token. Bluzelle (BLZ) SuperTrend Signal Line [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bluzelle-blz-fires-super-signal-suggesting-an-uptrend-is-starting/">Bluzelle (BLZ) Fires “Super” Signal Suggesting An Uptrend Is Starting</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bluzelle saw a massive more than 100% price explosion this week. The move up, while already significant, started a “super” uptrend signal to turn upward for the first time in over a year.</p>
<p>Keep reading to find out exactly what this signal means, and learn more about the BLZ token.</p>
<h3>Bluzelle (BLZ) SuperTrend Signal Line Turns Up For First Time Since 2022</h3>
<p>It’s a bird! It’s a plane! No, it’s the SuperTrend on 1W BLZUSD price charts, and it&#8217;s here to save the altcoin market from further despair. Unlike other cryptocurrencies which have remained stagnant throughout August, Bluzelle is up more than 130% in recent weeks.</p>
<p>BLZ could be ready for more upside, as the SuperTrend signal line on the weekly timeframe has begun to turn upward. Take particular note of how the signal line acted as support each time the price tried to break below the $0.05 level. The SuperTrend kept saving the day again and again, and now it&#8217;s moving up, up and away.</p>
<p>The SuperTrend turning up is notable, as it means that ironclad support level is now rising higher along with price. As long as the support holds longer-term, price could begin to make a series of higher highs and higher lows. This is the definition of an uptrend.</p>
<p>If Bluzelle continues its uptrend, the recent more than 100% rally will be only the beginning of what’s to come.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-79778" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Picture4-600x374.jpg" alt="" width="600" height="374" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Picture4-600x374.jpg 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Picture4.jpg 602w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></p>
<h3>Why Bluzelle Is Gaining Momentum In The Cryptocurrency Market</h3>
<p>Technical momentum appears fueled by Bluzelle&#8217;s strengthening fundamental position in providing a blockchain for GameFi. With claims of over 10,000 transactions per second, Bluzelle touts high throughput and seamless interoperability with other Cosmos-based chains, catering to gamers needs in the ecosystem.</p>
<p>Yet Bluzelle&#8217;s most intriguing expansion is into GameFi with GAMMA 4, the Crypto Sci-Fi Epic, a play-to-earn real-time card battle game where players can win BLZ tokens. Created &amp; developed by Bluzelle and the Starloop Studio with AAA gaming pedigree, GAMMA 4 lends credibility to Bluzelle&#8217;s gaming utility, emerging as a strong competitor for Immutable X, a leading Ethereum-based GameFi player in the space.</p>
<p>As Bluzelle extends its capabilities across NFT markets with Capella, DeFi with Osmosis integration with Stargate V9 upgrade, and GameFi with GAMMA 4, the platform&#8217;s multifaceted role may be garnering increased enthusiasm. With links to major GameFi partners, Bluzelle appears poised to build on its recent momentum.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bluzelle-blz-fires-super-signal-suggesting-an-uptrend-is-starting/">Bluzelle (BLZ) Fires “Super” Signal Suggesting An Uptrend Is Starting</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
