<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 03:09:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Face Uphill Task</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-face-uphill-task-2/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-face-uphill-task-2/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 03:18:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78283</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin is showing bearish signs and trading above $75 against the US Dollar. LTC price is now trading below $85 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $84.8 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-face-uphill-task-2/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-face-uphill-task-2/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Face Uphill Task</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Litecoin is showing bearish signs and trading above $75 against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>LTC price is now trading below $85 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $84.8 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could start a decent increase if it clears the $85 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Litecoin price is struggling below $85 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-29k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. LTC price could continue to decline if it stays below the $85 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few hours, there was a short-lived recovery in Bitcoin, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-at-risk-of-downside-break/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Ethereum</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-turns-red-and-at-risk-below-0-45/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Ripple</a>, and Litecoin against the US Dollar. Earlier, LTC settled below the $85 resistance zone to move into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>The price broke the $80 support zone and tested the $75 support. A low is formed near $75.32 and the price is now attempting a recovery wave. There was a move above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $79.76 swing high to the $75.32 low.</p>
<p>It is now trading below $85 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $82.50 zone.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $85 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $84.8 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair. The trend line is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $79.76 swing high to the $75.32 low.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $85 level could pump the price toward the $92 level or even $95. The next major resistance could be $100.</p>
<p>On the downside, immediate support is near the $78 level. The next key support is near the $75 level. If there is a downside break below the $75 support, the price could accelerate lower toward the $70 level in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_78284" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Litecoin-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78284" class="size-full wp-image-78284" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Litecoin-1.png" alt="Litecoin (LTC) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78284" class="wp-caption-text">Litecoin (LTC) Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Litecoin price is clearly trading below $85 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $85 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LTC/USD is now losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $78.00 and $75.00.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $82.50 and $85.00.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-face-uphill-task-2/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Face Uphill Task</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-face-uphill-task-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk Asks Judge to Toss Out Dogecoin-Centered Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-asks-judge-to-toss-out-dogecoin-centered-lawsuit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-asks-judge-to-toss-out-dogecoin-centered-lawsuit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 17:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lawsuit]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77740</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At the time of writing, South African billionaire and entrepreneur Elon Musk – the man who brought companies like Tesla and SpaceX to the forefront – is currently trapped in the middle of a $258 billion lawsuit centering on his promotion of digital currencies like Dogecoin. Elon Musk Requests Dismissal of Court Case Musk is<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-asks-judge-to-toss-out-dogecoin-centered-lawsuit/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-asks-judge-to-toss-out-dogecoin-centered-lawsuit/">Elon Musk Asks Judge to Toss Out Dogecoin-Centered Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>At the time of writing, South African billionaire and entrepreneur Elon Musk – the man who brought companies like Tesla and SpaceX to the forefront – is <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-i-never-forced-anyone-to-invest-in-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">currently trapped in the middle</a> of a $258 billion lawsuit centering on his promotion of digital currencies like Dogecoin.</p>
<h2>Elon Musk Requests Dismissal of Court Case</h2>
<p>Musk is now asking the judge <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/04/02/a-legitimate-cryptocurrency-dogecoin-price-suddenly-soars-after-elon-musk-hits-back-at-258-billion-lawsuit/?sh=4de179fb3185" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">overseeing the case to toss</a> it out. The lawsuit stems from a group of defendants that invested in Dogecoin last year following heavy promotion and praise from Musk, who’s had a lot of nice things to say about Dogecoin in the past. Not long ago, he referred to the asset as “the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-affirms-his-position-on-doge-its-the-peoples-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">people’s crypto</a>.”</p>
<p>Sadly, 2022 was marred by a heavy bear run that saw many digital currencies drop into the doldrums and lose 70 percent or more of their values. Bitcoin, for example, was trading at a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit in November of 2021, though 12 months later, it had fallen into the $16,000 range. It was a sad and ugly sight to see.</p>
<p>Dogecoin also suffered heavily during this time, and many people lost all their money after making investments in the popular meme currency co-invented by Jackson Palmer. They are now suing Musk, saying he’s responsible for their losses and that they never would have invested in the asset had they not seen Musk praise it so much.</p>
<p>Over the past few weeks, Dogecoin has jumped up in price by about ten percent. In a statement, lawyers for Musk said there’s no base to the lawsuit, as their client did not force anyone to engage in crypto trading. They commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>There is nothing unlawful about tweeting words of support for, or funny pictures about, a legitimate cryptocurrency that continues to hold a market cap of nearly $10 billion. This court should put a stop to [the] plaintiffs&#8217; fantasy and dismiss the complaint.</p></blockquote>
<p>At first glance, this appears like a one-and-done case that will be dismissed outright. After all, what Musk’s lawyers say is true. It’s not like the South African billionaire held a gun to anyone’s head and said to them, “Either invest in Dogecoin or I pull the trigger.” At the end of the day, there’s certainly sympathy for their losses, but those who invested in Dogecoin chose to do so on their own accord, and they were not forced into action by any outside party.</p>
<h2>Nefariously Pumping Up the Price?</h2>
<p>Still, lawyers for the defendants are not giving up. A member of the legal team recently said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We are more confident than ever that our case will be successful.</p></blockquote>
<p>The lawsuit says Musk is responsible for pumping up the Dogecoin price over the course of two years by about 36,000 percent, then allowing it to crash.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-asks-judge-to-toss-out-dogecoin-centered-lawsuit/">Elon Musk Asks Judge to Toss Out Dogecoin-Centered Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-asks-judge-to-toss-out-dogecoin-centered-lawsuit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elizabeth Warren Is Creating an Anti-Crypto Rhetoric as Part of Her Reelection Campaign</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elizabeth-warren-is-building-an-anti-crypto-rhetoric-as-part-of-her-reelection-campaign/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elizabeth-warren-is-building-an-anti-crypto-rhetoric-as-part-of-her-reelection-campaign/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 15:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coin Center]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Restrict Act]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77736</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Elizabeth Warren – the democrat senator from Massachusetts – has built a reputation as one of the most anti-crypto people in Congress. Reports are now emerging from organizations like crypto lobbying group Coin Center suggesting that Warren is now building a major “anti-crypto army” as part of her reelection campaign. Elizabeth Warren Still Hates Crypto<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elizabeth-warren-is-building-an-anti-crypto-rhetoric-as-part-of-her-reelection-campaign/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elizabeth-warren-is-building-an-anti-crypto-rhetoric-as-part-of-her-reelection-campaign/">Elizabeth Warren Is Creating an Anti-Crypto Rhetoric as Part of Her Reelection Campaign</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Elizabeth Warren – the democrat senator from Massachusetts – has built a reputation as one of the most anti-crypto people in Congress. Reports are now emerging from organizations like crypto lobbying group Coin Center suggesting <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/03/30/elizabeth-warren-is-building-an-anti-crypto-army-feeding-serious-us-bitcoin-ban-warnings/?sh=5223718171f6" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">that Warren is now building</a> a major “anti-crypto army” as part of her reelection campaign.</p>
<h2>Elizabeth Warren Still Hates Crypto</h2>
<p>The headlines are leading to concern amongst digital currency fans, who believe that a bitcoin ban in the U.S. isn’t too far off the mark. Not too long ago, on Twitter, Warren announced:</p>
<blockquote><p>I’m in this fight to put our government on the side of working families.</p></blockquote>
<p>Warren has never been a digital currency fan. Not long ago, she <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fidelity-is-still-taking-flak-for-its-crypto-offerings/" data-wpel-link="internal">adamantly criticized</a> Fidelity, a 401K and retirement platform that announced it was going to let people invest their hard-earned retirement funds in digital assets like bitcoin. Warren took serious issue with this given she felt when people are retired, they are the most vulnerable. Their funds are likely going towards medical issues and other problems that tend to arrive when old age sets in.</p>
<p>Given how volatile and speculative digital currencies are, she’s been very much against Fidelity and similar companies allowing people to invest their remaining funds in items that could literally lose their value overnight. Last December, Warren took issue with the idea that bitcoin and other digital assets are often used to fund terrorism or that they’re utilized in malicious schemes. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Rogue nations, oligarchs, drug lords, and human traffickers are using digital assets to launder billions in stolen funds, evade sanctions, and finance terrorism.</p></blockquote>
<p>In a blog, Coin Center issued a warning to all digital currency traders in America. The warning centered on what’s known as the Restrict Act, a new bill that allegedly opens the door to a potential bitcoin and crypto ban in the U.S. The company explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>Although the primary targets of this legislation are companies like TikTok, the language of the bill could potentially be used to block or disrupt cryptocurrency transactions and, in extreme cases, block Americans’ access to open-source tools or protocols like bitcoin.</p></blockquote>
<p>The American government appears to have been on the crypto warpath ever since the collapse of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX in November</a> last year. Since that time, there appears to have been a lot more action against digital currency companies through agencies such as the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), which has gone after companies like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/" data-wpel-link="internal">Kraken</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">Coinbase</a>.</p>
<h2>Just Be Straight with the People!</h2>
<p>Kevin Reynolds – a digital currency editor and writer – said:</p>
<blockquote><p>If&#8230; authorities do intend to restrain that progress, they should declare that goal openly and pursue it through transparent democratic channels. I hope&#8230; the Biden administration is not out to kill crypto. Assuming that’s the case, the White House needs to clearly demonstrate its positive intent.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elizabeth-warren-is-building-an-anti-crypto-rhetoric-as-part-of-her-reelection-campaign/">Elizabeth Warren Is Creating an Anti-Crypto Rhetoric as Part of Her Reelection Campaign</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elizabeth-warren-is-building-an-anti-crypto-rhetoric-as-part-of-her-reelection-campaign/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jason Lowery: Wars Will Be Fought with Bitcoin, Not Guns</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jason-lowery-wars-will-be-fought-with-bitcoin-not-guns/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jason-lowery-wars-will-be-fought-with-bitcoin-not-guns/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 13:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jason Lowery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wars]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77734</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Could wars be settled on the blockchain rather than a battlefield? According to Space Force officer Jason Lowery, the future of wars and conflicts between countries will not be settled by tanks and guns, but rather by how much bitcoin and crypto they have to their names. Jason Lowery Says the U.S. Must Adopt BTC<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jason-lowery-wars-will-be-fought-with-bitcoin-not-guns/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jason-lowery-wars-will-be-fought-with-bitcoin-not-guns/">Jason Lowery: Wars Will Be Fought with Bitcoin, Not Guns</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Could wars be settled on the blockchain rather than a battlefield? According to Space Force officer Jason Lowery, the <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/04/02/a-dramatic-impact-pentagon-told-bitcoin-can-prevent-war-by-space-force-major/?sh=33e2d4ff756d" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">future of wars and conflicts</a> between countries will not be settled by tanks and guns, but rather by how much bitcoin and crypto they have to their names.</p>
<h2>Jason Lowery Says the U.S. Must Adopt BTC</h2>
<p>Lowery is confident cyberspace will play a huge role in future conflicts. He says countries with a lot of bitcoins in their reserves will likely remain at the top of the power ladder, while those with lesser amounts will have a harder time establishing dominance and making their marks on society.</p>
<p>For this reason, Lowery is asking the U.S. federal government to adopt bitcoin as a national currency, saying that if it doesn’t, the nation runs the risk of falling behind and becoming vulnerable to a whole new string of villains and enemies. A 400-page report on the matter states:</p>
<blockquote><p>Using scientific concepts from biology, evolution, anthropology, political science, and computer theory, Lowery summarizes the dynamics of power projection in human society and provides an argument for why emerging proof-of-work technologies (namely bitcoin) will have a dramatic impact on how humans organize, cooperate, and compete on a global scale by empowering populations to project physical power in, from, and through cyberspace.</p></blockquote>
<p>Lowery is clearly suggesting a direction exactly the opposite of the one the U.S. has been traversing for the past several months. Right now, the country’s leaders are practically doing everything they can to shut out bitcoin and digital currency for good. For example, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has been prosecuting as many crypto firms as possible, recently sending a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">Wells notice to Coinbase</a> and forcing Kraken to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/" data-wpel-link="internal">end its staking services</a>.</p>
<p>In addition, head Gary Gensler has reached out to Congress asking for further funds so he and his cronies can <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-wants-more-funds-to-go-after-crypto-companies/" data-wpel-link="internal">continue their anti-crypto</a> agenda.</p>
<p>There are also many members of the federal government that are <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/janet-yellen-following-ftx-we-must-regulate-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">now calling for crypto regulation</a>. This is AFTER they accepted digital (and likely dirty) funds from Sam Bankman-Fried, the man who ran the now defunct crypto exchange FTX. Biden and several other democratic members of government accepted bribes and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-gave-a-lot-of-money-to-democrats-what-will-they-do-with-it/" data-wpel-link="internal">campaign donations in the</a> form of digital assets from SBF.</p>
<p>Now that the company has shut down, they are calling for instant crypto regulation as they are hoping to prevent another massive disaster, yet they’ve made no mention of what they plan to do with the dirty funds they received from the former crypto executive.</p>
<h2>The Regulatory Scene Is a Bit Concerning</h2>
<p>The situation also presents several scary conditions given that it’s unlikely they could have had such close relations with SBF and FTX and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-did-the-ftx-fall-expose-a-government-conspiracy/" data-wpel-link="internal">not realized what was going</a> on.</p>
<p>Lowery is an active duty astronautical engineer and a defense fellow at MIT.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jason-lowery-wars-will-be-fought-with-bitcoin-not-guns/">Jason Lowery: Wars Will Be Fought with Bitcoin, Not Guns</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jason-lowery-wars-will-be-fought-with-bitcoin-not-guns/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Block3000: Blockchain Battle Early Bird Tickets on Sale Now!</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block3000-blockchain-battle-early-bird-tickets-on-sale-now/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block3000-blockchain-battle-early-bird-tickets-on-sale-now/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 09:48:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78262</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Secure more than 40% off on tickets for one of the biggest blockchain events in Europe. More than 5,000+ delegates are expected to grace the stunning Altice Arena in Lisbon, Portugal this July 6 &#38; 7, 2023, as Block 3000: Blockchain Battle gathers the best and brightest of Blockchain, Web3 and Crypto to unveil exciting<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block3000-blockchain-battle-early-bird-tickets-on-sale-now/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block3000-blockchain-battle-early-bird-tickets-on-sale-now/">Block3000: Blockchain Battle Early Bird Tickets on Sale Now!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Secure more than 40% off on tickets for one of the biggest blockchain events in Europe.</em></p>
<p>More than 5,000+ delegates are expected to grace the stunning Altice Arena in Lisbon, Portugal this July 6 &amp; 7, 2023, as Block 3000: Blockchain Battle gathers the best and brightest of Blockchain, Web3 and Crypto to unveil exciting new projects, engage in priceless networking and to set the discourse for the industry.</p>
<p>Block 3000: Blockchain Battle will welcome a diverse range of speakers that includes C-Suite Executives from some of Fintech’s biggest movers and shakers, influential media figures, inspirational founders and Blockchain thought leaders.</p>
<p><strong>A Leading Lineup of World-Class Speakers</strong></p>
<p>Presented by the Count of Monte Crypto, Dustin Plantholt, Speakers at Block3000: Blockchain Battle include:</p>
<ul>
<li>Zoe Wei: shei is now the BNB Chain Head of Developer Relations. She has worked in several critical roles at BNB Chain and Binance for the past 4 years.</li>
<li>Carl “The Moon&#8221; Runefelt: Serial entrepreneur and crypto-evangelist who has invested in 400 blockchain-based startups. A social media icon who made Forbes 30 under 30.</li>
<li>Laurent Perello: TronDAO Blockchain Advisor in Europe. Serial entrepreneur and investor, evangelist in the field of cloud computing and digital transformation.</li>
<li>Cyrus Fazel: Founder &amp; CEO of SwissBorg. A multicultural fintech professional. Has created Europe’s top crypto wealth app with 700K+ active users.</li>
<li>Miguel Palencia: Co-founder and COO. He has 9 years experience in blockchain technology and 21 years in server administration, and Linux development.</li>
<li>Dmytro Budorin: Co-Founder &amp; CEO of Hacken, leads 120+ team, brings transparency to crypto with cybersecurity services, built CER.live &amp; Proof of Reserves.</li>
<li>Adrien Gheur: Director of Investments at Zilliqa. Has 20+ years of experience in investing, building companies and entrepreneurship.</li>
<li>Kiril Nikolov: DeFi strategist at Nexo. He has built out Defi operations and is currently incubating small, agile tech teams to become standalone DeFi protocols.</li>
<li>Sami Waittinen: Marketing Head at Trust Wallet, brings leadership experience in finance and tech, excels at managing products, operations, and stakeholders.</li>
<li>Javier Garcia: Country Leader for Iberia at Binance, experience in digital transformation and product management in Payments, Fintech, and E-commerce.</li>
</ul>
<p>And many others. A total of over 50 speakers are planned to be gathered.</p>
<p><strong>Block 3000: Blockchain Battle | What you Need to Know</strong></p>
<p>With 5,000+ attendees from around the world, 100 exhibitors and 50+ speakers, Block 3000 is the ultimate networking event for blockchain and crypto.</p>
<p>Talks from prominent thought leaders will set the discourse for the industry as a whole, paired with ample networking opportunities, with investors and exciting projects flocking to the event!</p>
<p>The event will feature Blockchain Battle: innovative and intellectual show held in a format of panel discussions with four to five speakers per round. During the panels, the speakers will delve into the various perspectives and challenges associated with blockchain networks, interoperability, scalability, and security. They will explore the potential of these technologies and how they can be leveraged to create innovative solutions to existing problems within both the blockchain ecosystem and the wider fintech space.</p>
<p><strong>Block: 3000 Blockchain Battle Early-Bird Tickets</strong></p>
<p>Time is running out to secure an early-bird ticket (with more than 40% off!) for one of the hottest crypto and blockchain events of 2023!</p>
<p>Tickets come in a variety of packages to suit delegates’ needs &#8211; from Standard which includes access to the conference and networking events, to our very special Whale package, which includes:</p>
<ul>
<li>Conference access (best Whale seats in 1-2 row)</li>
<li>Welcome bag from our partners and sponsors</li>
<li>Exclusive gifts from partners and sponsors</li>
<li>Networking app</li>
<li><strong>VIP</strong> coffee breaks and lunch</li>
<li>Conference video</li>
<li>PartyNight</li>
<li>VIP registration</li>
<li>VIP lounge area + access to <strong>speakers area with terrace</strong></li>
<li>3d Networking Day</li>
<li>There will also be some extra surprises to be revealed later!</li>
</ul>
<p>For more information and to buy your tickets, <a href="https://www.block3000.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">click here</a>.</p>
<p>Follow us on social media for all the latest updates on Block 3000: Blockchain Battle<br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/blockchain_3000?s=21&amp;t=cTQ56daBVF0L0KV3dnHdKQ" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener"> </a><a href="https://twitter.com/blockchain_3000?s=21&amp;t=cTQ56daBVF0L0KV3dnHdKQ" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a> | <a href="https://t.me/block3000channel" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block3000-blockchain-battle-early-bird-tickets-on-sale-now/">Block3000: Blockchain Battle Early Bird Tickets on Sale Now!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block3000-blockchain-battle-early-bird-tickets-on-sale-now/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Fresh Increase To $0.072 Seems Likely</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-fresh-increase-to-0-072-seems-likely/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-fresh-increase-to-0-072-seems-likely/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 05:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78259</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tron price started a fresh increase from the $0.0670 level against the US Dollar. TRX price is now trading near $0.0692 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0694 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could continue to move<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-fresh-increase-to-0-072-seems-likely/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-fresh-increase-to-0-072-seems-likely/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Fresh Increase To $0.072 Seems Likely</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Tron price started a fresh increase from the $0.0670 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>TRX price is now trading near $0.0692 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0694 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move up if it breaks the $0.070 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>TRON price started a fresh increase above $0.0685 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-29k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. TRX’s price could rise further if it clears the $0.070 resistance.</em></p>
<h2>Tron Price Analysis</h2>
<p>After a downside correction, Tron price found support near the $0.0672 zone against the US Dollar. TRX’s price formed a base and recently started a fresh increase from the $0.0671 low.</p>
<p>There was a break above the $0.0675 and $0.0680 levels. The price climbed above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.0714 swing high to the $0.0671 low. TRX is now trading near $0.0692 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bullish-break-signals-more-gains/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>On the upside, TRX is facing resistance near the $0.0694 level. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.0694 on the 4-hours chart.</p>
<p>The trend line is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.0714 swing high to the $0.0671 low. The next major resistance is near the $0.070 level. A close above $0.070 could send the price toward the $0.0720 resistance zone.</p>
<p>Any more gains might send TRX price toward $0.075, above which the price could even rise toward $0.078. On the downside, initial support is near the $0.0680 level. The next major support is now forming near $0.0670 or the recent low.</p>
<p>If there is a downside break below the $0.0670 support, the price might revisit the $0.0644 support. Any more losses might call for a move toward the $0.0620 zone in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_78260" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/TRON-TRX-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78260" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78260" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/TRON-TRX-1.png" alt="Tron (TRX) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78260" class="wp-caption-text">Tron (TRX) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/TRXUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that TRX’s price is now trading near $0.0693 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move up if it breaks the $0.070 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for TRX/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for TRX/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.0680 and $0.0670.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.0694, $0.070, and $0.0720.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-fresh-increase-to-0-072-seems-likely/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Fresh Increase To $0.072 Seems Likely</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-fresh-increase-to-0-072-seems-likely/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Turns Red Below $29K</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-29k/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-29k/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 03:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78255</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price started a fresh decline below the $29,000 pivot level against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $28,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support at $28,400 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-29k/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-29k/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Turns Red Below $29K</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin price started a fresh decline below the $29,000 pivot level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $28,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support at $28,400 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could extend its decline toward the $27,000 and $26,200 levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin price is declining below $28,500 against the US Dollar. BTC might extend losses if it stays below the $28,500 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price started a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-extend-losses-below-27000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">fresh decline</a> below the $29,000 zone. A high was formed near $29,850 before the price started a steady decline. There was a clear move below the $29,000 and $28,500 support levels.</p>
<p>The bears even pushed the price below the $28,000 support zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). The price traded as low as $27,279 and is currently correcting losses. There was a correction toward the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward wave from the $29,850 swing high to the $27,279 low.</p>
<p>However, it is still trading below $29,500 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-29250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. Immediate resistance on the upside is near the $27,900 level. The next major resistance might be near the $28,150 zone.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $28,150 level might send the price toward $28,500 or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward wave from the $29,850 swing high to the $27,279 low, above which the price might rise toward the $29,200 level. Any more gains might push the price toward the $30,000 zone.</p>
<p>If there is no upside break, the price might decline below the $27,250 level. The first major support is near $27,000. The next key support is near the $26,200 level, below which the price might accelerate lower. In the stated case, the price could decline toward the $25,500 level. Any more losses might send the price toward the $25,000 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_78256" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Bitcoin-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78256" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78256" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Bitcoin-1.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78256" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XBTUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Bitcoin price is clearly trading below $28,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could extend its decline toward the $27,000 and $26,200 levels.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD is now losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $27,250 and $27,000.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $28,000, $28,500, and $29,200.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-29k/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Turns Red Below $29K</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-29k/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jake Paul Settles Crypto-Related Charges with the SEC</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jake-paul-settles-crypto-related-charges-with-the-sec/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jake-paul-settles-crypto-related-charges-with-the-sec/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 17:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jake Paul]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lindsay Lohan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77732</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Social media star and boxer Jake Paul has recently settled crypto-related charges with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Paul had initially been hired by blockchain network Tron to promote a new digital currency, though he had allegedly failed to reveal he was being paid to engage in the promotion. Jake Paul and the SEC<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jake-paul-settles-crypto-related-charges-with-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jake-paul-settles-crypto-related-charges-with-the-sec/">Jake Paul Settles Crypto-Related Charges with the SEC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Social media star and boxer Jake Paul has recently settled <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/jake-paul-26-reaches-settlement-following-crazy-cryptocurrency-controversy/ar-AA19hmkP" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">crypto-related charges with</a> the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Paul had initially been hired by <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-targets-tron-in-latest-crypto-case/" data-wpel-link="internal">blockchain network Tron to promote</a> a new digital currency, though he had allegedly failed to reveal he was being paid to engage in the promotion.</p>
<h2>Jake Paul and the SEC Settle Their &#8220;Differences&#8221;</h2>
<p>The SEC says that this goes against present securities laws. If you are granted payment for taking part in a crypto or token-based promotion, you must reveal this data to your fans and followers. Discussing the present case against Tron and the numerous celebrities it paid to endorse its product(s), SEC head Gary Gensler explained in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>This case demonstrates again the high-risk investors face when crypto asset securities are offered and sold without proper disclosure. As alleged, Sun and his companies not only targeted U.S. investors in their unregistered offers and sales, generating millions in illegal proceeds at the expense of investors, but they also coordinated wash trading on an unregistered trading platform to create the misleading appearance of active trading in TRX. Sun further induced investors to purchase TRX and BTT by orchestrating a promotional campaign in which he and his celebrity promoters hid the fact that the celebrities were paid for their tweets.</p></blockquote>
<p>Paul is not the only celebrity being targeted by the federal financial agency. Among the others is Lindsay Lohan, who also took part in Tron’s online promotion. It’s alleged in lawsuit documents that the actress and former child star was paid roughly $10K to promote Tronix tokens on Twitter, though she failed to let her social media followers know she had received compensation. A spokesperson for Lohan said that she was unaware that she was required to disclose this information and that she’s agreed to pay a fine to resolve the matter.</p>
<p>It’s estimated that the fines Paul paid exceeded $400K. In other news, Paul is claiming to have at one time taken a hallucinogen with football star Aaron Rodgers. In an interview with FOX News, Paul said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Aaron and I were together when we did the ayahuasca. He&#8217;s more publicly known for speaking about it, but I was actually there with him when we did it. We spent the week there doing it. [We] share that similarity in terms of spirituality and reflecting and going into the deepest parts of the mind.</p></blockquote>
<h2>The Agency Is Going After Every Crypto Company, It Seems</h2>
<p>It’s unclear if the present SEC case against Tron is valid or if it’s just another attempt (in a long string of attempts) to bring the crypto space down.</p>
<p>Not long ago, the SEC forced Kraken to part with a $30 million fine and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/" data-wpel-link="internal">end its staking activities and services</a>. It <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">also sent a Wells notice</a> to Coinbase letting it know it could likely face charges.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jake-paul-settles-crypto-related-charges-with-the-sec/">Jake Paul Settles Crypto-Related Charges with the SEC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jake-paul-settles-crypto-related-charges-with-the-sec/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Event TAB Conf Will Soon Take Place in Atlanta</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-event-tab-conf-will-soon-take-place-in-atlanta/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-event-tab-conf-will-soon-take-place-in-atlanta/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 15:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brandon Iglesias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TAB Conf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77729</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Two crypto developers are establishing a new bitcoin-centered conference in Atlanta, Georgia. This will be a reimagining of the TAB Conf gathering that’s occurred every year for the last five years within the capital city. TAB Conf Is Almost Here TAB Conf is still set to occur at the end of 2023. The event allows<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-event-tab-conf-will-soon-take-place-in-atlanta/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-event-tab-conf-will-soon-take-place-in-atlanta/">Bitcoin Event TAB Conf Will Soon Take Place in Atlanta</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Two crypto developers are <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/planners-bitcoin-conference-atlanta-move-160405191.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">establishing a new bitcoin-centered</a> conference in Atlanta, Georgia. This will be a reimagining of the TAB Conf gathering that’s occurred every year for the last five years within the capital city.</p>
<h2>TAB Conf Is Almost Here</h2>
<p>TAB Conf is still set to occur at the end of 2023. The event allows members of the public to recommend specific crypto-related topics that they would like to discuss and hear about. This new conference will be more open-source and feature subjects relating to the open-source nature of bitcoin, which the developers seem to think has been dying out over time.</p>
<p>Co-founder of TAB Conf LLC Brandon Iglesias gave his initial ideas regarding the event in an interview. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Anyone can open an issue, and the issues are not selected based on whether a sponsor decides to give us money or whether a person has a certain status in the community. The issues are solely chosen based on merit.</p></blockquote>
<p>Both he and his fellow co-founder Michael Tidwell developed TAB Conf in 2018. The event was established through a long meetup series they initially organized to get more people interested in the growing crypto space. Iglesias also serves as the director of product at decentralized storage firm Storj, while Tidwell is the director of infrastructure at the bitcoin gaming and payments firm Zebedee (which has recently put out a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/zebedee-gaming-platform-unveils-bitcoin-chess/" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin-centered version of chess</a>).</p>
<p>Iglesias continued his statement with:</p>
<blockquote><p>What we&#8217;re doing is we&#8217;re having people go on to a GitHub repository and submit ideas for workshops and panels and talks that they want to either see at the conference or give at the conference. This is all public and transparent… The level of detail and time potential speakers put into their issues will show and help us decide what issues will bring the most value to the TAB Conf 2023 attendees. If we don&#8217;t select an issue with a lot of conversation or emojis compared to the rest, the attendees at least have transparency and can hold us accountable.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Strong, Five-Year History</h2>
<p>When TAB Conf first debuted, it attracted more than 500 attendees and featured several dozen speakers. Among them were bitcoin core developers Andrew Chow, Gloria Zhao, and Murch and Pieter Wuille. Jeremy Rubin, a developer, also discussed the growing world of bitcoin smart contracts. At that stage, said contracts were predominantly associated with Ethereum.</p>
<p>Before now, the job of coming up with the agenda to be featured in each conference lied on the shoulders of the event’s organizers, though now, both Iglesias and Tidwell are letting the public have more of a hand in deciding how and where the event should operate and the directions it should move in. This, they say, brings the democratic nature of bitcoin more front and center.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-event-tab-conf-will-soon-take-place-in-atlanta/">Bitcoin Event TAB Conf Will Soon Take Place in Atlanta</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-event-tab-conf-will-soon-take-place-in-atlanta/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
