<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 03:20:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Spikes Following Silicon Valley Bankruptcy</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-spikes-following-silicon-valley-bankruptcy/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-spikes-following-silicon-valley-bankruptcy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 17:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[banks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Silicon Valley]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77506</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Silicon Valley Bank is in the process of filing bankruptcy, bringing back rough memories of the FTX debacle five months ago. However, the effects appear to be the opposite of what they were back in November. During that time, bitcoin and its altcoin cousins fell to new lows, whereas this time around, bitcoin and several<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-spikes-following-silicon-valley-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-spikes-following-silicon-valley-bankruptcy/">Bitcoin Spikes Following Silicon Valley Bankruptcy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Silicon Valley Bank is in the process of filing bankruptcy, bringing back rough <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">memories of the FTX</a> debacle five months ago. However, the <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/03/17/buy-now-2-trillion-fed-bazooka-triggers-shock-hyperinflation-warning-amid-bitcoin-ethereum-and-crypto-price-boom/?sh=3c995c24651d" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">effects appear to be the</a> opposite of what they were back in November. During that time, bitcoin and its altcoin cousins fell to new lows, whereas this time around, bitcoin and several of its counterparts appear to be surging like crazy.</p>
<h2>Silicon Valley Dips While BTC Rises</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, BTC – the world’s number one cryptocurrency by market cap – has shot beyond the $27,000 mark, and there are many analysts out there that seem to believe $30K could be next granted the currency manages to keep up its present patterns. Just over the last few weeks, the currency has risen by more than 30 percent, and many other assets are following in its footsteps.</p>
<p>With bitcoin rising, many crypto-based stocks – such as Coinbase – are also on the rise. America’s largest and most popular digital currency exchange has seen its stock jump by more than nine percent during this time, and the momentum just keeps on picking up as time goes by.</p>
<p>Coinbase’s chief tech officer Balaji Srinivasan says that the current banking crisis being witnessed in the States could lead to a serious case of hyperinflation. He is now telling users to buy as much BTC and crypto as they can before the standard banking industry goes haywire. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The central bank, the banks, and the bank regulators have bankrupted all of us. They hid their insolvency from you, the depositors, and they&#8217;re about to print $2 trillion to hyperinflate the dollar. In the digital age, this will happen very quickly, so buy bitcoin now and get your coins off exchanges.</p></blockquote>
<p>The fall of Silicon Valley Bank is being labeled the biggest collapse since the 2008 financial crisis. The Federal Insurance Deposit Corporation (FDIC) has now had to step in and say that all deposits lost at both Silicon Valley and Signature Bank will be fully backed. Nikolaos Panigirtzoglou explained in a recent note to his clients:</p>
<blockquote><p>The usage of the Fed’s bank term funding program is likely to be big.</p></blockquote>
<p>Srinivasan continued his initial statement with:</p>
<blockquote><p>The entire banking system is lying to you about solvency. They are trying to ensure you don&#8217;t exit to bitcoin before they print the money.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Is the Banking System Lying to Us?</h2>
<p>Markus Thielen – head of research and strategy at Matrix Port – also threw his two cents into the mix, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin benefits from full-blown, government-guaranteed deposit insurance, from inflation falling back to the three percent level, which allows the central bank to become less hawkish, and from regulatory overhang that has impacted stablecoins such as BUSD and, recently, USDC. Bitcoin loves liquidity, and is the primary crypto weapon of choice when those liquidity floodgates are being alternated, such as now.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-spikes-following-silicon-valley-bankruptcy/">Bitcoin Spikes Following Silicon Valley Bankruptcy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-spikes-following-silicon-valley-bankruptcy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aaron Ford: I&#8217;ll Protect All Nevadans from Crypto Scams</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/aaron-ford-ill-protect-all-nevadans-from-crypto-scams/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/aaron-ford-ill-protect-all-nevadans-from-crypto-scams/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 15:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aaron Ford]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto scams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nevada]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77502</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nevada Attorney General Aaron Ford has sworn to protect all residents of his state from crypto scams, and he’s putting out notices to everyone to tell them what they can do to avoid becoming victims. Aaron Ford Vows to Protect People of His State In a recent statement, Ford commented: The safety of Nevada consumers<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/aaron-ford-ill-protect-all-nevadans-from-crypto-scams/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/aaron-ford-ill-protect-all-nevadans-from-crypto-scams/">Aaron Ford: I&#8217;ll Protect All Nevadans from Crypto Scams</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nevada Attorney General Aaron Ford <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/personalfinance/attorney-general-aaron-ford-warns-nevadans-of-recent-cryptocurrency-scams/ar-AA18IX5A" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">has sworn to protect</a> all residents of his state from crypto scams, and he’s putting out notices to everyone to tell them what they can do to avoid becoming victims.</p>
<h2>Aaron Ford Vows to Protect People of His State</h2>
<p>In a recent statement, Ford commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>The safety of Nevada consumers is a top priority at my office. As technology becomes an increasingly integral part of our lives, scams involving digital currency are becoming more prevalent. We want Nevadans to know how cryptocurrency works and what they should watch out for to protect themselves and their families.</p></blockquote>
<p>Crypto scams have been rather prominent as of late. Today, they are mostly taking on the form of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/romance-scam/" data-wpel-link="internal">romance scams</a>, in which hackers and cyberthieves find would-be victims by traveling through dating sites and related platforms to find people looking for love or lasting partners. They narrow in on certain individuals and get to know them personally.</p>
<p>All seems fine and dandy at first and a victim seems to think they’ve found a soul mate of sorts. It’s not long before they’re coaxed into investing in a phony crypto platform, though they’re not aware that it’s fake. All seems legitimate and real, and they don’t want to disappoint the new friend they’ve made, so they put money into the platform, not knowing that everything is run by their new partner’s alleged ring of fellow cybercriminals.</p>
<p>Everything initially goes well in that their investments appear to be growing. They’re convinced to invest more, and before long, they’ve made more money than they ever thought possible. However, when they go to make a withdrawal, problems usually arise. They are told that they cannot do so unless they pay heavy fees or invest even more funds into the platform.</p>
<p>Eventually, they realize what happened and walk away with bruised egos, broken hearts, and empty pockets. It’s a rough situation to be in, no doubt. Ford also says that with so many more businesses in his state (and elsewhere) now becoming more crypto friendly, there are many hackers out there that have become savvy to how these companies operate and have adapted to their thievery methods so they can make off with customer funds, not just money from those looking for love.</p>
<h2>How to Avoid Being a Victim</h2>
<p>Ford is telling people what they can do to avoid falling for crypto scams. For one thing, they should never share their financial data with anyone they meet on a dating site. They can also perform due diligence regarding certain platforms to see if they’re real or not. If something sounds too good to be true, it probably is.</p>
<p>Lastly, they can surround themselves with plenty of friends and family that they can turn to for advice if they’re ever unsure about what will happen.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/aaron-ford-ill-protect-all-nevadans-from-crypto-scams/">Aaron Ford: I&#8217;ll Protect All Nevadans from Crypto Scams</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/aaron-ford-ill-protect-all-nevadans-from-crypto-scams/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Does Eric Adams Plan to Use Blockchain?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-does-eric-adams-plan-to-use-blockchain/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-does-eric-adams-plan-to-use-blockchain/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 13:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Eric Adams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New York]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77500</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Eric Adams has long been a crypto fan. As the mayor of New York City, arguably one of the biggest cities in the world, Adams goes against what many of his democrat constituents in the region say and do regarding crypto. For them, the asset is something to be banned and ignored, while Adams has<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-does-eric-adams-plan-to-use-blockchain/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-does-eric-adams-plan-to-use-blockchain/">How Does Eric Adams Plan to Use Blockchain?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Eric Adams has long been a crypto fan. As the mayor of New York City, arguably one of the biggest cities in the world, Adams goes against what many of his democrat constituents in the region say and do regarding crypto. For them, the asset is <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-signs-crypto-moratorium-into-law/" data-wpel-link="internal">something to be banned</a> and ignored, while Adams has gone so far as to claim BTC should be <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eric-adams-wants-crypto-taught-in-nyc-schools/" data-wpel-link="internal">taught in public schoolrooms</a>.</p>
<h2>Eric Adams and Blockchain: What Are the Possibilities?</h2>
<p>The enthusiasm of Adams appears to be <a href="https://www.gothamgazette.com/city/11883-city-council-mayor-adams-blockchain-cryptocurrency" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">landing on the people</a> that now work with him and for him. Not long ago, Jennifer Gutierrez – a city council member – called for an oversight hearing into blockchain technology and how Adams wants to use it in future NYC operations. In her opening statements on the panel, she commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>We must do our due diligence to not only understand cryptocurrency and blockchain technology, but also make sure New Yorkers can properly access the necessary information to safely navigate these novel technologies. Today’s hearing aims to draw in any vision for both technologies, ensuring that as a city, we are giving thoughtful consideration to this potentially transformational technology and industry, rather than refusing to exchange because the issues are complicated and not yet fully formed.</p></blockquote>
<p>The city’s chief technology officer Matthew Fraser is also becoming a blockchain fan, saying it could be a powerful tool in driving New York City forward. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>In addition to the blockchain industry helping New York City’s economy recover from the lingering effects of the pandemic, blockchain technology has the potential to streamline and centralize document retention, enable real-time record consolidation, and support asset transfers, among many other applications. New York City has proudly been a pioneer in embracing the blockchain industry, as it evaluates the potential government applications and plants a flag as a viable home for blockchain companies that can grow our economy and hire new workers.</p></blockquote>
<p>The Adams administration has now been without controversy. One of the blockchain uses his team has proposed is using it to track what kind of food users are buying and then gather the information to educate them about healthier behavior. While the intent may be noble, this can be considered a clear invasion of privacy. Fraser commented on this by saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>Imagine for food benefits, if you had a digital wallet where you went out and spent a dollar on vegetables or something healthy versus sugary snacks or soda. The city could provide incentive points, meaning, dollar-matching, dollar-for-dollar, for what you spend on healthy products.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Don&#8217;t Spy on People!</h2>
<p>Queens republican and city council member Vickie Paladino also threw her two cents in, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>I don’t like the idea that you’re going to monitor people’s spending habits, whether they choose to buy healthy food or a bag of potato chips.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-does-eric-adams-plan-to-use-blockchain/">How Does Eric Adams Plan to Use Blockchain?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-does-eric-adams-plan-to-use-blockchain/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Bulls Struggle To Keep BCH In Bullish Zone</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bulls-struggle-to-keep-bch-in-bullish-zone/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bulls-struggle-to-keep-bch-in-bullish-zone/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 03:28:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78002</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline from the $135 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below the $130 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $131 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bulls-struggle-to-keep-bch-in-bullish-zone/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bulls-struggle-to-keep-bch-in-bullish-zone/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Bulls Struggle To Keep BCH In Bullish Zone</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline from the $135 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below the $130 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $131 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could start a decent increase if it stays above the $120 support zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin cash price is declining from the $135 zone against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-more-gains-above-31k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. BCH/USD could decline heavily if there is a move below $120.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin cash price struggled to gain pace for a move above the $135 and $136 resistance levels. BCH formed a high near $136.18 and started a fresh decline.</p>
<p>There was a clear move below the $130.00 and $125.00 support levels. Besides, there was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $131 on the 4-hours chart of the BCH/USD pair. The pair even declined below the $125 support.</p>
<p>A low is formed near $121.37 and the price is now consolidating losses. It is now trading below the $128 zone and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bulls-aim-higher-150-possible-target/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. Immediate resistance is near the $125 level. It is near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $136.18 swing high to the $121.37 low.</p>
<p>The next key resistance is near $128. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $136.18 swing high to the $121.37 low.</p>
<p>The main resistance sits near the $130 level. Any more gains above $128 and $130 could set the pace for a move toward the $135 level. If there is a move above the $135 resistance, the price could rise toward the $142 zone.</p>
<p>If not, the price might continue lower below $121. Immediate support on the downside is near the $120 zone. The next major support is near the $115 level, below which the bears might aim for $105.</p>
<div id="attachment_78003" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/04/Bitcoin-Cash-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78003" class="size-full wp-image-78003" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/04/Bitcoin-Cash-2.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78003" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Cash Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BCHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Bitcoin cash price is now trading below the $128 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start a decent increase if it stays above the $120 support zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for BCH/USD is losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BCH/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $120 and $115.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $125 and $128.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bulls-struggle-to-keep-bch-in-bullish-zone/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Bulls Struggle To Keep BCH In Bullish Zone</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bulls-struggle-to-keep-bch-in-bullish-zone/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Tool Chip Mixer Shut Down by the DOJ</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-tool-chip-mixer-shut-down-by-the-doj/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-tool-chip-mixer-shut-down-by-the-doj/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 17:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chip Mixer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DoJ]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mixer]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77491</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chip Mixer – a notorious crypto tool designed to hide where digital currencies have been garnered or who they’re being used by – has been shut down by authorities with the Department of Justice (DOJ). At the time of writing, it is believed the tool allowed cyberthieves and assorted criminals to launder as much as<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-tool-chip-mixer-shut-down-by-the-doj/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-tool-chip-mixer-shut-down-by-the-doj/">Crypto Tool Chip Mixer Shut Down by the DOJ</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chip Mixer – a notorious crypto tool designed to hide where digital currencies have been garnered or who they’re being used by – has <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/authorities-down-darknet-cryptocurrency-mixing-182047437.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">been shut down by authorities</a> with the Department of Justice (DOJ). At the time of writing, it is believed the tool allowed cyberthieves and assorted criminals to launder as much as $3 billion in illicit digital funds.</p>
<h2>Chip Mixer Is No More</h2>
<p>The DOJ also put out a statement claiming to have shuttered two sites associated with Chip Mixer along with the primary product itself. Chip Mixer may have been involved in several hacking schemes, as well as crypto heists, fraud, and even ransomware. The statement read as follows:</p>
<blockquote><p>This morning, working with partners at home and abroad, the Department of Justice disabled a prolific cryptocurrency mixer, which has fueled ransomware attacks, state-sponsored crypto-heists, and darknet purchases across the globe.</p></blockquote>
<p>Mixers can be very dangerous in that they are built to hide digital assets from prying eyes and law enforcement agencies. Thus, should crypto thieves or other illicit actors seek out their services, they can enclose where they receive their money, where they’re sending it, and who they got it from. This is troublesome because if the money is stolen (and most of the time, it is) it can be hard to trace, and thus victims stand to lose out 90 percent of the time.</p>
<p>In addition to shutting down the mixer, a Vietnamese operator of the tool has been arrested and charged with money laundering, operating an unlicensed money transmitting business, and identity theft among other things. A separate complaint reads:</p>
<blockquote><p>Chip Mixer attracted a significant criminal clientele and became indispensable in obfuscating and laundering funds from multiple criminal schemes.</p></blockquote>
<p>Jacqueline Maguire of the FBI Philadelphia Field Office also threw her two cents in, commenting:</p>
<blockquote><p>Criminals have long sought to launder the proceeds of their illegal activity through various means. Technology has changed the game, though, with a site like Chip Mixer and facilitator[s] like Nguyen enabling bad actors to do so on a grand scale with ease.</p></blockquote>
<p>This isn’t the first time the U.S. has targeted a foreign mixer. Not too long ago, the country issued <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/north-korea-crypto-mixer-tornado-cash-sanctioned-by-u-s/" data-wpel-link="internal">sanctions against</a> Tornado Cash, which is alleged to have been utilized by agents of North Korea to launder as much as $7 billion in crypto assets.</p>
<h2>This Wasn&#8217;t the First Time for the U.S.</h2>
<p>Brian Nelson – Secretary of the Treasury for Terrorism and Financial Intelligence – explained during the process:</p>
<blockquote><p>Despite public assurances otherwise, Tornado Cash has repeatedly failed to impose effective controls designed to stop it from laundering funds for malicious cyber actors on a regular basis and without basic measures to address its risks. The Treasury will continue to aggressively pursue actions against mixers that launder virtual currency for criminals and those who assist them.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-tool-chip-mixer-shut-down-by-the-doj/">Crypto Tool Chip Mixer Shut Down by the DOJ</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-tool-chip-mixer-shut-down-by-the-doj/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>More Crypto Scams Are Happening All Over the World</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/more-crypto-scams-are-happening-all-over-the-world/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/more-crypto-scams-are-happening-all-over-the-world/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 15:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto scams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gustavo Scarpa]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Scams]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77489</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>More crypto scams have been recorded to the digital currency books, and the ones in question are proof that it doesn’t matter how big or famous you are or where you’re located… You’re just as vulnerable as everyone else. Crypto Scams&#8230; They&#8217;re Everywhere! The first of the two new crypto scams saw Nottingham Forest midfielder<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/more-crypto-scams-are-happening-all-over-the-world/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/more-crypto-scams-are-happening-all-over-the-world/">More Crypto Scams Are Happening All Over the World</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>More crypto scams have been recorded to the digital currency books, and the ones in question are proof that it doesn’t matter how big or famous you are or where you’re located… You’re just as vulnerable as everyone else.</p>
<h2>Crypto Scams&#8230; They&#8217;re Everywhere!</h2>
<p>The first of the two new <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/scams/" data-wpel-link="internal">crypto scams</a> saw Nottingham Forest midfielder Gustavo Scarpa losing one million pounds <a href="https://www.bbc.com/sport/football/64971867" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">to a digital thief</a>. At 29 years old, Scarpa is developing a reputation as one of the greatest soccer players of the modern age, but this newfound scam is likely coming back to haunt him right about now. Based in Brazil, Scarpa is working hard to gain his money back through a potential court case.</p>
<p>The situation has prevented Scarpa from taking part in all his team’s practices and games, though his fellow fielders say they support his endeavors and will grant him this time to see about keeping his finances intact. His team issued a statement that read:</p>
<blockquote><p>It&#8217;s an unfortunate situation, and he&#8217;s got our full support with it… He has had some personal issues to sort out, and we are giving him our support, which is inclusive of allowing him to travel back. We&#8217;re supporting Gustavo in terms of what he&#8217;s going through and of course, it affects football performance and availability and all that sort of stuff. Those things go hand in hand, of course. We want him settled in his mind and sorting out the situation. Hopefully, he can get it sorted out and then focus on his availability for us.</p></blockquote>
<p>4,000 miles away, a man in Strongsville, Ohio has <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/fbi-investigating-after-strongsville-man-loses-500-000-in-cryptocurrency-scam/ar-AA18FWce" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reportedly lost about</a> half a million dollars at press time after investing his hard-earned funds into a phony crypto website. Clearly, digital currency scams are happening everywhere. The FBI is now investigating the situation.</p>
<p>Susan Licate – who works with the FBI branch of Cleveland – commented that this is a growing issue the agency is reportedly having to deal with. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The losses in 2021 were over $429 million, and in 2022, that figure nearly doubled to about $700 million.</p></blockquote>
<h2>The FBI Has Gotten Heavily Involved</h2>
<p>She says the victims reportedly meet the scammers online either as friends or romantic partners. From there, the scammers convince them to invest in crypto platforms that are in the control of their fellow criminals. When the people invest, they see returns, but they usually cannot withdraw any money without investing further. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The victim deposits more money, and sometimes even the scammer will bring in a bogus customer service group to put a little more pressure on the victim, and they deposit that money and it’s all over from there… These scammers are savvy, and what they try to do is gain trust and confidence from the victim.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/more-crypto-scams-are-happening-all-over-the-world/">More Crypto Scams Are Happening All Over the World</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/more-crypto-scams-are-happening-all-over-the-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Africa Is a Major BTC Hub Despite Its Lack of Internet Access</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/africa-is-a-major-btc-hub-despite-its-lack-of-internet/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/africa-is-a-major-btc-hub-despite-its-lack-of-internet/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 13:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[africa]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[internet]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77485</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Roughly 3,000 people in Africa have adopted bitcoin in recent weeks and months. The big clincher? Many of these people don’t have access to the internet, and bitcoin is “internet money.” In other words, if you don’t have access to the World Wide Web, then you likely can’t access your digital wallet, exchanges, or other<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/africa-is-a-major-btc-hub-despite-its-lack-of-internet/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/africa-is-a-major-btc-hub-despite-its-lack-of-internet/">Africa Is a Major BTC Hub Despite Its Lack of Internet Access</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Roughly 3,000 people in Africa have <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/machankura-boosts-african-bitcoin-adoption-204705167.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">adopted bitcoin in recent</a> weeks and months. The big clincher? Many of these people don’t have access to the internet, and bitcoin is “internet money.” In other words, if you don’t have access to the World Wide Web, then you likely can’t access your digital wallet, exchanges, or other trading tools that will grant you the power to trade, sell, and buy crypto.</p>
<h2>Africa Sure Loves Its Crypto</h2>
<p>The tool behind all this is called Machankura. Built by software developer Kgothatso Ngako, it’s designed for the utilization of bitcoin through featured phones. There are no computers involved, no smart technology, and – of course – no internet. As a result, Africa is becoming a major bitcoin haven even without the hardcore technology now being taken for granted by so many other nations.</p>
<p>In an interview, Ngako commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>I had set up a raspberry pi running both a bitcoin and Lightning node and was trying to figure out what I could build on top of it. A USSD project was intriguing because quite a lot of African bitcoiners were already talking about building a wallet for feature phone users.</p></blockquote>
<p>Africa has long been a center for financial and political corruption. The continent doesn’t have true access to a valid banking system, which has often been marred by those in power. Thus, when people think of bitcoin, they often believe it can aid those living in various African countries given its designs and power to assist those who are either underbanked or don’t have any form of access to traditional monetary tools and services whatsoever.</p>
<p>Men like Jack Dorsey, for example (the former chief executive of Twitter), even made it their mission to bring <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jack-dorsey-i-will-bring-btc-to-africa/" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin closer to Africa</a>. Before the pandemic, it was Dorsey’s goal to travel throughout the content on a “bitcoin tour” of sorts and do all he could to ensure people had the education necessary to make BTC a staple of their portfolios and financial habits. Ngako continued his statement with:</p>
<blockquote><p>I believe the tool could help bitcoin the un-bitcoined. Payment technology is very dependent on network effects. Both receiver and sender need the ability to send and receive for the payment technology to be adopted.</p></blockquote>
<h2>How Does It All Work?</h2>
<p>The way the tool works is like so. The person with the featured phone dials in a certain code on the device. The code will depend on their location and the services they wish to gain access to (this can include sending and receiving BTC or checking balances). The code would also allow the user to access Lightning addresses as a means of receiving and sending crypto units.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, customers have been recorded in a wide array of regions including Ghana, Malawi, Kenya, and Uganda.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/africa-is-a-major-btc-hub-despite-its-lack-of-internet/">Africa Is a Major BTC Hub Despite Its Lack of Internet Access</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/africa-is-a-major-btc-hub-despite-its-lack-of-internet/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EOS Price Analysis: Upsides Could be Limited above $1.15</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-upsides-could-be-limited-above-1-15-2/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-upsides-could-be-limited-above-1-15-2/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 05:48:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EOS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77991</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>EOS price started a fresh decline from the $1.25 resistance zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $1.20 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1.165 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-upsides-could-be-limited-above-1-15-2/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-upsides-could-be-limited-above-1-15-2/">EOS Price Analysis: Upsides Could be Limited above $1.15</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>EOS price started a fresh decline from the $1.25 resistance zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $1.20 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1.165 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to decline if it stays below the $1.15 and $1.165 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>EOS price is struggling below $1.165 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-more-gains-above-31k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. The price might attempt to recover if there is a clear move above $1.15.</em></p>
<h2>EOS Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, EOS price climbed above the $1.20 resistance against the US Dollar. The price traded above the $1.22 and $1.25 resistance levels.</p>
<p>However, the bears were active near the $1.30 zone. A high was formed near $1.2977 before there was a sharp decline. The price declined heavily below the $1.25 support. The bears were able to push the price below the $1.20 support and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-indicators-suggest-upside-break-to-1-3/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>A low is formed near $1.081 and the price is now consolidating losses. On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $1.132 level. It is near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $1.2977 swing high to the $1.0812 low.</p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $1.15 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1.165 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $1.165 level could start a steady increase toward the $1.19 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $1.2977 swing high to the $1.0812 low. Any more gains might send the price toward the $1.25 level.</p>
<p>On the downside, immediate support is near $1.08. The next key support is near the $1.02 level. If there is a downside break below the $1.02 support, the price could test the $0.920 support in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_77992" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/04/EOS-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-77992" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-77992" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/04/EOS-1.png" alt="EOS Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-77992" class="wp-caption-text">EOS Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/EOSUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, EOS price is now trading below the $1.20 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to decline if it stays below the $1.15 and $1.165 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for EOS/USD is gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $1.08 and $1.02.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $1.15 and $1.165.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-upsides-could-be-limited-above-1-15-2/">EOS Price Analysis: Upsides Could be Limited above $1.15</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-upsides-could-be-limited-above-1-15-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Struggle, Risk of More Losses</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-struggle-risk-of-more-losses/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-struggle-risk-of-more-losses/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 04:28:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77987</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin started a fresh decline below the $95 zone against the US Dollar. LTC price is now trading below $95 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $93 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-struggle-risk-of-more-losses/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-struggle-risk-of-more-losses/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Struggle, Risk of More Losses</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Litecoin started a fresh decline below the $95 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>LTC price is now trading below $95 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $93 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair is at risk of a downside break below the $90 and $88 support levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Litecoin price is struggling below $95 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-more-gains-above-31k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. LTC price could continue to decline if it stays below the $88 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past 2-3 sessions, there was a fresh decline in Bitcoin, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-holds-key-uptrend-support-2/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Ethereum</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-dips-likely-to-be-supported-above-0-5/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Ripple</a>, and Litecoin against the US Dollar. Earlier, LTC started a decent increase above the $95 and $100 resistance levels.</p>
<p>However, the bears were active near the $103.50 zone. A high is formed near $103.42 and the price started a major decline. There was a sharp move below the $100 and $95 levels. Besides, there was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $93 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>The price even spiked below the $90 level. A low is formed near $87.04 and the price is now consolidating losses. The price is now testing the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $103.42 swing high to the $87.04 low.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $92 zone. The next major resistance sits near the $95 level. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $103.42 swing high to the $87.04 low.</p>
<p>The main resistance is near the $100 level. A clear move above the $100 level could pump the price toward the $103 level or even $105. The next major resistance could be $115.</p>
<p>On the downside, immediate support is near the $89.20 level. The next key support is near the $87 level. If there is a downside break below the $87 support, the price could accelerate lower toward the $80 level in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_77988" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/04/Litecoin-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-77988" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-77988" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/04/Litecoin-2.png" alt="Litecoin (LTC) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-77988" class="wp-caption-text">Litecoin (LTC) Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">chart</a>, Litecoin price is clearly trading below $95 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price is at risk of a downside break below the $90 and $88 support levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LTC/USD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $89.20 and $87.00.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $92.00 and $95.00.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-struggle-risk-of-more-losses/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Struggle, Risk of More Losses</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-struggle-risk-of-more-losses/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
