<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 05:10:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>PayPointCoin (PPC) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paypointcoin-ppc-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paypointcoin-ppc-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 05:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76089</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec 16, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed PayPointCoin (PPC) on December 16, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the PPC/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading. As a universal loyalty program protocol, PayPointCoin (PPC) uses blockchain technology to track all transactions within<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paypointcoin-ppc-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paypointcoin-ppc-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">PayPointCoin (PPC) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec 16, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed PayPointCoin (PPC) on December 16, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the PPC/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading.</p>
<p>As a universal loyalty program protocol, <a href="https://etherscan.io/token/0x6fc0d20c7dE9a0ae891B39b3DD916F5ffcc7f33F" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">PayPointCoin</a> (PPC) uses blockchain technology to track all transactions within the protocol, providing more rewards to loyal customers. The PPC token has been listed on LBank Exchange at 8:00 UTC on December 16, 2022, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision.</p>
<p><strong>Introducing </strong><strong>PayPointCoin</strong></p>
<p>Addressing some of the challenges that current loyalty programs face due to inefficient data management, and lack of data privacy and ownership, PayPointCoin is a universal loyalty program protocol that can revolutionize the way that merchants track and distribute rewards points and coupons so that more perks and benefits will be provided to loyal users. It uses blockchain features such as smart contracts, wallets, and tokens to track all the transactions within the protocol.</p>
<p>Specifically speaking, PayPointCoin allows transaction ledgers to be shared across a network of participants. When a new transaction occurs (e.g. loyalty points are issued, redeemed or exchanged) a unique PayPointCoin is created and assigned to that transaction. PayPointCoins are grouped into blocks and distributed throughout the network, updating all ledgers at once.</p>
<p>By leveraging the blockchain technology, PayPointCoin makes it easy to track each transaction and its history, while making it irreversible, avoiding double-spending, fraud, abuse and other types of transactions manipulation. In addition, by allowing multiple parties to record and access transactions in near real-time, blockchain increases the opportunity for loyalty rewards program providers to reduce adjustment inertia for credit points more quickly.</p>
<p>Furthermore, PayPointCoin is supposed to reduce costs associated with errors and fraud by reducing system administration costs with smart contracts that report transactions securely, traceably and transparently to legacy systems. Large loyalty rewards program providers with well-developed programs in the early stages of building interconnected loyalty networks have a unique opportunity to provide value-added services to other businesses.</p>
<p>Last but not least, for consumers juggling different loyalty programs, blockchain provides instant redemption and can be exchanged for multiple loyalty points currencies on a single platform. With only one &#8220;wallet&#8221; for points – the PayPointCoin Wallet, consumers do not have to look for options, restrictions and usage rules for each program.</p>
<p><strong>About PPC Token</strong></p>
<p>PPC is the native token of PayPointCoin ecosystem. Based on ERC-20, PPC has a total supply of 2 billion (i.e., 2,000,000,000) tokens, of which 30% is provided for the ecosystem, 25% will be used for marketing, 20% is allocated for investment, 10% is provided for partners, 7% will be used to provide liquidity for transactions on the platform, 5% is allocated to the team, and the remaining 3% is allocated to advisors.</p>
<p>In addition, 100% of the revenue stream is used to buy back tokens from the market. They are then burned each month, reducing the total circulating supply, and increasing the value of PayPointCoin tokens.</p>
<p>The PPC token has been listed on LBank Exchange at 8:00 UTC on December 16, 2022, investors who are interested in the PayPointCoin investment can easily buy and sell PPC token on LBank Exchange right now. The listing of PPC token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p>
<p><strong>Learn More about</strong><strong> PPC Token:</strong></p>
<p>Official Website: <a href="http://paypointcoin.com" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://paypointcoin.com</a></p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media: </strong></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Facebook</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong></p>
<p>LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
LBank Exchange<br />
<a href="mailto:marketing@lbank.info">marketing@lbank.info</a><br />
<a href="mailto:business@lbank.info">business@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paypointcoin-ppc-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">PayPointCoin (PPC) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/paypointcoin-ppc-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC At Risk of Another Crash</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-at-risk-of-another-crash/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-at-risk-of-another-crash/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 05:08:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76086</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price started a fresh decline below the $17,200 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $17,200 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $17,180 on the 4-hours chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-at-risk-of-another-crash/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-at-risk-of-another-crash/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC At Risk of Another Crash</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin price started a fresh decline below the $17,200 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $17,200 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $17,180 on the 4-hours chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could start another decline if it stays below the $17,350 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin price is struggling below $17,200 against the US Dollar. BTC might extend losses if it stays below the $17,200 and $17,350 resistance levels.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price started a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-more-upsides-18k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">fresh decline</a> below the $17,800 zone. There was a steady decline below the $17,500 and $17,350 support levels.</p>
<p>The decline gained pace below the $17,200 level and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). The bears even pushed the price below the $16,500 level. Besides, there was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $17,180 on the 4-hours chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>The price again tested the $16,250 support zone and is now correcting losses. There was a minor increase above the $16,700 level. The price climbed above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $18,385 swing high to $16,273 low.</p>
<p>The price is now trading below $17,200 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-upside-break-above-18k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. An immediate resistance on the upside is near the $17,200 level.</p>
<p>The next major resistance might near the $17,350 zone. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $18,385 swing high to $16,273 low. The first major resistance is near the $17,500 level. A clear move above the $17,500 level might send the price towards $18,000, above which the price might rise towards the $18,500 level.</p>
<p>Any more gains might push the price towards the $19,000 zone. If there is no upside break, the price might continue to decline below $16,700. The next key support is near the $16,500 level, below which the price might accelerate lower.</p>
<p>In the stated case, the price could decline towards the $16,200 level. Any more losses might send the price towards the $15,500 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_76088" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Bitcoin-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76088" class="size-full wp-image-76088" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2022/12/Bitcoin-2.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76088" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XBTUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, bitcoin price is clearly trading below $17,200 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could start another decline if it stays below the $17,350 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD is now gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now near the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $16,500 and $16,200.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $17,200, $17,350 and $17,500.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-at-risk-of-another-crash/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC At Risk of Another Crash</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-at-risk-of-another-crash/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LBank Exchange Will List CRACLE (CRA) on December 20, 2022</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-cracle-cra-on-december-20-2022/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-cracle-cra-on-december-20-2022/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 04:53:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76083</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec 19, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list CRACLE (CRA) on December 20, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the CRA/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading at 10:00 UTC on December 20, 2022. Creating a new world optimized for Web 3.0, CRACLE<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-cracle-cra-on-december-20-2022/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-cracle-cra-on-december-20-2022/">LBank Exchange Will List CRACLE (CRA) on December 20, 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec 19, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list CRACLE (CRA) on December 20, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the CRA/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading at 10:00 UTC on December 20, 2022.</p>
<p>Creating a new world optimized for Web 3.0, <a href="https://bscscan.com/token/0x0fc0b3f6f5c769c138088266ac21760ab33f76ca" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">CRACLE</a> (CRA) is a metaverse X2E platform where anything becomes earning. Its native token CRA will be listed on LBank Exchange at 10:00 UTC on December 20, 2022, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision.</p>
<p><strong>Introducing </strong><strong>CRACLE</strong></p>
<p>CRACLE is an innovative Total Metaverse Platform that combines blockchain and various content services. Also, CRACLE introduced a new concept metaverse called ‘X2E’. X2E is an abbreviation of ‘X to Earn’, where ‘X’ stands for ‘infinite scalability’.</p>
<p>This is not only P2E (Play to Earn) and M2E (Move to Earn) games or services familiar to existing users, but also L2E (Listen to Earn), S2E (Sleep to Earn), and T2E (Trade to Earn) categories. It is a more comprehensive and progressive metaverse platform than ever before, infinitely expanded. In addition, the CRACLE Token of the CRACLE project is a coin specialized for Web 3.0 so that anyone can easily use X2E.</p>
<p>Participants in the CRACLE X2E ecosystem (hereinafter referred to as ‘players’) can directly participate in the CRACLE ecosystem by playing their favorite games or services on the X2E platform and receive CRACLE Token rewards as compensation. These actions of players contribute to the development of CRACLE into a sustainable ecosystem and realize the value of CRACLE&#8217;s first vision, &#8216;PLAY X2E with CRACLE&#8217;. Furthermore, based on the value of &#8216;PLAY X2E&#8217;, CRACLE has the second vision of dreaming of leaping to the Web 3.0 Global Metaverse Platform that can continuously be with various players around the world.</p>
<p>The platform structure of CRACLE X2E consists of ‘Platform Site’, which will serve as a base camp for CRACLE Contents, and ‘Contents’, which will be used by actual CRACLE X2E players. In addition, all players of X2E will have fair information and equal access to each content. Players will be able to manage their own information in accordance with the characteristics of blockchain, decentralization of information, and can use the CRACLE X2E platform with subjective responsibility for this.</p>
<p>The CRACLE Foundation has a priority goal of building a Total Metaverse Platform through the CRACLE X2E project, but in the long term, it aims to promote the development of the Global Blockchain ecosystem through the CRACLE Project. It will actively support decentralized services, build the metaverse global world, support promising blockchain investment, and grow together by building an ecosystem so that the whole world can become a metaverse.</p>
<p><strong>About CRA Token</strong></p>
<p>CRA is a token specialized for Web 3.0 so that anyone can easily use X2E in the crypto market. It naturally serves as an integrated platform token, and users need CRA tokens to participate in various activities given on the platform.</p>
<p>Based on BEP-20, CRA has a total supply of 1 billion (i.e., 1,000,000,000) tokens, of which 10% is provided for partners, 10% is allocated to the team, 20% will be used for marketing, 30% is provided for X2E, 10% is provided for seed round, 10% is allocated for building the ecosystem, 5% will be used for R&amp;D, and the remaining 5% is reserved.</p>
<p>The CRA token will be listed on LBank Exchange at 10:00 UTC on December 20, 2022, investors who are interested in the CRACLE investment can easily buy and sell CRA token on LBank Exchange by then. The listing of CRA token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p>
<p><strong>Learn More about</strong><strong> CRA Token:</strong></p>
<p>Official Website: <a href="https://www.cracle.io" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.cracle.io</a><br />
Telegram: <a href="http://t.me/cracleofficial" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://t.me/cracleofficial</a><br />
Telegram Chat: <a href="https://t.me/cracleofficialchat" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://t.me/cracleofficialchat</a><br />
Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/craclepro" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/craclepro</a><br />
Instagram: <a href="https://www.instagram.com/craclex2e/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.instagram.com/craclex2e/</a><br />
Medium: <a href="https://medium.com/@craclepro" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://medium.com/@craclepro</a></p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media: </strong></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Facebook</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong><br />
LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
LBank Exchange<br />
<a href="mailto:marketing@lbank.info">marketing@lbank.info</a><br />
<a href="mailto:business@lbank.info">business@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-cracle-cra-on-december-20-2022/">LBank Exchange Will List CRACLE (CRA) on December 20, 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lbank-exchange-will-list-cracle-cra-on-december-20-2022/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SFUSD Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sfusd-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sfusd-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 04:48:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76080</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec 14, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed SFUSD on December 14, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the SFUSD/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading. As a stable coin which is pegged to the value of USD, SFUSD runs on the Polygon<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sfusd-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sfusd-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">SFUSD Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, Dec 14, 2022 – LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, has listed SFUSD on December 14, 2022. For all users of LBank Exchange, the SFUSD/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading.</p>
<p>As a stable coin which is pegged to the value of USD, <a href="https://polygonscan.com/token/0x93fee753b548b4cf93c41ada062f80de12710db8" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">SFUSD</a> runs on the Polygon network, giving it an unfair advantage in terms of speed and cost per transaction. The SFUSD stable coin has been listed on LBank Exchange at 11:00 UTC on December 14, 2022, to further expand its global reach and help it achieve its vision.</p>
<p><strong>Introducing SFUSD</strong></p>
<p>As the world&#8217;s first stable coin native to the Polygon chain, SFUSD is a cheaper, faster and more secure way of moving new-aged digital money across the globe. Each SFUSD can be converted 1:1 for USD, and users can spend, send or exchange SFUSD to anyone across the globe in seconds.</p>
<p>SFUSD breaks conventional banking boundaries and gives the control of users’ money back into their hands. The service runs for users 24×7 and 365 days, all they need is an internet connection to send money anywhere across the globe. With SFUSD, users can finally enjoy limitless control over their funds to spend, send, save and invest as they desire.</p>
<p>In addition, users don’t have to spend money to use their money anymore. There’s no exaggerated fee on wire transfers, only a fraction of a cent. And vendors/merchants can now avoid the 2.9% fees on credit card payments and pass back savings to loyal customers with the instant cash flow.</p>
<p>Furthermore, SFUSD will be the first and only stable coin in the world offering 30% rewards per month to stake. Holders can earn up-to 30% monthly returns by simply just staking their SFUSD coin via its Stable Fund wallet.</p>
<p><strong>About SFUSD Stable Coin</strong></p>
<p>SFUSD is a stable coin which is pegged to the value of USD. Each SFUSD can be converted 1:1 for USD. Running on the Polygon network gives SFUSD an unfair advantage in terms of speed and cost per transaction. As of December 14, 2022, it has a total supply of 100 million (i.e., 100,000,000) coins. In the future, SFUSD will also be launched on BSC, Avalanche-C, and Ethereum.</p>
<p>The SFUSD stable coin has been listed on LBank Exchange at 11:00 UTC on December 14, 2022, investors who are interested in the SFUSD investment can easily buy and sell it on LBank Exchange right now. The listing of SFUSD stable coin on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p>
<p><strong>Learn More about</strong> <strong>SFUSD Token:</strong></p>
<p>Official Website: <a href="https://sfusd.io" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://sfusd.io</a></p>
<p>Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/SFUSDOfficial" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://t.me/SFUSDOfficial</a></p>
<p>Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/SFUSDOfficial" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">https://twitter.com/SFUSDOfficial</a></p>
<p><strong>About LBank</strong></p>
<p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 7 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&#8217; funds and aims to contribute the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><strong>Start Trading Now:</strong> <a href="https://www.lbank.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">lbank.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Community &amp; Social Media: </strong></p>
<p>l   <a href="https://t.me/LBank_en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LBank.info" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Facebook</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/lbank" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">LinkedIn</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lbank_exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a><br />
l   <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/LBankExchange" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p><strong>Contact Details:</strong></p>
<p>LBK Blockchain Co. Limited<br />
LBank Exchange<br />
<a href="mailto:marketing@lbank.info">marketing@lbank.info</a><br />
<a href="mailto:business@lbank.info">business@lbank.info</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sfusd-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/">SFUSD Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sfusd-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BC.GAME is Hosting A Huge Lottery Event to Celebrate Argentina&#8217;s Historic Win</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bc-game-is-hosting-a-huge-lottery-event-to-celebrate-argentinas-historic-win/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bc-game-is-hosting-a-huge-lottery-event-to-celebrate-argentinas-historic-win/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 18:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76068</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Buenos Aires, Argentina, December 20, 2022–BC.GAME, AFA’s official crypto casino sponsor, is celebrating Messi and Argentina’s legendary win with a huge lottery event. Up to $100,000 is up for grabs for the crypto casino’s VIP players. More information about the event will be disclosed to qualified players through email and platform notifications. Argentina Wins Over<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bc-game-is-hosting-a-huge-lottery-event-to-celebrate-argentinas-historic-win/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bc-game-is-hosting-a-huge-lottery-event-to-celebrate-argentinas-historic-win/">BC.GAME is Hosting A Huge Lottery Event to Celebrate Argentina&#8217;s Historic Win</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Buenos Aires, Argentina, December 20, 2022</em>–<a href="https://bc.game/i-946j27rm-n/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">BC.GAME</a>, AFA’s official crypto casino sponsor, is celebrating Messi and Argentina’s legendary win with a huge lottery event. Up to $100,000 is up for grabs for the crypto casino’s VIP players. More information about the event will be disclosed to qualified players through email and platform notifications.</p>
<p><strong>Argentina Wins Over France </strong></p>
<p>On a night full of anticipation and heart-pounding moments, Argentina takes home the championship in the 2022 FIFA World Cup. Argentina defeated France by 4-2 in a penalty shootout in the nerve-wracking final match held in the Lusail Stadium in Lusail, Qatar.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.afa.com.ar/es/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Argentinian football team</a>’s victory against France this Sunday night adds another win to Argentina’s World Cup championship titles list. This marks Argentina’s third World Cup win since their last World Cup championship title in 1986, making it 36 years since the country last won the World Cup.</p>
<p><strong>Messi’s Dream to Win the 2022 World Cup  </strong></p>
<p>Lionel Messi has obtained every possible football achievement throughout the entirety of his football career except one: winning the World Cup. After losing the finals to Germany in 2014, the 2022 World Cup marked his another chance to win the World Cup title.</p>
<p>Thanks to Argentina’s well-deserved victory, Messi has finally achieved and added the football’s grandest title to his roster of achievements. The historic win not only brings immense joy to all fans of the Argentinian football team but also provides a great ending to Messi’s legendary football career.</p>
<p>BC.GAME, AFA’s newest global sponsor in 2022, congratulates the team for winning the “greatest football game” ever. Argentina’s triumph brings more excitement to the football community and crypto casino players as it opens more sports betting opportunities globally. In the future, BC.GAME’s community can expect more events and promotions exclusive to players, in addition to social media activities and engagements brought by <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/press-releases/bcgame-becomes-the-global-crypto-sponsor-of-the-argentine-football-association" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">BC.GAME and AFA’s recent partnership</a>.</p>
<p><strong>About BC.GAME </strong></p>
<p>BC.GAME is a community-based online crypto casino platform launched in 2017 and is now operating for 5 years. The platform offers a wide range of casino games, live casinos, and sports betting opportunities and has more than 8,000 game titles on its platform, which can all be accessed on both desktop and mobile.</p>
<p>Other than integrating cryptocurrency and blockchain technology on its platform, BC.GAME is also one of the first online casinos to support the Lightning Network, Binance Smart Chain, Arbitrum, and other Layer 2 solutions, which have helped reshape the casino and blockchain industries. In June 2022, BC.GAME was recognized as the “<a href="https://blog.bc.game/bc-game-wins-crypto-casino-of-the-year-sigma-award-2022/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Crypto Casino of the Year</a>” in the 2022 Sigma Awards.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bc-game-is-hosting-a-huge-lottery-event-to-celebrate-argentinas-historic-win/">BC.GAME is Hosting A Huge Lottery Event to Celebrate Argentina&#8217;s Historic Win</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bc-game-is-hosting-a-huge-lottery-event-to-celebrate-argentinas-historic-win/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cal, Aka FTX Field, Seeks Legal Name Change After Exchange Falls</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cal-aka-ftx-field-seeks-legal-name-change-after-exchange-falls/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cal-aka-ftx-field-seeks-legal-name-change-after-exchange-falls/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75483</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, Live Bitcoin News reported that the FTX Arena for the Miami Heat was going to change its name following the collapse of FTX, the now disgraced cryptocurrency exchange based in the Bahamas. The company wanted nothing to do with the firm’s rotten legacy, and now Cal – aka the California Memorial Stadium/<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cal-aka-ftx-field-seeks-legal-name-change-after-exchange-falls/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cal-aka-ftx-field-seeks-legal-name-change-after-exchange-falls/">Cal, Aka FTX Field, Seeks Legal Name Change After Exchange Falls</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, <em>Live Bitcoin News</em> reported that the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-ftx-arena-is-changing-its-name-following-exchange-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX Arena for the Miami Heat</a> was going to change its name following the collapse of FTX, the now disgraced cryptocurrency exchange based in the Bahamas. The company wanted nothing to do with the firm’s rotten legacy, and now Cal – aka the California Memorial Stadium/ FTX Field – is <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/ncaafb/welcome-to-cals-ftx-field-a-naming-rights-deal-funded-by-cryptocurrency/ar-AA1479xl" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">looking to do the same</a>.</p>
<h2>Cal Doesn&#8217;t Like the Letters FTX Anymore</h2>
<p>Cal has stated that what happened with FTX is wrong and it wants no part in whatever shady deals FTX may have conducted. It doesn’t need this kind of trouble and is now looking to engage in a legal name change so the FTX letters are removed from its banner forever.</p>
<p>Cal serves as the home football field for the Golden Bears team. A few years back, Cal announced that it was joining hands with the now fallen digital trading platform and would be taking on a name change as a means of supporting the company’s legacy and operations.</p>
<p>The naming deal was set to last a full ten years. At the time, Cal director of athletics Jim Knowlton said the field had allegedly found a “great partner” in the digital exchange, and they were looking forward to a future filled with profit and possibilities. He stated in an interview at the time:</p>
<blockquote><p>We believe we have found a great partner in FTX. FTX is a growing company at the forefront of innovation in an emerging technology, one that fits well at both Cal and in the Bay Area. This agreement extends well beyond field naming rights, which is part of our strategic plan to diversify revenue streams in support of our student-athlete experience, and includes commitments for our Cameron Institute, Cal Veterans, and students in need here in Berkeley. We are looking forward to building our relationship now and in the years ahead.</p></blockquote>
<h2>One of Crypto&#8217;s Most Embarrassing Moments</h2>
<p>The collapse of FTX is likely going to go down as one of the most devastating (and embarrassing) things to happen within the confines of the crypto space. FTX first came to fruition in the year 2019. From there, it looked like a glorious future was written in the clouds for the exchange, and the company’s head executive – then 27-year-old Sam Bankman-Fried – was lauded as a genius businessman of sorts by several experts in the arena.</p>
<p>However, that reputation has faded fast as just a few weeks ago, the now crushed exchange ran to Binance for help, begging the larger competitor to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">buy it out in</a> part to an ongoing liquidity crunch the company was experiencing. While it looked like the deal was going to go through, Changpeng Zhao – the head of Binance – <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">eventually backed out</a>, claiming the problems the firm was facing were too big.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cal-aka-ftx-field-seeks-legal-name-change-after-exchange-falls/">Cal, Aka FTX Field, Seeks Legal Name Change After Exchange Falls</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cal-aka-ftx-field-seeks-legal-name-change-after-exchange-falls/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Light Up the Xmas Tree With 1xBit and Win this Christmas</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/light-up-the-xmas-tree-with-1xbit-and-win-this-christmas/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/light-up-the-xmas-tree-with-1xbit-and-win-this-christmas/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 16:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76065</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Press Release: 1xBit Casino celebrates the festive season with The Xmas Toy Adventure, with great Bitcoin prizes &#38; many chances to get lucky over Christmas. December 20 2022, Limassol, Cyprus — The holiday season is finally here, and it’s the most beautiful time of the year. It’s time to show your loved ones how much<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/light-up-the-xmas-tree-with-1xbit-and-win-this-christmas/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/light-up-the-xmas-tree-with-1xbit-and-win-this-christmas/">Light Up the Xmas Tree With 1xBit and Win this Christmas</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Press Release:</strong> <em>1xBit Casino celebrates the festive season with The Xmas Toy Adventure, with great Bitcoin prizes &amp; many chances to get lucky over Christmas. </em></p>
<p><strong>December 20 2022, Limassol, Cyprus </strong>— The holiday season is finally here, and it’s the most beautiful time of the year. It’s time to show your loved ones how much you care for them and what they mean to you. But Christmas is also about festive meals, giving and receiving presents, and spending time doing what you love the most.</p>
<p>That’s why 1xBit has prepared something extraordinary to bring joy to players from all over the world. It’s a magical tournament of celebrations, kindness, love, and hope. Everyone is invited to <a href="https://refpa4903566.top/L?tag=d_557249m_1732c_xmas_toy&amp;site=557249&amp;ad=1732&amp;r=promotions/the-xmas-toys-adventure" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">The Xmas Toys’ Adventure</a>.</p>
<h4>What Is The Xmas Toys’ Adventure?</h4>
<p>The Xmas Toys’ Adventure is a joyous slot tournament organized by 1xBit for this holiday season. Players are invited to take a look at the colorful presents cleverly placed under the Christmas tree and take one for themselves.</p>
<p>It’s a splendid occasion to share gifts with the valuable community, and 1xBit is waiting for you.</p>
<p>How to Take Part in the Xmas Toys’ Adventure?</p>
<p>Grab a cup of hot chocolate and get cozy because Santa&#8217;s sled has arrived bearing gifts. Log in to your 1xBit account or create a new one if this is your first time playing at this casino. You came at the right time.</p>
<p>The rules for <a href="https://refpa4903566.top/L?tag=d_557249m_1732c_xmas_toy&amp;site=557249&amp;ad=1732&amp;r=promotions/the-xmas-toys-adventure" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">the Xmas Toys’ Adventure</a> are easy to remember. Play slot games from any of the dozens of providers available on 1xBit and collect points. It doesn’t get easier than that. 1xBit has partnered with the best game creators in the industry to ensure a high standard and security of all hosted slots. The promotional period begins on 20 December 2022 and ends on 12 January 2023.</p>
<h4>Prizes</h4>
<p>The prize fund amounts to 600 mBTC. Since this is a happy and special occasion, there will be many winners! 1xBit will reward 25 top-ranked players with Bitcoin as follows:</p>
<ul>
<li>1<sup>st</sup> place – 130 mBTC</li>
<li>2<sup>nd</sup> place – 80 mBTC</li>
<li>3<sup>rd</sup> place – 65 mBTC</li>
<li>4<sup>th</sup> place – 50 mBTC</li>
<li>5<sup>th</sup> place – 40 mBTC</li>
<li>6<sup>th</sup> place – 25 mBTC</li>
<li>7-10<sup>th</sup> place – 20 mBTC</li>
<li>11-12<sup>th</sup> place – 15 mBTC</li>
<li>13-19<sup>th</sup> place – 10 mBTC</li>
<li>20-25<sup>th</sup> place – 5 mBTC</li>
</ul>
<h4>What Is the Difference Between 1xBit And Other Crypto Casinos?</h4>
<p><a href="https://refpa4903566.top/L?tag=d_557249m_1732c_xmas_toy&amp;site=557249&amp;ad=1732" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">1xBit</a> is the best option for casino and sportsbook enthusiasts online. The site offers thousands of sports events, slots, live dealer and table games, online poker, and more every day. The registration process is anonymous and requires only an email address and a password to create an account.</p>
<p>All deposits and withdrawals are processed instantly and free of charge. 1xBit has no hidden fees! There are a multitude of wagering options and support for +40 cryptocurrencies. Fans of casino games can enjoy regular slot tournaments with cash prizes featuring top gaming providers. A big Welcome Bonus of up to 7 BTC is available to all new players who sign up. The offer is available for the first four deposits to 1xBit.</p>
<p>The year is coming to an end, and it’s time to collect some prizes with the Xmas Toys’ Adventure!</p>
<p><strong>1xBit Socials</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://refpa4903566.top/L?tag=d_557249m_1732c_pr_polygon&amp;site=557249&amp;ad=1732&amp;r=blog/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Blog</a> | <a href="https://twitter.com/1x_bit" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Twitter</a> | <a href="https://t.me/sportsbook_1xBit" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a> | <a href="https://www.instagram.com/1xbit/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a> | <a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCPAFo4OYJGHCxWlENrdRtWA" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">YouTube</a></p>
<p><strong>Media Contact Details</strong><br />
<strong>Contact Nam</strong>e: Anastasia Semenova<br />
<strong>Contact Email:</strong> <a href="mailto:marketing@1x-bit.com">marketing@1x-bit.com</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><em>1xBit is the source of this content. This Press Release is for informational purposes only. The information does not constitute investment advice or an offer to invest</em></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/light-up-the-xmas-tree-with-1xbit-and-win-this-christmas/">Light Up the Xmas Tree With 1xBit and Win this Christmas</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/light-up-the-xmas-tree-with-1xbit-and-win-this-christmas/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sam Bankman-Fried Possibly Gave Dirty Money to Democrats. What Will They Do with It?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-gave-a-lot-of-money-to-democrats-what-will-they-do-with-it/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-gave-a-lot-of-money-to-democrats-what-will-they-do-with-it/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[democrats]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75479</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sam Bankman-Fried – the disgraced runner of now failed crypto exchange FTX – gave a lot of his money to democrat candidates during the midterm elections… So much, in fact, that he’s been listed as the second highest donor to said candidates this season. The Filth of Sam Bankman-Fried Fell into D.C. This raises big<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-gave-a-lot-of-money-to-democrats-what-will-they-do-with-it/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-gave-a-lot-of-money-to-democrats-what-will-they-do-with-it/">Sam Bankman-Fried Possibly Gave Dirty Money to Democrats. What Will They Do with It?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sam Bankman-Fried – the disgraced runner of now failed crypto exchange FTX – gave a lot of his money to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-billionaire-sam-bankman-fried-spends-big-in-the-name-of-politics/" data-wpel-link="internal">democrat candidates during</a> the midterm elections… So much, in fact, that he’s been listed as the <a href="https://fortune.com/2022/11/10/sam-bankman-fried-ftx-joe-biden-democratic-party-second-biggest-donor/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">second highest donor</a> to said candidates this season.</p>
<h2>The Filth of Sam Bankman-Fried Fell into D.C.</h2>
<p>This raises big questions <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-took-his-shady-crypto-money-will-they-keep-it/ar-AA147TZO" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">regarding where the money came</a> from and how it was used. Many people are wondering if the money given to democrats was filthy or had been laundered in some way. It’s not like Bankman-Fried – or SBF as he’s so commonly called – has the cleanest record to his name. There’s far too much coming out about the situation now, and several of these democrats are now being asked if they’re going to part with the money that they received from him.</p>
<p>In most cases, it seems like the obvious thing to do would be to give the funds back and say, “I won’t accept your filthy, lousy endorsement.” Strangely, however, that doesn’t seem to be the case with some of these candidates, who claim they are either keeping the funds or have given them to good causes. These slimy politicians will say just about anything necessary to keep paychecks rolling in, won’t they?</p>
<p>Representative Ruben Gallego – a democrat from Arizona – says he took the money he received from Bankman-Fried and put it towards the campaign of Andrea Salinas, a Latin woman that ran for – and won – a seat in Congress representing a district of Oregon. In an interview, he said of the funds:</p>
<blockquote><p>So, I think I’ve paid it back.</p></blockquote>
<p>Representative Carolyn Bourdeaux, a Georgia representative, was not on the receiving side when it came to money stemming from Bankman-Fried or the PAC he created, while her challenger was. She didn’t win her election, and says she has mixed feelings about the unraveling of FTX that followed. She commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>I knew that this was a very risky financial instrument, and these guys were likely to come to a bad end. Early on, I called for Lucy to disavow this funding. She had no control over it, but she could have at least said, ‘This is not appropriate.’</p></blockquote>
<h2>No Easy Way Out</h2>
<p>She continued to claim that the fraud surrounding SBF and FTX are relatively obvious, and she’s convinced lawmakers will come down hard on both. She mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>The horse is out of the barn. The fraud is so obvious, [and] what happened is so egregious that it’s going to be very hard for members to say, ‘We shouldn’t intervene to regulate this sector.’</p></blockquote>
<p>At the time of writing, Bankman-Fried is under supervision in the Bahamas, where FTX is stationed. He is facing potential fraud charges in that nation, though he could also face criminal charges in the U.S.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-gave-a-lot-of-money-to-democrats-what-will-they-do-with-it/">Sam Bankman-Fried Possibly Gave Dirty Money to Democrats. What Will They Do with It?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-gave-a-lot-of-money-to-democrats-what-will-they-do-with-it/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The future of betting is here as P2PBET launches an unprecedented blockchain betting ecosystem</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-future-of-betting-is-here-as-p2pbet-launches-an-unprecedented-blockchain-betting-ecosystem/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-future-of-betting-is-here-as-p2pbet-launches-an-unprecedented-blockchain-betting-ecosystem/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 13:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry and Adoption]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76062</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Most people like betting because they are always interested in trying their luck to win a big prize. However, as traditional betting is not transparent and over regulated, luck is not always enough. When betting, individuals can not control their funds every step of the way, and that’s why a lot of gimmicky situations appear.<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-future-of-betting-is-here-as-p2pbet-launches-an-unprecedented-blockchain-betting-ecosystem/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-future-of-betting-is-here-as-p2pbet-launches-an-unprecedented-blockchain-betting-ecosystem/">The future of betting is here as P2PBET launches an unprecedented blockchain betting ecosystem</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Most people like betting because they are always interested in trying their luck to win a big prize. However, as traditional betting is not transparent and over regulated, luck is not always enough. When betting, individuals can not control their funds every step of the way, and that’s why a lot of gimmicky situations appear. Also, normal betting is not anonymous and you have to give your personal info to a third party as a result.</p>
<p>It’s good that the betting revolution is happening right now: <a href="https://p2pbet.io/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">P2PBET</a> has launched a world-first crypto-betting platform based on the blockchain. All this sounds intriguing, but before we find out more about this platform, let&#8217;s first understand what cryptocurrency and the blockchain are and how they can influence betting.</p>
<p><strong>About blockchain and cryptocurrency</strong></p>
<p>A blockchain is a decentralized, distributed ledger that stores the record of ownership of digital assets. People who participate in the network are called nodes. The data stored on the blockchain can’t be modified, which makes the technology a legitimate disruptor for industries like payments, cybersecurity and healthcare. Similarity can be seen with Google Docs when a person shares their Google Doc with a group of people, the document becomes distributed among everyone who has access to it. Thus, it becomes decentralized and transparent. Of course, blockchain technology is far more complicated and one can not make any changes once the code is written which makes it more secure.</p>
<p>A cryptocurrency is a form of digital cash that enables individuals to transmit value in the digital world. Crypto functions on the blockchain and does not have a central bank or any party that can change the rules without reaching consensus.</p>
<p>By implementing the blockchain and crypto technology into the betting industry, we can get a completely new way of betting – decentralized betting.</p>
<p><strong>How do decentralized bets work on P2PBET?</strong></p>
<p>Now that we know how the blockchain and crypto work, let’s look at how blockchain decentralization makes betting better.</p>
<ul>
<li>All the transactions happen on the blockchain which means that every user can track the transfers that happen on the platform. What is more – there are no delays and stops in transfers.</li>
<li>There’s no KYC on <a href="https://t.me/p2pbet" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">P2PBET</a> which means that user info is not required.</li>
<li>User money is safe. The participants can be sure that nobody can have access to their money except themselves because the platform requires connecting MetaMask and TRC20 wallets.</li>
<li>Unlike traditional betting, P2PBET does not regulate any rates, because all the financial assets’ statuses are synchronized with the actual rates on Binance.</li>
<li>The platform’s commissions are always fixed at 3% from each win. Such conditions are written in the smart contract and as such, there’s no room for fee manipulation.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>More about P2PBET</strong></p>
<p>The advantages mentioned above can make the betting platform anonymous, transparent and unlimited. <a href="https://t.me/P2PBET_Chat" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">P2PBET</a> took a new innovative approach to betting and revolutionized the industry with the idea of connecting the blockchain, crypto and betting. Now, the ones who love betting can enjoy the process relying on their luck and professionalism, without worrying about other factors.</p>
<p>Moreover, P2PBET launched a <a href="https://free.p2pbet.io/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Free</a><a href="https://free.p2pbet.io/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> Game</a> on their platform where anybody can have 3 attempts to predict BTC’s price by the end of the day. The winner gets $100! The users do not need to invest any money to participate because the game is free. Also, as it has been launched recently, everyone has a big chance to be the winner in guessing the actual price of Bitcoin. This is the perfect chance to give yourself a nice present before Christmas!</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-future-of-betting-is-here-as-p2pbet-launches-an-unprecedented-blockchain-betting-ecosystem/">The future of betting is here as P2PBET launches an unprecedented blockchain betting ecosystem</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-future-of-betting-is-here-as-p2pbet-launches-an-unprecedented-blockchain-betting-ecosystem/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
