<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 05:18:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Brian Armstrong: The FTX Fallout Is Far from Over</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brian-armstrong-the-ftx-fallout-is-far-from-over/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brian-armstrong-the-ftx-fallout-is-far-from-over/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 17:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brian armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76201</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Despite several bullish predictions for 2023, Brian Armstrong – the CEO of Coinbase – believes it will be some time before the crypto space relieves itself of the drama caused by FTX, and he doesn’t think 2023 will offer the improvement over 2022 that so many analysts are either predicting or hoping for. Brian Armstrong<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brian-armstrong-the-ftx-fallout-is-far-from-over/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brian-armstrong-the-ftx-fallout-is-far-from-over/">Brian Armstrong: The FTX Fallout Is Far from Over</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite several bullish predictions for 2023, Brian Armstrong – the CEO of Coinbase – believes it will be <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/billybambrough/2022/12/24/cryptopocalypse-coinbase-ceo-issues-serious-contagion-warning-after-bitcoin-and-ethereum-price-crash/?sh=58a54be1a07f" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">some time before the crypto</a> space relieves itself of the drama caused by FTX, and he doesn’t think 2023 will offer the improvement over 2022 that so many analysts are either predicting or hoping for.</p>
<h2>Brian Armstrong Doesn&#8217;t Think 2023 Will Offer Much Improvement</h2>
<p>FTX will likely go down as one of the biggest blunders of the crypto world. Once considered one of the largest and most popular digital currency trading platforms in the world, FTX took only three years to rise to fruition, and its head executive – a young man named Sam Bankman-Fried – was lauded as a genius, a reputation he would only hold temporarily.</p>
<p>In mid-November, he complained on <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">social media of a liquidity crunch</a>, and said that the exchange was in desperate need of fast cash. However, things didn’t quite go according to plan. Initially, he sought the aid of Binance, his largest rival. The idea was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">that the big exchange</a> would buy out the smaller one, thus giving it the support and money that it needed to stay afloat.</p>
<p>But Binance <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">eventually backed away</a> from the deal, claiming that the problems FTX was facing were far too big for it to handle. From there, the company had <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">to file bankruptcy</a> and SBF resigned from his post. This was to be the least of his problems as he would later be arrested in the Bahamas for allegedly tampering with people’s money. From there, he <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2022/12/21/technology/sbf-ftx-extradition.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">would be extradited</a> to the United States, and he is currently awaiting his trial while living at his parents’ California home.</p>
<p>In a recent interview, Armstrong explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think there could be a little more contagion from FTX, but my hope is that [everything moves] through the system in the next couple of months or quarters at most. After 18 months, people moved on and nobody asked me about it after that.</p></blockquote>
<p>Many exchanges such as Armstrong’s Coinbase have been dealing with the aftermath of the FTX debacle. Coinbase has fallen into oblivion and its stock shares have plummeted from the near $300 unit prices they were enjoying when the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-spikes-following-public-debut-of-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">company first went public</a> in April of 2021.</p>
<p>It appears there are many exchanges out there that have fallen under a light of distrust. Nobody really sees exchanges as the powerhouses they once were anymore, and they are rushing to get their money out and into cold wallets or decentralized platforms.</p>
<h2>Coinbase Wants to Do Things the Right Way</h2>
<p>Armstrong continued with:</p>
<blockquote><p>The bull case for Coinbase is we&#8217;re the leader in the market from a trust point of view and the largest [exchange] in the U.S. The market is giving us very clear feedback that they want to work with trusted companies if they’re going to be centralized actors.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brian-armstrong-the-ftx-fallout-is-far-from-over/">Brian Armstrong: The FTX Fallout Is Far from Over</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brian-armstrong-the-ftx-fallout-is-far-from-over/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mining Pool BTC.com Hacked; $3 Million Goes Missing</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mining-pool-btc-com-hacked-3-million-goes-missing/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mining-pool-btc-com-hacked-3-million-goes-missing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 15:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC.Com]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mining pool]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76198</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It’s happened again, folks. Another crypto hack is in the books. This time, the victim is alleged to be BTC.com, one of the biggest crypto mining pools in the world. BTC.com Hacked; A Lot of Money Gone The mining pool is believed to have lost as much as $3 million at the time of writing,<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mining-pool-btc-com-hacked-3-million-goes-missing/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mining-pool-btc-com-hacked-3-million-goes-missing/">Mining Pool BTC.com Hacked; $3 Million Goes Missing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It’s happened again, folks. Another crypto hack is in the books. This time, the victim is alleged to be BTC.com, one of <a href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/btccom-lost-3-million-worth-of-cryptocurrency-in-cyberattack/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">the biggest crypto mining</a> pools in the world.</p>
<h2>BTC.com Hacked; A Lot of Money Gone</h2>
<p>The mining pool is believed to have lost as much as $3 million at the time of writing, which on paper, doesn’t appear as big as some of the other major hacks and scams that have occurred within the confines of the crypto space in recent years. However, it’s still another clear message that the digital currency arena is not where it needs to be. That safety measures aren’t as strong as we believe, and that the time has come for companies to step up and make sure all their users’ funds are safe and sound.</p>
<p>The money that was stolen belonged to both the company and its customers. BTC.com is reportedly the seventh largest crypto mining pool in the world and accounts for close to three percent of the bitcoin network’s total hash rate.</p>
<p>Approximately $700,000 in crypto was taken from the customers of the company, while just over $2 million belonged to BTC.com itself. The company explained in a recent statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>In the cyberattack, certain digital assets were stolen, including approximately US$700,000 in asset value owned by BTC.com&#8217;s clients, and approximately US$2.3 million in asset value owned by the company. On December 23rd, 2022, the authorities had launched an investigation, began collecting evidence, and had requested assistance from and coordination with relevant agencies. The company will devote considerable efforts to recover the stolen digital assets.</p></blockquote>
<p>The event has been reported to Chinese law enforcement agencies, and it is alleged that some of the stolen funds have been recovered at press time, though just how much is presently unclear. The company continued its statement by claiming it is now implementing new security protocols designed to keep its customers’ funds safer in the future and that operations are continuing as normal. It said:</p>
<blockquote><p>In the wake of discovering this cyberattack, the company has implemented technology to better block and intercept hackers. BTC.com is currently operating its business as usual, and apart from its digital asset services, its client fund services are unaffected.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Small Compared to Past Cases</h2>
<p>As bad as it all sounds, this is small beans when compared with major hacking incidents such as <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/mt-gox/" data-wpel-link="internal">Mt. Gox</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/coincheck/" data-wpel-link="internal">Coincheck</a>. Both took place in Japan approximately four years apart from each other, with Mt. Gox happening in February of 2014 and Coincheck in January of 2018, respectively.</p>
<p>Together, the companies lost more than $1 billion in crypto funds, with roughly $400 million in BTC taken from Mt. Gox and over half a billion in crypto stolen from Coincheck. The latter incident led to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/japans-cryptocurrency-association-to-vote-on-new-regulations-this-month/" data-wpel-link="internal">Japanese financial agencies</a> getting involved in crypto regulation and safety protocols.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mining-pool-btc-com-hacked-3-million-goes-missing/">Mining Pool BTC.com Hacked; $3 Million Goes Missing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mining-pool-btc-com-hacked-3-million-goes-missing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lewis Kaplan Will Be the Judge to Oversee FTX Court Case</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lewis-kaplan-will-be-the-judge-to-oversee-ftx-court-case/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lewis-kaplan-will-be-the-judge-to-oversee-ftx-court-case/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 13:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lewis Kaplan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76196</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Judge Lewis A. Kaplan, a Manhattan federal judge, will oversee the trial of Sam Bankman-Fried. SBF is presently facing several charges in connection with the collapse of FTX. It is alleged that Bankman-Fried likely utilized customer funds to engage in Ponzi-like behavior and purchase luxury items such as Bahamas-based condominiums for himself and fellow FTX<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lewis-kaplan-will-be-the-judge-to-oversee-ftx-court-case/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lewis-kaplan-will-be-the-judge-to-oversee-ftx-court-case/">Lewis Kaplan Will Be the Judge to Oversee FTX Court Case</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Judge Lewis A. Kaplan, a Manhattan federal judge, will <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/business/2022/dec/27/judge-trump-prince-andrew-trials-sbf-sam-bankman-fried-ftx-cryptocurrency" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">oversee the trial of</a> Sam Bankman-Fried. SBF is presently facing several charges in connection with the collapse of FTX. It is alleged that Bankman-Fried likely utilized customer funds to engage in Ponzi-like behavior and purchase luxury items such as Bahamas-based condominiums for himself and fellow FTX employees.</p>
<h2>Lewis Kaplan Will Decide SBF&#8217;s Fate</h2>
<p>Kaplan was a second-choice judge. The first one – who is unnamed at the time of writing – excused herself from the case given that her husband was employed by a law firm that did work with FTX and Sam Bankman-Fried. Thus, to avoid conflicts of interest, another judge has been given the case.</p>
<p>Kaplan has a “no-nonsense” attitude according to platforms like <em>The Guardian</em>. First nominated to the bench in 1994 by then-president Bill Clinton, Kaplan is 78 years of age and will be presiding over a case this coming April between President Donald Trump and <em>Elle</em> magazine advice columnist E. Jean Carroll, who alleges that Trump assaulted her in either 1995 or 1996. Trump has denied the accusation.</p>
<p>Kaplan also presided over a sex abuse claims case involving two women against Prince Andrew of England. Kaplan has garnered a reputation over the years for being short-tempered and very quick with his decisions, which can be a strength or a weakness depending on the circumstances of a case. In the one involving SBF, for example, several high-ranking members of society – including several members of Congress and politicians – were involved with Sam Bankman-Fried <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-gave-a-lot-of-money-to-democrats-what-will-they-do-with-it/" data-wpel-link="internal">and even accepted donations</a> from his end of the table.</p>
<p>It will be in Kaplan’s interest to really observe all the facts and hear every point of both sides before deciding what is to come next. Given the size and the gravity of what happened, time will be necessary for understanding what really occurred and how such a large and proficient business could come crashing down so suddenly.</p>
<p>His purported tendency to become irritable with lawyers could wind up playing against him if he is not careful. In 1997, he presided over an immigration and asylum case that allegedly took too long. He snapped at the attorneys:</p>
<blockquote><p>This is about as expedited as a glacier going uphill… The INS has in the three years I’ve been on the bench acquitted itself in disastrous fashion more than once, but this one takes the cake, and I’m not going to stand for it much longer.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Long Legal History</h2>
<p>In 2000, he ruled in favor of the entertainment industry and said that it had a right to protect all DVDs from being burned or copied on computers. He explained during that case:</p>
<blockquote><p>Computer code is not purely expressive any more than the assassination of a political figure is purely a political statement.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lewis-kaplan-will-be-the-judge-to-oversee-ftx-court-case/">Lewis Kaplan Will Be the Judge to Oversee FTX Court Case</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lewis-kaplan-will-be-the-judge-to-oversee-ftx-court-case/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Climbs Higher and Aims A Move To $0.10</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-climbs-higher-and-aims-a-move-to-0-10/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-climbs-higher-and-aims-a-move-to-0-10/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 07:28:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar Lumens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76527</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stellar lumen price started a fresh increase above the $0.080 resistance zone against the US Dollar. XLM price is now trading above $0.080 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.086 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could continue to<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-climbs-higher-and-aims-a-move-to-0-10/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-climbs-higher-and-aims-a-move-to-0-10/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Climbs Higher and Aims A Move To $0.10</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Stellar lumen price started a fresh increase above the $0.080 resistance zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>XLM price is now trading above $0.080 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.086 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to rise if it stays above the $0.0860 and $0.0850 support levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Stellar lumen price is trading above $0.0850 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-climbs-and-aims-steady-increase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. XLM price must stay above the $0.0845 support to rise further.</em></p>
<h2>Stellar Lumen Price Analysis (XLM to USD)</h2>
<p>After forming a base above the $0.075 level, stellar lumen price started a fresh increase against the US Dollar. The XLM/USD pair broke the $0.080 resistance zone to move into a positive zone.</p>
<p>The price even broke the $0.0850 resistance and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-regains-traction-what-could-be-the-target/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. The price is now trading comfortably above the $0.084 level. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $0.0912 level. The next major resistance is near the $0.0950 level.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $0.0950 level might send the price towards the $0.100 level. Any more gains could lead the price towards the $0.0920 level or even $0.1000 in the coming days. An initial support on the downside is near the $0.0880 level.</p>
<p>It is near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.0791 swing high to $0.0906 low. The next major support sits near the $0.0845 level. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.086 on the 4-hours chart.</p>
<p>The 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.0791 swing high to $0.0906 low. The main support is near the $0.080 zone. Any more losses could lead the price towards the $0.075 level in the near term, below which the price might even retest $0.0680.</p>
<div id="attachment_76528" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76528" class="size-full wp-image-76528" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-2.png" alt="Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76528" class="wp-caption-text">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XLMUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that XLM price is now trading above $0.0840 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could continue to rise if it stays above the $0.0912 and $0.095 support levels.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XLM/USD is gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for XLM/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.0880 and $0.0840.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.0912, $0.0950 and $0.1000.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-climbs-higher-and-aims-a-move-to-0-10/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Climbs Higher and Aims A Move To $0.10</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-climbs-higher-and-aims-a-move-to-0-10/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Price Analysis: Uptrend In Place Above $0.40</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-uptrend-in-place-above-0-40/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-uptrend-in-place-above-0-40/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 05:08:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76523</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple price is moving higher above the $0.38 level against the US dollar. The price is now trading above $0.380 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.3820 on the 4-hours chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Bittrex). The pair could gain<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-uptrend-in-place-above-0-40/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-uptrend-in-place-above-0-40/">Ripple Price Analysis: Uptrend In Place Above $0.40</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ripple price is moving higher above the $0.38 level against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $0.380 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.3820 on the 4-hours chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Bittrex).</li>
<li>The pair could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $0.4080 resistance zone in the near term.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ripple price is rising steadily above $0.380 against the US Dollar, unlike <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-climbs-and-aims-steady-increase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. XRP price must clear $0.408 to continue higher in the coming sessions.</em></p>
<h2>Ripple Price Analysis</h2>
<p>After forming a base near the $0.3400 zone, ripple price started a fresh increase against the US Dollar. The XRP/USD pair was able to clear the $0.3650 resistance zone.</p>
<p>The price even broke the $0.3800 resistance and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). The pair is now trading above the $0.400 resistance. It is also showing positive signs above $0.4000 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-aim-higher-above-0-37/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near $0.4080.  The next major resistance is near the $0.4200 level. A clear move above the $0.4200 resistance zone might start a strong increase. In the stated case, the price could even surpass the $0.4400 resistance.</p>
<p>Any more gains might send the price towards the $0.5000 resistance. An initial support on the downside is near the $0.3980 level. It is near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.3666 swing low to $0.4078 high.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $0.3820 level. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.3820 on the 4-hours chart of the XRP/USD pair.</p>
<p>The trend line is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.3666 swing low to $0.4078 high. Any more losses could lead the price towards the $0.3700 level, below which the price might even test $0.3650.</p>
<div id="attachment_76524" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Ripple-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76524" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-76524" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Ripple-2.png" alt="Ripple Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76524" class="wp-caption-text">Ripple Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, ripple price is now trading above the $0.380 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $0.4080 resistance zone in the near term.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XRP/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for XRP/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.3980, $0.3820 and $0.370.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.4080 and $0.440.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-uptrend-in-place-above-0-40/">Ripple Price Analysis: Uptrend In Place Above $0.40</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-uptrend-in-place-above-0-40/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mark Cuban: Forget Gold, Invest in BTC</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-forget-gold-invest-in-btc/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-forget-gold-invest-in-btc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 17:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gold]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mark Cuban]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76193</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Despite everything that’s happened in 2022, Mark Cuban is doubling down on his love of bitcoin and says he’s hoping to purchase more of the world’s number one digital currency by market cap should it drop even lower. Mark Cuban Doesn&#8217;t Like Gold That Much 2022 was a rough year for bitcoin and the crypto<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-forget-gold-invest-in-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-forget-gold-invest-in-btc/">Mark Cuban: Forget Gold, Invest in BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite everything that’s happened in 2022, Mark Cuban is <a href="https://sports.yahoo.com/mark-cuban-defends-bitcoin-says-230258502.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">doubling down on his love</a> of bitcoin and says he’s hoping to purchase more of the world’s number one digital currency by market cap should it drop even lower.</p>
<h2>Mark Cuban Doesn&#8217;t Like Gold That Much</h2>
<p>2022 was a rough year for bitcoin and the crypto space. Bitcoin fell by more than 70 percent in value and ended the year trading in the high $16,000 range. This is way off the mark from the $68,000 per unit that it achieved in November of 2021. Overall, the crypto space lost more than $2 trillion in overall valuation and was also marred by several scams and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">bankruptcies</a>.</p>
<p>But Cuban is trying his best to put all this aside. He still believes in the asset, even more so than he does gold. In a recent podcast, he commented that anyone who owned gold was “dumb as f*ck” and that having bitcoin as part of their portfolio was the smartest move to make. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>I want bitcoin to go down a lot further so I can buy some more. If you have gold, you&#8217;re dumb as f***.</p></blockquote>
<p>The host of the podcast was Bill Maher, formerly of the show “Politically Incorrect.” Maher claimed to be a big fan of gold, and said it was a hedge against all the economic problems people have been seeing over the last few years. However, Cuban begged to differ, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>No, but it&#8217;s not a hedge against anything, right? What it is, is the stored value, and you don&#8217;t own the physical gold, do you? Gold is a stored value and so is bitcoin… It’s a digital transaction and it&#8217;s a stored value&#8230; So, people perceive that there is value associated with gold, that there&#8217;s value associated with bitcoin.</p></blockquote>
<p>He stated that just because a person invests in gold doesn’t mean they truly own it. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>You don&#8217;t own the gold bar, and if everything went to hell in a handbasket and you had a gold bar, you know what would happen? Someone would beat the f*** out of you or kill you and take your gold bar.</p></blockquote>
<p>This is not the first time that Cuban has bashed gold. In an interview in the year 2019, he said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I hate gold. Gold is a religion.</p></blockquote>
<h2>He Still Believes in BTC</h2>
<p>Not long ago, Cuban also discussed the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-is-mad-about-whats-happened-with-ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">recent collapse of FTX</a> and the disaster surrounding former crypto head Sam Bankman-Fried. He said that while the situation was no doubt hairy, he isn’t allowing what happened to affect his opinion of the crypto space or bitcoin and stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Separate the signal from the noise. There’s been a lot of people making a lot of mistakes, but it doesn’t change the underlying value.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-forget-gold-invest-in-btc/">Mark Cuban: Forget Gold, Invest in BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-forget-gold-invest-in-btc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Magnates Like Changpeng Zhao Saw Their Net Worth Crash in 2022</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-magnates-like-changpeng-zhao-lost-a-ton-in-2022/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-magnates-like-changpeng-zhao-lost-a-ton-in-2022/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 15:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76189</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>2022 was a year of loss, and many crypto billionaires – from Changpeng Zhao of Binance fame to the Winklevoss Twins who run the Gemini exchange – have lost a ton of money. So much in fact, that in just nine short months, many of them have seen their net worth virtually collapse – in<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-magnates-like-changpeng-zhao-lost-a-ton-in-2022/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-magnates-like-changpeng-zhao-lost-a-ton-in-2022/">Crypto Magnates Like Changpeng Zhao Saw Their Net Worth Crash in 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>2022 was a year of loss, and <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/johnhyatt/2022/12/24/these-crypto-founders-and-bitcoin-moguls-lost-116-billion-in-2022/?sh=276675c742b2" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">many crypto billionaires</a> – from Changpeng Zhao of Binance fame to the Winklevoss Twins who run the Gemini exchange – have lost a ton of money. So much in fact, that in just nine short months, many of them have seen their net worth virtually collapse – in some cases, to zero.</p>
<h2>Changpeng Zhao and Others Have Lost Tons of Money</h2>
<p>Changpeng Zhao, for instance, had a net worth of approximately $65 billion in March of last year. By the end of December, that worth had dropped to less than $5 billion. This should give you a  clear idea of just how bad the previous year was for crypto. Matt Cohen – founder of Ripple Ventures – commented in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>We&#8217;re now at the breaking point in crypto where everyone will have to take a pause and say, ‘Okay, we&#8217;ve seen a ton of economic wealth destroyed in the last couple of months. We need to start taking this seriously. A lot of blockchain technologies and companies… built solutions for problems that didn&#8217;t need fixing, and I think we&#8217;re now going to have a hard reset.</p></blockquote>
<p>Lisa Ellis – an equity analyst at Moffett Nathanson – took aim at Binance and claimed it had a “dodgy operating model.” She said in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>I don’t believe a business can persist, operating in this amorphous way, not governed by anyone or anywhere, especially when it&#8217;s run by a public individual.</p></blockquote>
<p>There has been plenty of speculation as to whether Binance is in trouble. Recently, Zhao took to social media to explain the firm was not experiencing any difficulties and that it had enough reserves in its pockets to stay afloat. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We are quite a unique organization. We don’t have loans from any other organizations. We will prove all the FUD [fear, uncertainty and doubt] is wrong.</p></blockquote>
<p>Brian Armstrong – CEO of Coinbase – also struck at Zhao, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>Coinbase and Binance are following different approaches. We&#8217;re trying to follow a regulated, trusted approach. To look at it intellectually honestly, we&#8217;re choosing to follow the rules. It&#8217;s a more difficult path and sometimes your hands are tied, but I think that&#8217;s the right long-term strategy.</p></blockquote>
<p>Changpeng Zhao was number one in the crypto wealth category, but a close second was Sam Bankman-Fried of FTX fame. In his early 30s, SBF was lauded as a genius by many as his company rose through the ranks to become one of the world’s top five crypto exchanges in three years.</p>
<h2>SBF: Riches to Rags</h2>
<p>Sadly, his <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/john-ray-iii-ftx-is-the-most-mismanaged-company-ive-ever-seen/" data-wpel-link="internal">poor accounting skills</a> and Ponzi-like behavior led to the complete collapse of his company, and he recently served time in a Bahamian jail <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/judge-tells-30-year-old-sbf-to-move-back-in-with-parents-on-250-million-bail/ar-AA15zWM3" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">before being extradited</a> back to the U.S. where he now awaits trial.</p>
<p>His net worth prior to FTX’s fall from grace was $24 billion. It is now zilch.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-magnates-like-changpeng-zhao-lost-a-ton-in-2022/">Crypto Magnates Like Changpeng Zhao Saw Their Net Worth Crash in 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-magnates-like-changpeng-zhao-lost-a-ton-in-2022/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wallet Network Bit Keep Hacked; More than $8 Million Gone</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/wallet-network-bit-keep-hacked-more-than-8-million-gone/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/wallet-network-bit-keep-hacked-more-than-8-million-gone/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 13:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bit Keep]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coincheck]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mt Gox]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76187</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It’s happened again, folks. Another crypto hack has been recorded to the digital currency books. This time, the alleged victim is Bit Keep, a virtual wallet provider, and more than $8 million in crypto funds have gone missing. Bit Keep Compromised; A Lot of Money Missing To be fair, this is a small number compared<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/wallet-network-bit-keep-hacked-more-than-8-million-gone/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/wallet-network-bit-keep-hacked-more-than-8-million-gone/">Wallet Network Bit Keep Hacked; More than $8 Million Gone</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It’s happened again, folks. Another crypto hack has <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-ae/money/news/hackers-steal-8m-worth-of-cryptocurrency-from-bitkeep-wallets/ar-AA15FTOr" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">been recorded to the</a> digital currency books. This time, the alleged victim is Bit Keep, a virtual wallet provider, and more than $8 million in crypto funds have gone missing.</p>
<h2>Bit Keep Compromised; A Lot of Money Missing</h2>
<p>To be fair, this is a small number compared to the many digital currency hacks and scams that have occurred in the past, but it’s another clear reminder that the space is not where it needs to be, and that people and companies are just as vulnerable as ever. The time has come to take these threats seriously and ensure proper security protocols are in place to keep people’s money out of the wrong hands.</p>
<p>As a decentralized network, Bit Keep is not governed by a group of executives. This is a good thing in that it provides people with more privacy and autonomy, but it’s also rough in that a decentralized company often sees to it that its customers or those it does business with are on their own. That’s one of the downsides to not having a set of prying eyes watching your every move; there’s no one in charge to make sure you stay safe.</p>
<p>Many users of Bit Keep took to social media to explain that they saw many of their funds being moved without their consent. At the time of writing, it’s unclear how many users have been affected by the event. Based in Singapore, Bit Keep is alleged to have as many as 6.3 million users.</p>
<p>It is believed that the assets taken include Binance Coin, Ethereum, Tether, and Dai. Bit Keep confirmed the breach on Telegram and says it’s now taking necessary action to fix the issue. It said in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>It is suspected that some APK package downloads have been hijacked by hackers and installed with code implanted by hackers. If your funds are stolen, the application you download or [that] update may be an unknown version [unofficial release version] hijacked.</p></blockquote>
<p>The crypto space has been a haven for theft and similar crime since it first came to fruition roughly 14 years ago. Among the biggest digital currency exchange hacks to ever occur include <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/mt-gox/" data-wpel-link="internal">Mt. Gox</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/coincheck/" data-wpel-link="internal">Coincheck</a>. Both took place in Japan roughly four years apart.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Mt. Gox happened in February of 2014 and resulted in roughly $400 million in bitcoin funds being stolen overnight. Four years later, in January of 2018, more than half a billion dollars in crypto funds were stolen from Coincheck, a fellow trading platform.</p>
<p>The latter resulted in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/japans-cryptocurrency-association-to-vote-on-new-regulations-this-month/" data-wpel-link="internal">Japanese financial agencies</a> getting involved in crypto and working to make sure all digital currency businesses stationed in the country followed certain protocols to ensure traders’ funds remained in the right hands.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/wallet-network-bit-keep-hacked-more-than-8-million-gone/">Wallet Network Bit Keep Hacked; More than $8 Million Gone</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/wallet-network-bit-keep-hacked-more-than-8-million-gone/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Mining Firm Greenidge Generation Hints at Potential Bankruptcy</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-mining-firm-greenidge-generation-hints-at-potential-bankruptcy/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-mining-firm-greenidge-generation-hints-at-potential-bankruptcy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 17:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bankruptcy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Greenidge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76159</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Another crypto mining firm is in trouble. This time, the alleged victim is Greenidge Generation (GREE), which has hinted that it could file bankruptcy in the coming weeks if its present deal with NYDIG doesn’t work out. Greenidge Generation Could Be the Next to Go The company is struggling to restructure its nearly $75 million<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-mining-firm-greenidge-generation-hints-at-potential-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-mining-firm-greenidge-generation-hints-at-potential-bankruptcy/">Crypto Mining Firm Greenidge Generation Hints at Potential Bankruptcy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Another crypto mining firm is in trouble. This time, the alleged victim is Greenidge Generation (GREE), <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/bitcoin-miner-greenidge-reaches-debt-124316270.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">which has hinted that</a> it could file bankruptcy in the coming weeks if its present deal with NYDIG doesn’t work out.</p>
<h2>Greenidge Generation Could Be the Next to Go</h2>
<p>The company is struggling to restructure its nearly $75 million debt. By doing this, the company could avoid a long bankruptcy line that initially began last summer with firms like Celsius, though Greenidge is not out of the woods yet. Even if the plan goes through, the company is still required to garner at least $20 million in new funding before the end of 2023. This could prove challenging if the crypto space does not heal by then.</p>
<p>To say 2022 was a bad year for crypto would be a terrible understatement. The world’s biggest digital currency – bitcoin – fell by more than 70 percent from the all-time high of $68,000 per unit it achieved in November of 2021. By the time the year ended, the currency was trading in the high $16K range.</p>
<p>Several other leading tokens followed in the asset’s footsteps. The crypto space ultimately lost more than $2 trillion of its overall value and there were several companies that went under or were forced to file bankruptcy due to the weak sentiment surrounding the space.</p>
<p>Celsius is arguably the firm that started the trend. The company <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/another-mega-bitcoin-crash-is-in-the-books/" data-wpel-link="internal">halted all withdrawals</a> in the summer of 2022 and caused everyone to raise eyebrows when they suddenly couldn’t access their funds. From there, the company engaged in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/celsius-network-is-next-crypto-company-to-file-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">bankruptcy proceedings</a> to protect itself against angry creditors and customers, all the while dealing with a very unstable market.</p>
<p>Other enterprises followed suit, including <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-hedge-fund-three-arrows-capital-is-now-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">Three Arrows Capital</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-lender-voyager-digital-files-chapter-11-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">Voyager Digital</a>, and then <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX</a>, which appears to have engaged in various criminal acts including using traders’ assets to fund personal ventures such as buying luxury condominiums in the Bahamas for Sam Bankman-Fried – the head executive of the exchange – and other employees.</p>
<p>The company is now at the center of a huge scandal and Sam Bankman-Fried <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-to-await-trial-at-his-parents-house/" data-wpel-link="internal">is out on bail while</a> he awaits trial in California after spending time in a Bahamian jail cell.</p>
<h2>You Can&#8217;t Just Make Money Mining</h2>
<p>To try and survive for the next 12 months, Greenidge will no longer be hosting its own digital currency mining machines. Instead, it will play host to the machines of NYDIG. The company must also run completely on natural gas as a means of reducing its costs, and it must also sell energy produced in a natural gas plant and not just rely on crypto mining to make ends meet.</p>
<p>This is a huge change for a company that just last October and November, was driving through more than $8 million each month. Of that money, $5.5 million went to NYDIG payments.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-mining-firm-greenidge-generation-hints-at-potential-bankruptcy/">Crypto Mining Firm Greenidge Generation Hints at Potential Bankruptcy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-mining-firm-greenidge-generation-hints-at-potential-bankruptcy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
