<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 04:28:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>CFTC Sues Binance Alleging Financial Violations</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cftc-sues-binance-alleging-financial-violations/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cftc-sues-binance-alleging-financial-violations/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 17:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CFTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77664</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) is suing Binance and its founder Changpeng Zhao after the crypto exchange allegedly violated the Commodity Exchange Act and other regulations. The CFTC Is Going After Binance The agency claims Binance has had no regard for current financial laws and has been violating them for the past several<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cftc-sues-binance-alleging-financial-violations/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cftc-sues-binance-alleging-financial-violations/">CFTC Sues Binance Alleging Financial Violations</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) is suing Binance and its founder Changpeng Zhao after the crypto <a href="https://siliconangle.com/2023/03/27/cftc-sues-cryptocurrency-exchange-binance-founder-changpeng-zhao/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">exchange allegedly violated</a> the Commodity Exchange Act and other regulations.</p>
<h2>The CFTC Is Going After Binance</h2>
<p>The agency claims Binance has had no regard for current financial laws and has been violating them for the past several years. Heads of the CFTC are now seeking financial penalties and a permanent ban in the United States. CFTC chair Rostin Behnam claimed in a recent statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>For years, Binance knew they were violating CFTC rules, working actively to both keep the money flowing and avoid compliance. This should be a warning to anyone in the digital asset world that the CFTC will not tolerate willful avoidance of U.S. law.</p></blockquote>
<p>Gretchen Lowe – principal deputy director and chief counsel to the CFTC’s enforcement division – also threw her two cents into the mix, commenting:</p>
<blockquote><p>The defendants’ own emails and chats reflect that Binance’s compliance efforts have been a sham and Binance deliberately chose – over and over – to place profits over following the law.</p></blockquote>
<p>Binance is the world’s largest and most popular digital currency trading platform per its daily trading volume. In just the last few days alone, the company is alleged to have overseen roughly $9 billion in digital transactions. The company is also believed to have about 90 million users in multiple countries.</p>
<p>In its lawsuit against the exchange, the CFTC alleges that Binance is run by various corporate entities rather than a single governing body. This is designed to reportedly help it evade regulation and committee oversights. Right now, the lawsuit names three separate companies and/or divisions of Binance within its pages. They are Binance Holdings Ltd., Binance Holdings (IE) Ltd., and Finance (Services) Holdings Ltd.</p>
<p>The action has sent ripples throughout the space, with the price of bitcoin immediately descending from its nine-month high of around $28K to the high $26K range after the CFTC made the announcement. Ed Moya – an analyst at Oanda – <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-falls-after-cftc-sues-crypto-exchange-binance-for-allegedly-breaking-trading-rules/ar-AA198urA" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">commented on the situation</a>, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>Many knew Binance had a bullseye on its back, but this is still unnerving some crypto traders. Binance&#8217;s success is needed to ensure a good part of the cryptoverse can grow.</p></blockquote>
<h2>So Many Agencies Are Attacking Crypto</h2>
<p>Dessislava Aubert – an analyst at crypto data provider Kaiko – said Binance is the world’s largest crypto exchange, and thus any regulatory action against it would likely have hugely negative effects on the rest of the space.</p>
<p>It seems like lately federal agencies just want to prosecute and criminalize crypto companies as much as possible. Look at the recent track record of the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), for example. The group has nailed companies like Kraken, slapping <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/" data-wpel-link="internal">them with heavy fines</a> and ending their staking divisions, and it’s now going <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">after Coinbase</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cftc-sues-binance-alleging-financial-violations/">CFTC Sues Binance Alleging Financial Violations</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cftc-sues-binance-alleging-financial-violations/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kristi Noem Crypto Regulation Veto Remains in Place</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kristi-noem-crypto-regulation-veto-is-upheld/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kristi-noem-crypto-regulation-veto-is-upheld/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 15:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto-regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kristi Noem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Dakota]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77661</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, South Dakota Governor Kristi Noem vetoed a bill that would have paved the way for crypto regulation in her state. It was recently announced that the House of South Dakota has failed to override the veto, and thus digital currency legislation will not be making its way into the state anytime soon.<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kristi-noem-crypto-regulation-veto-is-upheld/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kristi-noem-crypto-regulation-veto-is-upheld/">Kristi Noem Crypto Regulation Veto Remains in Place</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, South Dakota Governor Kristi Noem vetoed a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/governor-kristi-noem-vetoes-central-bank-digital-currency-bill/" data-wpel-link="internal">bill that would have</a> paved the way for crypto regulation in her state. It was recently announced that the House of South Dakota has failed to override the veto, and thus digital currency legislation <a href="https://abcnews.go.com/Business/wireStory/south-dakota-govs-veto-cryptocurrency-regulations-upheld-98160004" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">will not be making its</a> way into the state anytime soon.</p>
<h2>Kristi Noem Is Getting Her Way</h2>
<p>The bill had initially passed through the legislative branch, though it failed to hold any ground after Noem initiated the veto. The new votes for the bill were 37 to 30. In a statement, Noem commented on why she felt the bill did not present a plausible future for the state of South Dakota. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>It would be imprudent to create regulations governing something that does not yet exist. More importantly, South Dakota should not open the door to a potential future overreach by the federal government.</p></blockquote>
<p>There are likely many hidden reasons for the veto, a big one being that cryptocurrency was initially designed to be ungovernable. Digital currencies were built to give the unbanked a chance and to prevent those that couldn’t gain access to standard financial products and services from being turned out in the streets. In other words, it didn’t matter what your past credit history was. So long as you had an internet connection and a digital wallet, you could begin purchasing, selling, and trading assets as you saw fit.</p>
<p>The idea of crypto regulation ultimately goes against this narrative as it would allow government heads to step in and have a say over what people could do with their money. In addition, Noem is also likely not a fan of who’s in charge of the federal government at this time, and thus doesn’t want to give Joe Biden and his nation-hating cronies the chance to have more control over people’s financial lives.</p>
<p>Ever since <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">the fall of FTX</a>, many individuals working within the federal government have renewed calls for crypto regulation. This would all be fine and dandy if you were to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-gave-a-lot-of-money-to-democrats-what-will-they-do-with-it/" data-wpel-link="internal">ignore the fact that many</a> of them accepted bribes from Sam Bankman-Fried, the man tasked with running the exchange. Now that he’s out of the picture and they’ve gotten the extra money they wanted, they suddenly want to step in and regulate the space. The whole situation feels and looks a bit fishy.</p>
<h2>Crypto Regulation&#8230; Will It Come Anyway?</h2>
<p>The bill’s sponsor – House Republican Hugh Bartels – believes crypto regulation will eventually enter the U.S. within a set period, and he’s not allowing this little setback to bring down his confidence or his mentality. He said in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>The misconception is that this bill is authorizing [a] central bank digital currency. It’s just setting up a way to do business with it.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kristi-noem-crypto-regulation-veto-is-upheld/">Kristi Noem Crypto Regulation Veto Remains in Place</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kristi-noem-crypto-regulation-veto-is-upheld/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX&#8217;s Sam Bankman-Fried Faces New Bribery Charges</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftxs-sam-bankman-fried-faces-new-bribery-charges/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftxs-sam-bankman-fried-faces-new-bribery-charges/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 13:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bribery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77658</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sam Bankman-Fried – the former crypto executive behind popular digital currency trading platform FTX – has been charged with violating the Foreign Corrupt Practices Act by allegedly attempting to bribe officials from China. Sam Bankman-Fried Is Facing New Charges Prosecutors claim that Sam Bankman-Fried attempted to send money to Chinese officials so they would unfreeze<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftxs-sam-bankman-fried-faces-new-bribery-charges/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftxs-sam-bankman-fried-faces-new-bribery-charges/">FTX&#8217;s Sam Bankman-Fried Faces New Bribery Charges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sam Bankman-Fried – the former crypto executive behind popular digital currency trading platform FTX – has been <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/sam-bankman-fried-directed-40m-cryptocurrency-bribe-to-chinese-officials-federal-prosecutors-allege/ar-AA19b1Zn" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">charged with violating</a> the Foreign Corrupt Practices Act by allegedly attempting to bribe officials from China.</p>
<h2>Sam Bankman-Fried Is Facing New Charges</h2>
<p>Prosecutors claim that Sam Bankman-Fried attempted to send money to Chinese officials so they would unfreeze roughly $1 billion under his name. The money is being held through his secondary company Alameda Research, a crypto trading hedge fund. With these new charges, Sam Bankman-Fried is now facing approximately 13 separate counts in court.</p>
<p>The indictment of the crypto executive reads as follows:</p>
<blockquote><p>In or about 2021, Samuel Bankman-Fried, a/k/a/ SBF, the defendant, authorized and directed a bribe of at least $40 million to one or more Chinese government officials. The purpose of this bribe was to influence and induce one or more Chinese government officials to unfreeze certain Alameda trading accounts containing over $1 billion in cryptocurrency, which had been frozen by Chinese authorities. Bankman-Fried and others sought to regain access to the assets to fund additional Alameda trading activity, to assist Bankman-Fried and Alameda in obtaining and retaining business.</p></blockquote>
<p>US attorney for the Southern District of New York Damian Williams – who has a knack for showing up when crypto cases like these arise – also threw his two cents into the mix, claiming:</p>
<blockquote><p>We are hard at work and will remain so until justice is done.</p></blockquote>
<p>Court documents purport that the assets held within Alameda were frozen as part of an ongoing investigation into a particular “Alameda trading counterparty,” and that SBF and several of his constituents made various attempts to get the money unlocked for private use. Some of the methods utilized – according to the indictment – included retaining attorneys to advocate in the country for the funds to be unfrozen and communicating with Chinese exchanges.</p>
<p>Sam Bankman-Fried is alleged to have tried to have the money unfrozen for months, but with no success at first. The indictment further states:</p>
<blockquote><p>As a result, in or about November 2021, Bankman-Fried caused a bribe payment of cryptocurrency then worth approximately $40 million to be transferred from Alameda’s main trading account to a private cryptocurrency wallet. At or around the time of the $40 million bribe payment, the accounts were unfrozen.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Long History of Crime?</h2>
<p>Sam Bankman-Fried is currently awaiting trial for <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-to-await-trial-at-his-parents-house/" data-wpel-link="internal">fraud at his parents’</a> Northern California home after he was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftxs-disgraced-founder-has-been-arrested/" data-wpel-link="internal">arrested in the Bahamas</a>, where FTX was initially situated. It is reported that SBF utilized customer funds to pay off loans taken out by Alameda Research and to invest in luxury real estate for himself and his fellow exchange executives.</p>
<p>FTX initially collapsed and entered <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">bankruptcy proceedings</a> in November of last year after it was reported the company was enduring <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">a harsh liquidity crunch</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftxs-sam-bankman-fried-faces-new-bribery-charges/">FTX&#8217;s Sam Bankman-Fried Faces New Bribery Charges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftxs-sam-bankman-fried-faces-new-bribery-charges/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EOS Price Analysis: Signs of Recovery Above $1.05</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-signs-of-recovery-above-1-05/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-signs-of-recovery-above-1-05/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 05:08:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EOS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78193</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>EOS price is trading in a bearish zone above the $0.98 support against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $1.05 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $1.015 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-signs-of-recovery-above-1-05/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-signs-of-recovery-above-1-05/">EOS Price Analysis: Signs of Recovery Above $1.05</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>EOS price is trading in a bearish zone above the $0.98 support against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $1.05 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $1.015 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could start a recovery wave if it clears the $1.05 and $1.08 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>EOS price is struggling below $1.08 against the US Dollar, unlike <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-extend-losses-below-27000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. The price might attempt to recover if there is a clear move above $1.050.</em></p>
<h2>EOS Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, EOS price range moves below the $1.12 resistance against the US Dollar. The price remained stable above the $0.98 and $1.00 support levels.</p>
<p>A low is formed near $0.9747 and the price is now attempting an upside correction. There was a move above the $1.015 and $1.02 resistance levels. Besides, there was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $1.015 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair.</p>
<p>The price is now trading below $1.05 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bears-in-control-below-1-10/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $1.03 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $1.05 level or the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $1.298 swing high to the $0.8747 low, above which the price might test the $1.08 level. Any more gains might send the price towards the $1.12 level.</p>
<p>The next resistance might be $1.135 or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $1.298 swing high to the $0.8747 low. On the downside, immediate support is near the $1.00 level.</p>
<p>The next key support is near the $0.98 level. If there is a downside break below the $0.980 support, the price could test the $0.95 support in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_78194" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/EOS.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78194" class="size-full wp-image-78194" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/EOS.png" alt="EOS Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78194" class="wp-caption-text">EOS Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/EOSUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, EOS price is now trading below the $1.05 level and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could start a recovery wave if it clears the $1.05 and $1.08 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4-hours MACD – The MACD for EOS/USD is losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4-hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $1.00 and $0.98.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $1.05 and $1.08.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-signs-of-recovery-above-1-05/">EOS Price Analysis: Signs of Recovery Above $1.05</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-signs-of-recovery-above-1-05/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Indicators Point Fresh Increase To $100</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-indicators-point-fresh-increase-to-100/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-indicators-point-fresh-increase-to-100/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 03:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78189</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin settled below the $90 resistance zone against the US Dollar. LTC price is now trading below $90 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major contracting triangle forming with resistance near $89.20 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could start a decent<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-indicators-point-fresh-increase-to-100/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-indicators-point-fresh-increase-to-100/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Indicators Point Fresh Increase To $100</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Litecoin settled below the $90 resistance zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>LTC price is now trading below $90 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major contracting triangle forming with resistance near $89.20 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could start a decent increase if it clears the $92 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Litecoin price is struggling below $90 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-extend-losses-below-27000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. LTC price could continue to decline if it stays below the $92 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few hours, there was a minor increase in Bitcoin, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-faces-increase-in-bearish-pressure/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Ethereum</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-could-dive-below-0-44/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Ripple</a>, and Litecoin against the US Dollar. Earlier, LTC settled below the $90 resistance zone to move into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>The price broke the $88 support zone and tested the $85 support. A low is formed near $85.13 and the price is now attempting a recovery wave. There was a move above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $91.46 swing high to the $85.13 low.</p>
<p>It is now trading below $90 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $49.00 zone.</p>
<p>There is also a major contracting triangle forming with resistance near $89.20 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $91.46 swing high to the $85.13 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance sits near the $90 level. The main resistance is near the $92 level. A clear move above the $92 level could pump the price toward the $95 level or even $98. The next major resistance could be $100.</p>
<p>On the downside, immediate support is near the $86.60 level. The next key support is near the $85.00 level. If there is a downside break below the $85.00 support, the price could accelerate lower toward the $80 level in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_78190" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Litecoin.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78190" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78190" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Litecoin.png" alt="Litecoin (LTC) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78190" class="wp-caption-text">Litecoin (LTC) Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Litecoin price is clearly trading below $90 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $92 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LTC/USD is now losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $86.60 and $85.00.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $90.00 and $92.00.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-indicators-point-fresh-increase-to-100/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Indicators Point Fresh Increase To $100</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-indicators-point-fresh-increase-to-100/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Analysts: Bitcoin Will Continue to Benefit from the Banking Crisis</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-bitcoin-will-continue-to-benefit-from-the-banking-crisis/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-bitcoin-will-continue-to-benefit-from-the-banking-crisis/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 17:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[banks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cathie Wood]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77648</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now that 2023 has arrived, bitcoin has found fresh ground following the ongoing banking crisis that has led to the closure of institutions like Silvergate, Silicon Valley Bank, and Signature. Bitcoin Could Do Even Better Many analysts and crypto industry heads believe this banking crisis is going to continue now that Deutsche Bank is at<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-bitcoin-will-continue-to-benefit-from-the-banking-crisis/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-bitcoin-will-continue-to-benefit-from-the-banking-crisis/">Analysts: Bitcoin Will Continue to Benefit from the Banking Crisis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now that 2023 has arrived, bitcoin has <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/03/25/massive-shock-new-bank-crisis-and-300-billion-fed-pump-has-primed-bitcoin-after-huge-crypto-and-ethereum-price-rally/?sh=386a4a0279d2" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">found fresh ground</a> following the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-spikes-following-silicon-valley-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">ongoing banking crisis</a> that has led to the closure of institutions like Silvergate, Silicon Valley Bank, and Signature.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Could Do Even Better</h2>
<p>Many analysts and crypto industry heads believe this banking crisis is going to continue now that Deutsche Bank is at the helm of controversy, and with heavy regulatory issues in play, bitcoin – they believe – could be poised for a solid breakout in the coming weeks and months.</p>
<p>The price of BTC has already risen <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-more-banks-fell-bitcoin-rose-beyond-28k/" data-wpel-link="internal">beyond $28K</a>. That’s about 70 percent higher than where it was at the end of 2022, arguably the worst year on record for bitcoin and many other digital assets. The space lost more than $2 trillion in overall valuation given that assets like BTC shed more than 70 percent of their values. The world’s number one digital currency by market cap was trading at a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit in November of 2021, though roughly 12 months later, the asset had dropped into the mid-$16K range.</p>
<p>Several additional cryptocurrencies, for one reason or another, chose to follow in bitcoin’s footsteps and shed dollars from their prices. It was a sad and ugly sight to see, and many traders lost everything they had, but since the new year began, it looks like everything is starting to turn around.</p>
<p>One of the big reasons for the sudden change is the banking situation in both America and Europe. Cathie Wood of Ark Invest fame commented in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>The behavior of the [bitcoin] price through this crisis is going to attract more institutions. The fact that bitcoin moved in a very different way from the equity markets, in particular, was quite instructive.</p></blockquote>
<p>Macro Hive also threw its two cents into the mix, stating:</p>
<blockquote><p>The banking crisis, which caused the market to price in rate cuts starting in the summer, has had little knock-on effect on crypto (so far).</p></blockquote>
<p>These words followed news that Deutsche Bank experienced a huge dip in its stock share prices over the last few weeks, thus wiping out about one fifth of the bank’s market capitalization.</p>
<h2>The Fed Isn&#8217;t Helping Things</h2>
<p>The situation also isn’t being helped by the Federal Reserve and similar institutions, which continue to hike rates even though the economy is in shambles and nobody can afford homes or cars. Not too long ago, the Fed announced interest <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/federal-reserve-hikes-rates-again-what-will-happen-to-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">rates were going up</a> another 0.25 basis points, and that inflation continues to be a major enemy.</p>
<p>It commented further that despite the state of the country’s banking sector, interest rates would continue to be pushed upward in 2023 unless inflation chose to stop rearing its ugly head. 2023 was initially believed to be a less hostile year in that sense.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-bitcoin-will-continue-to-benefit-from-the-banking-crisis/">Analysts: Bitcoin Will Continue to Benefit from the Banking Crisis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-bitcoin-will-continue-to-benefit-from-the-banking-crisis/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Venezuela Shutting Down All Its Crypto Platforms?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-venezuela-shutting-down-all-its-crypto-exchanges/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-venezuela-shutting-down-all-its-crypto-exchanges/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 15:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Petro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sunacrip]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[venezuela]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77645</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The relationship between Venezuela and crypto has always been a bit wonky, and this month is no exception. The arrest of the nation’s superintendent of crypto assets Joselit Ramirez has caused a huge uproar in the nation, and President Nicolas Maduro has ordered the region to completely upend its digital currency regulatory agency. Venezuela Is<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-venezuela-shutting-down-all-its-crypto-exchanges/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-venezuela-shutting-down-all-its-crypto-exchanges/">Is Venezuela Shutting Down All Its Crypto Platforms?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The relationship between Venezuela and crypto has always been a bit wonky, and this month is no exception. The arrest of the nation’s superintendent of crypto assets Joselit Ramirez has <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/exchanges-mining-farms-shut-down-201542174.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">caused a huge uproar</a> in the nation, and President Nicolas Maduro has ordered the region to completely upend its digital currency regulatory agency.</p>
<h2>Venezuela Is Acting Fishy Regarding Crypto</h2>
<p>Right now, it is widely rumored that all the crypto exchanges that have been established in Venezuela are scheduled to be closed down permanently. The order was reportedly given by Sunacrip, the country’s official crypto regulatory body, and while nothing has been confirmed yet, the National Association of Cryptocurrencies has hinted that such action is indeed occurring within the borders of Venezuela as part of an ongoing anti-corruption case.</p>
<p>Asonacrip president Jose Angel Alvarez explained in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>We believe that private companies should not be blamed for what is happening inside the regulatory body and that we should promote the full activation of all cryptocurrency operations (in the country). We are preparing a list of propositions to be delivered soon to Sunacrip and Dr. Anabel Pereira.</p></blockquote>
<p>The idea that Venezuela – a long-time socialist country – would suddenly be working towards “anti-corruption” is a bit of a laugh. In addition, it’s odd that the nation is suddenly so anti-crypto given its history <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/petro/" data-wpel-link="internal">with the Petro</a>, an oil-backed digital asset that the country worked very hard to market, promote, and sell about four to five years ago. Several lies are alleged to have swirled around the digital asset, and it’s unclear, exactly, how many units were sold, bought, or traded when it was at its peak.</p>
<p>Alvarez went on to say that a week prior to the investigation’s start, all crypto mining farms in regions such as Carabobo were told they had to cease their operations. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Indeed, at the beginning of the week in the state of Carabobo, all the farms were ordered to stop, which concerns us as a community since some affiliates are being affected by the measure.</p></blockquote>
<p>He was highly confused and concerned by this as he believes many of the mining facilities in the country had obtained the required permits and were fully compliant with present Venezuelan laws:</p>
<blockquote><p>We believe that although there is a situation in the superintendency, it should not affect the operations of all affiliated farms at the regional level.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Is All This Even Real?</h2>
<p>By contrast, Eleazar Colmenares – the CEO of Crypto Buyer in Venezuela – has unleashed a statement claiming Sunacrip hasn’t ordered the closure of any crypto exchanges, so it’s hard to know who’s telling the truth. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We want to clarify that the announcement made yesterday on our social media refers to the temporary non-operation of our crypto-fiat gateway service due to the transition process carried out by the competent authorities.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-venezuela-shutting-down-all-its-crypto-exchanges/">Is Venezuela Shutting Down All Its Crypto Platforms?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-venezuela-shutting-down-all-its-crypto-exchanges/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Banks in Germany Will Now Sell and Buy BTC</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/banks-in-germany-will-now-sell-and-buy-btc/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/banks-in-germany-will-now-sell-and-buy-btc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 13:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DWP Bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gemany]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77642</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new platform known as DWP Bank in Europe has been unveiled. Its purpose? To give roughly 1,200 banks in Germany access to bitcoin and digital currencies. Germany and Crypto Will Soon Go Hand in Hand The banking crisis that’s affecting America at the time of writing is not just happening in the U.S. it’s<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/banks-in-germany-will-now-sell-and-buy-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/banks-in-germany-will-now-sell-and-buy-btc/">Banks in Germany Will Now Sell and Buy BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new platform known as DWP Bank in Europe has been unveiled. Its purpose? To give roughly 1,200 banks in Germany access to <a href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/german-banks-access-bitcoin-trading-platform-124626025.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">bitcoin and digital currencies</a>.</p>
<h2>Germany and Crypto Will Soon Go Hand in Hand</h2>
<p>The banking crisis that’s affecting America at the time of writing is not just happening in the U.S. it’s spread 3,000 miles across the Atlantic and is also causing problems for Europe. Look, for example, at <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-more-banks-fell-bitcoin-rose-beyond-28k/" data-wpel-link="internal">Credit Suisse</a>. The enterprise was in serious trouble until UBS decided it had what it took to bail the institution out. Anyone who thinks we aren’t in a recession needs to look up the definition of “recession” and confirm with themselves that things aren’t as great as they might seem.</p>
<p>So, the idea that countries like Germany suddenly want to get their hands on bitcoin and other digital assets is a sign that perhaps banks aren’t as stable as we’ve all been led to believe, and thus they want to bring in bitcoin and other alternative assets to avoid the “stability” of fiat currencies and the institutions that have since failed them.</p>
<p>DWP Bank will now allow all the banks in Germany connected to its platform to purchase and sell BTC units while still carrying out standard online banking activities. In a statement, DWP Bank said:</p>
<blockquote><p>DWP Bank wants to connect the world of traditional securities business with the world of trading digital assets. To this end, it uses its central position in the German financial market with established interfaces to around 1,200 banks and savings banks and expands its portfolio to include trading and safekeeping of new assets.</p></blockquote>
<p>CEO of the company Heiko Beck also threw his two cents into the mix, claiming that the bank is planning to expand its crypto offerings and services in the coming future. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Digitized assets will become increasingly important in the future. That is why we are expanding our range of services in this area and focusing our portfolio more closely on the future opportunities that arise here.</p></blockquote>
<p>The new platform has already been tested out by MLP Banking AG, a client of DWP Bank. Head of account and securities settlement with MLP Paul Utzat said:</p>
<blockquote><p>In our MLP client portal, it is a logical addition to the existing wealth management offering.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Is the Banking Situation Getting Worse?</h2>
<p>The banking problems in America have caused three separate institutions (Silvergate, Silicon Valley, and Signature) to shutter their doors permanently. This has largely to do with the heightened interest rates of 2022 and the crypto ties these banks were alleged to boast. As we all remember, many assets saw their prices crash and burn during the months of the previous year.</p>
<p>Germany has been named one of the most crypto-friendly countries in Europe along with Switzerland, which is home to Crypto Valley.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/banks-in-germany-will-now-sell-and-buy-btc/">Banks in Germany Will Now Sell and Buy BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/banks-in-germany-will-now-sell-and-buy-btc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Bullish Break Signals More Gains</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bullish-break-signals-more-gains/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bullish-break-signals-more-gains/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 05:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78179</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tron price started a fresh increase from the $0.0670 level against the US Dollar. TRX price is now trading above $0.0680 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.0685 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could continue to move<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bullish-break-signals-more-gains/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bullish-break-signals-more-gains/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Bullish Break Signals More Gains</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Tron price started a fresh increase from the $0.0670 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>TRX price is now trading above $0.0680 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.0685 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move up if it breaks the $0.070 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>TRON price started a fresh increase above $0.0685 against the US Dollar, outperforming <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-extend-losses-below-27000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. TRX’s price could rise further if it clears the $0.070 resistance.</em></p>
<h2>Tron Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few sessions, Tron price started a decent increase from the $0.0672 support zone against the US Dollar. TRX’s price remained well-bid and was able to climb above the $0.0685 zone.</p>
<p>It traded above the $0.0690 and $0.0692 levels to move further into a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bulls-aim-for-key-bullish-break/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">positive zone</a>. A high is formed near $0.0699 and the price is now consolidating gains. It is trading above $0.0680 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, TRX is facing resistance near the $0.0695 level.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $0.070 level. A close above $0.070 could send the price toward the $0.0725 resistance zone. Any more gains might send TRX price toward $0.075, above which the price could even rise toward $0.080.</p>
<p>On the downside, initial support is near the $0.0685 level. There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.0685 on the 4-hours chart. The trend line is close to the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.0640 swing low to the $0.0699 high.</p>
<p>The next major support is now forming near $0.0670 or the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.0640 swing low to the $0.0699 high.</p>
<p>If there is a downside break below the $0.0670 support, the price might revisit the $0.064 support. Any more losses might call for a move toward the $0.0625 zone in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_78180" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/TRON-TRX.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78180" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78180" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/TRON-TRX.png" alt="Tron (TRX) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78180" class="wp-caption-text">Tron (TRX) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/TRXUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that TRX’s price is now trading above $0.0685 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move up if it breaks the $0.070 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for TRX/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for TRX/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.0685 and $0.0670.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.0695, $0.070, and $0.0725.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bullish-break-signals-more-gains/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Bullish Break Signals More Gains</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bullish-break-signals-more-gains/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
