<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 04:52:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/cropped-fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Why 2023 Has Been a Turnaround Year for Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/why-2023-has-been-a-turnaround-year-for-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 15:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brandon Zemp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79126</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>2023 has been a year of great turnaround for bitcoin and analysts are wondering why. Bitcoin Has Seen a Lot of Change This Year For one thing, it appears macroeconomic conditions have loosened up somewhat. While many financial experts still see an economic downturn happening towards the end of the year, talks of a recession [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/why-2023-has-been-a-turnaround-year-for-bitcoin/">Why 2023 Has Been a Turnaround Year for Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>2023 has been a year of great turnaround for bitcoin and <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-bounces-back-cryptocurrency-rebounds-after-rough-2022/ar-AA1dk1wD">analysts are wondering</a> why.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Has Seen a Lot of Change This Year</h2>
<p>For one thing, it appears macroeconomic conditions have loosened up somewhat. While many financial experts still see an economic downturn happening towards the end of the year, talks of a recession of somewhat subsided. Still, things are shaky enough (with <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-provide-their-thoughts-on-latest-bitcoin-rally/">bank failures</a> and what not) that people have looked to bitcoin and similar assets as “safe havens” through which they can funnel their money and keep their investments safe.</p>
<p>Crypto expert Brandon Zemp explained also that while some regulatory issues have arisen in the U.S., the markets around the world have eased up when it comes to crypto, thus helping the industry grow at least from an international perspective. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think most of the prior price action bitcoin has had in the past has come largely from the United States, and for the first time, I think you’re seeing a lot of that price action start to happen outside of the United States.</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition, there’s also been a lot of interest stemming from Wall Street players <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blackrock-etf-application-causes-btc-eth-to-surge/">such as BlackRock</a>, which recently filed a bitcoin ETF application with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). While the company had its application initially turned away for <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sends-blackrock-btc-etf-application-back-for-revisions/">not being comprehensive</a> enough, the firm is now looking to revamp the application and resubmit it to the financial agency for a new opinion.</p>
<p>Konstantin Shulga – CEO and co-founder of Finery Markets – said this has to do with the public still showing massive interest in BTC even though it bombed hard last year. Shulga said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The world of cryptocurrency has been facing a lot of uncertainty in the U.S. market due to regulatory issues. However, despite these challenges, institutions have still been showing interest in it as an asset class. It seems that the adoption of cryptocurrency is slowly but surely taking place.</p></blockquote>
<p>Still, Shulga thinks that the regulatory scene in the U.S. is going to be quite stringent, and thus it may take at least a few attempts from BlackRock and similar companies to get the attention of the SEC. Shulga said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Despite numerous attempts, not a single application for a spot [exchange-traded fund] has received the green light from the SEC so far. The biggest question now is whether BlackRock&#8217;s filing will meet a different fate than previous proposals from companies like Fidelity or CBOE Global Markets, which were met with rejection(s).</p></blockquote>
<h2>More Growth Coming?</h2>
<p>Zemp anticipates bitcoin will continue to grow through the rest of the year, stating:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think what will end up happening for bitcoin is we’ll see this continue to rise. Bitcoin could go to $35,000, $40,000, [or] $45,000 potentially. It will get closer and closer to its previous all-time high.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/why-2023-has-been-a-turnaround-year-for-bitcoin/">Why 2023 Has Been a Turnaround Year for Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Suisse Sees Big Things Happening for Crypto Soon</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-suisse-sees-big-things-happening-for-crypto-soon/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 13:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Suisse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dirk Klee]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79123</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto firm Bitcoin Suisse is confident another big bull rally is coming for bitcoin, and it wants to be prepared. It’s now reinventing itself as the ultimate “crypto asset manager” and trying to market its services to high-net-worth individuals that have a lot of digital currency to their names. Bitcoin Suisse Sees a Huge Rally [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-suisse-sees-big-things-happening-for-crypto-soon/">Bitcoin Suisse Sees Big Things Happening for Crypto Soon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto firm Bitcoin Suisse is confident <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/07/01/bitcoin-suisse-ceo-the-next-bull-market-is-coming-and-we-will-be-ready/?sh=3520585e3e8b">another big bull rally</a> is coming for bitcoin, and it wants to be prepared. It’s now reinventing itself as the ultimate “crypto asset manager” and trying to market its services to high-net-worth individuals that have a lot of digital currency to their names.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Suisse Sees a Huge Rally Coming</h2>
<p>Banking veteran and chief executive of Bitcoin Suisse Dirk Klee said in a recent interview that the recent washout of bad actors – including names like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/">FTX</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block-fi-is-the-latest-crypto-company-to-go-bankrupt/">Block Fi</a> – has cleaned the crypto house and paved the way for a bright and illustrious future. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Institutional players [need] to be safe places. So, on the back of the eruptions that we&#8217;ve seen in 2022, institutions have sharpened their focus on how to do proper risk management; who are the trusted partners; how deep do I have to go into technical details to understand the dynamics. With FTX, all the problems were traditional finance problems: misappropriation of client funds; no proper risk management; trading against client interests and so forth. Basic institutional standards were not being met. So, I think now, institutions want to go deeper. They want to do proper due diligence. They want to fully understand how [crypto companies] work; what we deliver; how we’re set up; are we safe, and that&#8217;s a good thing. There was hype in 2021. The market was getting ahead of itself, and the weaknesses of some players were exposed. I believe the washout is a healthy development.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also believes that bitcoin has been through the mill and is likely to experience steady growth over the coming years and be less vulnerable to volatility. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Regulators have really stepped into this space. They’re providing safe rail guards for wider adoption and access to crypto, and the other thing is that some months ago, [western economies] left a 30-year cycle of lowering interest rates and cheap money pouring into the next higher-risk asset class… That money is no longer available. Investing is getting tougher for companies in this industry, and we [need] to prove that we have a sound business model. The actors are becoming sounder on the back of better risk management, hopefully, and the use-cases of the protocols are becoming clearer. The protocols also [need] to prove that they are delivering value. The hype and the money that flew into the hype has stopped. Now it gets real.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Why is BTC not Real Money Yet?</h2>
<p>Bitcoin Suisse also wants to see a day where bitcoin is looked at as real, valid money and it’s used to pay for everyday items. Klee stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>The notion of bitcoin as a means of payment for smaller transactions has not come true. It has not evolved for everyday use like buying a coffee at Starbucks.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-suisse-sees-big-things-happening-for-crypto-soon/">Bitcoin Suisse Sees Big Things Happening for Crypto Soon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Faces Uphill Task Near $0.145</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-faces-uphill-task-near-0-145/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 06:08:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar Lumens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79744</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stellar lumen price is struggling below the $0.150 resistance zone against the US Dollar. XLM price is now trading below $0.150 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.140 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could start a fresh [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-faces-uphill-task-near-0-145/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Faces Uphill Task Near $0.145</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Stellar lumen price is struggling below the $0.150 resistance zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>XLM price is now trading below $0.150 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.140 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a fresh increase if it clears the $0.1420 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Stellar lumen price is trading below $0.150 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. XLM price could extend losses if it trades below the $0.132 support.</em></p>
<h2>Stellar Lumen Price Analysis (XLM to USD)</h2>
<p>After a sharp decline below $0.165, Stellar Lumen price moved into a bearish zone against the US Dollar. The XLM/USD pair traded below the $0.150 level.</p>
<p>There was also a spike below the $0.135 support zone. A low was formed near $0.1332 and the price is now consolidating losses. There was a move above the $0.135 and $0.138 levels. The price climbed above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.1719 swing high to the $0.1332 low.</p>
<p>However, the bears were active near the $0.145 zone. XLM is now trading below $0.150 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-aims-fresh-increase-to-0-18/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.140 on the 4-hour chart.</p>
<p>The next key resistance is seen near the $0.142 level. A clear upside break above the $0.142 zone might send the price toward $0.150. Any more gains could lead the price toward the $0.1520 level or even 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.1719 swing high to the $0.1332 low.</p>
<p>Initial support on the downside is near the $0.132 level. The next major support is near the $0.1250 zone. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.1120 level in the near term, below which the price might even retest $0.1050. The next major support is near $0.10.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79745" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79745" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Stellar-Lumen-XLM.png"><img decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" class="size-full wp-image-79745" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Stellar-Lumen-XLM.png" alt="Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price" width="1835" height="839" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Stellar-Lumen-XLM.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-600x274.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-1100x503.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-768x351.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-750x343.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79745" class="wp-caption-text">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XLMUSD/">chart</a> indicates that XLM price is now trading below $0.145 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start a fresh increase if it clears the $0.1420 resistance.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XLM/USD is gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for XLM/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.132 and $0.125.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.1420, $0.1450, and $0.1520.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-faces-uphill-task-near-0-145/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Faces Uphill Task Near $0.145</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Price Analysis: Key Barrier Sits at $0.68</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-key-barrier-sits-at-0-68/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 04:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79741</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple price is facing resistance near the $0.680 level against the US dollar. The price is now trading near $0.625 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.635 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Kraken). The pair could [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-key-barrier-sits-at-0-68/">Ripple Price Analysis: Key Barrier Sits at $0.68</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ripple price is facing resistance near the $0.680 level against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading near $0.625 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.635 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start another decline if it stays below $0.665 and $0.680.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ripple price is struggling below $0.665 against the US Dollar, unlike <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. XRP price must stay above the $0.620 support to start a recovery wave.</em></p>
<h2>Ripple Price Analysis</h2>
<p>After struggling to stay above $0.680, Ripple price started a fresh decline against the US Dollar. The XRP/USD pair gained bearish momentum below the 0.665 support zone.</p>
<p>The bears were able to push the price below the $0.62 support. A low was formed near $0.5926 and the pair is now attempting a recovery wave. There was a test of the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.7346 swing high to the $0.5926 low.</p>
<p>The price is now trading near $0.625 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-could-resume-slide-below-0-62/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.635 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near $0.635. The next major resistance is near the $0.665 level. A clear move above the $0.665 resistance zone might start a steady increase. In the stated case, the price could test the $0.680 resistance.</p>
<p>The 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.7346 swing high to the $0.5926 low is near $0.680 to act as a barrier. Any more gains might send the price toward the $0.720 resistance.</p>
<p>Initial support on the downside is near the $0.620 level. The next major support is near the $0.600 level, below which the price could accelerate lower toward the $0.5850 support. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.550 level.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79742" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79742" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Ripple-1.png"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-79742" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Ripple-1.png" alt="Ripple Price" width="1835" height="839" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Ripple-1.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Ripple-1-600x274.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Ripple-1-1100x503.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Ripple-1-768x351.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Ripple-1-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Ripple-1-750x343.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Ripple-1-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79742" class="wp-caption-text">Ripple Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/">chart</a>, Ripple price is now trading near the $0.625 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start another decline if it stays below $0.665 and $0.680.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XRP/USD is now losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for XRP/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.620, $0.600, and $0.585.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.665 and $0.680.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-key-barrier-sits-at-0-68/">Ripple Price Analysis: Key Barrier Sits at $0.68</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Sends BlackRock BTC ETF Application Back for Revisions</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sends-blackrock-btc-etf-application-back-for-revisions/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 17:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79006</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The price of bitcoin fell as much as five percent at the end of June and briefly dipped below $30K (where it had been for the past few weeks) before rebounding. The reason? The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) decided to pass up on the present versions of the BlackRock and Fidelity bitcoin-based exchange-traded fund [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sends-blackrock-btc-etf-application-back-for-revisions/">SEC Sends BlackRock BTC ETF Application Back for Revisions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price of bitcoin fell as much as five percent at <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/bitcoin-price-sec-says-spot-etf-applications-blackrock-fidelity-inadequate-2023-6">the end of June and briefly</a> dipped below $30K (where it had been for the past few weeks) before rebounding. The reason? The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) decided to pass up on the present versions of the BlackRock and Fidelity bitcoin-based exchange-traded fund (ETF) applications.</p>
<h2>The SEC is Again Disapproving a Bitcoin ETF</h2>
<p>The news might seem rough at first, though there’s still room to get things moving in the right direction. The SEC did not flat out reject the applications like it normally does. Rather, it described them as “inadequate,” and said that if the issuing companies were willing to make necessary changes, the applications would be reconsidered.</p>
<p>This opens a door of hope not just for both firms, but for the crypto industry. For too long, people have been waiting for a day in which a crypto-based ETF comes to market, and for the past several years, many companies have tried to make <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/perianne-boring-the-sec-needs-to-approve-a-btc-etf/">that dream come alive</a>.</p>
<p>However, the SEC has been rather stringent when it comes to crypto applications like these. It often says “no” <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-issues-another-no-to-van-ecks-bitcoin-etf/">straight away</a>, and when it doesn’t, the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/valkyrie-bitcoin-etf-decision-delayed-until-january/">delays set in</a>… So much so, that many companies have simply withdrawn their applications before the financial agency even has a chance to look at them.</p>
<p>The SEC claims that both BlackRock and Fidelity have very strong histories to them, which is why it’s allegedly willing to reconsider new applications. However, you can’t help but wonder – given the agency’s background and track record – if this is just a method of buying time or drawing things out to the extent that it usually does.</p>
<p>The SEC has shown repeatedly it’s at war with the crypto industry. Gary Gensler and the lackies he surrounds himself with have gone after crypto companies both large and small. They don’t care about their reputations or how long they’ve been in business. Companies like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sues-binance-alleges-selling-of-illegal-securities/">Binance</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-hit-with-sec-lawsuit-says-it-operated-as-an-exchange-broker/">Coinbase</a> – two of the largest digital currency firms around today – are feeling the wrath of the agency, and it’s become something of a joke in recent days that nobody is safe, regardless of how powerful or experienced they might appear.</p>
<p>One of the most domineering crypto-based <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/">lawsuits initiated by the SEC</a> was brought against Kraken. The firm was forced to pay $30 million in penalties. It was also made to cease all its crypto staking services and activities.</p>
<h2>Should We Calm Down?</h2>
<p>Chris Martin – head of research at Amber Data – believes that the present reaction to the SEC’s ruling is “overblown.” He commented that bullish <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-slips-after-sec-reportedly-calls-etf-filings-inadequate-but-still-heads-for-a-winning-month/ar-AA1dg7ri">signs still exist for many</a> digital assets and said:</p>
<blockquote><p>These tokens each have their own nuance and different reasons, but it&#8217;s reasonable to expect that market confusion is leading some to move into higher risk appetites.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sends-blackrock-btc-etf-application-back-for-revisions/">SEC Sends BlackRock BTC ETF Application Back for Revisions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Peter Schiff: Crypto Only Works if It&#8217;s Backed by Gold</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/peter-schiff-crypto-only-works-if-its-backed-by-gold/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 15:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gold]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peter Schiff]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79004</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Peter Schiff is not entirely for crypto, nor is he entirely for gold. Rather, he’s for a combination of the two. In other words, the big financial answer to everybody’s problems is gold-backed crypto stationed on the blockchain. Peter Schiff on Gold and Crypto Schiff said in a recent interview that blockchain could make precious [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/peter-schiff-crypto-only-works-if-its-backed-by-gold/">Peter Schiff: Crypto Only Works if It&#8217;s Backed by Gold</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Peter Schiff is not entirely for crypto, nor is he entirely for <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/gold/">gold</a>. Rather, he’s for a combination of the two. In other words, the big financial answer to everybody’s problems <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/bitcoin-gold-us-dollar-inflation-peter-schiff-095712032.html">is gold-backed crypto</a> stationed on the blockchain.</p>
<h2>Peter Schiff on Gold and Crypto</h2>
<p>Schiff said in a recent interview that blockchain could make precious metals even stronger than they are presently. He’s not exactly a bitcoin fan, going so far as to say that bitcoin (by itself) is nothing but a Ponzi scheme. He stated boldly:</p>
<blockquote><p>It will have a hard time even making a new high, and if it does make a new high, even getting to $100,000 is going to be a stretch, which only equates to four times your money.</p></blockquote>
<p>He did, however, comment that he doesn’t think gold ever loses its value, and if it does, it’s during very rare occasions. He thus commented that crypto could work so long as it had gold supporting it. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We don&#8217;t have to ignore blockchain technology. We can use it to improve the divisibility and the portability of gold and make it an even better monetary instrument than it was in the past… With the internet, with blockchain, there is a major improvement in the functionality of gold to act as a medium of exchange and as a unit of account.</p></blockquote>
<p>During the conversation, Schiff also claimed that the gold standard has been in place since 1971 for a reason. He believes the world is on the brink of financial collapse and the U.S. dollar has been suffering for quite some time. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Gold was the legitimate currency which we had at one point, but fiat currency is backed by nothing. Bitcoin is also backed by nothing, and it is kind of like a fiat cryptocurrency, but if you have a cryptocurrency that is backed by something of value, such as gold, then you have something legitimate that I think could work. I think that is the future.</p></blockquote>
<p>Even though bitcoin has been in high demand as of late due to inflation and other economic factors, he thinks this is a big mistake due to his belief that bitcoin (and many other cryptos) hold no inherent value. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>The demand for bitcoin is based on the belief that you can sell it to somebody else at a higher price, and the only reason that the other person is willing to pay a higher price is because he believes that he can sell it to someone for an even higher price.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Don&#8217;t Invest too Much</h2>
<p>He also issued a word of caution to whales, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>A lot of people that got into bitcoin years ago need to take some chips off the table. You can&#8217;t be overly exposed to bitcoin.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/peter-schiff-crypto-only-works-if-its-backed-by-gold/">Peter Schiff: Crypto Only Works if It&#8217;s Backed by Gold</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Steven Goldfeder: Blockchains Shouldn&#8217;t Try to Outdo Ethereum</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/steven-goldfeder-blockchains-shouldnt-try-to-outdo-ethereum/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 13:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitrum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Steven Goldfeder]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79002</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Steven Goldfeder of Arbitrum said in a recent interview he thinks it’s a mistake for blockchains to try and compete with Ethereum. Steven Goldfeder on What&#8217;s Coming for Blockchain Ethereum is the most popular network around. However, its high gas fees and slow speeds in the past have given rise to several Layer-2 blockchain networks [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/steven-goldfeder-blockchains-shouldnt-try-to-outdo-ethereum/">Steven Goldfeder: Blockchains Shouldn&#8217;t Try to Outdo Ethereum</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Steven Goldfeder of Arbitrum said in a recent <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/crypto-ceo-says-that-competing-with-ethereum-is-a-bad-idea/ar-AA1dgc2J">interview he thinks</a> it’s a mistake for blockchains to try and compete with <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ethereum/">Ethereum</a>.</p>
<h2>Steven Goldfeder on What&#8217;s Coming for Blockchain</h2>
<p>Ethereum is the most popular network around. However, its high gas fees and slow speeds in the past have given rise to several Layer-2 blockchain networks that have sought to complement it or aid it along. They realize it’s too big for them to compete with, and they seek to enhance its stability so they can garner solid pieces of the digital pie.</p>
<p>Discussing the differences between Layer-1 and Layer-2 blockchains built atop Ethereum, Goldfeder said:</p>
<blockquote><p>When it comes to Arbitrum and Layer-2s versus the alternative Layer-1s, the big differentiator is Layer-2s are part of Ethereum. They’re not competitive with Ethereum. The Layer-1s are generally competitive. I have no issue with technical experimentation, and different Layer-1s make different trade-offs when it comes to some of these core properties like security, decentralization, and scalability, and how they try to achieve that.</p></blockquote>
<p>Goldfeder also said that there really only  needs to be one node on Arbitrum that’s honest for the system to work. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>In a protocol like Ethereum, the nodes are always actively participating. They&#8217;re all trying to make blocks and you can see this running on the network. At Arbitrum, the way it works is one node goes ahead and posts something. Then, there&#8217;s a period where anyone can challenge a transaction before it becomes final.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also discussed the differences between ZK rollups and optimistic rollups, and explained why he chose to use the latter for Arbitrum:</p>
<blockquote><p>The core differences between ZK and optimistic rollups are how they do the proof of a transaction’s validity. What our members do is take all these transactions off-chain, and then they send the results back to Ethereum in an efficient data structure. That&#8217;s how they scale and get the correctness. ZK rollups give us what’s called validity proof. They say, ‘I’m going to prove to you that those transactions are accurate right here.’ Optimistic rollups do what [are] called fraud proof[s], which is [when] they say, ‘Okay, these are the transactions, these are the results. I&#8217;m not giving you proof. Optimistically, just accept my work, but if someone challenges me, that&#8217;s when the proof mechanism happens.’ So, that&#8217;s the difference between the two.</p></blockquote>
<h2>What&#8217;s Next for the Company?</h2>
<p>On how the ETH Merge could affect Arbitrum, he said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Our team is very integrated in Layer-1 development. That includes Ethereum improvement proposal 4844 (which will help the network scale), and there are some synergies that we can explore. I think that EIP-4844 is going to be very important to lowering our costs even more significantly. I think that we&#8217;re going to see a continued migration to Layer-2 technologies.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/steven-goldfeder-blockchains-shouldnt-try-to-outdo-ethereum/">Steven Goldfeder: Blockchains Shouldn&#8217;t Try to Outdo Ethereum</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ratan Tata is Clearly not a BTC Fan</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ratan-tata-is-clearly-not-a-btc-fan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 17:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ratan tata]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warren Buffett]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78997</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>While bitcoin has undoubtedly garnered huge legions of fans over the years, there are several individuals that still fall into the “hater” category. People like Warren Buffett and Charlie Munger check the “hater” box when it comes to bitcoin sentiment, and now, Ratan Tata – one of the world’s wealthiest people – is going to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ratan-tata-is-clearly-not-a-btc-fan/">Ratan Tata is Clearly not a BTC Fan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While bitcoin has undoubtedly garnered huge legions of fans over the years, there are several individuals that still fall into the “hater” category. People like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/warren-buffett-continues-to-hate-on-bitcoin/">Warren Buffett</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/charlie-munger-is-still-one-of-btcs-biggest-haters/">Charlie Munger</a> check the “hater” box when it comes to bitcoin sentiment, and now, Ratan Tata – one of the world’s wealthiest people – is <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-in/news/world/cryptocurrency-is-a-scam-have-zero-ties-to-the-industry-says-ratan-tata/ar-AA1dcXME">going to join them</a>.</p>
<h2>Ratan Tata Doesn&#8217;t Hold Any Ties to Crypto</h2>
<p>Tata recently gave an interview about why he doesn’t care for bitcoin and why he doesn’t see it as having any value. As the chairman of the Tata Group, he recently commented that he bears not ties to crypto. He also told his followers and listeners to remain aware of the endless dangers that seemingly surround crypto, and he warned them to think twice before getting involved in an industry that has allegedly caused so much pain.</p>
<p>He also mentioned that there have been several articles and marketing materials out there that have tied him to digital assets. He said these are all false and shouldn’t be taken seriously if seen. Discussing these phony ties, Satnam Narang – cyber security expert and senior staff research engineer at Tenable – said:</p>
<blockquote><p>It’s extremely common for scammers to fake articles and social media posts from well-known individuals, such as CEOs, business executives, or notable individuals with ties to industries such as finance and cryptocurrency. Mr. Ratan Tata highlighted an example of a fraudulent article discussing a fake ‘wealth loophole,’ which is a timely reminder that is one of the most reliable tools in the scammers’ toolbox.</p></blockquote>
<p>He further stated that people need to be aware of ongoing online scams and material that may not be entirely trustworthy. These kinds of tactics usually occur through unverified YouTube channels or other social media outlets. Narang said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Scammers will leverage the existing audio and video footage of these individuals to craft convincing deep fake footage, whereby these individuals talk of alternative investment opportunities including into cryptocurrencies. Users should be extremely skeptical of posts they see promoted on social media and video footage circulating on sites like YouTube.</p></blockquote>
<h2>So Many Mixed Emotions!</h2>
<p>Several digital platforms and social media companies – like WhatsApp of Facebook fame – are now looking to fight back. WhatsApp recently introduced the ability to silence unknown numbers. In addition, the company has put out a statement telling people to be cautious should they receive job offers or related inquiries through the WhatsApp platform, as taking part or falling for such tactics could result in heavy financial losses.</p>
<p>Many of the world’s wealthiest people are not privy to bitcoin, nor do they have terribly positive things to say about it. Warren Buffett, for example, has referred to BTC as “rat poison squared” in the past, though there are others – like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-says-charlie-munger-needs-more-time-with-btc/">Michael Saylor</a> – that swear by the asset.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ratan-tata-is-clearly-not-a-btc-fan/">Ratan Tata is Clearly not a BTC Fan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lawmakers in Canada Are Seriously Looking at Crypto Regulation</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lawmakers-in-canada-are-seriously-looking-at-crypto-regulation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 15:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[canada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto-regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United Kingdom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78995</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A group of lawmakers in Canada is calling for full-on regulation of the crypto industry. Will Canada Regulate Crypto? In a recent report, the lawmakers wrote: While many emphasized Canada’s strong regulatory safeguards, such as provincial securities regulation and federal anti-money laundering and anti-terrorism financing obligations, witnesses stated that governments need to partner with industry [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lawmakers-in-canada-are-seriously-looking-at-crypto-regulation/">Lawmakers in Canada Are Seriously Looking at Crypto Regulation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A group of lawmakers in Canada is calling for full-on <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/canadian-lawmakers-call-for-national-blockchain-crypto-strategy/ar-AA1ddcZa">regulation of the crypto</a> industry.</p>
<h2>Will Canada Regulate Crypto?</h2>
<p>In a recent report, the lawmakers wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>While many emphasized Canada’s strong regulatory safeguards, such as provincial securities regulation and federal anti-money laundering and anti-terrorism financing obligations, witnesses stated that governments need to partner with industry to better understand this rapidly evolving sector and enact regulations that protect consumers without unnecessarily hindering innovation.</p></blockquote>
<p>The situation is an interesting one for many reasons, a big one being that as it stands, Canada’s present regulatory structure pertaining to crypto is considered quite stringent. So stringent, in fact, that several companies working in the blockchain or crypto industries have packed up and left for greener pastures.</p>
<p>It’s likely Canada doesn’t like the idea of losing business or revenue. It’s now potentially looking to create simpler rules or “softer” situations for crypto companies so they can call Canada home with ease.</p>
<p>Putting this aside, though, Canada is likely falling into the same patterns that nations like the United Kingdom have fallen into. The U.K. recently put out <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/european-union-passes-heavy-string-of-new-crypto-regulations/">the most comprehensive</a> string of crypto regulations that any nation has witnessed, and the regulations are earning widespread praise for the verbiage they used and for the fact that they embrace so many different aspects of the industry.</p>
<p>These regulations came about not long after the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/">FTX fiasco</a>, and it became clear that the U.K. didn’t want its people falling for the same garbage tactics utilized by the defunct exchange. Thus, measures needed to be put in place so traders (who were likely going to play in the crypto arena regardless of what rules existed) could stay safe and secure in their investments.</p>
<p>Canada is now likely looking to do the same thing. It’s also home of the “FTX before FTX” in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/quadriga-cx/">Quadriga CX</a>, which was the subject of controversy a few years back when its head executive allegedly passed away abroad and nobody back home had the data necessary to access the exchange’s accounts, all of which together held more than $100 million in crypto.</p>
<h2>Could the U.S. Fall Further Behind?</h2>
<p>If Canada indeed follows through on potential crypto legislation, however, the country will be yet another one to beat the U.S., which has often been a huge financial and technological leader in the past. When it comes to crypto regulation, though, the region has fallen behind.</p>
<p>This has largely <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/republicans-arent-happy-with-the-sec-and-gary-genslers-approach-to-crypto-regulation/">to do with Gary Gensler</a> (the head of the SEC) and his tactics of “regulation through enforcement.” Rather than try to carve out laws and help establish the legal arena behind crypto, he’s simply going after crypto companies whenever he can – both big and small – to make a point and strike fear into the hearts of digital currency fans.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lawmakers-in-canada-are-seriously-looking-at-crypto-regulation/">Lawmakers in Canada Are Seriously Looking at Crypto Regulation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
