<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 03:08:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Face Uphill Task Near $92</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-face-uphill-task-near-92/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-face-uphill-task-near-92/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 03:18:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78105</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin started a fresh decline below the $92 zone against the US Dollar. LTC price is now trading below $92 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break below a key rising channel with support near $96 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-face-uphill-task-near-92/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-face-uphill-task-near-92/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Face Uphill Task Near $92</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Litecoin started a fresh decline below the $92 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>LTC price is now trading below $92 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break below a key rising channel with support near $96 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it stays below the $92 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Litecoin price is struggling below $92 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-29250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. LTC price could continue to decline if it stays below the $92 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past 2-3 sessions, there were swing moves in Bitcoin, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-revisits-key-support-but-struggles/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Ethereum</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-turns-red-below-0-50/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Ripple</a>, and Litecoin against the US Dollar. Earlier, LTC started a fresh decline from the $104 zone.</p>
<p>There was a clear move below the $100 and $98 support levels. Besides, there was a break below a key rising channel with support near $96 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair. The pair even broke the $92 support and tested the $84 zone.</p>
<p>A low is formed near $84.21 and the price is now rising. There was a move above the 50% % Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $94.01 swing high to the $84.21 low.</p>
<p>It is now trading below $92 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $90.50 zone. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $94.01 swing high to the $84.21 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance sits near the $92 level. The main resistance is near the $94 level. A clear move above the $94 level could pump the price toward the $98 level or even $100. The next major resistance could be $105.</p>
<p>On the downside, immediate support is near the $86.50 level. The next key support is near the $84.20 level. If there is a downside break below the $84.20 support, the price could accelerate lower toward the $80 level in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_78106" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/04/Litecoin-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78106" class="size-full wp-image-78106" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/04/Litecoin-3.png" alt="Litecoin (LTC) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78106" class="wp-caption-text">Litecoin (LTC) Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Litecoin price is clearly trading below $92 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $92 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LTC/USD is now losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $86.50 and $84.20.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $90.50 and $92.00.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-face-uphill-task-near-92/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Face Uphill Task Near $92</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-face-uphill-task-near-92/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The SEC Targets Tron in Latest Crypto Case</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-targets-tron-in-latest-crypto-case/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-targets-tron-in-latest-crypto-case/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 17:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Justin Sun]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77573</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is going after Justin Sun of Tron fame and a wide array of celebrities he hired to at one point, serve either as promoters or brand ambassadors for the company. The SEC Is Going After Tron At the time of writing, securities fraud charges have been filed against Tron,<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-targets-tron-in-latest-crypto-case/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-targets-tron-in-latest-crypto-case/">The SEC Targets Tron in Latest Crypto Case</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is going after Justin Sun of Tron <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/03/22/sec-hits-jake-paul-lindsey-lohan-justin-sun-with-crypto-violations.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">fame and a wide array</a> of celebrities he hired to at one point, serve either as promoters or brand ambassadors for the company.</p>
<h2>The SEC Is Going After Tron</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, securities fraud charges have been filed against Tron, the famed crypto company. In addition, several well-known figures – including musician Lindsay Lohan and internet personality Jake Paul – have been caught up in the case. The agency alleges that Sun engaged in fraud by manipulating the activity of various tokens. He thus created the image that valid and real trading was occurring when, in fact, it was not.</p>
<p>The company is also under the SEC’s gaze for taking part in an unregistered token offering. SEC chair Gary Gensler commented in a recent statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>This case demonstrates again the high-risk investors face when crypto asset securities are offered and sold without proper disclosure.</p></blockquote>
<p>Right now, the tokens that are alleged to have been part of Sun’s “infamous” scheme are TRX and BTT. Gensler continued his statement by commenting that Sun orchestrated a “promotional campaign in which he and his celebrity promoters hid the fact that the celebrities were paid for their tweet[s].&#8221;</p>
<p>This is something we have seen time and time again not just from the SEC, but from financial agencies around the world. One such case recently occurred with reality star Kim Kardashian, who failed to reveal that her promotion of a new <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/kim-kardashian-settles-with-the-sec-over-ethereum-max-promotion/" data-wpel-link="internal">cryptocurrency called Ethereum Max</a> was not done out of her own goodwill. Rather, she had received compensation to promote the asset, something she was required to tell all her fans and followers.</p>
<p>Many of the celebrities in question have already agreed to settle with the SEC. Several will forfeit as much as $400,000 in disgorgement, interest, and penalty fees to alleviate the charges. However, some – such as Soulja Boy – are fighting back and refusing to give in. It’s unclear what their chances in court are.</p>
<p>The celebrities were under contract to promote both TRX and BTT on social media and in Tron-affiliated Discord and Telegram channels. Gurbir Grewal – SEC enforcement chief – commented that Tron was at the center of an “age-old playbook to mislead and harm investors.” He further stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>At the same time, Sun paid celebrities with millions of social media followers to tout the unregistered offerings, while specifically directing that they [do] not disclose their compensation. This is the very conduct that the federal securities laws were designed to protect against regardless of the labels Sun and others used.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Kraken Is the Latest Victim</h2>
<p>The SEC has been at the heart of several crypto-related takedowns as of late, a recent one being Kraken.</p>
<p>The company was forced to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/" data-wpel-link="internal">part with $30 million</a> and cease all its staking services.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-targets-tron-in-latest-crypto-case/">The SEC Targets Tron in Latest Crypto Case</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-sec-targets-tron-in-latest-crypto-case/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>General Bytes ATMs Attacked By Cyberthief, $1.5 Million in BTC Gone</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/general-bytes-btc-atms-attacked-by-cyberthief-1-5-million-in-btc-gone/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/general-bytes-btc-atms-attacked-by-cyberthief-1-5-million-in-btc-gone/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 15:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ATMs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cyberattack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Bytes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77569</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A group of crypto hackers have drained all the coins and funds from several bitcoin ATMs throughout the world hosted by a company called General Bytes. General Bytes Loses a Lot of Money The hackers took advantage of what’s referred to as a zero-day vulnerability to prevent all transaction losses from being reversed. General Bytes<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/general-bytes-btc-atms-attacked-by-cyberthief-1-5-million-in-btc-gone/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/general-bytes-btc-atms-attacked-by-cyberthief-1-5-million-in-btc-gone/">General Bytes ATMs Attacked By Cyberthief, $1.5 Million in BTC Gone</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A group of crypto hackers have drained all the coins <a href="https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2023/03/hackers-drain-bitcoin-atms-of-1-5-million-by-exploiting-0-day-bug/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">and funds from several bitcoin</a> ATMs throughout the world hosted by a company called General Bytes.</p>
<h2>General Bytes Loses a Lot of Money</h2>
<p>The hackers took advantage of what’s referred to as a zero-day vulnerability to prevent all transaction losses from being reversed. <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/general-bytes/" data-wpel-link="internal">General Bytes</a> explained in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>The night of 17-18 March was the most challenging time for us and some of our clients. The entire team has been working around the clock to collect all data regarding the security breach and is continuously working to resolve all cases to help clients back online and continue to operate their ATMs as soon as possible. We apologize for what happened and will review all our security procedures and are currently doing everything we can to keep our affected customers afloat.</p></blockquote>
<p>In a separate post, the company explained how it was that the hackers were able to gain control of the machines and flee with so much money:</p>
<blockquote><p>1. The attacker identified a security vulnerability in the master service interface the BATMs use to upload videos to the CAS. 2. The attacker scanned the IP address space managed by cloud host Digital Ocean to identify running CAS services on ports 7741, including the General Bytes Cloud service and other BATM operators running their servers on Digital Ocean. 3. Exploiting the vulnerability, the attacker uploaded the Java application directly to the application server used by the admin interface. The application server was, by default, configured to start applications in its deployment folder.</p></blockquote>
<p>General Bytes has since told its customers that from here on out, it will no longer be managing CASes on behalf of its users. In other words, terminal holders will be required to manage all future servers themselves. Right now, the company is in the middle of collecting data from customers so it can get an idea of what their individual losses were. The firm is also cooperating with federal officials on the matter and performing an internal investigation to better understand what occurred.</p>
<h2>Trying to See What Happened</h2>
<p>Managers of General Bytes said they were extremely disturbed and surprised by the incident given the company has undergone “multiple security audits” over the past two years, and vulnerabilities such as the one that the hackers exploited have never been noticed in the past. The enterprise is presently contacting third-party security firms to see about beefing up protection in the coming months.</p>
<p>The issue with most crypto-based ATMs is that the wallets stored within them are referred to as “hot wallets,” meaning they are directly connected to the internet. This makes them particularly vulnerable to cyberthieves who can manipulate code and APIs to gain access to said wallets and the funds contained within them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/general-bytes-btc-atms-attacked-by-cyberthief-1-5-million-in-btc-gone/">General Bytes ATMs Attacked By Cyberthief, $1.5 Million in BTC Gone</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/general-bytes-btc-atms-attacked-by-cyberthief-1-5-million-in-btc-gone/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Federal Reserve Hikes Rates Again, What Will Happen to BTC?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/federal-reserve-hikes-rates-again-what-will-happen-to-btc/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/federal-reserve-hikes-rates-again-what-will-happen-to-btc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 13:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[federal reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Inflation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Interest Rates]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77567</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Federal Reserve hiked rates another 0.25 basis points in late March. The decision came in light of the banking failure occurring within America’s borders, and many analysts found themselves wondering if bitcoin’s meteoric run would somehow be affected. The Federal Reserve Again Hikes Interest Rates This new rate hike brought interest to its tallest<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/federal-reserve-hikes-rates-again-what-will-happen-to-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/federal-reserve-hikes-rates-again-what-will-happen-to-btc/">Federal Reserve Hikes Rates Again, What Will Happen to BTC?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Federal Reserve hiked <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/federal-reserve-raises-interest-rates-025-to-highest-since-2007-amid-bank-crisis/ar-AA18X4GZ" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">rates another 0.25 basis</a> points in late March. The decision came in light of the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-more-banks-fell-bitcoin-rose-beyond-28k/" data-wpel-link="internal">banking failure</a> occurring within America’s borders, and many analysts found themselves wondering if bitcoin’s meteoric run would somehow be affected.</p>
<h2>The Federal Reserve Again Hikes Interest Rates</h2>
<p>This new rate hike brought interest to its tallest peak since 2007. That’s a whopping 16 years! In a statement, the Federal Reserve mentioned that inflation in the country remains a dangerous adversary, and it clearly doesn’t care about the many external elements that appear to be affecting the nation’s economy at the time of writing. The Fed, in many ways, is running on a one-track mind, and this is all it can think to do when fighting an enemy such as inflation.</p>
<p>Federal Reserve officials issued the following statement after the rate hike:</p>
<blockquote><p>The U.S. banking system is sound and resilient. Recent developments are likely to result in tighter credit conditions for households and businesses and to weigh on economic activity, hiring, and inflation. The extent of these effects is uncertain.</p></blockquote>
<p>The Fed says America’s banking system is safe and sound, but is that really the truth? At this stage, many residents and citizens of America are aware that federal officials have practically turned lying and bending the truth into a career, and at this point, it almost feels as if those in charge are looking to bankrupt the very nation they were hired (or elected) to serve. How can this be?</p>
<p>The Fed continued its comments with:</p>
<blockquote><p>The Committee anticipates that some additional policy firming may be appropriate in order to attain a stance of monetary policy that is sufficiently restrictive to return inflation to two percent over time.</p></blockquote>
<p>They further stated that they are anticipating further rate hikes throughout the year should inflation be unwilling to fall back. At the time of writing, the average interest rate one can expect to pay on a home or auto loan is beyond five percent. Many residents have been cut off from the American dream; there’s no beating around the bush on this.</p>
<p>Jerome Powell, who heads the Federal Reserve, mentioned:</p>
<blockquote>
<p style="text-align: left">If the totality of the data were to indicate that faster tightening is warranted, we would be prepared to increase the pace of rate hikes.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>BTC Isn&#8217;t Doing too Badly</h2>
<p>This has been an ongoing problem for <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-fed-bitcoins-worst-enemy-right-now/" data-wpel-link="internal">well over a year</a>, but the good news is that bitcoin is showing resilience during this situation. Back in 2022, the world’s number one digital currency by market cap showed extreme vulnerability to interest rate hikes and related measures.</p>
<p>Now, however, the currency has a banking crisis to “lean back on,” meaning that while one end of the spectrum is fighting it, there is another that’s providing the support it needs to continue spiking.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/federal-reserve-hikes-rates-again-what-will-happen-to-btc/">Federal Reserve Hikes Rates Again, What Will Happen to BTC?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/federal-reserve-hikes-rates-again-what-will-happen-to-btc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Bulls Aim For Key Bullish Break</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bulls-aim-for-key-bullish-break/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bulls-aim-for-key-bullish-break/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 06:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78075</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tron price started a fresh increase from the $0.0625 level against the US Dollar. TRX price is now trading near $0.0660 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key contracting triangle forming with resistance near $0.0665 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could continue to move up<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bulls-aim-for-key-bullish-break/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bulls-aim-for-key-bullish-break/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Bulls Aim For Key Bullish Break</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Tron price started a fresh increase from the $0.0625 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>TRX price is now trading near $0.0660 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key contracting triangle forming with resistance near $0.0665 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move up if it breaks the $0.0672 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>TRON price started a fresh increase above $0.0625 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-29250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. TRX’s price could rise further if it clears the $0.0672 resistance.</em></p>
<h2>Tron Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, Tron price started a decent increase from the $0.0625 support zone against the US Dollar. TRX’s price remained well-bid and was able to climb above the $0.0635 zone.</p>
<p>It traded above the $0.0650 and $0.0650 levels to move into a positive zone. The price is now trading near $0.0660 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bulls-aim-important-bullish-break/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. It is also testing the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $0.0669 swing high to the $0.0652 low.</p>
<p>On the upside, TRX is facing resistance near the $0.0665 level. There is also a key contracting triangle forming with resistance near $0.0665 on the 4-hours chart.</p>
<p>The triangle resistance is close to the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $0.0669 swing high to the $0.0652 low. The next major resistance is near the $0.0672 level. A close above $0.0672 could send the price toward the $0.0700 resistance zone.</p>
<p>Any more gains might send TRX price toward $0.072, above which the price could even rise toward $0.075. On the downside, initial support is near the $0.0655 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is now forming near $0.0645. If there is a downside break below the $0.0645 support, the price might revisit the $0.0625 support. Any more losses might call for a move toward the $0.060 zone in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_78076" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/04/TRON-TRX-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78076" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78076" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/04/TRON-TRX-1.png" alt="Tron (TRX) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78076" class="wp-caption-text">Tron (TRX) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/TRXUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that TRX’s price is now trading near $0.0660 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move up if it breaks the $0.0672 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for TRX/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for TRX/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.0655 and $0.0645.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.0665, $0.0672, and $0.070.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bulls-aim-for-key-bullish-break/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Bulls Aim For Key Bullish Break</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bulls-aim-for-key-bullish-break/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Faces Uphill Task Near $29,250</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-29250/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-29250/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 03:28:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78072</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price is correcting losses from the $27,000 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading near $28,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $29,250 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-29250/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-29250/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Faces Uphill Task Near $29,250</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin price is correcting losses from the $27,000 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading near $28,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $29,250 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could start a fresh increase if it clears the $29,250 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin price is rising from $27,000 against the US Dollar. BTC might eye another increase if the bulls remain active above the $27,000 zone.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price started a fresh decline below the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-more-gains-above-31k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">$30,000 support zone</a>. There was a clear move below the $29,500 and $29,200 support levels. The pair even tested the $27,000 support zone.</p>
<p>It traded as low as $26,965 and recently started a fresh increase. There was a break above the $27,250 resistance zone. The price gained pace once it broke the $28,000 resistance zone and the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $31,050 swing high to the $26,695 low.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is now trading near $28,500 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-rally-loses-steam-above-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. Immediate resistance on the upside is near the $29,000 level and the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $31,050 swing high to the $26,695 low.</p>
<p>There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $29,250 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair. The next major resistance might be near the $29,450 zone.</p>
<p>A clear move above the trend line and $29,450 might send the price toward $30,000, above which the price might rise toward the $31,200 level. Any more gains might push the price toward the $32,500 zone. If there is no upside break, the price might start a fresh decline below the $28,000 level.</p>
<p>The first major support is near $27,200. The next key support is near the $27,000 level, below which the price might accelerate lower. In the stated case, the price could decline toward the $26,500 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_78073" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/04/Bitcoin-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78073" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78073" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/04/Bitcoin-3.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78073" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XBTUSD/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">chart</a>, Bitcoin’s price is trading near $28,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start a fresh increase if it clears the $29,250 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $27,200 and $27,000.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $29,000, $29,250, and $29,450.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-29250/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Faces Uphill Task Near $29,250</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-29250/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Provenance Blockchain Unveils $50 Million Tech Grant</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/provenance-blockchain-announces-50-million-grant-opportunity/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/provenance-blockchain-announces-50-million-grant-opportunity/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 17:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Apollo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mike Cagney]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Provenance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77556</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Earlier today, we published an article about Mike Cagney, the cofounder of Sofi. He also runs the Provenance blockchain, and there’s big news surrounding the network in that it’s launching a new $50 million HASH development grant to establish core services and experiences on the blockchain. Provenance Blockchain Has Big Plans for the Future The<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/provenance-blockchain-announces-50-million-grant-opportunity/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/provenance-blockchain-announces-50-million-grant-opportunity/">Provenance Blockchain Unveils $50 Million Tech Grant</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Earlier today, we <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-cagney-on-what-makes-blockchain-special/" data-wpel-link="internal">published an article</a> about Mike Cagney, the cofounder of Sofi. He also runs the Provenance blockchain, and there’s big news surrounding the network in that it’s launching a new $50 million HASH development grant to establish <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/03/21/provenance-blockchain-foundation-announces-50-million-grant-program/?sh=7bd99631232c" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">core services and experiences</a> on the blockchain.</p>
<h2>Provenance Blockchain Has Big Plans for the Future</h2>
<p>The grant comes by way of a new partnership formed between Provenance and Apollo, an asset management firm that controls more than half a trillion in overall assets. Not long ago, John Zito – the senior partner and deputy CIO of credit at Apollo – commented on what both entities are planning for the future:</p>
<blockquote><p>We are excited to work with Mike and his team at Figure on [several] initiatives using Provenance blockchain technology specifically developed for our industry. This collaboration extends Apollo’s strategy of working with best-in-class fintech firms to seek the operational and cost benefits that blockchain and other technologies can bring to bear.</p></blockquote>
<p>The Provenance blockchain is presently utilized by more than 60 separate financial institutions and fintech enterprises. Right now, the network has close to $10 billion in asset value locked within its confines. CEO Morgan McKenney says it’s different from other layer-1 blockchains in that it purely tries to service regulated monetary platforms on a regular basis. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>As we add asset classes, we add other participants to the ecosystem. We have private funds live on-chain that bring accredited investors. We have a lot of lending, mortgage and HELOCs, which brings bank and credit union buyers, and mortgage providers white labeling their services through Figure Technologies. Infrastructure lending brings in insurance companies and pensions… The grant program is so important because it brings developers to support the asset lifecycle. Our team has deep financial services knowledge as well as an amazing engineering team that’s trying to develop the protocol in ways that are competitively advantaged… We are enabling the crowdsourcing of the future of finance.</p></blockquote>
<p>About nine years ago, CEO of JPMorgan Chase Jamie Dimon warned that the banks of the modern era were becoming too entwined with the world of growing tech companies. Many of these enterprises were too speculative and volatile to be given all the attention they were receiving, and he warned this would come back to bite the banking industry in the rear (which it clearly has given how many institutions from <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-more-banks-fell-bitcoin-rose-beyond-28k/" data-wpel-link="internal">Signature to Silvergate</a> have crashed and burned as of late). He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>When I go to Silicon Valley…they all want to eat our lunch. Every single one of them is going to try.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Banks and Tech&#8230; Not a Great Combo</h2>
<p>He reiterated his sentiment five years later, commenting:</p>
<blockquote><p>I tell our people, don’t guess, you know they’re there, you know they’re coming, you know they want to eat our lunch. Assume it.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/provenance-blockchain-announces-50-million-grant-opportunity/">Provenance Blockchain Unveils $50 Million Tech Grant</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/provenance-blockchain-announces-50-million-grant-opportunity/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fidelity and Black Rock Keep Expanding Their Crypto Influence</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fidelity-and-black-rock-keep-expanding-their-crypto-influence/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fidelity-and-black-rock-keep-expanding-their-crypto-influence/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black Rock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fidelity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Halving]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77554</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fidelity Investments and Black Rock – two of the biggest investing companies in the world – are slowly expanding their reaches into the crypto and blockchain spaces. Fidelity and Black Rock Are the New Crypto Leaders Fidelity has long been a crypto player, going so far as to last year, when the space was enduring<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fidelity-and-black-rock-keep-expanding-their-crypto-influence/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fidelity-and-black-rock-keep-expanding-their-crypto-influence/">Fidelity and Black Rock Keep Expanding Their Crypto Influence</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fidelity Investments and Black Rock – two of the biggest investing companies in the world – are slowly expanding their reaches <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/03/21/14-trillion-earthquake-fidelity-and-blackrock-are-quietly-laying-the-groundwork-for-the-next-bitcoin-ethereum-and-crypto-price-bull-run/?sh=63a7ce4a6759" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">into the crypto and blockchain</a> spaces.</p>
<h2>Fidelity and Black Rock Are the New Crypto Leaders</h2>
<p>Fidelity has long been a crypto player, going <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fidelity-is-still-taking-flak-for-its-crypto-offerings/" data-wpel-link="internal">so far as to last year</a>, when the space was enduring its biggest bear run in history, allow retirees and those with 401K funds to their names to use their hard-earned money to invest in digital assets like BTC and Ethereum. This move caught a lot of people off guard and even made certain individuals – such as democrat senator from Massachusetts Elizabeth Warren – very angry.</p>
<p>But this hasn’t stopped the company from moving forward. Fidelity has long commented that crypto is the wave of the future, and it’s not about to prevent people from getting involved early. It and Black Rock are now leading the charge for standard financial investment firms to grow alongside the arena. Larry Fink – the chief executive of Black Rock – explained in a letter to investors:</p>
<blockquote><p>At BlackRock we continue to explore the digital assets ecosystem, especially areas most relevant to our clients such as permissioned blockchains and tokenization of stocks and bonds. Very interesting developments are happening in the digital asset space.</p></blockquote>
<p>Bitcoin is already up more <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-more-banks-fell-bitcoin-rose-beyond-28k/" data-wpel-link="internal">than 50 percent from</a> where it ended 2022, and it’s reached a nine-month high. Last year was arguably the worst year for digital assets, with the space losing more than $2 trillion in valuation and currencies such as bitcoin dropping by more than 70 percent. The asset had reached a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit in November of 2021, though about 12 months later, the currency had dropped into the $16K range. It was a sad and ugly sight to see.</p>
<p>Now, however, BTC – at the time of writing – has shot up to about $28K per unit. This isn’t where it was two Novembers ago, but it’s a step up from where it sat last December, that’s for sure, and many asset holders are starting to once again hold a strong belief that there’s more to crypto than meets the eye.</p>
<p>Next year, another bitcoin halving will be upon us, and some analysts are convinced that what we’re witnessing today could be attributed to the anticipation many investors and traders are beginning to feel about the event. It is well documented that prior to every halving, BTC incurs a solid price boost, and some believe this time around will be no exception.</p>
<h2>The Next Halving Is Coming</h2>
<p>Alex Thorn – Galaxy’s head of research – said in emailed comments:</p>
<blockquote><p>We’re about a year away from bitcoin’s next halving. Historically, these have been bullish events for the digital asset.</p></blockquote>
<p>The next halving is currently scheduled to happen a year from now (April of 2024).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fidelity-and-black-rock-keep-expanding-their-crypto-influence/">Fidelity and Black Rock Keep Expanding Their Crypto Influence</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/fidelity-and-black-rock-keep-expanding-their-crypto-influence/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mike Cagney on What Makes Blockchain Special</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-cagney-on-what-makes-blockchain-special/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-cagney-on-what-makes-blockchain-special/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 13:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mike Cagney]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sofi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77551</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mike Cagney has made a real name for himself in the blockchains pace. He is the co-founder of Sofi and the current CEO of Figure. He’s also made public the Provenance blockchain, which has supported about $12 million in transactions at the time of writing. Mike Cagney on Blockchain In a recent interview, he talked<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-cagney-on-what-makes-blockchain-special/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-cagney-on-what-makes-blockchain-special/">Mike Cagney on What Makes Blockchain Special</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mike Cagney has made a <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/savingandinvesting/future-of-finance-figure-s-cagney-says-blockchain-for-payments-nearing-tipping-point/ar-AA18HxQM" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">real name for himself</a> in the blockchains pace. He is the co-founder of Sofi and the current CEO of Figure. He’s also made public the Provenance blockchain, which has supported about $12 million in transactions at the time of writing.</p>
<h2>Mike Cagney on Blockchain</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, he talked about just how prominent <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/blockchain/" data-wpel-link="internal">blockchain</a> is. He also delved a bit into what his company does, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>One of the most important roles that I play with Figure and supporting the Provenance ecosystem is just evangelizing the use cases for blockchain and trying to make them as tangible and accessible as possible. The most fundamental thing that we strive for is the idea that blockchain allows you to displace trust with truth, so it allows you to create native digital assets where I can look at those assets and know for certain their ownership composition and history, and it allows you to transact bilaterally so that you and I can transact without an intermediate.</p></blockquote>
<p>Cagney has always been positive when it comes to blockchain, and this is a narrative he’s carried with him since his early Sofi days. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>When I was at Sofi, I talked a lot about blockchain, but I didn&#8217;t really understand what it was and what the power of it was, so I just had an aha moment of this disintermediation construct, where I said, ‘Wait a minute, this is huge. This is probably one of the most transformative technologies that we’ll experience in our lifetime.’</p></blockquote>
<p>Addressing the lack of women working in blockchain and crypto, he mentioned the following about what is largely a male-dominated industry:</p>
<blockquote><p>We achieved a lot of great things at Sofi, and we learned a lot as well. We have taken those learnings with us in starting Figure, particularly around culture. One of the biggest changes we incorporated at Figure is hiring people for culture first. When you prioritize ability and skill set during recruitment, you can often leave culture as an afterthought. That then leads to an environment where bad behaviors are tolerated when they shouldn&#8217;t be, simply because they&#8217;re coming from top performers. Our president and head of lending are both women, and that diversity transcends through not just the executive team but also the organization, where we have higher representation of women in product and engineering than tech/fintech averages.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Joining Banks and Crypto Together</h2>
<p>He concluded with:</p>
<blockquote><p>When we built Provenance and made it public, we went to a bunch of banks early on, and my thesis was, ‘Hey, you could do a securitization on here and save, you know, roughly 90 basis points,’ and every bank universally said, ‘This is great. We love it. We&#8217;d like to be the 10th bank to do a securitization on here.’</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-cagney-on-what-makes-blockchain-special/">Mike Cagney on What Makes Blockchain Special</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-cagney-on-what-makes-blockchain-special/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
