<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 03:26:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/cropped-fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Could Regain Strength Above This Hurdle</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-regain-strength-above-this-hurdle/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 03:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79331</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price is attempting a fresh increase from the $29,525 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $30,400 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,180 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-regain-strength-above-this-hurdle/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Could Regain Strength Above This Hurdle</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin price is attempting a fresh increase from the $29,525 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $30,400 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,180 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could start a fresh increase if it clears the $30,400 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin price is rising from $29,525 against the US Dollar. BTC might eye another increase if the bulls remain active above the $29,500 zone.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price started a fresh decline it failed to clear the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-restart-rally-above-this-resistance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$31,800 resistance</a>. BTC declined below the $30,500 and $30,000 support levels to enter a short-term bearish zone.</p>
<p>The recent swing low was formed near $29,525 before the price moved higher. The bulls were able to push the price above the $29,650 and $29,850 levels. The price is now approaching the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward wave from the $31,862 swing high to the $29,525 low.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is now trading below $30,400 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-more-upsides-above-31250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. Immediate resistance on the upside is near the $30,150 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,180 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>The next major resistance might be near the $30,400 zone or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward wave from the $31,862 swing high to the $29,525 low.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $30,400 and $30,600 resistance levels might send the price toward $31,200. Any more gains might push the price toward the $32,000 zone. If there is no upside break, the price might start a fresh decline below the $30,000 level.</p>
<p>The first major support is near $29,525. The next key support is near the $29,250 level, below which the price might accelerate lower. In the stated case, the price could decline toward the $28,400 level.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79332" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79332" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-3.png"><img decoding="async" class="wp-image-79332 size-full" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-3.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-3.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-3-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-3-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-3-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-3-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-3-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-3-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79332" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XBTUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, Bitcoin’s price is trading below $30,400 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start a fresh increase if it clears the $30,400 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD is now losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $29,850 and $29,525.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $30,180, $30,400, and $30,600.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-regain-strength-above-this-hurdle/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Could Regain Strength Above This Hurdle</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mike Novogratz: Crypto&#8217;s &#8220;Lackadaisical&#8221; Right Now</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-novogratz-cryptos-lackadaisical-right-now/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mike Novogratz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rug pulls]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78638</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, we put out an article talking about how May was the worst month for bitcoin this year. The currency ended May about two percent less than where it had been in previous months, and this was the first time this year in which BTC didn’t finish a 30-day period on a high. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-novogratz-cryptos-lackadaisical-right-now/">Mike Novogratz: Crypto&#8217;s &#8220;Lackadaisical&#8221; Right Now</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, we put out an article talking about <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/may-has-been-the-worst-month-for-bitcoin-this-year/">how May was the worst</a> month for bitcoin this year. The currency ended May about two percent less than where it had been in previous months, and this was the first time this year in which BTC didn’t finish a 30-day period on a high. Mike Novogratz – a bitcoin bull and hedge fund manager – had a lot to say on <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/technology/galaxy-digital-ceo-mike-novogratz-says-the-dog-days-of-summer-came-early-for-crypto-as-bitcoin-posts-worst-month-since-november/ar-AA1c03cO">the matter as he made</a> clear in a recent interview.</p>
<h2>Mike Novogratz on the Current State of BTC</h2>
<p>In his discussion, Novogratz described the situation as the “dog days of summer” coming early for the world’s leading digital currency by market cap. He stated with an air of gloom and doom:</p>
<blockquote><p>The dog days of summer started early in crypto. That doesn&#8217;t make me thrilled. That&#8217;s just the reality.</p></blockquote>
<p>The good news, however, is that bitcoin is still about 60 percent higher than where it ended last year. 2022 was arguably the worst period on record for bitcoin. Things started off well in November of 2021 when BTC reached a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit.</p>
<p>Sadly, while everyone thought bitcoin was an unstoppable asset and likely to reach the pinnacles of finance, the following 12 months proved harsh and gruesome in ways that nobody thought possible, and bitcoin wound up losing more than 70 percent of its overall value and dipping into mid-$16K territory.</p>
<p>The trouble didn’t quite stop there. The rest of the crypto industry lost more than $2 trillion in value, as several additional coins chose to follow in BTC’s ugly and twisted footsteps. It was a rough and depressing sight.</p>
<p>And while bitcoin is up right now when compared with the horrendous conditions it faced last year, it’s certainly not where it could be, and it’s not in a position that’s even comparable with where it was two Novembers ago. Novogratz took note of this and said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Crypto&#8217;s lackadaisical right now. There&#8217;s a constant bid from retail. We&#8217;re seeing it through all the platforms. There&#8217;s not a lot of institutional excitement right now.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Lot of Deception</h2>
<p>As other news has related, it wasn’t just the price of bitcoin that makes May a relatively weak month. The period also saw lots <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/crypto-investors-lost-54m-to-rugpulls-scams-in-may-blockchain-security-firm-defi-1032367227">of new fraud and rug pulls</a> taking place, and it appears many investors lost more than $50 million in combined assets.</p>
<p>Rug pulls often occur when new crypto companies enter the fray and seek to raise funds for their operations. The more money they get, the higher their tokens spike. All who invested early see their portfolios rise and things look solid, but it isn’t long before all the executives shut down and run off with the money they’ve earned, leaving their supporters in bad states and their portfolios in shambles.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-novogratz-cryptos-lackadaisical-right-now/">Mike Novogratz: Crypto&#8217;s &#8220;Lackadaisical&#8221; Right Now</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Arthur Hayes: BTC Will Explode at the End of 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/arthur-hayes-btc-will-explode-at-the-end-of-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 15:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arthur Hayes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Halving]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78635</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Arthur Hayes – the former chief executive of crypto exchange BitMEX – has commented that quarters three and four of this year are going to be among the best for bitcoin. Arthur Hayes on the Fate of BTC For the most part, 2023 has been a powerful year for the crypto arena. The world’s biggest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/arthur-hayes-btc-will-explode-at-the-end-of-2023/">Arthur Hayes: BTC Will Explode at the End of 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Arthur Hayes – the former chief executive of crypto exchange BitMEX – <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/06/02/crypto-now-braced-for-a-powder-keg-that-could-play-havoc-with-the-price-of-bitcoin-and-ethereum/?sh=1d04c95a38d9">has commented that</a> quarters three and four of this year are going to be among the best for bitcoin.</p>
<h2>Arthur Hayes on the Fate of BTC</h2>
<p>For the most part, 2023 has been a powerful year for the crypto arena. The world’s biggest and most popular digital currency by market cap has surged more than 60 percent from where it was at the end of last year, though this doesn’t mean that there isn’t still room for improvement.</p>
<p>The fact remains that in November of 2021, bitcoin reached a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit, though it spent the next 12 or 13 months traveling through the doldrums and hitting new lows, and while things may be up in 2023, they are not where they were two Novembers ago. In a recent interview, Hayes mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>You’re basically putting this powder keg together of a situation that’s going to be exploding in [the third and fourth quarter] of this year, and I think, ultimately, it will be good for bitcoin. It will be quite volatile on the upside and the downside.</p></blockquote>
<p>While all the drama with the debt deal in the United States has come to an end, things are still up in the air thanks to the Treasury being engaged in a few questionable <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-treasury-is-set-to-make-things-rough-for-bitcoin/">practices at the time of writing</a>… practices that could make things very rough for bitcoin and its altcoin cousins.</p>
<p>Hayes commented that more than $1 trillion in Treasury bills could wind up coming our way over the next few months. He believes that this could liquidate millions or even billions of dollars in the crypto marketplace, and that in that sense, things won’t go well for the world’s primary assets.</p>
<p>However, he was also quick to suggest that the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-next-btc-halving-is-a-year-away-whats-going-to-happen/">next bitcoin halving</a> – currently set to take place in April of next year – will bear similar results with all the crypto arena’s past halvings, and that BTC and Ethereum are likely to rise to new levels following this event. In fact, he believes bitcoin could wind up reaching a price of $70K. Hayes stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I don’t think we’ll get up to $70,000 this year. I think next year is when we cross that barrier, then we get the blow off top [2025], [2026] and then it’s Armageddon. It doesn’t have to be too straightforward; we just have this situation. We have this tinderbox of too much money, no trust, and people trying to eke out a living for themselves.</p></blockquote>
<h2>So Much Financial Drama!</h2>
<p>At press time, the price of bitcoin is hovering between the $27,000 and $28,000 marks.</p>
<p>There has been quite a bit of hoopla surrounding America’s financial situation, and this hasn’t helped BTC decide on a lasting position.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/arthur-hayes-btc-will-explode-at-the-end-of-2023/">Arthur Hayes: BTC Will Explode at the End of 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brad Garlinghouse: Ripple&#8217;s Battle with the SEC Will End Soon</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brad-garlinghouse-the-ripple-sec-battle-will-end-in-a-few-weeks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 13:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brad Garlinghouse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78633</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Brad Garlinghouse – the CEO of leading crypto platform Ripple – is confident his company is going to put the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in its place. Where Will Ripple Stand? Not long ago, the SEC announced its plans to sue Ripple and charge it with securities violations. This isn’t the first time something [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brad-garlinghouse-the-ripple-sec-battle-will-end-in-a-few-weeks/">Brad Garlinghouse: Ripple&#8217;s Battle with the SEC Will End Soon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Brad Garlinghouse – the CEO of leading crypto platform Ripple – is <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/05/31/confident-ripple-ceo-helps-the-xrp-price-outperform-bitcoin/?sh=4a15961e77a7">confident his company is going</a> to put the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in its place.</p>
<h2>Where Will Ripple Stand?</h2>
<p>Not long ago, the SEC announced its plans to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-secs-case-against-ripple-could-result-in-a-massive-win-for-the-crypto-company/">sue Ripple and charge</a> it with securities violations. This isn’t the first time something like this has happened. There have been many crypto companies over the years that have fallen victim to the financial agency, but many of them chose to settle and move on. However, Ripple selected a different route.</p>
<p>Rather than curl up into a ball and allow itself to get whipped, the company chose to go to court with the SEC and fight back, and now it looks like the company could win the case against it. In a recent interview, Garlinghouse said he’s confident the case will come to an end in the coming weeks rather than the coming months, suggesting things could be over soon. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I feel very confident that we’ll see a decision from the courts this year. In fact, I think I would guess that it will be in weeks, not months… The judge ruled against the SEC&#8217;s effort to redact certain information, a very kind of infamous speech that the then director of corporate finance Bill Hinman gave talking about why ETH, in his view, is not a security.</p></blockquote>
<p>The SEC has developed a reputation for being a bully in the crypto arena. Not long ago, the agency went after big-name firms such as Kraken and Coinbase, two of the largest digital currency exchanges in existence. The <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/">latter was forced</a> to end all its staking services and activities while also parting with a $30 million fee.</p>
<p>At Coinbase, executives were <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/">served a Wells notice</a>, implying that while they hadn’t been charged with anything yet, the day was not far off when charges would be thrown in their direction. Garlinghouse further commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>The court just ruled last week that the notes in the emails associated with that are going to be made public and should be public&#8230; So, I think that’s a huge win for transparency, but what it really calls out is there really hasn’t been clarity despite calls and demands from leaders across the crypto industry.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Never Back Down</h2>
<p>Thus far, the company’s legal battle with the SEC has lasted a whopping two years, though it could be argued that Ripple is setting a precedent for <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-ripple-is-showing-crypto-firms-how-to-handle-a-bully-in-its-sec-fight/">how to defeat a bully</a>. Garlinghouse concluded with:</p>
<blockquote><p>Ripple decided to lean in and fight this fight, both for Ripple and the whole industry. We’ve spent a lot of money defending it, and I think what we’ve called out is the government in the United States, and the SEC particularly, is putting politics ahead of smart policy.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/brad-garlinghouse-the-ripple-sec-battle-will-end-in-a-few-weeks/">Brad Garlinghouse: Ripple&#8217;s Battle with the SEC Will End Soon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Key Uptrend Support Nearby At $0.30</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-key-uptrend-support-nearby-at-0-30/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 05:28:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79327</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ADA price is correcting gains from the $0.380 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above $0.300 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.30 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Coinbase). The price could start a fresh increase [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-key-uptrend-support-nearby-at-0-30/">Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Key Uptrend Support Nearby At $0.30</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>ADA price is correcting gains from the $0.380 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $0.300 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.30 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Coinbase).</li>
<li>The price could start a fresh increase if it clears the $0.320 and $0.335 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Cardano’s price is rising above $0.300 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-restart-rally-above-this-resistance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. ADA price could resume its rally if there is a clear move above the $0.335 resistance.</em></p>
<h2>Cardano Price (ADA) Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, Cardano’s price started a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-is-the-recovery-just-getting-started/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">steady increase above the $0.335 resistance zone</a> against the US Dollar. The ADA/USD pair gained pace for a move above the $0.350 and $0.365 levels.</p>
<p>The price tested the $0.380 zone. A high was formed near $0.3801 and the price is now correcting lower. There was a move below the $0.350 support zone. The price dipped below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.2850 swing low to the $0.3801 high.</p>
<p>However, ADA price is now trading above $0.30 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $0.320 zone.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $0.335 zone. A clear move above the $0.335 resistance might start a strong increase toward $0.365. Any more gains above the $0.365 resistance might send Cardano toward the $0.380 resistance or even $0.40.</p>
<p>On the downside, immediate support is near the $0.305 level. It is near the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.2850 swing low to the $0.3801 high.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $0.300 level. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.30 on the 4-hours chart. A clear move below the $0.30 level might send Cardano toward the $0.275 level. Any more losses might send the price toward the $0.250 support.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79328" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79328" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Cardano-Price-2.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-79328" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Cardano-Price-2.png" alt="Cardano (ADA) Price " width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Cardano-Price-2.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Cardano-Price-2-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Cardano-Price-2-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Cardano-Price-2-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Cardano-Price-2-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Cardano-Price-2-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Cardano-Price-2-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79328" class="wp-caption-text">Cardano (ADA) Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ADAUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a> indicates that ADA price is now trading above $0.300 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $0.320 and $0.335 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ADA/USD is now losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for ADA/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.30 and $0.275.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.320 and $0.335.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-key-uptrend-support-nearby-at-0-30/">Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Key Uptrend Support Nearby At $0.30</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Could Resume Increase Above $1,950</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-resume-increase-above-1950/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 03:38:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79324</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum price is eyeing an upside break above the $1,950 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH price is now trading near $1,900 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $1,890 on the 4-hour chart (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could climb further [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-resume-increase-above-1950/">Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Could Resume Increase Above $1,950</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ethereum price is eyeing an upside break above the $1,950 resistance against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>ETH price is now trading near $1,900 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $1,890 on the 4-hour chart (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could climb further if it stays above the $1,880 support zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ethereum price is consolidating above the $1,850 level against the US Dollar. ETH/USD could rise again if it clears the $1,950 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Ethereum Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, Ethereum saw a bearish wave from the $2,030 zone against the US Dollar. ETH price declined below the $1,950 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>The bears even pushed the price below the $1,900 level. A low was formed near $1,873 and the price is now attempting a fresh increase. There was a move above the $1,900 resistance level. The price broke the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward wave from the $2,029 swing high to the $1,873 low.</p>
<p>It is now trading near $1,900 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-aims-fresh-run-to-2000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. Immediate resistance on the upside is near the $1,920 level. The next major resistance is near the $1,950 zone.</p>
<p>The 50% Fib retracement level of the downward wave from the $2,029 swing high to the $1,873 low is also near the trend line. A clear move above the $1,950 level could send the price toward $1,975. Any more gains could even send the price toward the $2,030 resistance zone or $2,080 in the near term.</p>
<p>On the downside, initial support is near the $1,890 level. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $1,890 on the 4-hour chart. The next major support is now near the $1,880 level. A break below the $1,880 support could push the price to $1,822. Any more losses could lead the price toward $1,780 or even $1,720 in the coming days.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79325" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79325" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum-2.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-79325" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum-2.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum-2.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum-2-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum-2-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum-2-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum-2-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum-2-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ethereum-2-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79325" class="wp-caption-text">Ethereum Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, Ethereum price is clearly trading near the $1,900 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-rally-above-2000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ether price could climb again</a> if it stays above the $1,880 support zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now losing momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for ETH/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $1,890, followed by the $1,880 zone.</p>
<p>Key Resistance$ Levels – $1,920 and $1,950.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-resume-increase-above-1950/">Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Could Resume Increase Above $1,950</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mike Novogratz: BTC and ETH Are Among the Best Long-Term Investments</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-novogratz-btc-and-eth-are-the-best-long-term-investments/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 17:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mike Novogratz]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78610</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin bull and hedge fund manager Mike Novogratz is again in the news trying to tell everyone that bitcoin and Ethereum are the best long-term investments anyone can take part in. Mike Novogratz Still Loves Bitcoin In a recent interview, Novogratz took issue with the trading volumes for both cryptocurrencies, which appear to be somewhat [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-novogratz-btc-and-eth-are-the-best-long-term-investments/">Mike Novogratz: BTC and ETH Are Among the Best Long-Term Investments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin bull and hedge fund manager Mike Novogratz is again in <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-and-ether-may-be-better-bets-than-jp-morgan-stock-on-a-risk-adjusted-basis-says-michael-novogratz/ar-AA1bZKZl">the news trying to tell</a> everyone that bitcoin and Ethereum are the best long-term investments anyone can take part in.</p>
<h2>Mike Novogratz Still Loves Bitcoin</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, Novogratz took issue with the trading volumes for both cryptocurrencies, which appear to be somewhat down at the time of writing. He said bitcoin and Ethereum are the best items a person can invest in over the next several years, and he believes both digital currencies are going to put major stocks for big-time financial firms like JPMorgan to shame. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>You shouldn’t buy as much bitcoin as you do JPMorgan stock, but volatility adjusted, it’s been a much better bet than JPMorgan.</p></blockquote>
<p>It’s interesting that Novogratz would bring up volatility in the above quote <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-bitcoin-volatility-lowest-in-three-years/">given volatility for bitcoin</a> has allegedly sunk to its lowest point in roughly three years. The currency has been on something of a roll since the start of 2023, and while there have been little hiccups along the way, the asset is up about 65 percent from where it ended 2022 (arguably the worst year on record for crypto).</p>
<p>Still, this doesn’t change the fact that a lot of room for healing remains. The currency, back in November of 2021, was trading for about $68,000 per unit (a new all-time high), but it fell into the mid-$16K range just over a year later. While the asset may be up more than 60 percent from where it was at the end of 2022, there’s still another 60 percent to go if it wants to be back where it was two Novembers ago.</p>
<p>The good news, according to Novogratz, is that bitcoin has endured something of a tight range over the past few months. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>You could pierce either side of the range and have a quick move.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also said he’s certain bitcoin will endure another major rally as soon as the Fed agrees to end its rate hikes to curb inflation. However, his one serious complaint was that many institutions are still refusing to get involved in bitcoin, claiming:</p>
<blockquote><p>That’s stopped by a combination of Sam and Gary.</p></blockquote>
<p>He is, of course, referring to Sam Bankman-Fried – the disgraced executive of fallen crypto exchange FTX – and Gary Gensler, the persecuting leader of the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<h2>An AI Bubble Has Hit the U.S.</h2>
<p>He also pointed out another problem and said the U.S. is trapped in an AI bubble, something he thinks will last a while. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bubbles always happened around things that fundamentally changed the way we live. They’ve almost happened around the real thing. The story is so powerful, and people buy way in advance and get caught up in the frenzy.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mike-novogratz-btc-and-eth-are-the-best-long-term-investments/">Mike Novogratz: BTC and ETH Are Among the Best Long-Term Investments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cheelee – The Breakthrough of 2023: How Social Media Delivers Basic Income Worldwide</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cheelee-the-breakthrough-of-2023-how-social-media-delivers-basic-income-worldwide/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 16:12:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry and Adoption]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79304</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cheelee, a GameFi short video platform, emerged as a game-changer by introducing a groundbreaking concept – the delivery of basic income to people all over the globe by watching feed. What sets Cheelee apart from traditional social media is its unique approach to distributing revenue. Instead of distributing solely to content makers, Cheelee introduced an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cheelee-the-breakthrough-of-2023-how-social-media-delivers-basic-income-worldwide/">Cheelee – The Breakthrough of 2023: How Social Media Delivers Basic Income Worldwide</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cheelee.io/">Cheelee</a>, a GameFi short video platform, emerged as a game-changer by introducing a groundbreaking concept – the delivery of basic income to people all over the globe by watching feed.</p>
<p>What sets Cheelee apart from traditional social media is its unique approach to distributing revenue. Instead of distributing solely to content makers, Cheelee introduced an innovative economic model that redistributed wealth back to its users, who watch feed. This concept harnessed social networks&#8217; potential to propel financial empowerment.</p>
<h4>Web3 Social Media Landscape</h4>
<p>In the constantly changing Web3 social network ecosystem, several crypto startups have emerged as notable players, including Cheelee, Steemit, Minds, Akasha, Synereo, and Indorse. Cheelee stands out nonetheless because of its original concept. While other SocialFi platforms require content production for monetization, Cheelee has revolutionized the landscape by allowing ordinary users to become beneficiaries.</p>
<p>By adhering to the philosophy of the Attention Economy, Cheelee compensates its participants for their active engagement and time spent consuming the platform`s content. With the help of this ground-breaking strategy, Cheelee is gaining more and more prominence because it has made it possible for a larger proportion of social media users to profit financially from their involvement.</p>
<h4>Cheelee Pays You For Watching Feeds</h4>
<p>Unlike its competitors, Cheelee thanks to its well-developed GameFi mechanics, allows users to earn on watching feeds. By purchasing and upgrading Digital (formerly NFT) glasses, everyone can get X2 income in tokens.</p>
<p>Cheelee&#8217;s introduction of basic income has far-reaching socioeconomic implications. By ensuring a minimum level of income for all its users, Cheelee addresses issues such as poverty, unemployment, and economic instability.</p>
<p>“We want Cheelee to be the tool that enables every mobile phone owner to make money from their attention,” Cheelee CEO and founder Ruslan Sharov says. “We see our mission as some kind of countering the trend when AI takes jobs from people. We&#8217;ve created an app where any user can start earning money steadily. You can support a household, study, or start your first business with this income. In our app, high technologies are applied in the interests of humanity”.</p>
<h4>How to Start Earning in Cheelee</h4>
<ul>
<li>Sign up and get free Digital Glasses;</li>
<li>Watch the feed and get boxes with LEE tokens;</li>
<li>Buy Digital Glasses and get LEE tokens while watching the feed;</li>
<li>Upgrade Digital Glasses and choose the best strategy for earning.</li>
</ul>
<p>The marketplace lists the Digital glasses for between $51.5 and $1854. According to <a href="https://twitter.com/Cheelee_Tweet/status/1664290755567841283?s=20">reports</a> from Cheelee users on the project&#8217;s social networks, the revenue generated while utilizing this tool may be x1,8-2,2. Users may earn quite a substantial income after investing their initial earnings into leveling up their existing glasses and purchasing additional ones. When their glasses reach high levels, their earnings in Cheelee can eventually become their basic income.</p>
<h4>Conclusion</h4>
<p>Cheelee&#8217;s breakthrough highlights social media&#8217;s enormous potential as a force for positive change. By merging technology, connectivity, and economic empowerment, Cheelee has paved the way for a future where SocialFi platforms can serve as catalysts for socioeconomic progress. The success of Cheelee&#8217;s approach also provides a chance for legislators and governments to reassess the notion of basic income and look for ways to implement it outside of the digital realm.</p>
<p>Cheelee&#8217;s advent in 2023 marked a groundbreaking moment in the evolution of social networks and economic empowerment. By reinventing the income distribution paradigm, Cheelee has transformed social media from a source of mere entertainment into a tool for socioeconomic progress.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cheelee-the-breakthrough-of-2023-how-social-media-delivers-basic-income-worldwide/">Cheelee – The Breakthrough of 2023: How Social Media Delivers Basic Income Worldwide</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blockchain Company Nansen Engages in Massive Layoffs</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-firm-nansen-engages-in-massive-layoffs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 15:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Layoffs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nansen]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78607</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nansen – a blockchain data firm based in Singapore – has laid off about 50 people at the time of writing, suggesting the crypto winter is not fully over. Nansen Says Goodbye to Many Employees 2022 was marred by news of many large crypto firms and companies laying off employees. Big names like Gemini in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-firm-nansen-engages-in-massive-layoffs/">Blockchain Company Nansen Engages in Massive Layoffs</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nansen – a blockchain data firm based in Singapore – has <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/blockchain-data-firm-nansen-cuts-headcount-by-almost-50-ceo-says/ar-AA1bWpYN">laid off about 50 people</a> at the time of writing, suggesting the crypto winter is not fully over.</p>
<h2>Nansen Says Goodbye to Many Employees</h2>
<p>2022 was marred by news of many large crypto firms and companies laying off employees. Big names like Gemini in New York and Coinbase joined the ranks, with the latter initially putting off plans to triple its workforce. Originally, Coinbase had the goal to become bigger than ever in 2022 and hire loads more people. Sadly, the state of bitcoin and its many altcoin cousins brought <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-says-its-freezing-all-2022-hiring-plans/">about a quick end to</a> those plans.</p>
<p>When things got even worse in the market, Coinbase said it <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-says-its-laying-off-several-employees/">would be laying</a> off roughly 18 percent of its staff. Several months went by, but eventually, a time came when Coinbase <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-forced-to-release-1000-more-people-from-employment/">was forced to let go</a> of even more people.</p>
<p>Gemini also engaged in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gemini-exchange-engages-in-more-layoffs/">two separate layoffs</a>. The first was in the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/gemini-exchange-says-major-layoffs-are-coming/">summer of last year</a>. The company announced it was going to let go of roughly ten percent of the people that it had employed. News spread quickly that the headcount with Gemini fell from about 1,000 people (per its LinkedIn page) to around 900.</p>
<p>However, many people took issue with the idea that Gemini was going to be engaging in the layoffs through Zoom calls rather than through in-person meetings. The company was still having many staff members work remotely following the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/coronavirus/">coronavirus pandemic</a>, and many of the layoffs were to occur via video screens.</p>
<p>2022 was arguably the worst year on record for BTC and crypto. The world’s number one digital currency by market cap initially surged beyond $68,000 per unit in November of 2021, a new all-time high, though about a year later, the currency had fallen into the mid-$16K region.</p>
<p>Several other digital assets followed in its footsteps, thus causing the crypto arena to lose more than $2 trillion in valuation in less than 12 months.</p>
<p>Nansen has suddenly joined the ongoing layoff ranks. The firm, like Coinbase, has also said that all plans to hire additional souls have been put on hold. CEO Alex Svanevik explained in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>We wanted to invest and build in a tough market when others needed to scale back. This organic growth led the organization to taking on surface area that&#8217;s not truly part of Nansen&#8217;s core strategy. The new org will do fewer things but do them extremely well.</p></blockquote>
<h2>The News Follows Heavy Growth</h2>
<p>The news comes as somewhat of a shock given that Nansen – per its LinkedIn profile – has grown rapidly over the past few years.</p>
<p>The company currently has about 155 people working under its roof. This is a 180 percent surge from where it stood just a little over a year ago.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-firm-nansen-engages-in-massive-layoffs/">Blockchain Company Nansen Engages in Massive Layoffs</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
