<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 03:04:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/cropped-fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Jack Dorsey Backs BTC Fan Robert Kennedy Jr. for President</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jack-dorsey-backs-btc-fan-robert-kennedy-jr-for-president/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 13:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robert Kennedy Jr.]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trump]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78671</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jack Dorsey – the former head of Twitter – has put out a video suggesting he’s endorsing bitcoin-loving presidential candidate Robert Kennedy Jr. to assume nation-leading duties in the White House in 2025. Jack Dorsey is Pushing Robert Kennedy Jr. Not long ago, Dorsey put out a video on social media about the candidate and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jack-dorsey-backs-btc-fan-robert-kennedy-jr-for-president/">Jack Dorsey Backs BTC Fan Robert Kennedy Jr. for President</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jack Dorsey – the former head of Twitter – has put out a video <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jack-dorsey-endorses-fellow-bitcoin-001943733.html">suggesting he’s endorsing</a> bitcoin-loving presidential candidate Robert Kennedy Jr. to assume nation-leading duties in the White House in 2025.</p>
<h2>Jack Dorsey is Pushing Robert Kennedy Jr.</h2>
<p>Not long ago, Dorsey put out a video on social media about the candidate and commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Robert. F. Kennedy, Jr. argues he can beat Trump and DeSantis in 2024. He can and will.</p></blockquote>
<p>Kennedy entered the presidential race a few months back and is working hard to garner the democratic nomination in 2024 and thus remove current democrat commander-in-chief Joe Biden from the ticket altogether. Kennedy has repeatedly <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-hopeful-robert-kennedy-jr-appeared-at-this-years-miami-btc-conference/">initiated comments about bitcoin</a> and crypto use and even made an appearance at this year’s Miami Bitcoin Conference where he stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>As president, I will make sure that your right to hold and use bitcoin is inviolable. You should be able to own your own private keys, the same as you own the keys to your car or own your wallet…I don’t think the government has the right to demand access to your bitcoin key or indeed any of your passwords. To say otherwise [is] to cede essential territory to [a] surveillance state.</p></blockquote>
<p>When a commenter on Twitter said there was no way Kennedy would be nominated due to likely interference from the Democratic National Committee (DNC), Dorsey responded with, “Even more reason.” He was also quick to add that the DNC is losing relevance and that its present state marks the “end of an empire.”</p>
<p>It makes sense Dorsey would be such an advocate for Kennedy. Dorsey has long been a major bitcoin fan, commenting in the year <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2018/03/21/jack-dorsey-expects-bitcoin-to-become-the-worlds-single-currency-in-about-10-years.html#:~:text=Twitter%20and%20Square%20CEO%20Jack%20Dorsey%20predicts%20bitcoin,bitcoin%2C%E2%80%9D%20Dorsey%20said%20in%20a%20report%20published%20Wednesday.">2018 that the currency</a> would ultimately become the world’s sole form of money. Thus, if Kennedy is pro bitcoin, it seems only natural that Dorsey would fall in line behind him.</p>
<p>At the same time, Dorsey needs to remain realistic about Kennedy’s chances. Right now, polls are showing that while Kennedy has <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/pro-bitcoin-candidate-robert-kennedy-093706291.html">about 20 percent of the</a> democratic vote, he is still miles behind Biden, who presently holds 60 percent, and Biden has been slipping <a href="https://www.politico.com/news/2023/05/07/biden-polling-approval-rating-trump-00095699">heavily in the polls</a> as of late.</p>
<h2>Trump is Still the Frontrunner</h2>
<p>Thus, the idea that this man could even come near someone like Donald Trump – who <a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/meet-the-press/meetthepressblog/new-polls-show-trump-commanding-lead-2024-gop-race-rcna86232">is not only leading</a> by triple digits in republican polls, but is also leading <a href="https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/4012722-trump-beats-biden-by-7-points-in-hypothetical-2024-matchup-poll/">Biden by several points</a> – is a tad ludicrous if not completely farfetched.</p>
<p>Right now, Trump is the true frontrunner for the White House in 2024, likely due to his past track record and performance as president. Biden has done so much damage in the last 2.5 years that many Americans probably don’t want to take too many chances and prefer a candidate with a solid history and a proven ability to turn things around quickly under his belt.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jack-dorsey-backs-btc-fan-robert-kennedy-jr-for-president/">Jack Dorsey Backs BTC Fan Robert Kennedy Jr. for President</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Bears In Action Below $250</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bears-in-action-below-250/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 03:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79381</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline below the $265 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below the $255 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $250 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bears-in-action-below-250/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Bears In Action Below $250</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline below the $265 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below the $255 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $250 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it stays below the $265 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin cash price is declining below the $255 zone against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-regain-strength-above-this-hurdle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. BCH/USD could extend losses if there is a close below $232.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin cash price struggled to gain pace for a move above the $295 and $300 resistance levels. BCH formed a high near $295 and started a fresh decline.</p>
<p>There was a clear move below the $285 and $265 support levels. The pair even declined below the $250 support. It tested the $232 zone. A low is formed near $231.61 and the price is now consolidating losses. It is now trading near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $295.00 swing high to the $231.61 low.</p>
<p>Besides, it is trading below the $250 zone and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bulls-aim-for-fresh-rally-to-350/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. Immediate resistance is near the $249.50 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $250 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair.</p>
<p>The next key resistance is near $265 and the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $295.00 swing high to the $231.61 low. Any more gains above $115 could set the pace for a move toward the $280 level.</p>
<p>If there is a move above the $280 resistance, the price could rise toward the $295 zone. If not, the price might continue lower below $240. Immediate support on the downside is near the $235 zone. The next major support is near the $232 level, below which the bears might aim for $220.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79382" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79382" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-2.png"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-79382" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-2.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-2.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-2-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-2-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-2-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-2-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-2-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-2-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79382" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Cash Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BCHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, Bitcoin cash price is now trading below the $255 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $265 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for BCH/USD is losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BCH/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $240 and $232.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $255 and $265.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bears-in-action-below-250/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Bears In Action Below $250</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Best Meme Coin To Buy Now &#124; Beginner’s Guide To New Meme Coins And New Trending Crypto Projects</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/best-meme-coin-to-buy-now-beginners-guide-to-new-meme-coins-and-new-trending-crypto-projects/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 19:11:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sponsored]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79370</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this extensive guide, we will discuss the best meme coins in the cryptocurrency market. Drawing on insights from credible crypto sources, this detailed resource serves as a helpful guide, discussing key questions that readers have when exploring the world of memecoins. This article walks readers through some of the top meme coins that have [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/best-meme-coin-to-buy-now-beginners-guide-to-new-meme-coins-and-new-trending-crypto-projects/">Best Meme Coin To Buy Now | Beginner’s Guide To New Meme Coins And New Trending Crypto Projects</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this extensive guide, we will discuss the best meme coins in the cryptocurrency market. Drawing on insights from credible crypto sources, this detailed resource serves as a helpful guide, discussing key questions that readers have when exploring the world of memecoins. This article walks readers through some of the top meme coins that have been generating excitement in the crypto world, and provides more detailed information on each of these top meme coins. Uncover the exciting realm of meme coins that are making waves amongst crypto fans.</p>
<p><strong>List of best meme coins to buy now</strong></p>
<p>Below is detailed list of the top meme coins for 2023, gathered through extensive research and analyst insights:</p>
<ol>
<li><strong>ApeMax</strong>: <a href="https://apemax.io/?ref=live_bitcoin_news_1">ApeMax</a> is a cutting-edge meme coin with unique features and fun staking.</li>
<li><strong>Dogecoin</strong>: Original meme coin with a massive following.</li>
<li><strong>Shiba Inu</strong>: Popular meme coin with metaverse and NFT utility.</li>
<li><strong>Floki</strong>: Fast-growing meme token with play-to-earn games and a vibrant marketplace.</li>
<li><strong>Pepe Coin</strong>: Memorable ERC token on Ethereum with a market cap over $600 million.</li>
<li><strong>Sponge</strong>: Fun and light-hearted meme coin inspired by a famous cartoon character.</li>
<li><strong>Copium</strong>: New coin based on internet culture meme.</li>
<li><strong>Wall Street Memes</strong>: Meme token inspired by the Wall Street Bets movement.</li>
<li><strong>SafeMoon</strong>: Popular meme coin with unique tokenomics.</li>
<li><strong>Baby DogeCoin</strong>: Reflective meme coin with emphasis on animal welfare causes.</li>
</ol>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-79372 aligncenter" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture63-600x338.png" alt="" width="600" height="338" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture63-600x338.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture63.png 624w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></p>
<p><strong>What is a meme coin?</strong></p>
<p>A meme coin refers to a form of digital currency that often achieves widespread recognition through its connection to internet memes and viral content. Notable examples include ApeMax, an innovative new meme coin boasting distinctive attributes, Dogecoin, the initial and well-known meme coin, and PEPE Coin, renowned for its propensity for becoming a meme and built on the Ethereum blockchain.</p>
<p><strong>What is the best meme coin?</strong></p>
<p>Following extensive research and analysis, ApeMax emerges as one of the most exciting new meme coins in the crypto space today. Primarily, <a href="https://apemax.io/?ref=live_bitcoin_news_1">ApeMax</a> distinguishes itself with its cutting-edge features and intuitive interface, setting it apart from its counterparts. Additionally, its distinct stake-to-earn mechanism empowers holders to actively participate and possibly earn rewards. Lastly, ApeMax’s cartoon astronaut ape is a fun and lighthearted mascot.</p>
<p><strong>Where to buy meme coins?</strong></p>
<p>When it comes to purchasing meme coins, many crypto analysts often advise to opt for a trustworthy cryptocurrency exchange that provides a diverse range of meme coins for trading to eligible buyers. Furthermore, for eligible buyers interested in acquiring <a href="https://apemax.io/?ref=live_bitcoin_news_1">ApeMax</a>, the presale is currently accessible through their official website, and with discounts of up to 50% for lootboxes.</p>
<p><strong>Where to find meme coins?</strong></p>
<p>To discover new meme coins before they gain widespread attention, individuals can delve into well-known cryptocurrency forums, social media platforms, and dedicated Telegram groups that focus on emerging meme coins. It is also crucial to stay informed about the latest news and updates shared by reputable cryptocurrency influencers and conduct comprehensive research to identify new meme coin projects in their early phases. As for ApeMax, it presents a fun adventure as a novel and innovative meme coin, boasting distinctive attributes and interesting tokenomics. This makes it an entertaining option for eligible buyers to look into if they are searching for exciting new meme coins.</p>
<p><strong>What is Dogecoin?</strong></p>
<p>Dogecoin is a prominent cryptocurrency that gained immense popularity due to its association with internet memes and viral content. It emerged as a lighthearted and playful digital currency, originally created as a fun project in 2013. Dogecoin quickly garnered a massive following and became a recognizable meme coin within the crypto community. Despite its origins as a joke, Dogecoin has established itself as a significant player in the cryptocurrency market, boasting a substantial market capitalization and a passionate community of supporters. Its unique charm and widespread adoption have contributed to its enduring presence and made it one of the most well-known meme coins in the industry.</p>
<p><strong>What is ApeMax?</strong></p>
<p>ApeMax is a revolutionary meme coin that is generating buzz in the crypto space. It stands out as an innovative and cutting-edge digital currency that could have an impact on the cryptocurrency landscape. With its unique features and state-of-the-art tokenomics, <a href="https://apemax.io/?ref=live_bitcoin_news_1">ApeMax</a> offers a fresh and exciting approach to the meme coin market. One of its standout characteristics is its intuitive staking mechanism, which empowers token holders to earn rewards by staking their coins on both Web2 and Web3 entities they like. ApeMax has gained traction and garnered attention for its vibrant community, dynamic ecosystem, and fun image. ApeMax is an interesting new coin worth looking into for those interested in learning about a groundbreaking meme coin that could push the boundaries of what is possible in the crypto world.</p>
<p><strong>What is Shiba Inu?</strong></p>
<p>Shiba Inu is a popular meme coin that has gained significant attention in the cryptocurrency world. Often referred to as the &#8220;Doge Killer,&#8221; <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/shiba-inu">Shiba Inu</a> draws inspiration from the famous Dogecoin and has created its own unique identity within the meme coin space. Shiba Inu offers additional utility beyond being a mere digital token, with its metaverse and NFT features adding fun and engagement for its community. With a growing following and substantial market capitalization, Shiba Inu has captured the interest of both crypto enthusiasts and meme coin fans. Its playful and meme-centric approach, coupled with its innovative features, has contributed to its rise in popularity and its status as a <a href="https://www.outlookindia.com/outlook-spotlight/best-meme-coin-to-buy-now-the-ultimate-guide-to-the-top-meme-coins-and-new-trending-cryptocurrencies-news-298315">prominent meme coin</a> in the market.</p>
<p>Before considering purchasing cryptocurrencies, conduct in-depth independent research, proceed with caution, seek advice from impartial external specialists, and fully comprehend all the risks involved. It is crucial to recognize that cryptocurrencies may not be suitable for all people. Keep in mind that all cryptocurrencies carry inherent high risks and volatility. Individuals from the United States, Canada, countries under sanctions, and other blocked countries are prohibited from acquiring ApeMax tokens. For a comprehensive list of blocked countries, please visit the official ApeMax website.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/best-meme-coin-to-buy-now-beginners-guide-to-new-meme-coins-and-new-trending-crypto-projects/">Best Meme Coin To Buy Now | Beginner’s Guide To New Meme Coins And New Trending Crypto Projects</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Neon EVM Launches on Solana Mainnet</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/neon-evm-launches-on-solana-mainnet/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 19:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79367</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>[PARIS] – July 17, 2023 – During ETHCC23, Neon EVM launched on the Solana Mainnet to help close the gap between the different programming, computing, and memory models of Ethereum and Solana, bringing a low-friction solution to allow EVM dApps to settle to Solana. The Neon EVM program is a smart contract on the Solana [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/neon-evm-launches-on-solana-mainnet/">Neon EVM Launches on Solana Mainnet</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PARIS] – July 17, 2023 –</strong> During ETHCC23, <a href="https://neonevm.org/"><strong>Neon EVM</strong></a> launched on the Solana Mainnet to help close the gap between the different programming, computing, and memory models of Ethereum and Solana, bringing a low-friction solution to allow EVM dApps to settle to Solana.</p>
<p>The Neon EVM program is a smart contract on the Solana blockchain. It accepts wrapped Ethereum-like transactions and processes them on Solana.</p>
<p>Previously, when EVM dApps wanted to leverage low-cost solutions, they had to use a rollup or sidechain. By using Solana as the settlement layer, an EVM is well-placed to outcompete such L2 solutions. The average transaction fee for sending ETH on the Ethereum network is ~$2. The L2s offer between <a href="https://l2fees.info/">$0.5–$0.1</a>, a saving of 4–20 times. In comparison, Solana’s average transaction fees are ~0.00001 SOL ($0.0002) per transaction, 10,000 times saving. Initial tests of Neon EVM in Devnet demonstrate that the protocol <a href="https://medium.com/neon-labs/neon-synthetic-load-test-report-d53212711556">translates these optimizations in practice</a>.</p>
<p>“We are very excited to see Neon EVM live on Solana Mainnet,” says <strong>Marina Guryeva, Director of Neon Foundation</strong>. “Once we repeat these tests in production, we will present the figures based on the real-world data.”</p>
<p>With the launch of Neon EVM on the Solana Mainnet, the Neon DAO is activated to begin participating in, and influencing the future development of, Neon EVM.</p>
<p><strong>About Neon EVM</strong></p>
<p>Neon EVM is an Ethereum Virtual Machine operating as a smart contract on Solana. It gives developers the power to directly deploy Ethereum dApps with minimal reconfiguration to the code, while benefiting from Solana&#8217;s technical advantages. It is built with security, decentralization, and sustainability as core tenants. For more information about Neon EVM and future updates, visit <a href="https://neonevm.org/">NeonEVM.org</a> and connect with the community on <a href="https://twitter.com/Neon_EVM">Twitter</a> or <a href="https://discord.gg/neonevm">Discord</a>.</p>
<p><strong><u>Links and resources:</u></strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Find the Neon EVM community on <a href="https://twitter.com/Neon_EVM">Twitter</a> or <a href="https://discord.gg/neonevm">Discord</a></li>
<li>To choose a public RPC endpoint, see <a href="https://chainlist.org/?chain=245022926&amp;testnets=true&amp;search=Neon+EVM">ChainList</a></li>
<li>For a high-level overview of the technical architecture and features of Neon EVM, the whitepaper is available at <a href="https://neonevm.org/whitepaper.pdf">NeonEVM.org/whitepaper.pdf</a></li>
<li>View Neon EVM transactions settled to Solana with the <a href="https://neonscan.org">NeonScan</a> or <a href="https://neon-mainnet.blockscout.com/">BlockScout</a> explorers.</li>
<li>IRL: Epic Layer 2 Day, an event for researchers, developers, and enthusiasts dedicated to Ethereum L2 Scaling, see <a href="https://lu.ma/l2paris">lu.ma/l2paris</a></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/neon-evm-launches-on-solana-mainnet/">Neon EVM Launches on Solana Mainnet</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Whales are to meet at Blockchain Life 2023 in Dubai</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-whales-are-to-meet-at-blockchain-life-2023-in-dubai/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 18:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79361</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Influential figures such as heads of global funds, government officials, investors, business owners and promising startups come together in Dubai to shape the future of cryptocurrencies and Web3 at the 11th International Blockchain Life Forum on October 24-25 in Dubai, Festival Arena. Watch the epic trailer of the event: https://youtu.be/WCC_w90THWs The event remains as a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-whales-are-to-meet-at-blockchain-life-2023-in-dubai/">Crypto Whales are to meet at Blockchain Life 2023 in Dubai</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Influential figures such as heads of global funds, government officials, investors, business owners and promising startups come together in Dubai to shape the future of cryptocurrencies and Web3 at the 11th International Blockchain Life Forum on October 24-25 in Dubai, Festival Arena.</p>
<p>Watch the epic trailer of the event: <a href="https://youtu.be/WCC_w90THWs">https://youtu.be/WCC_w90THWs</a></p>
<p>The event remains as a meeting point for Crypto Whales, attracting over 7,000 visitors from 120 countries.</p>
<p>Attendees can look forward to informative sessions led by leaders in the crypto industry, innovative expo featuring 100 companies and amazing networking with key decision makers.</p>
<p>Over 80 speakers are going to share their analytics and world-changing ideas.<br />
Among them:</p>
<ul>
<li>E. Justin Sun (Founder of TRON)</li>
<li>Alexander Chehade (General Manager at MENA, Binance)</li>
<li>Fred Thiel (Chairman and CEO of Marathon Digital Holdings)</li>
<li>Sergei Khitrov (Founder of Jets.Capital and Listing.Help)</li>
<li>Xinxi Wang (Co-Founder and Director of Litecoin Foundation)</li>
<li>Carl Runefelt (Crypto Entrepreneur, Founder of CryptoJobs.com)</li>
<li>Chris MMCrypto (Cryptotrader, Founder of MMCrypto)</li>
<li>Tone Vays (Trader, Economic Trends Expert and Analyst, ex-VP at JP Morgan Chase)</li>
<li>Sameer Al Ansari (CEO of Ras Al Khaimah DAO and ICC, UAE Government)</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Hurry up and buy your ticket</em><a href="https://blockchain-life.com/asia/en/?utm_campaign=idolme/#tickets-row"><em> now</em></a><em>.</em></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong> </strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-whales-are-to-meet-at-blockchain-life-2023-in-dubai/">Crypto Whales are to meet at Blockchain Life 2023 in Dubai</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The U.S. is Getting Serious About Crypto Regulation</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-u-s-is-getting-serious-about-crypto-regulation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 17:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paul Grewal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[U.S.]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78669</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new crypto bill designed to at least create a basic framework for crypto regulation in the United States has been submitted to Congress for review and subsequent approval. Is Regulation in the U.S. Getting Stronger? The 162-page draft bill was introduced by House Financial Services Committee chair Patrick McHenry, a republican from North Carolina, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-u-s-is-getting-serious-about-crypto-regulation/">The U.S. is Getting Serious About Crypto Regulation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new crypto bill designed to at least create a basic <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/06/03/congress-introduces-a-game-changing-crypto-bill-amid-bitcoin-ethereum-bnb-and-xrp-price-pump/?sh=204ce1ce3cbb">framework for crypto regulation</a> in the United States has been submitted to Congress for review and subsequent approval.</p>
<h2>Is Regulation in the U.S. Getting Stronger?</h2>
<p>The 162-page draft bill was introduced by House Financial Services Committee chair Patrick McHenry, a republican from North Carolina, and House Agriculture Committee chair Glenn Thompson, a republican from Pennsylvania (leave it to the republicans to take the lead in getting things done).</p>
<p>The U.S. has really fallen behind in many ways when it comes to crypto regulation. Not long ago, the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-eu-is-implementing-new-crypto-regulations/">European Union</a> (EU) and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-united-kingdom-announces-plans-for-new-crypto-regulations/">the UK</a> introduced new crypto legislation designed to not only keep investors safe, but also ensure blockchain and crypto firms stayed in line. By contrast, while the U.S. has spoken about crypto regulation for some time, the nation has done little to nothing to get it implemented.</p>
<p>This has led to several issues in that right now, in the nation, agencies such as the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) have little to go on and are thus operating in a very persecuting way. These agencies are simply going after crypto companies and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/">inflicting penalties wherever</a> possible, though everyone knows this is not the strategy you use to get firms to fall in line.</p>
<p>Several companies – including Coinbase – <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-is-now-active-in-bermuda/">have even left</a> the U.S. or opened separate divisions in international territory as a means of avoiding ongoing crypto regulation confusion in America.</p>
<p>The bill seeks to ensure that the boundaries of both the SEC and the CFTC (Commodity Futures Trading Commission) are set in stone. It makes it clear which arenas are controlled or overseen by which, and the other cannot step into territory dominated or monitored by the other.</p>
<p>The bill leaves a lot of room open for improvement, though for the most part, bitcoin and crypto advocates are lauding the bill as a solid step forward for the industry. Paul Grewal – chief legal officer at bitcoin and crypto exchange Coinbase – commented on Twitter:</p>
<blockquote><p>A comprehensive bill of this magnitude warrants an in-depth review, which we’ll be conducting over the coming days, but what we’re seeing so far is encouraging.</p></blockquote>
<h2>This is a Gamechanger</h2>
<p>This sentiment was echoed by Ryann Selkis, founder at crypto data company Messari. He wrote online:</p>
<blockquote><p>It’s a win this year for crypto to even get some attention in DC right now after last year&#8217;s setbacks. There is still a lot of work to do to get to a viable piece of legislation, but this is a good starting point for a sensible market structure bill.</p></blockquote>
<p>Over the last eight months, the U.S. has faced increasing pressure to input the appropriate crypto-related laws into its legal system due to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/">the FTX collapse</a> of eight months ago.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-u-s-is-getting-serious-about-crypto-regulation/">The U.S. is Getting Serious About Crypto Regulation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Head David Duong Says Blockchain Can Fix Up AI</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-head-david-duong-says-blockchain-can-fix-up-ai/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 15:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[David Duong]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78667</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>David Duong – head of research at Coinbase – says in a new report that blockchain could potentially aid in the many problems already coming about in the artificial intelligence (AI) arena. David Duong on Blockchain and AI In the report, Duong said: As applications within AI and blockchain mature, the disruptions these technologies represent [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-head-david-duong-says-blockchain-can-fix-up-ai/">Coinbase Head David Duong Says Blockchain Can Fix Up AI</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>David Duong – head of research at Coinbase – says in a <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/crypto-and-blockchain-technology-can-be-crucial-tools-that-help-keep-ai-from-running-wild-coinbase-says/ar-AA1c9kdJ">new report that blockchain</a> could potentially aid in the many problems already coming about in the artificial intelligence (AI) arena.</p>
<h2>David Duong on Blockchain and AI</h2>
<p>In the report, Duong said:</p>
<blockquote><p>As applications within AI and blockchain mature, the disruptions these technologies represent may lead to areas of collaboration and the emergence of new use cases for crypto to help address specific societal challenges posed by AI.</p></blockquote>
<p>Duong lists five distinct problems in the document that have emerged through the introduction of applications like Chat GPT. The first is the demand for data resources. With this one, he writes:</p>
<blockquote><p>A system of token incentives and penalties could ensure that the data meets the sufficient standards of quality needed by these models.</p></blockquote>
<p>The second problem is the demand for computational resources. He says there’s a lot of computing power necessary to ensure generative AI moves accordingly. He also said <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/blockchain/">blockchain</a> could potentially create a system where resources are regularly shared. He wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>Decentralized networks of computing power can reward users who volunteer their idle GPUs to help relieve some of this computational burden.</p></blockquote>
<p>The third problem to emerge involves misinformation or disinformation. Duong commented on the large amount of fake news that has emerged in recent years and platforms that often spew out lies as pure facts. Regarding this issue, he writes:</p>
<blockquote><p>Blockchain and non-fungible token (NFT) technology can help combat this by establishing the provenance of images, video, music, and other media.</p></blockquote>
<p>The fourth problem is auditability. Right now, he described AI decision-making processes as “opaque,” and said the verifiability of blockchain is what could make AI as clear and as transparent as the latter technology. He writes:</p>
<blockquote><p>Integrating blockchain technology into AI models can help make those processes more transparent and allow users to scrutinize the logic and reliability of AI-produced outcomes.</p></blockquote>
<p>The fifth and final issue discussed in the report is the democratizing of AI development and subsequent use. He said that crypto, which was designed to ensure people could gain equal access to financial and technological arenas, might help to ensure AI can be accessible by a larger group of people. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Crypto platforms can help source a more diverse set of contributions, as well as redistribute access so more users can take advantage of its benefits (e.g., healthcare advice or e-commerce).</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Scary Arena?</h2>
<p>AI, in many ways, is a growing industry. While it’s been around for some time, not until now was it beginning to show true promise and a real capacity for growth.</p>
<p>This has ultimately made several people involved in the technology space a little frightened. For example, South African billionaire Elon Musk has commented <a href="https://www.vox.com/future-perfect/2018/11/2/18053418/elon-musk-artificial-intelligence-google-deepmind-openai">that it could ruin</a> society as we know it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-head-david-duong-says-blockchain-can-fix-up-ai/">Coinbase Head David Duong Says Blockchain Can Fix Up AI</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coin Center and Blockchain Association Fight Tornado Cash Crypto Sanctions</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coin-center-and-blockchain-association-fight-tornado-cash-crypto-sanctions/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 13:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Association]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coin Center]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tornado Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78654</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Blockchain Association has filed an amicus brief in a lawsuit filed by the think tank Coin Center against the Treasury Department and the Office of Foreign Asset Control. The brief has to do with the latter two agencies’ sanctions against crypto mixer Tornado Cash. Tornado Cash Has Some Soldiers Fighting for It Last year, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coin-center-and-blockchain-association-fight-tornado-cash-crypto-sanctions/">Coin Center and Blockchain Association Fight Tornado Cash Crypto Sanctions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Blockchain Association has filed an amicus brief in <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/blockchain-association-files-amicus-brief-in-coin-center-lawsuit-against-u-s-treasury-over-tornado-cash-sanctions/ar-AA1c3hQI">a lawsuit filed by the</a> think tank Coin Center against the Treasury Department and the Office of Foreign Asset Control. The brief has to do with the latter two agencies’ sanctions against crypto mixer Tornado Cash.</p>
<h2>Tornado Cash Has Some Soldiers Fighting for It</h2>
<p>Last year, sanctions were filed against Tornado Cash <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/north-korea-crypto-mixer-tornado-cash-sanctioned-by-u-s/">after it was alleged that</a> the tool had been used to launder crypto funds garnered by bad actors in North Korea, who were using the money to build the nation’s ongoing nuclear program. It’s alleged that the tool has been utilized to launder over $7 billion dollars in crypto.</p>
<p>At the time, Brian Nelson – Secretary of the Treasury for Terrorism and Financial Intelligence – mentioned in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Despite public assurances otherwise, Tornado Cash has repeatedly failed to impose effective controls designed to stop it from laundering funds for malicious cyber actors on a regular basis and without basic measures to address its risks. The Treasury will continue to aggressively pursue actions against mixers that launder virtual currency for criminals and those who assist them.</p></blockquote>
<p>In the lawsuit against the Treasury, Coin Center said the sanctions against Tornado Cash have blocked Americans from using the tool and from trading privately. Blockchain Association CEO Kristin Smith explained in a recent statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>It&#8217;s critical to recognize that Tornado Cash is simply a tool. Punishing the tool itself simply because it can be used by anyone, including bad actors, runs contrary to the values this country was founded upon. Blockchain Association stands with Coin Center, advocating for the responsible and lawful use of blockchain technology. Regulatory actions should only be targeted at bad actors who abuse this tool for illegal purposes.</p></blockquote>
<p>This is the second lawsuit filed against the Treasury over its sanctions of Tornado Cash, which has been getting hit by agencies since last August. OFAC was the first department to file sanctions against Tornado (nearly one year ago), claiming hackers in North Korea laundered hundreds of millions of dollars in crypto just weeks after it was first put in play.</p>
<h2>A Lot of Illegal Activity</h2>
<p>It’s estimated that as many as 20 percent of the transactions to be put through Tornado have been illicit. The present Coin Center suit explains:</p>
<blockquote><p>An order effectively requiring [the] defendants to decriminalize use of the 20 Tornado Cash addresses would allow [the] plaintiffs to conduct their legitimate activities with some measure of anonymity, use their preferred software tool without fear of penalties, and engage in important expressive associations. Judicial relief would also serve the public interest by averting harm to Tornado Cash users who are United States persons, to Ethereum as a freedom and privacy enhancing technology, and to the important sector of the economy that depends on Ethereum.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coin-center-and-blockchain-association-fight-tornado-cash-crypto-sanctions/">Coin Center and Blockchain Association Fight Tornado Cash Crypto Sanctions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EOS Price Analysis: Key Uptrend Support Nearby</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-key-uptrend-support-nearby/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 05:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EOS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79358</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>EOS price is trading in a bearish zone below the $0.785 support against the US Dollar. The price is now trading near $0.760 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key contracting triangle forming with resistance near $0.770 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-key-uptrend-support-nearby/">EOS Price Analysis: Key Uptrend Support Nearby</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>EOS price is trading in a bearish zone below the $0.785 support against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading near $0.760 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key contracting triangle forming with resistance near $0.770 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to rise toward the $0.78 and $0.80 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>EOS price is struggling below $0.80 against the US Dollar, like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-regain-strength-above-this-hurdle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. The price might attempt to recover if there is a clear move above $0.78.</em></p>
<h2>EOS Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few sessions, EOS price range moves below the $0.80 resistance against the US Dollar. The price remained stable above the $0.735 and $0.740 support levels.</p>
<p>A low is formed near $0.7379 and the price is now attempting an upside correction. There was a move above the $0.750 resistance level. Besides, there was a break above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.8339 swing high to the $0.7379 low.</p>
<p>The price is now trading near $0.76 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-key-uptrend-support-intact-at-0-70/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. There is also a key contracting triangle forming with resistance near $0.770 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair.</p>
<p>On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $0.77 level. The next major resistance is near the $0.785 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.8339 swing high to the $0.7379 low, above which the price might test the $0.80 level.</p>
<p>Any more gains might send the price toward the $0.840 level. On the downside, immediate support is near the $0.74 level. The next key support is near the $0.735 level. If there is a downside break below the $0.735 support, the price could test the $0.70 support in the near term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79359" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79359" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-2.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-79359" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-2.png" alt="EOS Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-2.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-2-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-2-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-2-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-2-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-2-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-2-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79359" class="wp-caption-text">EOS Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/EOSUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, EOS price is now trading near the $0.76 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to rise toward the $0.78 and $0.80 resistance levels in the near term.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for EOS/USD is losing pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $0.740 and $0.735.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $0.780 and $0.800.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-key-uptrend-support-nearby/">EOS Price Analysis: Key Uptrend Support Nearby</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
