<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 01:52:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Aims Steady Increase To $18K</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-steady-increase-to-18k/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-steady-increase-to-18k/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 01:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76335</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price started a recovery wave above the $16,500 support against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above $16,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $16,780 on the 4-hours chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-steady-increase-to-18k/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-steady-increase-to-18k/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Aims Steady Increase To $18K</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin price started a recovery wave above the $16,500 support against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $16,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $16,780 on the 4-hours chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could rise further if it clears the $17,000 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin price is recovering above $16,500 against the US Dollar. BTC might extend its recovery if it stays above the $16,600 support zone.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-drop-to-new-2022-lows/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">remained well supported</a> near the $16,250 zone. The price formed a base and started a recovery wave above the $16,500 level.</p>
<p>There was a decent increase above the $16,650 resistance zone and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $16,780 on the 4-hours chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>The pair surpassed the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $18,385 swing high to $16,273 low. The price is now trading above $16,500 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-at-risk-of-another-crash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. The price is now consolidating above $16,800.</p>
<p>An immediate resistance on the upside is near the $17,000 level. The next major resistance might near the $17,320 zone. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $18,385 swing high to $16,273 low.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $17,320 level might send the price towards $18,000, above which the price might rise towards the $18,500 resistance. Any more gains might push the price towards the $19,000 zone. If there is no upside break, the price might start a fresh decline below $16,750.</p>
<p>The first major support is near the $16,650 level. The next key support is near the $16,250 level, below which the price might accelerate lower.</p>
<p>In the stated case, the price could decline towards the $16,000 level. Any more losses might send the price towards the $15,500 level.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Bitcoin.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-76336" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Bitcoin.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a></p>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XBTUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, bitcoin price is clearly trading above $16,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could rise further if it clears the $17,000 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $16,650 and $16,250.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $17,000, $17,320 and $18,000.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-steady-increase-to-18k/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Aims Steady Increase To $18K</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-steady-increase-to-18k/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Matrix Port: Crypto Insurance Should Be a Regular Offering</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/matrix-port-crypto-insurance-should-be-a-regular-offering/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/matrix-port-crypto-insurance-should-be-a-regular-offering/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 17:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[insurance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Matrix Port]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75777</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Matrix Port – a crypto services provider – believes it’s time for all crypto custody firms and related businesses to begin offering insurance to digital currency customers. Matrix Port Wants Crypto Insurance Offered Everywhere The belief stems from the recent fall of disgraced crypto exchange FTX, which took less than a week to crash and<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/matrix-port-crypto-insurance-should-be-a-regular-offering/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/matrix-port-crypto-insurance-should-be-a-regular-offering/">Matrix Port: Crypto Insurance Should Be a Regular Offering</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Matrix Port – a crypto services provider – believes it’s time <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/matrixport-favors-systematic-bitcoin-call-115331208.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">for all crypto custody firms</a> and related businesses to begin offering insurance to digital currency customers.</p>
<h2>Matrix Port Wants Crypto Insurance Offered Everywhere</h2>
<p>The belief stems from the recent fall of disgraced crypto exchange FTX, which took less than a week to crash and burn. Despite being only three years old, FTX (which began in 2019) rose through the ranks rather quickly to become one of the biggest and most popular digital currency exchanges in the world. Many crypto enthusiasts and analysts labeled Sam Bankman-Fried, the company’s founder and head executive, as a genius, and felt he possessed true business acumen.</p>
<p>Sadly, this reputation fell apart quickly <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">when in mid-November</a>, Bankman-Fried issued a statement claiming his company was experiencing a liquidity crunch, and that funds were needed fast. Initially, it looked like the company <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">was going to be bought</a> out by its larger competitor Binance, though this didn’t happen given the bigger enterprise felt the problems FTX was dealing <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">with were too big for it</a> handle.</p>
<p>From there, FTX had no choice but to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">enter bankruptcy proceedings</a>. Sam Bankman-Fried also resigned from his post.</p>
<p>Given this situation and the fact that bitcoin has lost more than 70 percent of its value in the past 12 months, Matrix Port thinks crypto insurance policies should be a new and regular thing for all investors seeking to place their funds into this growing space. Markus Thielen – the head of research at Matrix Port – commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8216;The &#8216;weekly systematic call overwriting strategy&#8217; could be a winner as the industry likely moves through several months of uncertainty.</p></blockquote>
<p>While he feels the idea has a lot of promise, he was quick to acknowledge that it would not come without certain issues, and he discussed how those issues could be addressed and dealt with. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The biggest risk for this strategy is a raging bull market with high volatility due to excessive leverage returns, as we have seen in early to mid-2021. Since the summer of 2021, exchanges have cut down on leverage, and offering customers excessive leverage seems unlikely in a post-FTX crypto world when the regulator will likely take a close look at retail’s ability to access leverage.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Now Might Be the Time</h2>
<p>He finished by saying that over the last year, the crypto space has been subjected to more stress than ever since it first came about in late 2008, and he’s confident that the time for invoking such an insurance plan is now. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>The recent stress in the crypto world has lifted volatility above the five-year moving average. The rise in volatility has increased the value of calls. Hence, this strategy has become even more attractive now as the strategy can sell calls for a higher premium.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/matrix-port-crypto-insurance-should-be-a-regular-offering/">Matrix Port: Crypto Insurance Should Be a Regular Offering</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/matrix-port-crypto-insurance-should-be-a-regular-offering/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Opinion: New York REALLY Needs to Change Its Attitude Towards Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-new-york-really-needs-to-change-its-attitude-towards-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-new-york-really-needs-to-change-its-attitude-towards-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 15:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OpEd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kathy Hochul]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New York]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75774</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York, for lack of better terms, is behaving very foolishly when it comes to the growing crypto space. New York Should View Crypto in a Stronger Light The industry has shown itself to have a lot of prowess despite the volatility of coins and the actions of a few bad companies here and there.<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-new-york-really-needs-to-change-its-attitude-towards-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-new-york-really-needs-to-change-its-attitude-towards-crypto/">Opinion: New York REALLY Needs to Change Its Attitude Towards Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York, for lack of better terms, is behaving very foolishly when it comes to the growing crypto space.</p>
<h2>New York Should View Crypto in a Stronger Light</h2>
<p>The industry has shown itself to have a lot of prowess despite the volatility of coins and the actions of a few bad companies here and there. In many ways, the industry is likely to revolutionize finance in more ways than one, but when a major hub like the Empire State continues to turn its back on the industry and label it as something that should be ignored or passed over, you know there’s a problem.</p>
<p>New York is one of the biggest, most populated areas in the United States. With so many people living there, crypto companies stand to gain a lot of business. This business can feed funds back into the local and state economies and make New York more powerful than it’s been. Sadly, the region continues to show it doesn’t care about crypto, nor does it have any intention of allowing the crypto space to hold sway or presence.</p>
<p>Proof of this arrived <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-continues-to-not-care-about-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">in the recent re-election</a> of Governor Kathy Hochul, who has done nothing for the state except keep it in a constant blue swing of depression and crime. Hochul ran a relatively weak campaign against her republican candidate Lee Zeldin, who throughout his time in the governor’s race, showed that he wanted to do things to improve the state. He commented that it was time to bring an end to crime, and he also brought crypto into the midst.</p>
<p>At the time, New York <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-governor-hochul-facing-real-pressure-to-sign-crypto-moratorium/" data-wpel-link="internal">had a new bill on</a> the table that was slated to bring a temporary end to all new crypto mining ventures within its borders. Zeldin felt that the bill was going to limit innovation and that it could potentially prevent New York from moving ahead in the financial arena. He said he would not sign the bill into law if he was elected governor.</p>
<p>Sadly, nobody seemed to care about this as Hochul won her race. Despite her taking no clear stance on any of the matters at hand, native and incoming New Yorkers clearly showed that they preferred to maintain the status quo – no matter how shaky it was – and keep moving in the same direction.</p>
<h2>The State Is Losing Out!</h2>
<p>Now, Hochul has signed <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-signs-crypto-moratorium-into-law/" data-wpel-link="internal">the new crypto bill into law</a>, enforcing a new moratorium that will prevent mining companies from setting up shop in the Empire State for the next two years. The only way they can do so is if they revoke their proof of work protocols, which allegedly utilize too much energy.</p>
<p>Between all this and the <a href="https://cryptowallet.com/glossary/bitlicense/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">BitLicense</a> it refuses to get rid of, New York is in great danger of falling behind when it comes to crypto innovation and growth.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-new-york-really-needs-to-change-its-attitude-towards-crypto/">Opinion: New York REALLY Needs to Change Its Attitude Towards Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-new-york-really-needs-to-change-its-attitude-towards-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MLB Ends Partnership with Fallen Crypto Exchange FTX</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mlb-ends-partnership-with-fallen-crypto-exchange-ftx/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mlb-ends-partnership-with-fallen-crypto-exchange-ftx/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 13:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OpEd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MLB]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75771</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Major League Baseball (MLB) has announced it’s not looking to continue the deal it struck with now fallen crypto exchange FTX. The MLB Is Stepping Away from FTX The deal was initially formed prior to 2021, though it’s taken some time for things to get off the ground. Now that the company has filed bankruptcy<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mlb-ends-partnership-with-fallen-crypto-exchange-ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mlb-ends-partnership-with-fallen-crypto-exchange-ftx/">MLB Ends Partnership with Fallen Crypto Exchange FTX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Major League Baseball (MLB) has announced <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/mlb/major-league-baseball-to-cut-ties-with-cryptocurrency-firm-ftx-in-2023/ar-AA14AybJ" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">it’s not looking to continue</a> the deal it struck with now fallen crypto exchange FTX.</p>
<h2>The MLB Is Stepping Away from FTX</h2>
<p>The deal was initially formed prior to 2021, though it’s taken some time for things to get off the ground. Now that the company has filed bankruptcy and lost so much money due to illicit accounting activities, the MLB has said that it’s looking to back out of the deal and part ways with the disgraced digital currency company for good.</p>
<p>MLB commissioner Rob Manfred issued the following statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>The FTX development was a little jarring. We have been careful moving forward in this space. We’ve been religious about staying away from coins themselves as opposed to more company-based sponsorships. We think that was prudent particularly given the way things unfolded. We will proceed with caution in the future.</p></blockquote>
<p>The deal was considered one of the most revolutionary in the space. This was the first time when a professional sports league had conjured such a deal with a crypto exchange. What a shame that things have come to such an ugly and drastic end.</p>
<p>FTX will likely go down as one of the most embarrassing events to ever occur within the realms of the digital currency arena. Formed in the year 2019, FTX was still a relatively new venture, though it came to fruition rather quickly and rose through the ranks to become one of the biggest and most popular digital currency exchanges in the world.</p>
<p>Many industry heads and analysts lauded the company’s founder and head executive, Sam Bankman-Fried, as a genius. They were surprised by how far he was allegedly able to take the company in a relatively short period, and they commended him for what they felt was true business acumen. Unfortunately, this reputation has fallen apart in recent weeks given the company has suddenly come crashing down.</p>
<p>Trouble began in mid-November when Bankman-Fried announced that FTX <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">was experiencing a liquidity</a> crunch and needed funds. Initially, the company went to Binance for help and asked if the larger company was willing to buy it out or engage in an acquisition of sorts to bring it back to form. At first, it looked like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">this was going to happen</a>, though eventually, Binance backed out of the deal and issued a statement that the problems FTX was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">dealing with were too</a> big for it to handle.</p>
<h2>The End of an Era?</h2>
<p>From there, FTX had no choice but to engage in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">bankruptcy proceedings</a>. Its executive Sam Bankman-Fried also resigned from his post, and the company’s reputation has now been fully tarnished, likely on a permanent basis.</p>
<p>Several MLB players such as <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tom-brady-named-in-new-ftx-based-lawsuit/" data-wpel-link="internal">former slugger David Ortiz</a> have been named in a lawsuit for their alleged promotion of the failed company.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mlb-ends-partnership-with-fallen-crypto-exchange-ftx/">MLB Ends Partnership with Fallen Crypto Exchange FTX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mlb-ends-partnership-with-fallen-crypto-exchange-ftx/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Bulls Aim Fresh Increase Above $0.28</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-bulls-aim-fresh-increase-above-0-28/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-bulls-aim-fresh-increase-above-0-28/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 04:28:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76312</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ADA price seems to be forming a support base above the $0.24 level against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above $0.250 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.270 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Bitfinex). The price could gain<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-bulls-aim-fresh-increase-above-0-28/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-bulls-aim-fresh-increase-above-0-28/">Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Bulls Aim Fresh Increase Above $0.28</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>ADA price seems to be forming a support base above the $0.24 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $0.250 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.270 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Bitfinex).</li>
<li>The price could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $0.270 and $0.30 levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Cardano price is showing positive signs above $0.250 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-drop-to-new-2022-lows/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. ADA price could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $0.270 resistance.</em></p>
<h2>Cardano Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, cardano price started a steady increase from the $0.2380 zone against the US Dollar. The ADA/USD pair gained pace for a move above the $0.245 and $0.250 levels.</p>
<p>It even broke the $0.260 level and settled above the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-key-resistance-and-downtrend-intact/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. There was a clear move above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3200 swing high to $0.2391 low. It is now showing positive signs above the $0.2600 level.</p>
<p>The price is trading above $0.260 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $0.265 zone.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $0.270 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.270 on the 4-hours chart. A clear move above the $0.270 resistance might start a strong increase. In the stated case, the price may perhaps rise towards the $0.300 resistance.</p>
<p>An intermediate resistance might be near the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3200 swing high to $0.2391 low. On the downside, an immediate support is near the $0.250 level. The next major support is near the $0.240 level.</p>
<p>A clear move below the $0.240 level might send the price towards the $0.220 level. Any more losses might send the price towards the $0.200 support.</p>
<div id="attachment_76313" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Cardano-Price.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76313" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-76313" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Cardano-Price.png" alt="Cardano (ADA) Price " width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76313" class="wp-caption-text">Cardano (ADA) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ADAUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that ADA price is now trading above $0.250 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $0.270 and $0.300 levels.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ADA/USD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for ADA/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.250 and $0.240.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.270 and $0.300.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-bulls-aim-fresh-increase-above-0-28/">Cardano (ADA) Price Analysis: Bulls Aim Fresh Increase Above $0.28</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cardano-ada-price-analysis-bulls-aim-fresh-increase-above-0-28/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Could Gain Pace Above $1,250</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-gain-pace-above-1250/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-gain-pace-above-1250/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 01:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76308</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum price is slowly moving higher from the $1,180 level against the US Dollar. ETH price is now trading above $1,180 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $1,195 on the 4-hours chart (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could start a decent increase<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-gain-pace-above-1250/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-gain-pace-above-1250/">Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Could Gain Pace Above $1,250</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ethereum price is slowly moving higher from the $1,180 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>ETH price is now trading above $1,180 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $1,195 on the 4-hours chart (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could start a decent increase if it clears the $1,250 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ethereum price is struggling below $1,250 against the US Dollar. ETH/USD could start a decent increase if it clears the $1,250 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Ethereum Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, ethereum <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-attempt-fresh-increase-above-1240/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">remained well bid</a> above the $1,165 level against the US Dollar. ETH price formed a base and slowly moved higher above the $1,180 level.</p>
<p>The price climbed above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the key decline from the $1,351 swing high to $1,150 low. Ether price is now trading above $1,180 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-turns-red-again-risk-of-more-downsides/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support near $1,195 on the 4-hours chart.</p>
<p>However, the price is now facing a major hurdle near the $1,230 level. The first major resistance is near the $1,250 level. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the key decline from the $1,351 swing high to $1,150 low. The next major resistance is near the $1,274 zone.</p>
<p>The main resistance is near the $1,300 zone. A clear move above the $1,274 and $1,300 resistance levels might call for a fresh move to $1,350. Any more gains could even send the price towards the $1,400 resistance zone or even $1,450 in the near term.</p>
<p>On the downside, an initial support is near the $1,200 level and the trend line. The next major support is now near the $1,180 level. A break below the $1,180 support could push the price to $1,150. If the bulls struggle to protect the $1,150 support, the price might decline towards $1,080.</p>
<div id="attachment_76309" style="width: 1950px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Ethereum.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76309" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-76309" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Ethereum.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1950" height="1109" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76309" class="wp-caption-text">Ethereum Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Ethereum price is clearly trading above $1,200 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, ether price could start a decent increase if it clears the $1,250 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $1,200, followed by the $1,150 zone.</p>
<p>Key Resistance$ Levels – $1,250 and $1,275.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-gain-pace-above-1250/">Ethereum Price Analysis: ETH Could Gain Pace Above $1,250</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-gain-pace-above-1250/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Offers Proof of Bitcoin Reserves to Calm Traders&#8217; Fears</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-offers-proof-of-bitcoin-reserves-to-calm-traders-fears/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-offers-proof-of-bitcoin-reserves-to-calm-traders-fears/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75769</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance, the world’s largest and most popular digital currency exchange, has announced a new program that will give all current and future crypto investors proof of its present bitcoin and Ethereum reserves. Binance Tries to Show It&#8217;s Not Like FTX The goal is to shed light on the issue of transparency and show the company<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-offers-proof-of-bitcoin-reserves-to-calm-traders-fears/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-offers-proof-of-bitcoin-reserves-to-calm-traders-fears/">Binance Offers Proof of Bitcoin Reserves to Calm Traders&#8217; Fears</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance, the world’s largest and most popular digital currency exchange, <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/binance-launches-proof-system-bitcoin-141925970.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">has announced a new program</a> that will give all current and future crypto investors proof of its present bitcoin and Ethereum reserves.</p>
<h2>Binance Tries to Show It&#8217;s Not Like FTX</h2>
<p>The goal is to shed light on the issue of transparency and show the company is nothing like FTX, the now failed digital currency exchange that came to fruition only three years ago in 2019. Binance was initially in line to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">purchase the digital currency</a> exchange when it began experiencing financial problems, though the company later decided that the issues FTX was facing were too big for it to handle, and it <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">wound up backing out</a> of the deal.</p>
<p>In any case, it looks like Binance is taking a lesson from the fiasco that is FTX and trying to not only separate itself from the now deceased company, but also show people why it and the crypto arena in general can still be trusted.</p>
<p>Right now, the company has made clear how much BTC and ETH it has in its reserves tank, though it’s not stopping here. The company has issued a statement suggesting it has more crypto units to its name, and information about those reserves will be made available in the coming weeks.</p>
<p>The statement says:</p>
<blockquote><p>When we say proof of reserves, we are specifically referring to those assets that we hold in custody for users. This means that we are showing evidence and proof that Binance has funds that cover all our users’ assets 1:1, as well as some reserves.</p></blockquote>
<p>At the time of this article’s writing, Binance has released a screenshot showing that it has more than 582,000 bitcoin units stashed away. Right now, there are just over 572,000 units of bitcoin stored on the exchange that are owned by individual traders. From this information alone, we can assume that Binance has enough money to cover everybody’s stashes and potential losses (should they occur) while still having a little left over.</p>
<p>This may appear positive at first glance, but there are several traders out there who feel this isn’t enough. Binance anticipated this attitude and provided steps in a recent press release discussing how traders can verify this data for themselves and ensure their units are privately accounted for.</p>
<h2>See for Yourself!</h2>
<p>The release said:</p>
<blockquote><p>For those who want to go a step further and independently verify their funds, they can copy the source code into a python application and cross reference it themselves.</p></blockquote>
<p>FTX was long considered the golden child of the digital currency world, and its founder and chief executive, Sam Bankman-Fried, was lauded as a genius by many for his ability to potentially take a major company as far as he reportedly did in just three years.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-offers-proof-of-bitcoin-reserves-to-calm-traders-fears/">Binance Offers Proof of Bitcoin Reserves to Calm Traders&#8217; Fears</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-offers-proof-of-bitcoin-reserves-to-calm-traders-fears/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mark Cuban Still Believes in Crypto&#8217;s Power</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-still-believes-in-cryptos-power/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-still-believes-in-cryptos-power/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 15:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mark Cuban]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Voyager Digital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75766</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Billionaire investor and crypto bull Mark Cuban has not lost faith in digital currencies. Despite all the problems that have been occurring with FTX and the price of bitcoin, Cuban still feels that there’s a lot the space can offer. Mark Cuban Remains Confident in Crypto In a recent interview, he mentioned: Separate the signal<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-still-believes-in-cryptos-power/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-still-believes-in-cryptos-power/">Mark Cuban Still Believes in Crypto&#8217;s Power</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Billionaire investor and crypto bull Mark Cuban <a href="https://www.thestreet.com/investing/cryptocurrency/ftx-collapse-billionaire-mark-cuban-remains-a-crypto-follower" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">has not lost faith in digital</a> currencies. Despite all the problems that have been <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">occurring with FTX</a> and the price of bitcoin, Cuban still feels that there’s a lot the space can offer.</p>
<h2>Mark Cuban Remains Confident in Crypto</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, he mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Separate the signal from the noise. There&#8217;s been a lot of people making a lot of mistakes, but it doesn&#8217;t change the underlying value.</p></blockquote>
<p>He doesn’t think the space is in any danger of tanking given that so many people continue to invest in digital currencies and there are so many doors open to it. He admits that while FTX and other bad actors have delivered some wounds, he doesn’t think any of them are fatal. These are a few bad companies in a larger industry that is likely to last based on the power of the technology behind it.</p>
<p>Mark Cuban is currently the subject of a crypto-based lawsuit. Several investors of Voyager Digital – a firm <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-in-the-age-of-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">that went bust in 2022</a> – say they lost all their life savings due to investing their money in the company, which Cuban had spent quite a bit of time promoting. They say they would not have placed their money into the company had Cuban not been their spokesperson. The suit also named Stephen Ehrlich, the former CEO of Voyager.</p>
<p>The lawsuit mentions:</p>
<blockquote><p>Cuban and Ehrlich, as will be explained, went to great lengths to use their experience as investors to dupe millions of Americans into investing — in many cases, their life savings — into the deceptive Voyager platform and purchasing Voyager earn program accounts (EPAs), which are unregistered securities. As a result, over 3.5 million Americans have now all but lost over $5 billion in cryptocurrency assets.</p></blockquote>
<p>The bankruptcy of Voyager Digital happened as a direct <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-luna-token-has-experienced-a-dramatic-drop/" data-wpel-link="internal">result of the Terra Luna</a> coin’s collapse in the summer of last year. Citing his faith in the digital currency market, Cuban wrote on Twitter:</p>
<blockquote><p>A basic question. Why have I invested in crypto? Because I believe smart contracts will have a significant impact in creating valuable applications. I have said from day one [that] the value of a token is derived from the applications that run on its platform and the utility they create. What has not been created is an application that is ubiquitous. One that is obviously needed by everyone, and they are willing to go through the learning curve to use. Maybe it never comes. I hope and think it will.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Crypto Is Like Streaming Music</h2>
<p>He also said that the crypto industry is a lot like the streaming industry, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>The best analogy I can use is the early days of streaming. The sh*t people had to do to listen to a 16K stream of music was insane.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-still-believes-in-cryptos-power/">Mark Cuban Still Believes in Crypto&#8217;s Power</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mark-cuban-still-believes-in-cryptos-power/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Oregon Tells Residents to Avoid Crypto Investments</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/oregon-tells-residents-to-avoid-crypto-investments/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/oregon-tells-residents-to-avoid-crypto-investments/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 13:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oregon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=75763</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The state of Oregon has put out a notice to all its residents warning them that investing in crypto could be a costly mistake. Oregon to Investors: Avoid Crypto The warning stems from the Oregon Division of Financial Regulation (DFR) and comes fresh off the heels of the FTX collapse, which arguably sent ripples throughout<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/oregon-tells-residents-to-avoid-crypto-investments/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/oregon-tells-residents-to-avoid-crypto-investments/">Oregon Tells Residents to Avoid Crypto Investments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The state of Oregon has put out a notice to all its <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/caution-urged-state-issues-cryptocurrency-041900070.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">residents warning them</a> that investing in crypto could be a costly mistake.</p>
<h2>Oregon to Investors: Avoid Crypto</h2>
<p>The warning stems from the Oregon Division of Financial Regulation (DFR) and comes fresh off the heels of the FTX collapse, which arguably sent ripples throughout the space and caused many analysts, traders, and industry heads alike to be stunned with surprise. Nobody expected what has been labeled the industry’s golden player over the last three years to fall into a dismal array of crime and failure.</p>
<p>The warning tells Oregon investors to diversify their portfolios as much as they can and to steer clear of largely unregulated products which, unfortunately, include cryptocurrencies. In the statement, DFR administrator TK Keen explains:</p>
<blockquote><p>It is important to know the risks involved with cryptocurrency or any investment opportunities. No investment opportunities are risk-free, and you should always do your homework on where you are sending your money. This is especially true when cryptocurrency is involved.</p></blockquote>
<p>Further discussing what’s been <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">happening with FTX</a>, Keen commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Investing in cryptocurrency is extremely risky given what&#8217;s going on right now. It&#8217;s important to not invest more than you can afford to lose or put all of your assets in one bucket.</p></blockquote>
<p>The DFR is also warning residents to keep their eyes and ears open for crypto scams, many of which show up on social media platforms like TikTok and Discord. The release mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>These schemes make numerous misrepresentations about the investment and its rate of return through TikTok and Discord, making it difficult to later track down these misrepresentations and the individuals involved. The investment offerings are often targeted at people who have recently lost money on investments in cryptocurrency or stocks.</p></blockquote>
<p>Once crypto funds are gone, they are extremely difficult to track down and retrieve, meaning most of the time, money that gets lost to a scam gets lost for good. Thus, the DFR is telling investors to be extremely cautious about what they choose to put their money in and to only invest funds they can afford to lose.</p>
<h2>2022 Was a Bad Year for Crypto</h2>
<p>2022 was arguably the darkest year for crypto, and while 2023 has indeed arrived, many in the space are still reeling from the problems that occurred over the previous 12 months. Aside from all the issues that arrived due to FTX and the collapse of so many other companies, the prices of the world’s leading digital currencies also took heavy hits, with bitcoin losing more than 70 percent of its value and dropping from its November 2021 all-time high of about $68,000 per unit into the $16K range.</p>
<p>It was a sad and ugly sight to see, and something that’s probably going to take a very long time to fix.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/oregon-tells-residents-to-avoid-crypto-investments/">Oregon Tells Residents to Avoid Crypto Investments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/oregon-tells-residents-to-avoid-crypto-investments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
