<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 03:22:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/cropped-fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Opinion: Is Trump Crypto&#8217;s Best Hope for Survival in America?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-is-trump-cryptos-best-hope-for-survival-in-america/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 17:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OpEd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[America]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trump]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78519</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Several people have thrown their hats into the 2024 presidential ring, and while many of them are talking about their alleged plans involving crypto and America, it’s interesting that the one man who’s stayed relatively silent on the subject – Donald Trump – could still be the best hope for the country’s digital currency arena. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-is-trump-cryptos-best-hope-for-survival-in-america/">Opinion: Is Trump Crypto&#8217;s Best Hope for Survival in America?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Several people have thrown their hats into the 2024 presidential ring, and while many of them are talking about their alleged plans involving crypto and America, it’s interesting that the one man who’s stayed relatively silent on the subject – Donald Trump – could still be the best hope for the country’s digital currency arena.</p>
<h2>Why Trump Remains the #1 Choice</h2>
<p>Let’s look at the most known presidential candidates to see which one stands higher than the rest:</p>
<h2>Joe Biden</h2>
<p>Everyone knows that another term for Joe Biden would mean the death of crypto. As the leading face of the democrat party, Biden has worked hard to make traders’ lives miserable. Between an Obama-era policy designed to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-biden-using-an-obama-era-program-to-ban-btc/">shut out the crypto</a> arena from traditional financial tools, a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-amendment-for-infrastructure-bill-leads-to-more-problems-and-infighting/">phony infrastructure bill</a> aimed at traders, and now a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/biden-wants-to-tax-crypto-mining-companies-at-30/">30 percent tax</a> on all crypto mining, it’s clear Biden seeks a future for America where crypto doesn’t exist.</p>
<p>Unless Americans want more persecution and financial repression, they should do all they can to get Biden out of office.</p>
<h2>Robert Kennedy Jr.</h2>
<p>Arguably Biden’s biggest threat when it comes to this year’s democratic nomination, Kennedy has said, in passing, he’s against Biden on all things when it comes to crypto. Making an appearance at this year’s Miami Bitcoin Conference, he <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-candidate-robert-kennedy-jr-has-big-plans-for-the-crypto-space/">mentioned he’s not only</a> accepting crypto donations for his campaign, but he’ll ensure no government interference ever occurs when it comes to bitcoin trading.</p>
<p>While this sounds dandy, the fact remains that Kennedy is still an active member of the democrat party, which one could argue is the main enemy of all crypto fans in the U.S. Figures like <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elizabeth-warren-is-building-an-anti-crypto-rhetoric-as-part-of-her-reelection-campaign/">Elizabeth Warren</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-attorney-generals-office-now-suing-ku-coin-exchange/">Leticia James</a> in New York, and others have made it clear they seek to end the reign of crypto in this country for good.</p>
<p>They’ve also made a habit of sticking together no matter what. This raises several questions, a big one being whether Kennedy, down the line, will have the guts to always stand up against those he calls his colleagues, and if he does, will he have the strength to maintain such fortitude for four years? Getting the answers to these questions <em>after</em> he’s entered the White House may prove too late.</p>
<h2>Vivek Ramaswamy</h2>
<p>Republican candidate Ramaswamy has stated that he <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vivek-ramaswamy-is-making-crypto-a-big-part-of-his-white-house-campaign/">seeks to limit all taxes</a> on crypto mining. He’s also very much against the damaging tactics Biden has instilled and wants America to ring in a whole new wave of crypto innovation.</p>
<p>While this sounds promising, however, what else is he planning? Ramaswamy, for the most part, has remained relatively silent when it comes to other policy aspects. What will he do, for example, about the economy should he win next year? Bitcoin and crypto can only go so far, and it’s unlikely they’ll solve all the damage done to America’s financial system… at least not quickly, so what else does he have in store?</p>
<p>Unfortunately, we don’t quite know, and until we do, we cannot assume that his candidacy is strong or legitimate enough simply because he’s willing to discuss crypto and blockchain when others won’t.</p>
<h2>Ron DeSantis</h2>
<p>At first glance, DeSantis – the republican governor of Florida who announced <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ron-desantis-is-running-for-president-appears-to-be-very-pro-crypto/">his candidacy in late</a> May – seems like the perfect candidate. He’s commented, in the past, that everyone has a right to bitcoin trading, and he’s worked to prevent CBDCs from <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ron-desantis-signs-anti-cbdc-crypto-bill-into-law/">being established in Florida</a>, as he believes they’ll be tools for government spying. This is all good… Right?</p>
<p>Unfortunately, DeSantis’ background and network appear rather shady when one looks deep enough. There are several allegations, for example, that DeSantis is a neocon secretly <a href="https://truenewsamerica.com/2023/02/25/ron-desantis-accepts-endorsement-and-donations-from-george-soros/">being funded by</a> George Soros, a known enemy of the U.S. Soros is <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-fans-see-joe-biden-for-the-destructive-force-he-is/">also funding Alvin Bragg</a>, the corrupt DA in Manhattan who lets violent criminals get off with warnings while going after President Trump for an NDA case from roughly seven years ago that both the federal government and the Federal Election Commission (FEC) looked at and passed on after feeling there was nothing worthy of prosecution.</p>
<p>If such statements regarding DeSantis are true, that’s scary, and it’s something Americans likely don’t want to find out after he’s already been elected to the White House. If DeSantis indeed has connections to Soros, one can bet that all his talk about crypto will probably go out the door if he’s pressed to police Americans and their financial liberties.</p>
<h2>Donald Trump</h2>
<p>When it comes to crypto’s future in America, Trump (who&#8217;s currently <a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/meet-the-press/meetthepressblog/new-polls-show-trump-commanding-lead-2024-gop-race-rcna86232">leading in all the polls</a>) may seem like the least likely candidate given he’s said some <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/donald-trump-is-no-fan-of-bitcoin/">negative things about digital</a> assets in the past. However, when one puts these comments aside, they can’t help but realize that he’s the one, true choice if crypto is going to survive within this nation’s borders.</p>
<p>The fact is that Trump already has a proven track record, meaning he can potentially get the current financial state of America back on track in the shortest period. During his first term as president, <a href="https://www.newsweek.com/face-it-economy-under-trump-great-opinion-1484645">the economy was in</a> its best shape in a long while. Bitcoin reached its first all-time high of <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/gmnovp/what_caused_bitcoin_to_rise_to_20k_in_2017/">nearly $20K during</a> 2017, and the arena endured a remarkable <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/bitcoin-and-cryptocurrencys-2020-turnaround-5094080">turnaround in 2020 during</a> the COVID pandemic, a time when it likely should have gone to pieces.</p>
<p>In addition, <a href="https://www.gobankingrates.com/investing/stocks/stocks-soared-under-trumps-presidency/">stocks</a> and <a href="https://www.mining.com/gold-price-rockets-on-trump-victory/">gold</a> were also high, and this is <em>exactly</em> what crypto fans should be eager for. An arena where all three primary asset classes – stocks, precious metals, and digital currencies – are strong and on the same level. This is the only way to achieve economic balance. This doesn’t happen when one is performing miles above another or when one endures shakiness while another is steady. Trump, in many ways, leveled the playing field for America’s economy like no other president has, and for this reason alone, he’s likely the top candidate when it comes to crypto’s safety.</p>
<p>Lastly, Trump has pledged freedom for all American citizens, suggesting that while he may not partake in crypto trading, investors can rest assured their plans will not be hindered while he’s in office.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-is-trump-cryptos-best-hope-for-survival-in-america/">Opinion: Is Trump Crypto&#8217;s Best Hope for Survival in America?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Report: Bitcoin Volatility Lowest in Nearly Three Years</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-bitcoin-volatility-lowest-in-three-years/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 15:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Noelle Acheson]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[volatility]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78516</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Despite what has still felt like a relatively up-and-down period for bitcoin, the world’s number one digital currency by market cap, a new study suggests that the volatility of the asset is at its lowest since 2020. Bitcoin Volatility is Slowing Down Big Time The last time bitcoin was this calm was in October three [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-bitcoin-volatility-lowest-in-three-years/">Report: Bitcoin Volatility Lowest in Nearly Three Years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite what has still felt like a relatively up-and-down period for bitcoin, the world’s number one digital currency by market cap, a new <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-volatility-drops-lowest-since-161846391.html">study suggests that the</a> volatility of the asset is at its lowest since 2020.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Volatility is Slowing Down Big Time</h2>
<p>The last time bitcoin was this calm was in October three years ago. During that period, bitcoin either didn’t move at all or endured very small maneuvers over 70 separate sessions, and it looks like those patterns are repeating. Strahinja Savic – head of data and analytics at FRNT Financial – commented on the situation and said:</p>
<blockquote><p>There are a few macro catalysts playing out right now. Whether debt-ceiling negotiations or the Fed rate policy, traders are waiting for more clarity. It’s just a wait-and-see-type of moment.</p></blockquote>
<p>The news is odd given that in May, for example, bitcoin endured a near $4,000 slide <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/">from the $30K price</a> it hit just a month earlier. In April, bitcoin struck a ten-month high, and many felt that the days of 2022 – arguably the worst period on record for the currency – were finally coming to an end.</p>
<p>However, the following month, it was clear that present resistance was still proving to be too harsh an enemy for the world’s leading digital asset. The currency fell into the mid-$26,000 range and only hit $27K briefly after it was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-prices-rise-following-positive-sentiment-from-hong-kong/">announced that Hong Kong</a> would allow certain forms of retail crypto trading through specific (licensed) platforms.</p>
<p>When one looks at data like this, it’s easy to assume that volatility is still relatively constant in the digital currency arena, though it could also be argued that bitcoin has remained almost completely still compared with where it was last year. In her newsletter “Crypto Is Macro Now,” Noelle Acheson explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>There could be some downside, but conviction in this is not strong enough to offset the possibility of missing out on any rally. Obviously, there is some buying and selling going on, but it is not enough to boost volatility despite the low volumes and liquidity.</p></blockquote>
<h2>2022: The Worst Year on Record!</h2>
<p>The good news is that 2023 has offered a degree of healing that many crypto fans and traders likely needed to see before they jumped back into the trading game. The fact is nothing has ever been as damaging as the trends witnessed in 2022, which will probably go down as one of the worst years for bitcoin and crypto.</p>
<p>During that period, the leading digital asset lost more than 70 percent of its value, dropping from $68,000 (an all-time high) in November 2021 to about $16,600 just a year later. Sadly, the trouble didn’t stop there, as several assets chose to follow in BTC’s footsteps and bring the overall valuation of the crypto arena down by more than $2 trillion.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-bitcoin-volatility-lowest-in-three-years/">Report: Bitcoin Volatility Lowest in Nearly Three Years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rick Nott Provides His Thoughts on Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/rick-nott-provides-his-thoughts-on-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 13:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rick Nott]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[taxes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78514</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Rick Nott – a CFA, CFP, and senior wealth advisor at Lourd Murray – recently had a few things to say about the world of cryptocurrency. Rick Nott Discusses Crypto As a man who has established a large career for himself in finance, Nott had several notes to make in a recent interview about the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/rick-nott-provides-his-thoughts-on-crypto/">Rick Nott Provides His Thoughts on Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Rick Nott – a CFA, CFP, and senior wealth advisor at Lourd Murray – <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/m-financial-advisor-think-cryptocurrency-200040990.html">recently had a few things</a> to say about the world of <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/cryptocurrency/">cryptocurrency</a>.</p>
<h2>Rick Nott Discusses Crypto</h2>
<p>As a man who has established a large career for himself in finance, Nott had several notes to make in a recent interview about the growing crypto arena. He said that while allotting some of your portfolio into bitcoin and crypto may not be a bad idea, it really depends on how much tolerance you have for risk, and crypto is indeed a risky business. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>The consideration to invest in any asset should be taken within the context of your entire portfolio and your ability to take the risk of that investment. Crypto is no different and is a distinct asset class with, at this point, a decent history.</p></blockquote>
<p>Also, while he feels crypto is a legitimate asset class, he thinks bitcoin is a standalone asset that should not be part of the same arena. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think it’s important to separate ‘crypto’ as all the digital assets (new coins, NFTs, etc.) versus bitcoin. I truly believe that bitcoin is in a class of its own, and if someone were looking to invest in crypto, bitcoin is the only asset with enough history, size, accessibility, and legal resiliency to be considered. It is very likely that all other crypto assets are unregulated securities. The U.S. government is actively waging regulatory war against those assets (and rightly so).</p></blockquote>
<p>Nott also warned that novice investors may not want to jump into crypto so quickly, and that waiting a little bit to garner experience in the field of investing might be a good idea before considering BTC and its cousins. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Unlike a traditional investment that you might buy at a qualified and insured custodian like Schwab or Fidelity, there is tremendous complexity around buying and storing any bitcoin/crypto that you own. The safety of where you buy, the entity that holds your funds, or the risks if you [engage in] self-custody require much more technical know-how than most other investments.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Be Aware of Tax Issues</h2>
<p>Lastly, he said one should always consider the tax implications of crypto before heading forward with digital investing. He commented that the taxes surrounding crypto can be quite complicated, and it’s important to understand things well before getting involved:</p>
<blockquote><p>In buying any crypto, you will be significantly increasing your tax complexity. Not only are tax laws not truly adapted to crypto yet, but your tax preparer may not have the expertise to properly advise you on it. Even worse, if you transact frequently in it, you [must] keep records of those transactions, and the custodians don’t provide the tax documentation as your trading account would at year-end.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/rick-nott-provides-his-thoughts-on-crypto/">Rick Nott Provides His Thoughts on Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Eyes Another Increase Above $0.10</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-eyes-another-increase-above-0-10/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 05:08:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar Lumens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79183</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stellar lumen price started a downside correction from the $0.1180 zone against the US Dollar. XLM price is now trading below $0.1050 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.100 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could start another [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-eyes-another-increase-above-0-10/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Eyes Another Increase Above $0.10</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Stellar lumen price started a downside correction from the $0.1180 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>XLM price is now trading below $0.1050 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.100 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start another increase if it clears the $0.10 and $0.102 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Stellar lumen price is trading above $0.095 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-more-upsides-above-31250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. XLM’s price must stay above the $0.092 support to rise again.</em></p>
<h2>Stellar Lumen Price Analysis (XLM to USD)</h2>
<p>After forming a base above the $0.090 level, Stellar lumen price started a fresh increase against the US Dollar. The XLM/USD pair broke the $0.100 resistance zone to move into a positive zone.</p>
<p>The price even cleared the $0.1120 resistance and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). The upward move was such that the price spiked to $0.1180 before it corrected lower. There was a drop below the $0.105 support level. There is a break below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.0752 swing low to the $0.1177 high.</p>
<p>However, the bulls were active near the $0.0950 level. It is also stable above the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.0752 swing low to the $0.1177 high.</p>
<p>XLM is now trading below $0.105 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-could-rally-further-above-0-12/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $0.100 zone. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.100 on the 4-hour chart.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $0.1020 level. A clear move above the $0.1020 level might send the price toward the $0.1050 level.</p>
<p>Any more gains could lead the price toward the $0.1150 level or even $0.1180. Initial support on the downside is near the $0.095 level. The next major support sits near the $0.0920 level. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.085 level in the near term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79184" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79184" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-1.png"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-79184" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-1.png" alt="Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-1.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-1-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-1-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-1-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-1-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-1-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Stellar-Lumen-XLM-1-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79184" class="wp-caption-text">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XLMUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a> indicates that XLM’s price is now trading below $0.105 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start another increase if it clears the $0.10 and $0.102 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XLM/USD is losing momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for XLM/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.095 and $0.092.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.100, $0.1020, and $0.1050.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/stellar-lumen-xlm-price-eyes-another-increase-above-0-10/">Stellar Lumen (XLM) Price Eyes Another Increase Above $0.10</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Price Analysis: XRP Could Struggle Above 0.485</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-could-struggle-above-0-485/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 03:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79180</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple price started a fresh decline from the $0.4950 zone against the US dollar. The price is now trading below $0.485 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.476 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Bittrex). The pair [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-could-struggle-above-0-485/">Ripple Price Analysis: XRP Could Struggle Above 0.485</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ripple price started a fresh decline from the $0.4950 zone against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $0.485 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.476 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Bittrex).</li>
<li>The pair could extend losses if it stays below the $0.485 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Ripple price is struggling below $0.485 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-more-upsides-above-31250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. XRP price could decline further if it settles below the $0.455 support in the near term.</em></p>
<h2>Ripple Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, Ripple price started a fresh decline from well above $0.4950 against the US Dollar. The XRP/USD pair gained bearish momentum below the $0.4850 level.</p>
<p>The bears were able to push the price below the $0.4800 support. It even traded below the 55 simple moving average (4 hours) and spiked below the $0.462 support. A low is formed near $0.4580 and the price is now attempting a recovery wave.</p>
<p>XRP is now trading below $0.485 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-aim-fresh-surge-to-0-52/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. Besides, there is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.476 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near $0.475 and the trend line. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.4956 swing high to the $0.4580 low. The next major resistance is near the $0.4860 level.</p>
<p>It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.4956 swing high to the $0.4580 low. A clear move above the trend line resistance and $0.4860 might start a fresh increase. In the stated case, the price could even surpass the $0.495 resistance. Any more gains might send the price toward the $0.520 resistance.</p>
<p>Initial support on the downside is near $0.4550. The next major support is near the $0.4450 level. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $0.420 level, below which the price might even test $0.40.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79181" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79181" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple-1.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-79181" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple-1.png" alt="Ripple Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple-1.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple-1-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple-1-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple-1-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple-1-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple-1-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Ripple-1-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79181" class="wp-caption-text">Ripple Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, Ripple’s price is now trading below the $0.485 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could extend losses if it stays below the $0.455 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for XRP/USD is now losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for XRP/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.4550, $0.4450, and $0.4200.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.4760 and $0.4850.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-could-struggle-above-0-485/">Ripple Price Analysis: XRP Could Struggle Above 0.485</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cynthia Lummis: BTC Can Make the Planet Clean Again</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cynthia-lummis-btc-can-make-the-planet-clean-again/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 17:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cynthia Lummis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[national security]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78512</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cynthia Lummis – the republican senator of Wyoming – has proven herself to be a major bitcoin bull. During the recent Miami Bitcoin Conference, Lummis made an appearance and commented that bitcoin and cryptocurrencies could help clean up the environment. Cynthia Lummis on the Power of Crypto She explained: One of the advantages of bitcoin [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cynthia-lummis-btc-can-make-the-planet-clean-again/">Cynthia Lummis: BTC Can Make the Planet Clean Again</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cynthia Lummis – the republican senator of Wyoming – has proven herself to be a major bitcoin bull. During the recent Miami Bitcoin Conference, Lummis <a href="https://www.thestreet.com/cryptocurrency/news/cynthia-lummis-bitcoin-environment-miami">made an appearance and</a> commented that bitcoin and cryptocurrencies could help clean up the environment.</p>
<h2>Cynthia Lummis on the Power of Crypto</h2>
<p>She explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>One of the advantages of bitcoin mining is that when you drill an oil and gas well, and it is distant from other oil and gas wells, you vent the gas into the atmosphere until you can bring in a pipeline to hook it up. Well, while that’s being vented, you can pull a bitcoin mining operation in a trailer, use the vented methane gas to mine your bitcoin, and you are preventing that gas from being vented into the atmosphere. Bitcoin is cleaning up the environment.</p></blockquote>
<p>The news is interesting given that for the past several years, many environmentalists have stepped in to say that bitcoin and crypto are doing incredible harm to the environment – the <em>exact opposite</em> of what Lummis is stating. There have been many reports, for example, for some time, that bitcoin and crypto mining <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-bitcoin-mining-may-require-more-energy-than-180-countries/">uses more energy than</a> most developing nations such as Iceland.</p>
<p>Also, in April of 2023, reports from the Environmental Working Group linked bitcoin and crypto mining to higher air, noise, and water pollution. Many industry heads – from Kevin O’Leary to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-has-taken-a-nasty-stumble-many-are-blaming-elon-musk/">Elon Musk</a> – have also expressed concerns about how the mining industry has affected Earth’s atmosphere and resources.</p>
<p>Continuing her speech, Lummis further stated that bitcoin is also a national security issue. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I’m actually worried as we go into another debt ceiling debate that we will eventually increase the debt ceiling to the point where our interest payments will exceed how much money we spend on national defense, so it is a national security issue.</p></blockquote>
<p>She also criticized other lawmakers in Washington for not doing enough to know more about the crypto industry. She said that many of her constituents in Congress do not recognize the differences between bitcoin and its many altcoin cousins, a scary fact in her opinion. She commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Even though you all know that when FTX failed, they held zero bitcoin, there are a lot of people in Washington D.C. that conflate companies with digital assets. They conflate bitcoin with other cryptocurrencies.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Major Bull</h2>
<p>Since she first entered Congress <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/wyoming-bitcoin-advocate-heads-for-the-senate/">in January of 2021</a>, Lummis has shown herself to be a major bitcoin and crypto advocate, as she was very clear that she had invested in bitcoin multiple times prior.</p>
<p>She also introduced a crypto bill in mid-2022 that would allegedly carve <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/wyomings-cynthia-lummis-is-drafting-a-new-crypto-bill/">out rules and structures</a> for all future crypto legislation. The move was alleged proof that crypto innovation in America was an important talking point for Lummis and her staff.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cynthia-lummis-btc-can-make-the-planet-clean-again/">Cynthia Lummis: BTC Can Make the Planet Clean Again</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Gemini Exchange is Relocating to Ireland</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-gemini-exchange-is-relocating-to-ireland/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 15:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dublin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ireland]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78510</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Gemini exchange in New York is relocating to Dublin, Ireland, and joins a growing list of digital currency exchanges and related companies leaving the U.S. either due to complicated regulations or persecution from agencies like the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The Gemini Sets Its Sights on the Emerald Isle The crypto industry in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-gemini-exchange-is-relocating-to-ireland/">The Gemini Exchange is Relocating to Ireland</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Gemini exchange in New York <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/cryptocurrency-platform-founded-by-us-entrepreneurs-chooses-ireland-as-european-hq/ar-AA1bJfyA">is relocating to</a> Dublin, Ireland, and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-is-now-active-in-bermuda/">joins a growing list</a> of digital currency exchanges and related companies leaving the U.S. either due to complicated regulations or persecution from agencies like the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<h2>The Gemini Sets Its Sights on the Emerald Isle</h2>
<p>The crypto industry in the U.S. has been under heavy scrutiny from organizations like the one mentioned above. Its head, Gary Gensler, has gone after several leading digital currency companies over the past few months. Among the big names he’s attacked are Kraken, a crypto exchange based in Northern California, and Coinbase, arguably the largest and most dominant digital trading platform in the country.</p>
<p>Kraken was forced to end <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/">all its staking activities</a> and services while also parting with a $30 million penalty fee. Coinbase, on the other hand, was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/">served what’s called</a> a Wells notice that informed executives that financial charges were likely coming in the future. The group’s leaders took issue with the notice on account of they had allegedly met with representatives of the SEC several times over a nine-year period to ensure the company was fully compliant.</p>
<p>Gemini services have only been available in Europe for about a year, though in a statement, the company’s founders Tyler and Cameron Winklevoss made it clear they have a positive view of the Irish regulatory landscape. They’re also thrilled by how far the nation has come in terms of technology adoption and innovation. They commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>We look forward to being a part of and adding to the vibrant tech community in Dublin. Crypto is as transformative as the internet, and we are committed to unlocking the opportunities it represents.</p></blockquote>
<p>Irish politician Taoiseach Leo Varadkar TD commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>This is significant for Ireland as the government focuses on innovation as a driver of growth. Gemini&#8217;s decision to locate in Ireland highlights our competitive offering for the international financial services sector. We take pride in how it has grown from 60 staff in Dublin 30 years ago, to approximately 56,000 people around the country working in finance today. I wish Gemini every success as they build their team in Ireland.’</p></blockquote>
<p>Gillian Lynch – head of Ireland and Europe at Gemini – also threw her two cents in, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>As we continue to expand our global footprint, we’re excited to tap into the talent and innovation that Dublin and the Irish market have to offer. Dublin has long been a hub for innovation and technology, with a thriving startup scene and deep talent pool. We continue to be encouraged by the city’s commitment to fostering innovation, by a policy environment which encourages entrepreneurship.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Great Landscape?</h2>
<p>Michael Lohan – CEO of IDA Ireland – said:</p>
<blockquote><p>This investment will act as a strong reference case in seeking to further develop the digital assets sector.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-gemini-exchange-is-relocating-to-ireland/">The Gemini Exchange is Relocating to Ireland</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ron DeSantis is Running for President, Appears to Be Very Pro Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ron-desantis-is-running-for-president-appears-to-be-very-pro-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 13:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[President]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ron DeSantis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78504</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Republican governor of Florida Ron DeSantis has thrown his hat into the presidential ring. He has filed the necessary paperwork with the Federal Election Commission (FEC) and has officially launched his 2024 campaign on Twitter. Ron DeSantis Has Entered the White House Race Like several of this year’s candidates, DeSantis appears to be very pro [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ron-desantis-is-running-for-president-appears-to-be-very-pro-crypto/">Ron DeSantis is Running for President, Appears to Be Very Pro Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Republican governor of Florida Ron DeSantis has thrown his <a href="https://www.thestreet.com/cryptocurrency/news/ron-desantis-bitcoin-elon-musk-twitter-spaces">hat into the presidential</a> ring. He has filed the necessary paperwork with the Federal Election Commission (FEC) and has officially launched his 2024 campaign on Twitter.</p>
<h2>Ron DeSantis Has Entered the White House Race</h2>
<p>Like several of this year’s candidates, DeSantis appears to be very pro crypto, and is arguably hoping to garner some extra votes by saying a thing or two about the industry. In a recent interview, he claimed that Biden and his group of nation haters are likely to end the bitcoin reign in America should they win another four years in office as they’re doing all they can to outlaw it. DeSantis said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The current regime, clearly, they have it out for bitcoin, and if it continues for another four years, they’ll probably end up killing it. Bitcoin represents a threat to them. They’re trying to regulate it out of existence. You have every right to… bitcoin. The only reason these people in Washington don’t like it is because they don’t control it.</p></blockquote>
<p>There have been a wide array of politicians and presidential hopefuls this year that have spoken positively about bitcoin. Among them are democratic hopeful Robert F. Kennedy Jr., who in a speech at this <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-candidate-robert-kennedy-jr-has-big-plans-for-the-crypto-space/">year’s bitcoin conference</a> stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Our campaign will be the first presidential campaign in history to accept bitcoin donations through the Lightning Network, and today, we move one step closer to the future. Today, we show the world the power, durability, and flexibility of bitcoin.</p></blockquote>
<p>His love for crypto-based enterprises was seconded by another White House contender in republican Vivek Ramaswamy, who <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vivek-ramaswamy-is-making-crypto-a-big-part-of-his-white-house-campaign/">during a campaign discussion</a> said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The thriving bitcoin universe should actually better empower me to do what I want to do as the U.S. president, which is to stabilize the U.S. dollar as a unit of measurement and put the Federal Reserve back in its place with that as its single mandate.</p></blockquote>
<p>Ron DeSantis recently <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ron-desantis-signs-anti-cbdc-crypto-bill-into-law/">took measures against</a> a central bank digital currency (CBDC) and signed a law in Florida disallowing the creation of such a tool. He says that a digital dollar of CBDC will undoubtedly be used by the federal government to spy on users. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Anyone with their eyes open could see the danger this type of an arrangement would mean for Americans who want to exercise their financial independence and would like to be able to conduct business without having the government know every single transaction they’re making in real time.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Will Bitcoin Decide the President in 2024?</h2>
<p>As mentioned in a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-bitcoin-could-be-a-big-topic-in-next-years-presidential-election/">previous opinion piece</a>, bitcoin and crypto are shaping up to be major talking points in next year’s presidential election.</p>
<p>Now, with the recent stance being taken by new contender Ron DeSantis, it looks like this sentiment is correct.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ron-desantis-is-running-for-president-appears-to-be-very-pro-crypto/">Ron DeSantis is Running for President, Appears to Be Very Pro Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alaya：High-quality data is the future of AI</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/alaya%ef%bc%9ahigh-quality-data-is-the-future-of-ai/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 09:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79175</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As the field of artificial intelligence continues to evolve, security and stability have improved, and so have the requirements for data quality. If the former algorithm model using the general data set is the rough food, then now the algorithm model needs to be customized nutritional meal. If companies want to further improve the ability [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/alaya%ef%bc%9ahigh-quality-data-is-the-future-of-ai/">Alaya：High-quality data is the future of AI</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As the field of artificial intelligence continues to evolve, security and stability have improved, and so have the requirements for data quality. If the former algorithm model using the general data set is the rough food, then now the algorithm model needs to be customized nutritional meal. If companies want to further improve the ability to implement the model, they must gradually move away from the original common data set and Internet data, and actively engage in customized data collection to create a core data barrier. At present, the world-wide Alaya data labeling platform has been known for its pursuit of data quality.</p>
<p>In a talk titled &#8220;AI is the new electricity&#8221;, the international authority on artificial intelligence, Enda Wu, highlighted the importance of data &#8220;The rise of AI is changing the competitive landscape for companies. The barrier for companies is no longer algorithms, but data, so that the algorithm can use enough data to make the product work&#8230;&#8221;</p>
<p>So why do people in artificial intelligence continue to seek high quality data?</p>
<p>When faced with a poorly performing model, engineers spend months tinkering with product features and new algorithms, not realizing that the problem exists in their data. High-quality data can lead to greater breakthroughs for humans.</p>
<h4>High quality data that is capable of understanding the problem you are trying to solve.</h4>
<p>While AI systems are becoming more complex, we need advanced and clever human marker systems to teach and measure their performance. Models that currently know enough about the world to identify and classify misleading information will not increase in complexity by using more low-skilled workers. To identify algorithmic biases, we need high-quality data to identify the right world.</p>
<h4>High-quality data can drive target functions consistent with human values</h4>
<p>Models are often trained on datasets that are only approximations of their true goals, leading to unexpected divergences. Machine learning is about teaching computers to work the way we want them to, and we achieve our goals by showing positive examples. So in order to build high-quality models, the most important skill a machine learning engineer needs to master should be building high-quality datasets and making sure they match the problem at hand.</p>
<p>If we want AI to solve our own real-world needs, we need to think deeply about the datasets that define our models and give them a certain human touch.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-79177 aligncenter" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture40-600x342.jpg" alt="" width="600" height="342" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture40-600x342.jpg 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture40-1100x628.jpg 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture40-768x438.jpg 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture40-750x428.jpg 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture40-1140x650.jpg 1140w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture40.jpg 1241w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></p>
<p>Alaya is always innovating and seeking world-wide growth when it comes to data quality.Alaya is a distributed AI data platform that integrates collection and labeling, that originated from Swarm Intelligence and connects communities, data, and AI through Social Commerce, providing the AI industry with high quality scalable data and full protection of its ownership and privacy. Provide high quality bid collection data for AI industry and  has achieved exponential growth through its built-in social recommendation mechanism. The community is used to solve the pain point of lack of data and scarcity of labor for AI practitioners and to bring group intelligence together across time and space and reorganize it efficiently.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-79178 aligncenter" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture41-600x489.jpg" alt="" width="600" height="489" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture41-600x489.jpg 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture41-1100x896.jpg 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture41-768x625.jpg 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture41-750x611.jpg 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture41-1140x928.jpg 1140w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture41.jpg 1292w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></p>
<p>In terms of data quality, Alaya has achieved the following three things:</p>
<ol>
<li>The theoretical guidance of the discipline of community intelligence, linking global communities, using the community economy to constantly link to everyone in the world, so that the collection of data is no longer constrained by space, and global data collection and labeling can better highlight the quality of data;</li>
<li>With a built-in hierarchy and a unique intelligent recommendation algorithm, alaya accurately assigns needs to users with the same attribute tags, ensuring that needs are addressed by professional groups and improving data quality. User data will be an important part of the industry&#8217;s best quality data;</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>Alaya&#8217;s unique data quality assessment system ensures the accuracy and consistency of data after it is collected and labeled, and addresses errors and inconsistencies to guarantee customers the highest quality data sets.</li>
</ul>
<p>Alaya was founded on the idea of providing high quality data to help the industry grow. In the field of artificial intelligence, which is increasingly pursuing data quality, companies like Alaya will be the future of the industry.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/alaya%ef%bc%9ahigh-quality-data-is-the-future-of-ai/">Alaya：High-quality data is the future of AI</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
