<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 03:21:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Indicators Point Fresh Increase To $100</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-indicators-point-fresh-increase-to-100/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-indicators-point-fresh-increase-to-100/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 03:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78189</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin settled below the $90 resistance zone against the US Dollar. LTC price is now trading below $90 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major contracting triangle forming with resistance near $89.20 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could start a decent<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-indicators-point-fresh-increase-to-100/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-indicators-point-fresh-increase-to-100/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Indicators Point Fresh Increase To $100</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Litecoin settled below the $90 resistance zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>LTC price is now trading below $90 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major contracting triangle forming with resistance near $89.20 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could start a decent increase if it clears the $92 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Litecoin price is struggling below $90 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-extend-losses-below-27000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. LTC price could continue to decline if it stays below the $92 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few hours, there was a minor increase in Bitcoin, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-faces-increase-in-bearish-pressure/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Ethereum</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-could-dive-below-0-44/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Ripple</a>, and Litecoin against the US Dollar. Earlier, LTC settled below the $90 resistance zone to move into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>The price broke the $88 support zone and tested the $85 support. A low is formed near $85.13 and the price is now attempting a recovery wave. There was a move above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $91.46 swing high to the $85.13 low.</p>
<p>It is now trading below $90 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $49.00 zone.</p>
<p>There is also a major contracting triangle forming with resistance near $89.20 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $91.46 swing high to the $85.13 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance sits near the $90 level. The main resistance is near the $92 level. A clear move above the $92 level could pump the price toward the $95 level or even $98. The next major resistance could be $100.</p>
<p>On the downside, immediate support is near the $86.60 level. The next key support is near the $85.00 level. If there is a downside break below the $85.00 support, the price could accelerate lower toward the $80 level in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_78190" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Litecoin.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78190" class="size-full wp-image-78190" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Litecoin.png" alt="Litecoin (LTC) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78190" class="wp-caption-text">Litecoin (LTC) Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Litecoin price is clearly trading below $90 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $92 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LTC/USD is now losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $86.60 and $85.00.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $90.00 and $92.00.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-indicators-point-fresh-increase-to-100/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Indicators Point Fresh Increase To $100</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-indicators-point-fresh-increase-to-100/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Analysts: Bitcoin Will Continue to Benefit from the Banking Crisis</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-bitcoin-will-continue-to-benefit-from-the-banking-crisis/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-bitcoin-will-continue-to-benefit-from-the-banking-crisis/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 17:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[banks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cathie Wood]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77648</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now that 2023 has arrived, bitcoin has found fresh ground following the ongoing banking crisis that has led to the closure of institutions like Silvergate, Silicon Valley Bank, and Signature. Bitcoin Could Do Even Better Many analysts and crypto industry heads believe this banking crisis is going to continue now that Deutsche Bank is at<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-bitcoin-will-continue-to-benefit-from-the-banking-crisis/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-bitcoin-will-continue-to-benefit-from-the-banking-crisis/">Analysts: Bitcoin Will Continue to Benefit from the Banking Crisis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now that 2023 has arrived, bitcoin has <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/03/25/massive-shock-new-bank-crisis-and-300-billion-fed-pump-has-primed-bitcoin-after-huge-crypto-and-ethereum-price-rally/?sh=386a4a0279d2" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">found fresh ground</a> following the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-spikes-following-silicon-valley-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">ongoing banking crisis</a> that has led to the closure of institutions like Silvergate, Silicon Valley Bank, and Signature.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Could Do Even Better</h2>
<p>Many analysts and crypto industry heads believe this banking crisis is going to continue now that Deutsche Bank is at the helm of controversy, and with heavy regulatory issues in play, bitcoin – they believe – could be poised for a solid breakout in the coming weeks and months.</p>
<p>The price of BTC has already risen <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-more-banks-fell-bitcoin-rose-beyond-28k/" data-wpel-link="internal">beyond $28K</a>. That’s about 70 percent higher than where it was at the end of 2022, arguably the worst year on record for bitcoin and many other digital assets. The space lost more than $2 trillion in overall valuation given that assets like BTC shed more than 70 percent of their values. The world’s number one digital currency by market cap was trading at a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit in November of 2021, though roughly 12 months later, the asset had dropped into the mid-$16K range.</p>
<p>Several additional cryptocurrencies, for one reason or another, chose to follow in bitcoin’s footsteps and shed dollars from their prices. It was a sad and ugly sight to see, and many traders lost everything they had, but since the new year began, it looks like everything is starting to turn around.</p>
<p>One of the big reasons for the sudden change is the banking situation in both America and Europe. Cathie Wood of Ark Invest fame commented in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>The behavior of the [bitcoin] price through this crisis is going to attract more institutions. The fact that bitcoin moved in a very different way from the equity markets, in particular, was quite instructive.</p></blockquote>
<p>Macro Hive also threw its two cents into the mix, stating:</p>
<blockquote><p>The banking crisis, which caused the market to price in rate cuts starting in the summer, has had little knock-on effect on crypto (so far).</p></blockquote>
<p>These words followed news that Deutsche Bank experienced a huge dip in its stock share prices over the last few weeks, thus wiping out about one fifth of the bank’s market capitalization.</p>
<h2>The Fed Isn&#8217;t Helping Things</h2>
<p>The situation also isn’t being helped by the Federal Reserve and similar institutions, which continue to hike rates even though the economy is in shambles and nobody can afford homes or cars. Not too long ago, the Fed announced interest <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/federal-reserve-hikes-rates-again-what-will-happen-to-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">rates were going up</a> another 0.25 basis points, and that inflation continues to be a major enemy.</p>
<p>It commented further that despite the state of the country’s banking sector, interest rates would continue to be pushed upward in 2023 unless inflation chose to stop rearing its ugly head. 2023 was initially believed to be a less hostile year in that sense.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-bitcoin-will-continue-to-benefit-from-the-banking-crisis/">Analysts: Bitcoin Will Continue to Benefit from the Banking Crisis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-bitcoin-will-continue-to-benefit-from-the-banking-crisis/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Venezuela Shutting Down All Its Crypto Platforms?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-venezuela-shutting-down-all-its-crypto-exchanges/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-venezuela-shutting-down-all-its-crypto-exchanges/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 15:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Petro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sunacrip]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[venezuela]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77645</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The relationship between Venezuela and crypto has always been a bit wonky, and this month is no exception. The arrest of the nation’s superintendent of crypto assets Joselit Ramirez has caused a huge uproar in the nation, and President Nicolas Maduro has ordered the region to completely upend its digital currency regulatory agency. Venezuela Is<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-venezuela-shutting-down-all-its-crypto-exchanges/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-venezuela-shutting-down-all-its-crypto-exchanges/">Is Venezuela Shutting Down All Its Crypto Platforms?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The relationship between Venezuela and crypto has always been a bit wonky, and this month is no exception. The arrest of the nation’s superintendent of crypto assets Joselit Ramirez has <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/exchanges-mining-farms-shut-down-201542174.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">caused a huge uproar</a> in the nation, and President Nicolas Maduro has ordered the region to completely upend its digital currency regulatory agency.</p>
<h2>Venezuela Is Acting Fishy Regarding Crypto</h2>
<p>Right now, it is widely rumored that all the crypto exchanges that have been established in Venezuela are scheduled to be closed down permanently. The order was reportedly given by Sunacrip, the country’s official crypto regulatory body, and while nothing has been confirmed yet, the National Association of Cryptocurrencies has hinted that such action is indeed occurring within the borders of Venezuela as part of an ongoing anti-corruption case.</p>
<p>Asonacrip president Jose Angel Alvarez explained in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>We believe that private companies should not be blamed for what is happening inside the regulatory body and that we should promote the full activation of all cryptocurrency operations (in the country). We are preparing a list of propositions to be delivered soon to Sunacrip and Dr. Anabel Pereira.</p></blockquote>
<p>The idea that Venezuela – a long-time socialist country – would suddenly be working towards “anti-corruption” is a bit of a laugh. In addition, it’s odd that the nation is suddenly so anti-crypto given its history <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/petro/" data-wpel-link="internal">with the Petro</a>, an oil-backed digital asset that the country worked very hard to market, promote, and sell about four to five years ago. Several lies are alleged to have swirled around the digital asset, and it’s unclear, exactly, how many units were sold, bought, or traded when it was at its peak.</p>
<p>Alvarez went on to say that a week prior to the investigation’s start, all crypto mining farms in regions such as Carabobo were told they had to cease their operations. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Indeed, at the beginning of the week in the state of Carabobo, all the farms were ordered to stop, which concerns us as a community since some affiliates are being affected by the measure.</p></blockquote>
<p>He was highly confused and concerned by this as he believes many of the mining facilities in the country had obtained the required permits and were fully compliant with present Venezuelan laws:</p>
<blockquote><p>We believe that although there is a situation in the superintendency, it should not affect the operations of all affiliated farms at the regional level.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Is All This Even Real?</h2>
<p>By contrast, Eleazar Colmenares – the CEO of Crypto Buyer in Venezuela – has unleashed a statement claiming Sunacrip hasn’t ordered the closure of any crypto exchanges, so it’s hard to know who’s telling the truth. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We want to clarify that the announcement made yesterday on our social media refers to the temporary non-operation of our crypto-fiat gateway service due to the transition process carried out by the competent authorities.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-venezuela-shutting-down-all-its-crypto-exchanges/">Is Venezuela Shutting Down All Its Crypto Platforms?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-venezuela-shutting-down-all-its-crypto-exchanges/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Banks in Germany Will Now Sell and Buy BTC</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/banks-in-germany-will-now-sell-and-buy-btc/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/banks-in-germany-will-now-sell-and-buy-btc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 13:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DWP Bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gemany]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77642</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new platform known as DWP Bank in Europe has been unveiled. Its purpose? To give roughly 1,200 banks in Germany access to bitcoin and digital currencies. Germany and Crypto Will Soon Go Hand in Hand The banking crisis that’s affecting America at the time of writing is not just happening in the U.S. it’s<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/banks-in-germany-will-now-sell-and-buy-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/banks-in-germany-will-now-sell-and-buy-btc/">Banks in Germany Will Now Sell and Buy BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new platform known as DWP Bank in Europe has been unveiled. Its purpose? To give roughly 1,200 banks in Germany access to <a href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/german-banks-access-bitcoin-trading-platform-124626025.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">bitcoin and digital currencies</a>.</p>
<h2>Germany and Crypto Will Soon Go Hand in Hand</h2>
<p>The banking crisis that’s affecting America at the time of writing is not just happening in the U.S. it’s spread 3,000 miles across the Atlantic and is also causing problems for Europe. Look, for example, at <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/as-more-banks-fell-bitcoin-rose-beyond-28k/" data-wpel-link="internal">Credit Suisse</a>. The enterprise was in serious trouble until UBS decided it had what it took to bail the institution out. Anyone who thinks we aren’t in a recession needs to look up the definition of “recession” and confirm with themselves that things aren’t as great as they might seem.</p>
<p>So, the idea that countries like Germany suddenly want to get their hands on bitcoin and other digital assets is a sign that perhaps banks aren’t as stable as we’ve all been led to believe, and thus they want to bring in bitcoin and other alternative assets to avoid the “stability” of fiat currencies and the institutions that have since failed them.</p>
<p>DWP Bank will now allow all the banks in Germany connected to its platform to purchase and sell BTC units while still carrying out standard online banking activities. In a statement, DWP Bank said:</p>
<blockquote><p>DWP Bank wants to connect the world of traditional securities business with the world of trading digital assets. To this end, it uses its central position in the German financial market with established interfaces to around 1,200 banks and savings banks and expands its portfolio to include trading and safekeeping of new assets.</p></blockquote>
<p>CEO of the company Heiko Beck also threw his two cents into the mix, claiming that the bank is planning to expand its crypto offerings and services in the coming future. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>Digitized assets will become increasingly important in the future. That is why we are expanding our range of services in this area and focusing our portfolio more closely on the future opportunities that arise here.</p></blockquote>
<p>The new platform has already been tested out by MLP Banking AG, a client of DWP Bank. Head of account and securities settlement with MLP Paul Utzat said:</p>
<blockquote><p>In our MLP client portal, it is a logical addition to the existing wealth management offering.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Is the Banking Situation Getting Worse?</h2>
<p>The banking problems in America have caused three separate institutions (Silvergate, Silicon Valley, and Signature) to shutter their doors permanently. This has largely to do with the heightened interest rates of 2022 and the crypto ties these banks were alleged to boast. As we all remember, many assets saw their prices crash and burn during the months of the previous year.</p>
<p>Germany has been named one of the most crypto-friendly countries in Europe along with Switzerland, which is home to Crypto Valley.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/banks-in-germany-will-now-sell-and-buy-btc/">Banks in Germany Will Now Sell and Buy BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/banks-in-germany-will-now-sell-and-buy-btc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Bullish Break Signals More Gains</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bullish-break-signals-more-gains/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bullish-break-signals-more-gains/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 05:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78179</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tron price started a fresh increase from the $0.0670 level against the US Dollar. TRX price is now trading above $0.0680 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.0685 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could continue to move<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bullish-break-signals-more-gains/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bullish-break-signals-more-gains/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Bullish Break Signals More Gains</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Tron price started a fresh increase from the $0.0670 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>TRX price is now trading above $0.0680 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.0685 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move up if it breaks the $0.070 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>TRON price started a fresh increase above $0.0685 against the US Dollar, outperforming <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-extend-losses-below-27000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. TRX’s price could rise further if it clears the $0.070 resistance.</em></p>
<h2>Tron Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few sessions, Tron price started a decent increase from the $0.0672 support zone against the US Dollar. TRX’s price remained well-bid and was able to climb above the $0.0685 zone.</p>
<p>It traded above the $0.0690 and $0.0692 levels to move further into a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bulls-aim-for-key-bullish-break/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">positive zone</a>. A high is formed near $0.0699 and the price is now consolidating gains. It is trading above $0.0680 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, TRX is facing resistance near the $0.0695 level.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $0.070 level. A close above $0.070 could send the price toward the $0.0725 resistance zone. Any more gains might send TRX price toward $0.075, above which the price could even rise toward $0.080.</p>
<p>On the downside, initial support is near the $0.0685 level. There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.0685 on the 4-hours chart. The trend line is close to the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.0640 swing low to the $0.0699 high.</p>
<p>The next major support is now forming near $0.0670 or the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.0640 swing low to the $0.0699 high.</p>
<p>If there is a downside break below the $0.0670 support, the price might revisit the $0.064 support. Any more losses might call for a move toward the $0.0625 zone in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_78180" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/TRON-TRX.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78180" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78180" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/TRON-TRX.png" alt="Tron (TRX) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78180" class="wp-caption-text">Tron (TRX) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/TRXUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that TRX’s price is now trading above $0.0685 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move up if it breaks the $0.070 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for TRX/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for TRX/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.0685 and $0.0670.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.0695, $0.070, and $0.0725.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bullish-break-signals-more-gains/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Bullish Break Signals More Gains</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bullish-break-signals-more-gains/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Could Extend Losses Below $27,000</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-extend-losses-below-27000/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-extend-losses-below-27000/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 03:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78176</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price started a fresh decline from the $30,000 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $29,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $29,200 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-extend-losses-below-27000/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-extend-losses-below-27000/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Could Extend Losses Below $27,000</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin price started a fresh decline from the $30,000 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $29,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $29,200 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could extend its decline toward the $27,000 and $26,000 levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin price is declining below $29,500 against the US Dollar. BTC might extend losses if it stays below the $30,000 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price started a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-29250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">fresh decline from the $30,000 resistance zone</a>. A high was formed near $29,969 before the price started a steady decline. There was a clear move below the $29,500 and $29,200 support levels.</p>
<p>The bears even pushed the price below the $28,000 support zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). The price traded as low as $27,664 and is currently correcting losses. There was a correction above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $29,969 swing high to the $27,664 low.</p>
<p>However, it is still trading below $29,500 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-more-gains-above-31k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. Immediate resistance on the upside is near the $28,820 level. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $29,969 swing high to the $27,664 low.</p>
<p>There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $29,200 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair. The next major resistance might be near the $29,500 zone.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $29,500 level might send the price toward $30,000, above which the price might rise toward the $32,000 level. Any more gains might push the price toward the $32,500 zone.</p>
<p>If there is no upside break, the price might decline below the $28,000 level. The first major support is near $27,650. The next key support is near the $27,000 level, below which the price might accelerate lower. In the stated case, the price could decline toward the $26,000 level. Any more losses might send the price toward the $25,000 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_78177" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Bitcoin.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78177" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78177" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Bitcoin.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78177" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XBTUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Bitcoin price is clearly trading below $29,000 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could extend its decline toward the $27,000 and $26,000 levels.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD is now gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $27,660 and $27,000.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $28,820, $29,200, and $30,000.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-extend-losses-below-27000/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Could Extend Losses Below $27,000</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-extend-losses-below-27000/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Could BTC Revamp the Financial Industry in Africa?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/could-btc-revamp-the-financial-industry-of-africa/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/could-btc-revamp-the-financial-industry-of-africa/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 17:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[africa]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77640</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The banking sector of Africa is worth $86 million at the time of writing, and bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies are expected to disrupt the industry like no other technologies can. Africa Could Be Completely Changed Thanks to Bitcoin Mike Brock – CEO of TBD at Block, a financial company run by Jack Dorsey – says<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/could-btc-revamp-the-financial-industry-of-africa/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/could-btc-revamp-the-financial-industry-of-africa/">Could BTC Revamp the Financial Industry in Africa?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The banking sector of Africa is worth $86 million at the time of writing, and bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies are expected <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-is-poised-to-blow-up-africas-86-billion-banking-system/ar-AA195JiF" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">to disrupt the industry</a> like no other technologies can.</p>
<h2>Africa Could Be Completely Changed Thanks to Bitcoin</h2>
<p>Mike Brock – CEO of TBD at Block, a financial company run by Jack Dorsey – says one of the big ways that bitcoin can help Africa is that it can be used to ultimately move money around regardless of the present state of the economy. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>It doesn&#8217;t matter to me if the price goes down or up because I can still use bitcoin as a vehicle to move money around the world instantaneously. I can exchange dollars for bitcoin and then bitcoin for Brazilian rial. There is a market for bitcoin in every corner of the world today.</p></blockquote>
<p>Ray Youssef – the CEO of Paxful – seconded this idea, commenting:</p>
<blockquote>
<p style="text-align: left">If someone wants to move money to the country next door, normally, you&#8217;d have to fill up a suitcase full of cash and move it over the border.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The banking industry of Africa has long been on its knees for several reasons, the inflation (or deflation) of national currencies being a big one. In addition, many governments in Africa are also riddled with corruption, thus causing several residents of the continent to be denied access to standard financial tools like bank accounts. With bitcoin, they don’t need to worry about this and can still gain access to all the tools and services they need to survive. Youssef mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>The entire banking system in Africa is completely and utterly broken, even amongst the mobile money providers, the telcos. Two thousand payment networks and only two percent of them talk to each other. That number continues to grow. It&#8217;s not getting better, it&#8217;s getting worse.</p></blockquote>
<p>While there are other products and enterprises out there – such as Western Union and MoneyGram – that offer money conversion services, many of them charge heavy fees or require that transacting parties to lose large chunks of their money. Alex Gladstein – chief strategy officer for the Human Rights Foundation – was quick to say:</p>
<blockquote><p>We&#8217;re going to move to a model where we can make payments without IOUs, or credit, or promises, or fiat. It&#8217;s literally like sending a piece of gold or a $20 bill instantly somewhere else. If you can get access to the internet, you can settle bitcoin payments, and the government can&#8217;t do anything about it.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Dorsey&#8217;s Comments on Crypto</h2>
<p>While touring Accra – the capital city of Ghana in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/africa/" data-wpel-link="internal">Africa</a> – Dorsey said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The Nigerian government went to various bank corps to stop protesters from receiving money which bitcoin made up for, so our whole reason for being as a company is solving the same problem that bitcoin will ultimately solve for everyone in the world.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/could-btc-revamp-the-financial-industry-of-africa/">Could BTC Revamp the Financial Industry in Africa?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/could-btc-revamp-the-financial-industry-of-africa/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Skull of Satoshi&#8217;s Benjamin Wong Apologizes for &#8220;Anti-Bitcoin&#8221; Project</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/skull-of-satoshi-benjamin-wong-apologizes-for-anti-bitcoin-project/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/skull-of-satoshi-benjamin-wong-apologizes-for-anti-bitcoin-project/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 15:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Benjamin Wong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Skull of Satoshi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77638</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Benjamin Von Wong – a Canadian artist responsible for creating the “Skull of Satoshi” installation back in mid-March – has apologized for his work, claiming in a recent interview that it was “never meant to be anti-bitcoin,” and he is not pleased people took it in such a way. Benjamin Wong: I Never Sought to<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/skull-of-satoshi-benjamin-wong-apologizes-for-anti-bitcoin-project/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/skull-of-satoshi-benjamin-wong-apologizes-for-anti-bitcoin-project/">Skull of Satoshi&#8217;s Benjamin Wong Apologizes for &#8220;Anti-Bitcoin&#8221; Project</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Benjamin Von Wong – a Canadian artist responsible for creating the “Skull of Satoshi” installation back in mid-March – has <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/skull-satoshi-artist-says-wrong-101225197.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">apologized for his work</a>, claiming in a recent interview that it was “never meant to be anti-bitcoin,” and he is not pleased people took it in such a way.</p>
<h2>Benjamin Wong: I Never Sought to Create an Anti-Bitcoin Project</h2>
<p>Wong stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>It was an optimistic hope that bitcoin could shift away from the needless burning of fossil fuels without losing all the other features that make bitcoin safe, secure, and decentralized… I’ve spent my entire career trying to reduce real-world physical waste, and PoW felt intuitively wasteful. Of course, I was wrong.</p></blockquote>
<p>Skull of Satoshi was unveiled after Wong and his fellow associates at Greenpeace worked on it for over a year. The goal was to try and shed light on the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-bitcoin-mining-may-require-more-energy-than-180-countries/" data-wpel-link="internal">wasteful energy</a> use in the bitcoin mining industry. The project has been supported by several cryptocurrency heads including Chris Larsen, the Ripple co-founder. The idea behind it is to “change the code, not the climate.&#8221;</p>
<p>Sadly, there has been backlash thrown at the project from those who feel bitcoin is simply being pushed towards PoS territory like Ethereum. Rolf Skar, a special projects manager at Greenpeace USA, explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>We are pointing to the fact that other cryptocurrencies realized that PoW has an energy problem and changed. Bitcoin is the laggard in this area and is sticking to decade-old technology while other newer cryptocurrencies are using different consensus mechanisms and cutting their carbon emissions.</p></blockquote>
<p>Wong has further stated he’s going to remove himself from future projects similar with Skull of Satoshi so he can really analyze himself and his work and see where it is, specifically, that he can contribute to stronger aspects of environmental responsibility. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I needed to first string together some official responses to the Twitterverse and [I’d] been trying to digest all the different fragments of information I was receiving from various places. I&#8217;m trying to better understand the nuance between progress and perfection.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Pos Isn&#8217;t Possible for BTC</h2>
<p>Skar further commented he’s not necessarily against bitcoin, and he’s confident humans can be innovative enough that they manage to find new ways of ensuring the environment’s survival while remaining creative. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>The climate crisis demands that we all, not just Greenpeace or bitcoin, find ways to ensure a just and green future. We regularly work on issues that are objectively more complicated and difficult to figure out than changing bitcoin’s code. It is only impossible if we refuse to try.</p></blockquote>
<p>Some, such as Phil Harvey – CEO of bitcoin mining firm Sabre56 – says it’s virtually impossible for BTC to switch to a PoS network, and he’s confident that users would never accept it as an original network even if this was doable.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/skull-of-satoshi-benjamin-wong-apologizes-for-anti-bitcoin-project/">Skull of Satoshi&#8217;s Benjamin Wong Apologizes for &#8220;Anti-Bitcoin&#8221; Project</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/skull-of-satoshi-benjamin-wong-apologizes-for-anti-bitcoin-project/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nvidia Is Clearly Not a Cryptocurrency Fan</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nvidia-is-clearly-not-a-cryptocurrency-fan/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nvidia-is-clearly-not-a-cryptocurrency-fan/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 13:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chat GPT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nvidia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77636</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Despite a relatively broad history with cryptocurrencies and digital assets, graphics card manufacturer Nvidia has come out to say that crypto has no purpose in society. Nvidia Doesn&#8217;t Think Crypto Has Much to It In a recent interview, the company’s chief technology officer Micheal Kagan commented that the graphics cards Nvidia creates should be utilized<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nvidia-is-clearly-not-a-cryptocurrency-fan/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nvidia-is-clearly-not-a-cryptocurrency-fan/">Nvidia Is Clearly Not a Cryptocurrency Fan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite a relatively broad history with cryptocurrencies and digital assets, graphics card manufacturer Nvidia has <a href="https://www.techspot.com/news/98081-nvidia-calls-cryptocurrency-useless-society-gpus-better-used.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">come out to say that crypto</a> has no purpose in society.</p>
<h2>Nvidia Doesn&#8217;t Think Crypto Has Much to It</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, the company’s chief technology officer Micheal Kagan commented that the graphics cards Nvidia creates should be utilized for activities other than simply mining crypto. He suggested using them to power AI-based technologies like Chat GPT. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>All this crypto stuff, it needed parallel processing, and [Nvidia] is the best, so people just programmed it to use for this purpose. They bought a lot of stuff, and then eventually it collapsed because it doesn&#8217;t bring anything useful for society. AI does. With Chat GPT, everybody can now create his own machine, his own program. You just tell it what to do, and it will, and if it doesn&#8217;t work the way you want it to, you tell it, &#8216;I want something different.’</p></blockquote>
<p>Chat GPT is getting a lot of traction as of late given it’s an application that will pretty much write whatever you need it to, from a blog post to a speech, as in the case of a recent one produced for Joe Biden. Apparently the President’s brain is <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-chat-gpt-could-be-used-to-boost-blockchain/" data-wpel-link="internal">melting so badly he can’t</a> even take the time to write his own speech; he needs a machine to do it for him.</p>
<p>In any case, putting this present situation aside, Kagan is confident in the technology and he thinks the company’s graphics cards will be put to greater use should they be utilized to power said applications instead of extracting new units of crypto from the blockchain. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>We were heavily involved in algo trading. People on Wall Street were buying our stuff to save a few nanoseconds on the wire, the banks were doing crazy things like pulling the fibers under the Hudson taut to make them a little bit shorter, to save a few nanoseconds between their datacenter and the stock exchange. I never believed that [crypto] is something that will do something good for humanity. You know, people do crazy things, but they buy your stuff, you sell them stuff, but you don&#8217;t redirect the company to support whatever it is.</p></blockquote>
<h2>The Company Was Once Heavily Tied to Digital Currency</h2>
<p>The funny thing about this entire situation is the fact that Nvidia has been used heavily over the years specifically for mining purposes. So many of the firm’s products were sold to miners that the company wound up getting indirectly tied to digital assets about five years earlier, and when crypto prices crashed, so did its revenue and stock shares.</p>
<p>At the same time, Nvidia failed to disclose how much money it made from miners in 2022. This led to a $5.5 million fine from the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nvidia-is-clearly-not-a-cryptocurrency-fan/">Nvidia Is Clearly Not a Cryptocurrency Fan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/nvidia-is-clearly-not-a-cryptocurrency-fan/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
