<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 11:06:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>New Pepe the Frog Meme Currency Is Exploding in Price</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-pepe-the-frog-meme-currency-is-exploding-in-price/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-pepe-the-frog-meme-currency-is-exploding-in-price/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 17:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pepe the Frog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78027</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Meme coins are all the rage, and now it appears one based on the infamous image of Pepe the Frog is making waves in the crypto industry and witnessing price hikes like no other in its category. Pepe the Frog Is Now a Currency! Meme coins have always been extremely popular. One of the biggest<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-pepe-the-frog-meme-currency-is-exploding-in-price/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-pepe-the-frog-meme-currency-is-exploding-in-price/">New Pepe the Frog Meme Currency Is Exploding in Price</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Meme coins are all the rage, and now it appears <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/04/23/the-price-of-this-new-crypto-meme-coin-rose-21000-as-bitcoin-and-ethereum-stalled-but-theres-a-nasty-catch/?sh=2b35a11b3400" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">one based on the infamous</a> image of Pepe the Frog is making waves in the crypto industry and witnessing price hikes like no other in its category.</p>
<h2>Pepe the Frog Is Now a Currency!</h2>
<p>Meme coins have always been extremely popular. One of the biggest ones – <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/dogecoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">Dogecoin</a> – was initially created as a joke. It was literally built to make fun of the crypto arena and all those that sought to utilize its offerings or that had any respect for it. By some odd chance of fate, the currency has literally become one of the biggest digital currencies out there. It presently boasts a market cap that exceeds $1 billion and has been the subject of heavy <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/latest-elon-musk-tweet-sends-dogecoin-soaring/" data-wpel-link="internal">praise from Elon Musk</a>.</p>
<p>Dogecoin spawned other assets such as the Shiba Inu coin. The Shiba Inu dog long served as the cute little mascot for the parent digital asset Doge, and it wasn’t long before a spinoff of sorts was conceived in the Shiba Inu currency, which has also long been loved amongst crypto fans.</p>
<p>But Pepe the Frog appears to be on an entirely different playing field. At the time of writing, the currency is shooting up in price by a whopping 21,000 percent, and this is a currency that was only launched a few weekends ago. It now sits as the sixth-largest meme currency by market cap, which at press time, exceeds $150 million.</p>
<p>In a recent report, crypto research company Messari explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>Meme coins are once again polarizing the crypto world. A new project, Pepe, has amassed a $100 million market cap in less than one week. Similar to previous meme coin price surges, Pepe has generated eye-popping returns for its early investors.</p></blockquote>
<p>Pepe the Frog has been adopted by a wide array of online communities. The image has a circulation of about 420.69 trillion, though it’s not without controversy. The meme currency, for example, comes with a warning on sites like Coinmarketcap.com, which says traders should “exercise caution” if they choose to purchase or trade the asset.</p>
<p>The Messari report also said that while the currency may presently be doing well on paper, it doesn’t feel like it has any real future as a method of payment or as an actual digital token. Right now, the liquidity pool for the meme coin sits at a mere $3 million. Compare this with Ethereum, for example, whose daily trading volume is just shy of $800 million.</p>
<h2>Try to Be Careful</h2>
<p>The report said:</p>
<blockquote><p>One of the earliest buyers has turned a 0.125 Ethereum purchase into close to $2 million on-chain. However, since this individual owns 1.4 percent of the total supply, they will not be able to realize these returns without crashing the market.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-pepe-the-frog-meme-currency-is-exploding-in-price/">New Pepe the Frog Meme Currency Is Exploding in Price</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-pepe-the-frog-meme-currency-is-exploding-in-price/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Can Blockchain Boost the Transparency of Climate Credits?</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/can-blockchain-boost-the-transparency-of-climate-credits/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/can-blockchain-boost-the-transparency-of-climate-credits/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 15:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[climate credits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Salmeron Barnes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78025</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Many companies are beginning to use blockchain technology to boost the transparency of carbon credits. Blockchain and Carbon Credits&#8230; Are They Coming Together? Carbon credits are designed to help companies bankroll protocols and projects that ultimately preserve the environment from poor or improper climate activity. However, the problem with these credits is that they are<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/can-blockchain-boost-the-transparency-of-climate-credits/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/can-blockchain-boost-the-transparency-of-climate-credits/">Can Blockchain Boost the Transparency of Climate Credits?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Many companies are beginning to use blockchain technology to <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/startups-want-to-use-blockchain-technology-to-improve-the-carbon-credit-markets-here-s-why-big-names-in-the-climate-industry-are-warming-up-to-the-idea/ar-AA1abJYy" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">boost the transparency of</a> carbon credits.</p>
<h2>Blockchain and Carbon Credits&#8230; Are They Coming Together?</h2>
<p>Carbon credits are designed to help companies bankroll protocols and projects that ultimately preserve the environment from poor or improper climate activity. However, the problem with these credits is that they are not always transparent, and it’s not entirely clear if they’ve been effective when it comes to keeping the planet and its atmosphere clean and clear from pollution.</p>
<p>Blockchain is presenting several answers for companies like Toucan, Return, and Open Forest Protocol, and they’re seeking to tie climate initiatives in with the illustrious technology that has powered the crypto arena for so long.</p>
<p>The way climate credits work is that they are bought by companies who spew greenhouse gas emissions such as methane into the atmosphere through their operations. These credits are then put towards environmentally friendly projects and initiatives. Think of them as companies’ way of saying “we’re sorry” for all the alleged damage they may be doing to the planet.</p>
<p>This way, for every poor initiative that occurs through the company’s operations, they can at least make sure a project seeking to offset any emissions has what it needs to stay afloat and keep working. Sadly, it’s never been clear if these projects are doing what they say they do, nor is it clear if their methods for cleaning up the planet truly work.</p>
<p>Erin Murphy – the chief growth officer at Topl, a company that’s designed a blockchain specifically for climate-based issues – said in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>It&#8217;s a fundamental issue in the [industry]. We want to see more competition [and] more scientific rigor in this space.</p></blockquote>
<p>Many believe blockchain can provide the answers eco-friendly individuals seek. Blockchain can give them specific information by bringing together several different groups to ensure a project’s merits are in place. They can also see to it that participation in these projects is incentivized, and that general criteria for issuing and using climate credits are laid out properly.</p>
<p>Salmeron Barnes – the co-founder and managing director of Aureus Earth, which builds financial tools to encourage carbon reduction – said in an emailed note:</p>
<blockquote><p>The decentralized verification capability and the promise of new low-emissions blockchain offerings are what attracted AE to create a blockchain-based registry.</p></blockquote>
<h2>An Interesting Reversal of Sorts</h2>
<p>Interestingly, blockchain is centered in a world that <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-bitcoin-mining-may-require-more-energy-than-180-countries/" data-wpel-link="internal">has long been criticized</a> for its alleged lack of ecological and environmental awareness. Blockchain powers crypto, which was born through the mining process, and it’s this process that has attracted so much hate from environmentalists over the years.</p>
<p>Many claims have been made that crypto mining ultimately uses more energy than most developing countries, and that the process is pushing the planet towards an unforgiving (and irreversible) end.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/can-blockchain-boost-the-transparency-of-climate-credits/">Can Blockchain Boost the Transparency of Climate Credits?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/can-blockchain-boost-the-transparency-of-climate-credits/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Base Protocol from Coinbase Set to Go Live Later This Year</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-base-protocol-from-coinbase-set-to-go-live-later-this-year/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-base-protocol-from-coinbase-set-to-go-live-later-this-year/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 13:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Base]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78022</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Leading digital currency exchange Coinbase is getting ready to release its new Base protocol in late 2023. Coinbase Says It Will Bring One Billion Users Onboard Base is an Ethereum-focused, layer-2 blockchain. The program has been in a testing phase since February of this year, and those in charge are now preparing it for a<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-base-protocol-from-coinbase-set-to-go-live-later-this-year/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-base-protocol-from-coinbase-set-to-go-live-later-this-year/">New Base Protocol from Coinbase Set to Go Live Later This Year</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Leading digital currency exchange Coinbase is getting <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/coinbase-layer-2-blockchain-plans-155304979.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">ready to release its new</a> Base protocol in late 2023.</p>
<h2>Coinbase Says It Will Bring One Billion Users Onboard</h2>
<p>Base is an Ethereum-focused, layer-2 blockchain. The program has been in a testing phase since February of this year, and those in charge are now preparing it for a mainnet launch that will allow it to be utilized by all the exchange’s customers.</p>
<p>Jesse Pollack – the lead for Base – recently divulged several facts about the upcoming protocol in an interview. He said that while Coinbase is not set on releasing any official timelines or dates just yet, he can confirm that 2023 will be the year in which it becomes fully available. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>It’s coming soon. We’re working hard on it. It’s our number one priority alongside decentralization goals, and the rest of the year is about making sure we get there as quickly as possible.</p></blockquote>
<p>The move will mark a nice change of pace for the once prominent digital currency trading platform. While still popular amongst many crypto traders and fans, Coinbase has endured its fair share of blows to the head in recent weeks in the shape of the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), which recently sent a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">Wells notice to the prominent</a> investing enterprise.</p>
<p>While a Wells notice does not instigate that the company has been charged with a crime, it hints that potential charges may be coming soon, and that the firm should prepare itself. Coinbase took serious issue with the notice and claimed that it met with SEC officials several times over the past few years to ensure it always remained compliant with present rules and regulations.</p>
<p>Not long ago, Coinbase mentioned that the regulatory environment in the United States has grown so speculative and frightening that the company is now <a href="https://fortune.com/crypto/2023/04/19/coinbase-gets-bermuda-license-plans-to-launch-offshore-exchange-in-coming-weeks/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">considering leaving America</a> and setting up shop in Bermuda. While U.S. customers will still be privy to services offered by the firm, the company will no longer be settled on American soil.</p>
<p>Pollack continued his statement by claiming that the company is looking to bring at least one million builders on board, which will in turn lead to about one billion more users. The goal is to have everyone on-chain and provide access to “easy to use” crypto-centered products. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think less about Base passing Coinbase and more about how Base plus Coinbase over the next decade are going to work together to bring those million developers [and] billions of users on-chain.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Keeping Things Off the Radar</h2>
<p>He also said that per verbiage issued by Brian Armstrong – the CEO of Coinbase – the program is going to be fully decentralized.</p>
<p>This makes perfect sense given the many issues the company has clearly dealt with from the SEC and similar agencies.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-base-protocol-from-coinbase-set-to-go-live-later-this-year/">New Base Protocol from Coinbase Set to Go Live Later This Year</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-base-protocol-from-coinbase-set-to-go-live-later-this-year/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The World of Web3 &#8211; A New Film by #TheFutureisNowFilm Series Creates Mass Adoption for Web3</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-world-of-web3-a-new-film-by-thefutureisnowfilm-series-creates-mass-adoption-for-web3/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-world-of-web3-a-new-film-by-thefutureisnowfilm-series-creates-mass-adoption-for-web3/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 10:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry and Adoption]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78623</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Have you ever wondered what it’s like to dive deep into the world of Web3? What lurks around those corners? Is this a path of decentralization and salvation of humanity&#8217;s monotonous jobs and rather boring dogma-like lifestyles that have so far kept the human kind working in silos and well, working in on-end? Or is<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-world-of-web3-a-new-film-by-thefutureisnowfilm-series-creates-mass-adoption-for-web3/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-world-of-web3-a-new-film-by-thefutureisnowfilm-series-creates-mass-adoption-for-web3/">The World of Web3 &#8211; A New Film by #TheFutureisNowFilm Series Creates Mass Adoption for Web3</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Have you ever wondered what it’s like to dive deep into the world of Web3? What lurks around those corners? Is this a path of decentralization and salvation of humanity&#8217;s monotonous jobs and rather boring dogma-like lifestyles that have so far kept the human kind working in silos and well, working in on-end? Or is it just a bridge to a much more centralized conditioning of the human psyche.</p>
<p>Considering today&#8217;s financial climate, the dollar&#8217;s obvious decline, BRICS nations announcing a gold backed digital currency, the clash of CBDC and Bitcoin&#8217;s Web3 is certainly coming to a climax. Yet the industry of blockchain and Web3 that undoubtedly has been made popular due to Bitcoin&#8217;s mass adoption, still to this day promotes the idea of monetary and data sovereignty, while successfully attracting thousands of people daily who open their wallets, get a bit of crypto and find themselves deep in the world of Web3.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-78624 aligncenter" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Picture36-600x428.jpg" alt="" width="600" height="428" /></p>
<p>2020 marked a big year for cryptocurrency mass adoption, as people had what seemed back then an endless amount of time to get into the topic and read Satoshi&#8217;s white-paper thanks to the pandemic. Two years prior to that, on the brink of Bitcoin&#8217;s beyond-20k unprecedented bull run, a film series by the name of #TheFutureisNowFilm came to be. Created by an American filmmaker Miguel Francis-Santiago who radically changed his career path from being a journalist in the world of current affairs, geopolitics &amp; more, to a roving crypto documentarist traveling the world and exposing both the good and the bad but most of all all the excitement behind the industry of Blockchain, through a unique cinematic approach that over the 5 years has had no analogues to the film series he currently creates with his team, which has an uncanny name by today’s standards &#8211; &#8220;<a href="http://youtube.com/thefutureisnow" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">The Future is Now</a>&#8220;, implying that every moment counts and all we truly have is the present, for the past we cannot change and the future we cannot truly predict.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-78625 aligncenter" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Picture37-600x255.png" alt="" width="600" height="255" /></p>
<p>Its latest iteration called &#8220;<a href="https://youtu.be/Cuto1kx0A5o" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">The World of Web3</a>&#8221; being the 18th edition of the series, the filmmaker takes us on a ride through today&#8217;s Dubai industry of decentralization and its milestones with such prominent figures like one of the prime authorities on crypto in the region Dr. Marwan AlZarouni of Dubai Blockchain Center, appointed by The Ruler of Dubai H.H. Sheikh Mohammed bin-Rashid Al Maktoum himself to help co-create Dubai as a harbor of innovation. According to Dr. Marwan, &#8220;Dubai is run as a business, and we prefer to work with only the best of the best&#8221;, to no surprise as Dubai clearly has become the epicenter for Web3 and digital currencies in today’s world. However, another not far away Emirate of Ras Al-Khaimah is potentially about to take the lead as it is now officially on verge of becoming a Web3 Hub with licenses available for issuing and distribution of digital currencies.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-78626 aligncenter" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Picture38-600x270.jpg" alt="" width="600" height="270" /></p>
<p>&#8220;If the people of America only knew how the money system works, there&#8217;d be a revolution the next day&#8221; says Davinci Jeremie, a famous crypto influencer and Founder of DavinciJ15. While another star of the film, Car Runefelt of The Moon Group, who went from a supermarket clerk about 5 years ago, to now a crypto millionaire driving his Bugatti around Dubai, believes that &#8220;Bitcoin has become the Noah&#8217;s Ark, and if you&#8217;re not in, you might find the future bleak&#8221;. There is certainly truth to this, as more assets devalue and the world clearly feels the effects of the current economic and information war that is happening between quite a few nations, sometimes being compared to a proxy world war.<br />
<img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-78627 aligncenter" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Picture39-600x257.png" alt="" width="600" height="257" /></p>
<p>&#8220;The World of Web3&#8221; was filmed at the same titled <a href="https://dubai2023.wowsummit.net/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">WOW Summit</a> organized by GuyWay Events and the film director&#8217;s original idea was to create a guide for anyone entering the space or interested in exploring this industry, says Miguel Francis-Santiago, the CEO and Founder of The Future is Now DAO and the creator of The Future is Now Film &#8211; &#8220;I wanted to create a Web3 encyclopedia for people, while telling the story through tangible innovators who have experienced both highs and lows and are ready to speak about their experience to the public&#8221;. Miguel certainly achieved this through industry professionals like Ilman Shazhaev of <a href="http://farcana.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Farcana</a>, which is quite an interesting source for Web3 mass adoption being a 3D-Shooter GameFi Universe where you enter with its native token but you get to win Bitcoin in what was branded as &#8220;Play to Hash&#8221; algorithm. The company provides mining services as well, and has enabled their data centers to allocate the prize in the form of Bitcoin&#8217;s hashrate. Other revolutionary concepts like MediaChain being a gateway for influencers to monetize their art and enter the Web3 space with the help of industry professionals who create incentives for the audience to join the influencer and become a part of his or her community through for example a unique NFT collection &#8211; is also certainly a way for mass adoption.</p>
<p>It was interesting to note that traditional market making is not far off from crypto market making and if traditional market makers are essentially gatekeepers for the bank liquidity into clients of interest, in the Web3 world, Market Making Pro with Aleks Gladskih and Mikhail Fillipov provides the lifeline for projects in Web3 and from what they describe does it in the same sometimes astronomical manner like traditional market makers, who according to them are simply world’s top banks like JP Morgan.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-78628 aligncenter" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Picture40-600x258.png" alt="" width="600" height="258" /></p>
<p>Another major influencer in the film happens to be Matthias &#8220;Sheikh&#8221; Mende, who has been a Dubai Resident for over 5 years now. Heading something called <a href="http://bonuz.market" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Bonuz Market</a>, Matthias aims to revolutionize the way celebrities interact with their fans, while also giving them the right to distribute control of their celebrity avatars in the Bonuz Metaverse, to the AI itself as an insurance policy after they die! How exciting? Imagine if Larry King or John McAfee would still be alive in the world of the never ending collective AI consciousness of the world wide web 3.0?</p>
<p>The private screening and premiere party was held at the end of April 2023 in Dubai, under the patronage of H.H. Sheikh Abdulhakim Al-Maktoum Family Office &amp; Royal Investment Club, while the public release appeared on the film&#8217;s YouTube channel a week later (http://youtube.com/thefutureisnow). If you are into Web3 or you feel it&#8217;s time to let loose and discover, you might want to put this on the schedule if you believe that film, emotions and the excitement this combination can cause may actually move the needle in this tug of war between centralized and decentralized powers through the power of cinema.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-world-of-web3-a-new-film-by-thefutureisnowfilm-series-creates-mass-adoption-for-web3/">The World of Web3 &#8211; A New Film by #TheFutureisNowFilm Series Creates Mass Adoption for Web3</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-world-of-web3-a-new-film-by-thefutureisnowfilm-series-creates-mass-adoption-for-web3/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Make Money Quickly With HappyMiner Cloud Mining platform</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-to-make-money-quickly-with-happyminer-cloud-mining-platform/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-to-make-money-quickly-with-happyminer-cloud-mining-platform/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 08:47:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78620</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>HappyMiner is a cloud mining company that allows individuals to return investment through its cloud mining services. The company is pleased to announce new affordable cloud mining plans. To address the latest innovation, HappyMiner announces new affordable cloud mining plans. It enables individuals to invest in cryptocurrency mining while minimizing the associated costs. By offering<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-to-make-money-quickly-with-happyminer-cloud-mining-platform/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-to-make-money-quickly-with-happyminer-cloud-mining-platform/">How to Make Money Quickly With HappyMiner Cloud Mining platform</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://happyminer.us/?livebitcoinnews" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">HappyMiner</a> is a cloud mining company that allows individuals to return investment through its cloud mining services. The company is pleased to announce new affordable cloud mining plans.</p>
<p>To address the latest innovation, HappyMiner announces new affordable cloud mining plans. It enables individuals to invest in cryptocurrency mining while minimizing the associated costs. By offering affordable cloud mining plans, HappyMiner helps to democratize the mining industry and make it accessible to a broader audience.</p>
<p>Including more, with the opportunity of $10, <a href="https://happyminer.us/?livebitcoinnews" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">HappyMiner</a> offers users a chance to acquire cryptocurrency. Additionally, the mining process is fully automated, meaning users can start mining with just a few clicks. HappyMiner provides exceptional services around-the-clock.</p>
<p>In addition, the platform&#8217;s new plans offer credible features that attract investors, such as:</p>
<ul>
<li>Those that <a href="https://happyminer.us/signup?livebitcoinnews" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">sign up</a> receive $10 right away. They will receive $0.80 daily, which they may use to purchase the Primary Mining package daily.</li>
<li>There is a $100 minimum deposit requirement. The users can create their cryptocurrency business without huge investments.</li>
<li>An easy and quick start procedure. In only a few minutes, register and begin mining Bitcoin.</li>
<li>On HappyMiner, users can daily benefit from cloud hash contracts (review available withdrawal methods on their website).</li>
<li>The users can leave the cloud mining industry at any time with HappyMiner.</li>
<li>The daily yield rate ranges from 8%, depending on the selected crypto package.</li>
<li>HappyMiner offers an affiliate program with 4.5% lifetime rewards.</li>
<li>It gives the opportunity to choose from different crypto contracts.</li>
<li> No overhead or electricity fees.</li>
<li> 24-hour online support.</li>
<li>DDoS and SSL protect the system.</li>
</ul>
<p>Let&#8217;s take a closer look at these packages:</p>
<ol>
<li>Free Primary Mining: This contract is valid for 1 day and priced at $10. Its fixed return is $10.8</li>
<li>Bitcoin Mining: This contract is valid for 3 days and priced at $100. Its fixed return is $104.5</li>
<li>Litecoin Mining: This contract is valid for 7 days and priced at $500. Its fixed return is $563</li>
<li>BitcoinCash Mining: This contract is valid for 15 days and is priced at $1200. Its fixed return is $1545</li>
<li>Dogecoin Mining: This contract is valid for 30 days and is priced at $3000. Its fixed return is $4890</li>
<li>Dashcoin Mining: This contract is valid for 60 days and is priced at $6400. It has a fixed return of $15280</li>
<li>Filecoin Mining: This contract is valid for 90 days and is priced at $9600. Its fixed return is $29644</li>
</ol>
<p><a href="https://happyminer.us/?livebitcoinnews" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">HappyMiner</a> brings solutions for both experienced traders and newcomers to the market who are looking to participate in mining. The company brings game-changing development to the industry as it opens up the world of cryptocurrency mining to a wider audience and allows more individuals to take advantage of the potential rewards. The platform is truly disrupting the market and paving the way for the new era of cryptocurrency mining.</p>
<p>According to the CEO of HappyMiner, &#8220;Our mission is to make cryptocurrency mining accessible and affordable for everyone. With our new cloud mining plans, we are offering a cost-effective solution that enables anyone to start mining Bitcoin or other cryptocurrencies without having to worry about the associated costs and technical difficulties.&#8221;</p>
<p>Furthermore, <a href="https://happyminer.us/?livebitcoinnews" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">HappyMiner&#8217;s</a> cloud mining offers user-friendly services to all its investors. Users can start mining within minutes of signing up, with no technical expertise required. The platform also provides a range of tools and resources to help users to maximize their mining advantages, including mining calculators, profitability trackers as well as mining guides.</p>
<p><strong>About HappyMiner:</strong></p>
<p>HappyMiner is a licensed cloud mining company founded in 2018 in the United States. Like any certified hash provider, HappyMiner owns industrial facilities with a big tech park of professional Bitcoin mining rigs. Data centers are located in Iceland, Norway, and Canada. 2,800K+ individuals from all around the globe currently earn cryptocurrency on HappyMiner. visit its website at <a href="https://happyminer.us/?livebitcoinnews" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://happyminer.us/</a></p>
<p><strong>S</strong><strong>o</strong><strong>cial Media:</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@happyminerUS" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener"><strong>YOUTUBE</strong></a><strong>    </strong><a href="https://twitter.com/happyminerUS" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener"><strong>TWITTER</strong></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-to-make-money-quickly-with-happyminer-cloud-mining-platform/">How to Make Money Quickly With HappyMiner Cloud Mining platform</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/how-to-make-money-quickly-with-happyminer-cloud-mining-platform/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Key Breakout Resistance Sits At $118</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-key-breakout-resistance-sits-at-118/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-key-breakout-resistance-sits-at-118/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 03:08:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78614</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin cash is attempting a recovery wave above the $112 resistance against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above the $114 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $116 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-key-breakout-resistance-sits-at-118/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-key-breakout-resistance-sits-at-118/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Key Breakout Resistance Sits At $118</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin cash is attempting a recovery wave above the $112 resistance against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above the $114 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $116 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair must clear $116 and $118 to start a steady upward movement in the near term.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin cash price is rising above $114 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-key-resistance-near-28-5k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. BCH/USD could start a fresh surge if it clears the $118 level.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin cash price formed a decent support base above the $110 level. BCH started a decent increase and was able to clear the $112 resistance zone.</p>
<p>The price climbed above the $114 resistance level. There was a move above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $117.30 swing high to the $111.60 low. It is now trading above the $114 zone and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-105-2/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $116 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $116 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair.</p>
<p>The trend line is near the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $117.30 swing high to the $111.60 low. The next major resistance is near the $118 level, above which the price may perhaps rise toward the $120 level. Any more gains above $120 could set the pace for a move toward the $126 level.</p>
<p>If not, the price might decline again. Immediate support on the downside is near the $113 level. The first major support sits near the $112 level. The next major support is near $110, below which the bears might aim for $102. The next target for them may perhaps be near the $100 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_78615" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Bitcoin-Cash.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78615" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78615" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Bitcoin-Cash.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash Price " width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78615" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Cash Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BCHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Bitcoin Cash’s price is now trading above the $114 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price must clear $116 and $118 to continue higher in the near term.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for BCH/USD is gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BCH/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $113 and $110.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $116 and $118.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-key-breakout-resistance-sits-at-118/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Key Breakout Resistance Sits At $118</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-key-breakout-resistance-sits-at-118/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Texas Passes New Proof of Reserves Bill for Crypto Exchanges</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-passes-new-proof-of-reserves-bill-for-crypto-exchanges/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-passes-new-proof-of-reserves-bill-for-crypto-exchanges/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 17:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[proof of reserves]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Texas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78020</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Texas House of Representatives has passed a bill saying that all crypto exchanges and related platforms must provide proof of reserves. This means that all trading companies must give regular proof that they have enough assets and currency in play to keep themselves afloat and to ensure all customers get their due funds should<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-passes-new-proof-of-reserves-bill-for-crypto-exchanges/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-passes-new-proof-of-reserves-bill-for-crypto-exchanges/">Texas Passes New Proof of Reserves Bill for Crypto Exchanges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Texas House of Representatives has passed a bill <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/savingandinvesting/texas-house-passes-cryptocurrency-bill-requiring-proof-of-reserves/ar-AA1a8Guv" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">saying that all crypto exchanges</a> and related platforms must provide proof of reserves. This means that all trading companies must give regular proof that they have enough assets and currency in play to keep themselves afloat and to ensure all customers get their due funds should problems arise.</p>
<h2>Texas Pushes for Stronger Crypto Regulations</h2>
<p>The move is clearly a reaction to the FTX debacle, which occurred last November. FTX will likely go down as one of the biggest debacles of the digital currency space. The exchange – which first opened its doors for business in 2019 – rose to prominence three years later to become one of the top five digital currency trading platforms in the world. Its founder and chief executive Sam Bankman-Fried was lauded as a genius by many, and his net worth was in the billions towards the end of 2022.</p>
<p>Sadly, this reputation was short-lived as in mid-November, SBF complained of a liquidity crunch on social media. He said he <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>needed fast cash</strong></a> to keep his business in operation, and he eventually turned to his biggest rival Binance about a possible buyout. While things <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>appeared to be moving</strong></a> in that direction for some time, Binance eventually backed <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>away from the deal</strong></a>, claiming the problems FTX was facing were simply too big for it to handle.</p>
<p>From there, the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>company filed bankruptcy</strong></a> and SBF resigned from his post. Things would have been bad enough if they had stopped there, but the trash meter kept rising. It was later discovered that SBF had utilized customer funds to invest in luxury Bahamian real estate and to pay off loans taken out by his other company Alameda Research. He <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftxs-disgraced-founder-has-been-arrested/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>was eventually arrested</strong></a> and extradited back to the United States. He has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-ftx-exec-sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-fraud/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>entered a not guilty plea</strong></a> and is awaiting trial at his <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-to-await-trial-at-his-parents-house/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>parents’ California home</strong></a>.</p>
<p>Texas is a state that <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-is-still-a-major-crypto-mining-hub/" data-wpel-link="internal">clearly takes crypto seriously</a>. The state opened itself to all the digital currency miners that had to flee their native <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-crypto-mining-clampdown-in-china-is-not-over/" data-wpel-link="internal">China after the country</a> implemented rules that outlawed all digital currency mining. Texas is known for low-priced electricity and vast open regions, thus making it the perfect place for extraction operations.</p>
<h2>Keeping Traders Safe</h2>
<p>But it’s precisely because it takes crypto so seriously that it doesn’t want to see anyone get hurt, nor does it want to see investors lose their hard-earned money due to a few faulty or fraudulent activities from those in charge. Thus, all crypto exchanges that do business within Texas or with customers in the state must submit reports no later than 90 days after the start of each fiscal year showing what reserves they have in place.</p>
<p>Many believe the move will lead to more adoption of crypto and stronger legitimacy in the industry.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-passes-new-proof-of-reserves-bill-for-crypto-exchanges/">Texas Passes New Proof of Reserves Bill for Crypto Exchanges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-passes-new-proof-of-reserves-bill-for-crypto-exchanges/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Firm Unchained Capital Has Made a Ton of Money</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-firm-unchained-capital-has-made-a-ton-of-money/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-firm-unchained-capital-has-made-a-ton-of-money/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 15:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HODLing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Unchained Capital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78010</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Unchained Capital – a crypto firm based in Austin, Texas – has garnered more than $60 million through a new funding round. Unchained Capital Garners $60 Million The news is positive for many reasons, a big one being that the crypto space appears to be returning to form, and confidence is once again making its<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-firm-unchained-capital-has-made-a-ton-of-money/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-firm-unchained-capital-has-made-a-ton-of-money/">Crypto Firm Unchained Capital Has Made a Ton of Money</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Unchained Capital – a crypto firm based in Austin, Texas – has <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/austin-based-bitcoin-financial-services-110140047.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">garnered more than $60 million</a> through a new funding round.</p>
<h2>Unchained Capital Garners $60 Million</h2>
<p>The news is positive for many reasons, a big one being that the crypto space appears to be returning to form, and confidence is once again making its way into the arena. All throughout 2022, the crypto space appeared to suffer from an apparent lack of interest due to ongoing price dips and other problems.</p>
<p>Bitcoin, for example, lost more than 70 percent of its value and fell into the mid-$16K range by the time the year was over. This was a huge step down from the new all-time high it achieved in November of 2021 (at that time, it was trading for about $68K per unit).</p>
<p>Many other digital assets chose to follow in BTC’s footsteps, and the crypto world lost more than $2 trillion in valuation in just under a year. This caused many investors to step away, and the industry lost a lot of the funding it was so prone to receiving over the past few years.</p>
<p>But with a new drop of happiness in the form of $60 million for Unchained Capital, it appears things are once again turning around. Not long ago, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin rose to $30K</a>, a ten-month high for the world’s number one digital currency by market cap, and while the price <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-falls-to-28k-analysts-are-wondering-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">has once again fallen</a> into the high $20K range, things are still in a powerful-enough position that crypto companies, right and left, are attracting institutional investors and new funding to help the industry expand and become more mature.</p>
<p>Vivek Pattipati – a partner at Vali that will soon be on Unchained Capital’s board of directors – said that while the crypto arena is enduring many challenges, he believes the company will serve as a primary leader and lift the industry out of its present doldrums. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>In the midst of market chaos, Unchained has emerged as a highly trusted provider of bitcoin custody and financial services through superior technology, risk management, regulatory compliance, and client service. Particularly in lending, the company has differentiated itself by minimizing risk to both the lender and the borrower, leading to resilience and an extraordinary opportunity to capture market share.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Working for Long-Term HODLers and Investors</h2>
<p>The company was founded seven years ago in 2016 and seeks to develop long-term technology for both individuals and enterprises looking to heighten their private key ownership. These figures are not interested in short-term gains and are instead looking to HODL their funds for a long while.</p>
<p>Unchained has also commented that the individuals it works with can maximize and secure their bitcoin holdings over “multiple generations.” Right now, the enterprise has more than $2 billion in bitcoin under its management.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-firm-unchained-capital-has-made-a-ton-of-money/">Crypto Firm Unchained Capital Has Made a Ton of Money</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-firm-unchained-capital-has-made-a-ton-of-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Moon Blocks to Permit Crypto-Based Payments</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/moon-blocks-to-permit-crypto-based-payments/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/moon-blocks-to-permit-crypto-based-payments/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 13:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bit Pay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto payments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Moon Blocks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78015</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Web3 and fintech company Moon Blocks has joined hands with payment processor Bit Pay to allow for cryptocurrency-based payments on its platform. Moon Blocks and Bit Pay Are Partners The move is pushing the goals of bitcoin and its digital counterparts closer to being achieved. What many people likely forget is that while bitcoin and many<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/moon-blocks-to-permit-crypto-based-payments/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/moon-blocks-to-permit-crypto-based-payments/">Moon Blocks to Permit Crypto-Based Payments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Web3 and fintech company Moon Blocks has <a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/press-release/moonblocks-selects-bitpay-to-accept-cryptocurrency-payments-2023-04-21" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">joined hands with payment</a> processor Bit Pay to allow for cryptocurrency-based payments on its platform.</p>
<h2>Moon Blocks and Bit Pay Are Partners</h2>
<p>The move is pushing the goals of bitcoin and its digital counterparts closer to being achieved. What many people likely forget is that while bitcoin and many of its crypto cousins have taken on either speculative or even hedge-like statuses in recent years, many of them were initially designed to serve as payment tools. They were built to push checks, credit cards, and fiat currencies to the side, but this has been a relatively slow journey given the volatility that continues to drag them down.</p>
<p>It is extremely hard to understand when <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a> and its crypto family will go up or down when it comes to their prices. Many stores and companies have been reluctant to say “yes” when it comes to accepting crypto payments for this reason, and to a degree, we can’t blame them.</p>
<p>Consider the following scenario: someone walks into a store and buys $50 worth of merchandise with bitcoin. For one reason or another, the store doesn’t trade the BTC into fiat right away and about 24 hours go by. From there, the price of BTC goes down and that $50 becomes $40. The customer gets to keep everything he or she bought, but the store loses money in the end. Is this a fair situation? Not everyone thinks so.</p>
<p>That’s what makes enterprises like Moon Blocks so important. They understand the initial purposes of bitcoin and digital currencies and are trying to transform them into usable tools that everyday people can benefit from.</p>
<p>Giuseppe – CEO at Moon Blocks – said in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>We decided to accept crypto because of [many] reasons. Firstly, we want to show that we understand and cater to a crypto-savvy audience to build trust with potential clients. Secondly, by accepting cryptocurrency payments, we can avoid high transaction fees associated with traditional payment methods and potentially offer lower prices to our clients. Additionally, embracing decentralization is at the heart of our philosophy, and accepting cryptocurrency payments can help us to position ourselves as a leader in the [industry]. To that end, by offering more payment options and flexibility, we can attract and retain clients who prefer to pay in cryptocurrency for various reasons, such as privacy concerns or a belief in the long-term value of certain cryptocurrencies. Bit Pay manages the entire process and makes it easy to receive crypto from the customer and deposits cash into our account.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Keeping Things Modern</h2>
<p>Merrick Theobald – vice president of marketing at Bit Pay – said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Moon Blocks realizes the potential for crypto to transform the Web3, fintech, SAAS, and gaming marketing industries, making payments faster, more secure, and less expensive on a global scale.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/moon-blocks-to-permit-crypto-based-payments/">Moon Blocks to Permit Crypto-Based Payments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/moon-blocks-to-permit-crypto-based-payments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
