<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 03:00:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Why was May a Rough Month for Bitcoin? Analysts Weigh In</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/why-was-may-a-rough-month-for-bitcoin-analysts-weigh-in/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/why-was-may-a-rough-month-for-bitcoin-analysts-weigh-in/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 17:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Antoni Trenchev]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78317</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin hit its lowest levels since March during the midway point of May, and analysts are trying hard to figure out why. Bitcoin and Last Month Didn&#8217;t Go Well Together In many ways, the arena was set for bitcoin to have an explosive month. While the currency was still miles above the position it stood<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/why-was-may-a-rough-month-for-bitcoin-analysts-weigh-in/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/why-was-may-a-rough-month-for-bitcoin-analysts-weigh-in/">Why was May a Rough Month for Bitcoin? Analysts Weigh In</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin hit its lowest levels since March during the <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-falls-to-lowest-level-since-march-as-thin-liquidity-regulatory-pressure-hits-crypto-markets/ar-AA1b5ZrX" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">midway point of May</a>, and analysts are trying hard to figure out why.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin and Last Month Didn&#8217;t Go Well Together</h2>
<p>In many ways, the arena was set for bitcoin to have an explosive month. While the currency was still miles above the position it stood at during 2022 – as we <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-is-still-65-higher-than-where-it-was-last-year/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported earlier today</a> – the currency experienced a nasty little dip that saw it fall into the mid-$26K range, an area it hadn’t seen in a while.</p>
<p>Prior to this fall, banks were <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-provide-their-thoughts-on-latest-bitcoin-rally/" data-wpel-link="internal">failing left and right</a>, which ultimately should have paved the way for bitcoin. The currency tends to do quite well when the standard financial arena is stumbling, so what could have happened? In addition, the Fed had hinted that rate hikes were going to slow down if they didn’t come to a full halt. The situation is a baffling one, and it’s left analysts in a strange daze.</p>
<p>Clara Medalie – director of research at Kaiko – said the price dips exhibited by bitcoin had more to do with a “notable drop in market depth” for the world’s number one digital currency. There were also issues arising from both Jane Street and Jump Crypto, two of the biggest crypto market makers. Both announced they were going to be stepping back from crypto trading in regions like the U.S. given the unstable nature of regulation and agencies like the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<p>Naturally, such news wouldn’t be taken well by the industry. She explained in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>While it is yet unclear the catalyst for today&#8217;s sharp drop, the volatility is to be expected given the current state of liquidity, especially after larger market makers Jane Street and Jump Crypto revealed they were winding down their crypto exposure.</p></blockquote>
<p>The lack of clear regulation has caused a wide scope of issues in both the U.S. and abroad. Coinbase – one of the world’s largest and most popular digital currency trading platforms – was recently issued a Wells notice from the SEC, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">informing it that it was likely</a> to face financial charges in the coming future.</p>
<p>Executives took serious issue with the notice, claiming they had met with representatives of the SEC at least 30 times over a nine-year period to ensure the company and all its operations were compliant. Brian Armstrong – the CEO of the exchange – has stated that he believes Coinbase is going to be involved in a very lengthy battle with the agency.</p>
<h2>So Many Issues at Once</h2>
<p>Antoni Trenchev -co-founder of Nexo – said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin&#8217;s attempts to break through $30,000 have come undone amidst a triple whammy of congestion issues on the blockchain, liquidity constraints caused by the scaling back of top market makers Jane Street and Jump Crypto, and ever-circling regulators.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/why-was-may-a-rough-month-for-bitcoin-analysts-weigh-in/">Why was May a Rough Month for Bitcoin? Analysts Weigh In</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/why-was-may-a-rough-month-for-bitcoin-analysts-weigh-in/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New $POOH Meme Token Wants to Save Bee Populations</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-pooh-meme-token-wants-to-save-bee-populations/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-pooh-meme-token-wants-to-save-bee-populations/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 15:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[$POOH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Winnie the Pooh]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78319</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It looks like crypto is on its way to the Hundred Acre Wood – the legendary home of famed literary character Winnie the Pooh. A new meme currency called $POOH, inspired by the heavyset, honey-loving bear is the latest addition to the crypto industry, and it’s got noble intent behind it as well. $POOH Wants<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-pooh-meme-token-wants-to-save-bee-populations/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-pooh-meme-token-wants-to-save-bee-populations/">New $POOH Meme Token Wants to Save Bee Populations</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It looks like crypto is on its way to the Hundred Acre Wood – the legendary home of famed literary character Winnie the Pooh. A <a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/press-release/new-cryptocurrency-pooh-is-bringing-back-nostalgia-for-a-beloved-character-while-helping-do-good-for-the-environment-2023-05-10" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">new meme currency</a> called $POOH, inspired by the heavyset, honey-loving bear is the latest addition to the crypto industry, and it’s got noble intent behind it as well.</p>
<h2>$POOH Wants to Help Bees</h2>
<p>As the star of countless movies and television programs, Winnie the Pooh has made his way into the hearts of both children and adults. He eventually walked into the Disney studio and became one of the company’s most beloved characters. Many of us still remember his trademark phrase of “Oh, bother!” when something was tough or didn’t quite go as expected.</p>
<p>With so many outlets featuring the “silly old bear,” it seems only natural that the crypto arena would eventually fall victim to his cute and loveable antics. The new $POOH token was built to ensure bees have a steady future in the world given how thin their numbers have become over the past few years. While it’s unclear if this is due to pesticide use, climate change, or some other anomaly, one thing is for certain: bee populations <a href="https://www.npr.org/2020/04/01/825305756/honeybees-need-your-help-honey" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">everywhere are suffering</a>.</p>
<p>If bees go out, the world is in a rough spot. Bees do a lot of good for the planet through their pollination efforts, and without them, Mother Earth is going to have a tough time surviving. This is where $POOH comes in. Executives behind the asset want it to be the most held meme token. They also want it to support all kinds of projects out there working towards bee conservation.</p>
<p>An anonymous developer for the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/token/" data-wpel-link="internal">token</a> explained in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>While we are a self-owned community that is collecting all the honey, ultimately, we care about the bees and want to make an impact. We wanted to create a cryptocurrency that not only brings joy and entertainment to people, but also has a meaningful impact on the environment. The decline of bee populations is a significant threat to the environment, and we&#8217;re committed to doing our part to help save the bees by contributing money to this important cause.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Bringing a Loveable Character to Crypto</h2>
<p>He continued with:</p>
<blockquote><p>Our meme coin ecosystem will help support healthier bees through a range of conservation activities that will help protect food security for future generations. Also, we want to make it clear that $POOH is not associated with any company, and the token only shows love to a much beloved character… It&#8217;s time for the most recognizable bear in the world to claim his rightful position on the charts at the start of a life-changing bull market. $POOH launched stealthily with no presale, zero taxes, 95 percent LP burnt, and contract renounced. $POOH is for the people forever.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-pooh-meme-token-wants-to-save-bee-populations/">New $POOH Meme Token Wants to Save Bee Populations</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-pooh-meme-token-wants-to-save-bee-populations/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin is Still 65% Higher than Where it Was Last Year</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-is-still-65-higher-than-where-it-was-last-year/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-is-still-65-higher-than-where-it-was-last-year/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 13:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78313</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The price of bitcoin fell somewhat in mid-May, causing a bit of a scare amongst digital currency investors. However, analysts are telling them not to worry so much given the world’s number one digital asset by market cap is still about 65 percent higher than where it was at the end of last year. Bitcoin&#8230;<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-is-still-65-higher-than-where-it-was-last-year/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-is-still-65-higher-than-where-it-was-last-year/">Bitcoin is Still 65% Higher than Where it Was Last Year</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price of bitcoin fell somewhat in mid-May, <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/bitcoin-has-climbed-65-this-year-despite-crypto-woes-experts-explain-why/ar-AA1b5IvN" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">causing a bit of a scare amongst</a> digital currency investors. However, analysts are telling them not to worry so much given the world’s number one digital asset by market cap is still about 65 percent higher than where it was at the end of last year.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin&#8230; It&#8217;s Still in a Solid Place</h2>
<p>During the month of May, bitcoin – after <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">trading at $30K</a>, a ten-month high – fell into the high $26,000 range. Analysts feel that much of the fear that surrounded the dip was premature in that bitcoin was still in a solid position compared with where it was in 2022, arguably the worst period on record for the currency and for crypto in general.</p>
<p>During that time, bitcoin fell by more than 70 percent from the all-time high it achieved in November of 2021. That was when it was trading for about $68,000 per unit. However, 12 months later, the currency had fallen into the mid-$16,000 range. It was a sad and ugly sight to see.</p>
<p>However, if this wasn’t bad enough, several other assets chose to follow in bitcoin’s footsteps and lost mountains of value as well. This ultimately contributed to the crypto arena losing more than $2 trillion in overall valuation over the course of one year, and it’s taken quite a bit of energy to bring these assets back up to their present levels.</p>
<p>Discussing the circumstances surrounding bitcoin and its previous rise and subsequent falls, James Butterfill – head of research at digital currency management firm Coin Shares – stated that the Fed and its endless array of rate hikes are largely to blame for all the madness seen over the previous 12 months. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>There had been a big bubble. The bubble was pricked by the Fed.</p></blockquote>
<p>Interestingly, Callie Cox – an analyst at crypto firm e-Toro – also threw her two cents in. Her opinion is unique in that she feels the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">collapse of FTX</a>, while contributing to short-term disdain and troubles for bitcoin, made people flock to it more in the long run.</p>
<p>They were concerned about the lesser performances of smaller assets following the exchange’s death, and they all turned to tokens like BTC and ETH – more mainstream and legitimate in many eyes – as a means of ensuring their crypto portfolios could remain steady. She says:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin has been the beneficiary of a flight to quality within the crypto industry. This is the crypto name that my mom and your family probably know.</p></blockquote>
<h2>So Much Junk Out There!</h2>
<p>Butterfull was quick to agree, stating:</p>
<blockquote><p>People are becoming a lot more discerning. There are 50,000 crypto coins out there and a lot of them are rubbish… Economic data continues to deteriorate. In that environment, bitcoin would be volatile and perform quite well.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-is-still-65-higher-than-where-it-was-last-year/">Bitcoin is Still 65% Higher than Where it Was Last Year</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-is-still-65-higher-than-where-it-was-last-year/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Disgraced Crypto Exec Do Kwon is Out on Bail</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/disgraced-crypto-exec-do-kwon-is-out-on-bail/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/disgraced-crypto-exec-do-kwon-is-out-on-bail/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 17:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bail]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Do Kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Montenegro]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78311</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Montenegro court has accepted a bail payment on behalf of Do Kwon, the disgraced crypto executive behind fallen digital currency firm Terraform Labs. The company established the crumbled algorithmic stable currency known as Terra USD. Do Kwon is Out on Bail At the time of writing, Kwon – along with another detained South Korean<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/disgraced-crypto-exec-do-kwon-is-out-on-bail/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/disgraced-crypto-exec-do-kwon-is-out-on-bail/">Disgraced Crypto Exec Do Kwon is Out on Bail</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Montenegro court has accepted a bail <a href="https://www.usnews.com/news/business/articles/2023-05-12/montenegro-court-agrees-to-release-founder-of-cryptocurrency-firm-terraform-labs-on-bail" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">payment on behalf</a> of Do Kwon, the disgraced crypto executive behind fallen digital currency firm Terraform Labs. The company established the crumbled algorithmic stable currency known as Terra USD.</p>
<h2>Do Kwon is Out on Bail</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Kwon – along with another detained South Korean man believed to have been involved in the project – is out of prison after presenting $435,000 to court officials to ensure he would not have to await his upcoming trial behind bars. He is now confined to a nearby apartment, and he and his associate are not allowed to leave the domicile until the trial has been concluded.</p>
<p>The court has put out the following statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>They promised&#8230; they will not hide until the end of the criminal procedures, that they will regularly answer court summons, and that they will be available [at] the address submitted by their attorney. If the defendants run away or violate the surveillance measure, the bail will fall through and will be added to the special budget for court work.</p></blockquote>
<p>Kwon was a fugitive for some time <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-executive-do-kwon-arrested-in-montenegro/" data-wpel-link="internal">after his company</a> completely collapsed and (figuratively) burnt to the ground. Organizations such as the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) charged him with fraud, and it wasn’t long before his own country of South Korea issued a warrant for his arrest.</p>
<p>Kwon remained active on social media for a while after the warrant was issued. He said he was not on the run, and that he was willing to cooperate with police authorities in any way possible. He also said he wasn’t going anywhere, and that he was busily coding in his living room, thus practically inviting police to come knock on his door and question him in his company’s failings.</p>
<p>However, the social media activity didn’t last forever, and it wasn’t long before Kwon shut his accounts down and proceeded to make his way across the globe allegedly to hide himself from those who would see him behind bars. His plight didn’t last long, however, as it was in the nation of Montenegro (where he possessed multiple fake passports) that he was finally caught.</p>
<h2>A Rug Pull, Perhaps?</h2>
<p>At the time of his detainment, authorities in that nation put out the following statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>Montenegrin police have detained a person suspected of being one of the world’s most wanted fugitives, South Korean citizen Do Kwon, co-founder and CEO of Singapore-based Terraform Labs. The former ‘cryptocurrency king’, who is behind losses of more than 40 billion dollars, was detained at the Podgorica airport with falsified documents, and South Korea, the USA, and Singapore are demanding [his extradition].</p></blockquote>
<p>Kwon has been accused of initiating a rug pull given he and his fellow executives switched several of their Terra assets out for BTC prior to the collapse.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/disgraced-crypto-exec-do-kwon-is-out-on-bail/">Disgraced Crypto Exec Do Kwon is Out on Bail</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/disgraced-crypto-exec-do-kwon-is-out-on-bail/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elderly Residents of Ohio Targeted By Crypto Scams</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elderly-residents-of-ohio-targeted-by-crypto-scams/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elderly-residents-of-ohio-targeted-by-crypto-scams/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 15:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto scams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elderly]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ohio]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77804</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ohio law enforcement agencies are telling residents about several growing crypto scams in the area that are targeting members of the elderly community. Ohio Is a Center of Crypto Fraud There are many crypto scams out there that seek to take advantage of older generations given they don’t always understand how computers or modern technology<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elderly-residents-of-ohio-targeted-by-crypto-scams/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elderly-residents-of-ohio-targeted-by-crypto-scams/">Elderly Residents of Ohio Targeted By Crypto Scams</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ohio law enforcement agencies are telling residents about <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/ohio-agencies-warn-of-cryptocurrency-scams-targeting-older-ohioans/ar-AA19AS7D" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">several growing crypto</a> scams in the area that are targeting members of the elderly community.</p>
<h2>Ohio Is a Center of Crypto Fraud</h2>
<p>There are many <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/scams/" data-wpel-link="internal">crypto scams</a> out there that seek to take advantage of older generations given they don’t always understand how computers or modern technology work. For this reason, they’re less likely to question things that might appear suspicious to others. Many of them also have heavy retirements saved up that make them “richer” than other individuals in scammers eyes.</p>
<p>The Ohio Narcotics Intelligence Center (ONIC) is claiming that it became aware of these scams against elderly citizens through a string of recent drug-related investigations. Andy Wilson – director of the Ohio Department of Public Safety – explained in a recent statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>Recently, ONIC has assisted several local law enforcement agencies with their cryptocurrency scam investigations. Our agencies issued this bulletin to raise awareness about the dangers of these new scams targeting older Ohioans. We are working closely together to make resources available for consumers who believe they have been a target.</p></blockquote>
<p>He further mentioned that several of the scammers are in regular contact with their victims as a means of guiding them through the process of sending funds via bitcoin ATMs and similar tools. It’s often very difficult to track funds that are delivered this way, and about 90 percent of the time, once crypto is gone, it’s gone for good.</p>
<p>The Federal Trade Commission is now warning residents of Ohio – and the general U.S. population – about the growing number of scams and telling them about things to watch out for. For example, it said no legitimate business will ever ask that you forward crypto funds, as many of these companies are likely to operate through cash and even then, they’ll only ask you for payments if transactions occurred and you’ve bought products or services.</p>
<p>In addition, meeting people on dating sites or applications that request to show you how to invest in digital currency sites usually means they’re not who they say they are, and they’re looking to carry out theft.</p>
<p>Also, no business will engage in texting, emailing, or messaging on social media to try and get you to part with money, nor will they ever ask that you purchase anything with digital assets. Lastly, if you do wind up getting a social media message, text, or email from an entity you don’t recognize, and it contains a link of some sort, it’s best to avoid clicking on it.</p>
<h2>Going After Old People Ain&#8217;t Cool</h2>
<p>Ohio Department of Aging Director Ursel J. McElroy said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Despite the fact that older adults are more likely to report suspected fraud than younger adults, scammers are finding new and sophisticated ways to deceive people, like these emerging cryptocurrency scams.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elderly-residents-of-ohio-targeted-by-crypto-scams/">Elderly Residents of Ohio Targeted By Crypto Scams</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elderly-residents-of-ohio-targeted-by-crypto-scams/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Report: How Blockchain Could Pave the Way for Real Estate</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-how-blockchain-could-pave-the-way-for-real-estate/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-how-blockchain-could-pave-the-way-for-real-estate/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 13:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[real estate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trevor Bacon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78307</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There are many people out there that simply associate blockchain with crypto and digital currencies, but it works quite well when performing transactions and other activities pertaining to real estate. Real Estate Is the Way to Go In America, real estate has always been king. It’s often said that if you can buy your own<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-how-blockchain-could-pave-the-way-for-real-estate/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-how-blockchain-could-pave-the-way-for-real-estate/">Report: How Blockchain Could Pave the Way for Real Estate</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are many people out there that simply associate blockchain with crypto and digital currencies, but it works quite well when <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/blockchain-real-estate-more-accessible-153618572.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">performing transactions and other</a> activities pertaining to real estate.</p>
<h2>Real Estate Is the Way to Go</h2>
<p>In America, real estate has always been king. It’s often said that if you can buy your own house, you’re pretty much set for life. In addition, while everyone talks about the stock market and gold and other precious metals, most of the rich people in this nation invest in real estate. From Donald Trump to Warren Buffett, having properties to your name is the way to become a billionaire.</p>
<p>Several analysts think blockchain and real estate could make a good team, and that bringing the latter onto the former would make it more accessible to everyday investors that haven’t had clear and concise access to the American dream. A new report from Citigroup states the following:</p>
<blockquote><p>Traditional real estate often struggles with poor transparency, illiquidity, and multiple intermediaries. Blockchain could be a good fit as a single shared source of truth in a market with multiple players, all working with overlapping data and the need for constant reconciliation. Tokenization could also help reduce minimum investment amounts and open asset discovery.</p></blockquote>
<p>Trevor Bacon – co-founder and CEO of real estate investing platform Parcl – also threw his two cents into the mix. He said putting real estate on the blockchain could ensure its future as a yield source through decentralized means. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>You can tokenize a loan, a house, a building, or car loans. You can put that on the blockchain and it’s a much more efficient way to do stuff… We’re allowing people to speculate, hedge, bet, and trade on real estate prices much like they would on any other type of stock or derivative. Real world assets are a new theme. It’s a moniker for what people are doing, using the blockchain for real utility rather than NFTs or gaming… From an operational perspective, it’s more efficient. It’s all done through software. You could issue a mortgage directly instead of going through a bank. It’s governed through smart contracts and enforceable by software, not people.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Inaccessible for Over a Year</h2>
<p>For the last year and a half or so, real estate in America has been virtually inaccessible. A big reason for this is because Joe Biden – the current commander-in-chief – has instilled economic policies that have ultimately brought the nation to its knees. Inflation is at an all-time high, and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-fed-bitcoins-worst-enemy-right-now/" data-wpel-link="internal">thus the Fed has been</a> forced into a position of constantly having to hike rates.</p>
<p>These rate hikes have hurt people’s finances and made it so that many of them can no longer afford things like cars and homes, thus edging them out of major ownership opportunities.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-how-blockchain-could-pave-the-way-for-real-estate/">Report: How Blockchain Could Pave the Way for Real Estate</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-how-blockchain-could-pave-the-way-for-real-estate/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Rally Seems Unstoppable above $130</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-rally-seems-unstoppable-above-130/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-rally-seems-unstoppable-above-130/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 03:08:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78911</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin cash started a strong increase above the $115 and $120 levels against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above the $125 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key rising channel forming with support near $133.00 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-rally-seems-unstoppable-above-130/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-rally-seems-unstoppable-above-130/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Rally Seems Unstoppable above $130</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin cash started a strong increase above the $115 and $120 levels against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above the $125 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key rising channel forming with support near $133.00 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair must clear $140 and $142 to continue higher in the near term.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin cash price is climbing above $130 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-bulls-aim-fresh-uptrend/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. BCH/USD could start a fresh surge if it clears the $142 level.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin cash price formed a decent support base above the $100 level. BCH started a decent increase and was able to clear the $115 resistance zone.</p>
<p>The price climbed above the $120 and $125 resistance levels. It even spiked above $145 and traded as high as $149.56. It is now trading above the $125 zone and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bulls-eye-recovery-to-115/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. The current price action is positive, suggesting high chances of more gains.</p>
<p>There is also a key rising channel forming with support near $133.00 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $140.80 level.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $142 level, above which the price may perhaps rise toward the $150 level. Any more gains above $150 could set the pace for a move toward the $160 level.</p>
<p>Immediate support on the downside is near the channel trend line at $133.00. The first major support sits near the $120 level. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $90.77 swing low to the $149.56 high.</p>
<p>The next support is near the $113 level or the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $90.77 swing low to the $149.56 high, below which the bears might aim for $105. The next target for them may perhaps be near the $100 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_78912" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Bitcoin-Cash-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78912" class="size-full wp-image-78912" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/06/Bitcoin-Cash-3.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash Price" width="1835" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78912" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Cash Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BCHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Bitcoin cash price is now trading above the $130 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price must clear $140 and $142 to continue higher in the near term.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for BCH/USD is gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BCH/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $133 and $120.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $140 and $142.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-rally-seems-unstoppable-above-130/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Rally Seems Unstoppable above $130</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-rally-seems-unstoppable-above-130/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Canton Blockchain Network Attracts Big Names like Deloitte and Microsoft</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/canton-blockchain-network-attracts-big-names-like-deloitte-and-microsoft/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/canton-blockchain-network-attracts-big-names-like-deloitte-and-microsoft/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Canton Network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78301</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Canton Network is a brand new blockchain system. Very few people appear to have heard of it at press time, but there’s a good chance this blockchain is going to be making waves soon throughout the industry given the names it&#8217;s attracting in terms of partnerships. Canton Blockchain Network Getting Big and Bold Thus<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/canton-blockchain-network-attracts-big-names-like-deloitte-and-microsoft/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/canton-blockchain-network-attracts-big-names-like-deloitte-and-microsoft/">Canton Blockchain Network Attracts Big Names like Deloitte and Microsoft</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Canton Network is a brand new blockchain system. Very few people appear to have heard of it at press time, but there’s a good chance this blockchain is going to be making waves soon throughout the industry given the names it&#8217;s <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/deloitte-goldman-sachs-microsoft-among-institutional-players-partnering-on-new-blockchain-network/ar-AA1aXaVw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">attracting in terms of partnerships</a>.</p>
<h2>Canton Blockchain Network Getting Big and Bold</h2>
<p>Thus far, the company has joined hands with some of the biggest companies in both technology and finance including Goldman Sachs, Deloitte, and Microsoft.</p>
<p>Behind the implementation of the Canton Network is a firm called Digital Asset, a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/blockchain/" data-wpel-link="internal">blockchain</a> startup that was once led by former JPMorgan executive Blythe Masters. Yuval Rooz – co-founder and CEO of Digital Asset – explained in a recent statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>For the first time, financial institutions can realize the full benefits of a global blockchain network while operating within the regulatory guardrails.</p></blockquote>
<p>At the time of writing, other big companies to join hands with Cantos include BNP Paribas, CBOE, Moody’s, and even Paxos, which creates stable currencies for companies like PayPal and Binance, the biggest and most popular digital currency trading platform in the world. These firms have been experimenting with the Cantos network for some time already, though it’s not quite clear what their intentions are.</p>
<p>In any case, the news is positive in that it suggests blockchain technology is becoming more mainstream and legitimate. It has been said over the last few years that blockchain, while primarily used for crypto-based transactions and financial confirmations, can be utilized in several other industries from healthcare to manufacturing. While there is certainly <a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S266660302100021X#:~:text=In%20healthcare%2C%20a%20blockchain%20network%20is%20useful%20to,deception%20in%20clinical%20trials%20for%20better%20healthcare%20outcomes." data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">evidence supporting this</a>, the statement has never fully been put into action given blockchain is still very much a birthing technology that some people do not trust enough to try.</p>
<p>As such, blockchain – while revolutionary – is not accomplishing all it can, and primarily remains confined to the crypto arena. However, with names like Microsoft and Deloitte now entering the picture, one can assume that blockchain is going to pick up steam and attract the attention of many other companies similar in both size and scope.</p>
<p>Regarding what her company has in mind for blockchain and Canton, Cathy Clay – an executive vice president of CBOE Global Markets – explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>By leveraging new blockchain technologies, we can potentially unlock new opportunities for market participants. Efforts like the Canton Network will help our industry further explore this frontier.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Tokenization of Assets?</h2>
<p>While unclear, it’s believed that many of the above-mentioned companies are primarily interested in the tokenization of assets such as stocks and bonds. The tokenization process of these assets would ultimately remove all middlemen and third parties required for verification, thus ensuring they’re safer for their users and that auditing is easier in the future.</p>
<p>Many of these companies also claim to have been examining blockchain for years.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/canton-blockchain-network-attracts-big-names-like-deloitte-and-microsoft/">Canton Blockchain Network Attracts Big Names like Deloitte and Microsoft</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/canton-blockchain-network-attracts-big-names-like-deloitte-and-microsoft/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Network Solana Sets Up Huge Office in New York</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-network-solana-sets-up-huge-office-in-new-york/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-network-solana-sets-up-huge-office-in-new-york/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 15:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Andrew Kimball]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New York]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78299</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The popular crypto network Solana is opening a new office in downtown Manhattan, New York. The office will occupy roughly 25,000 square feet in a multiple-story building. Solana and New York&#8230; An Unusual Match Solana is presently the tenth largest digital currency by market capitalization. The news is odd for several reasons, one being that<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-network-solana-sets-up-huge-office-in-new-york/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-network-solana-sets-up-huge-office-in-new-york/">Crypto Network Solana Sets Up Huge Office in New York</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The popular crypto network Solana is <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/solana-labs-opening-25-000-164716748.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">opening a new office</a> in downtown Manhattan, New York. The office will occupy roughly 25,000 square feet in a multiple-story building.</p>
<h2>Solana and New York&#8230; An Unusual Match</h2>
<p>Solana is presently the tenth largest digital currency by market capitalization. The news is odd for several reasons, one being that several brick-and-mortar, Solana-themed locations and stores in both New York and Miami just shut down, suggesting the area hasn’t offered Solana the popularity or attention it clearly felt it deserved.</p>
<p>In addition, it’s interesting that Solana would choose New York as its place of residence given that the Empire State has proven to be quite anti-crypto over the past several years and continues to do so. Not long ago, a crypto moratorium in the region <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/some-want-the-crypto-moratorium-in-new-york-to-last-longer/" data-wpel-link="internal">was instituted as a means</a> of preventing any new digital currency mining companies from stepping in and setting up quarters within the state’s borders. It was decided that only those who chose to run fully on clean, renewable energy could gain access to New York territory.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Leticia James – New York’s present Attorney General – has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-attorney-generals-office-now-suing-ku-coin-exchange/" data-wpel-link="internal">gone after every digital</a> currency company she can with full force and steam. She has sued several institutions from Celsius to Ku Coin to Coin Ex, and it doesn’t look like this string of lawsuits is going to stop anytime soon.</p>
<p>She has stated in the past that this is a measure to try and prevent further fraud and corruption in the digital currency industry but considering her actions against <a href="https://abcnews.go.com/US/york-ag-letitia-james-files-250m-lawsuit-trump/story?id=90240332" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">President Donald Trump</a>, as well as New York’s implementation of restrictive bills such as <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitlicense/" data-wpel-link="internal">the BitLicense</a>, one can’t help but see her actions as just more attempts to end innovation in her state.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, it appears – for now, at least – like New York is the spot Solana has chosen. A spokesperson for the company explained in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>Solana Labs did not purchase the space. Solana Labs is a tenant of the 141 E Houston St. [building]. The company has a ten-year lease and occupies floors [six through nine]. 75 percent of the space is reserved for Solana ecosystem teams to co-work for free upon approval.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Allowing Entrepreneurs to Work with Each Other</h2>
<p>New York City Economic Development Corporation (NYCEDC) president and CEO Andrew Kimball also threw his two cents into the mix, commenting:</p>
<blockquote><p>New York City has all the ingredients to be the global epicenter of Web3. It has the arts, culture, innovation, technology, and talent. It’s exciting to see the Solana community plant a flag right here in New York and let the world know the city is the place to build in blockchain.</p></blockquote>
<p>Raj Gokal – the co-founder of Solana Labs – says the new office space will be a perfect area for new entrepreneurs to build and collaborate with each other.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-network-solana-sets-up-huge-office-in-new-york/">Crypto Network Solana Sets Up Huge Office in New York</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-network-solana-sets-up-huge-office-in-new-york/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=3869 metric#misses=5 metric#hit-ratio=99.9 metric#bytes=6626716 metric#prefetches=398 metric#store-reads=16 metric#store-writes=3 metric#store-hits=403 metric#store-misses=0 metric#sql-queries=17 metric#ms-total=144.73 metric#ms-cache=12.26 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.6810 metric#ms-cache-ratio=8.5 sample#redis-hits=1761503619 sample#redis-misses=1453451 sample#redis-hit-ratio=99.9 sample#redis-ops-per-sec=44 sample#redis-evicted-keys=0 sample#redis-used-memory=679061056 sample#redis-used-memory-rss=689242112 sample#redis-memory-fragmentation-ratio=1.0 sample#redis-connected-clients=1 sample#redis-tracking-clients=0 sample#redis-rejected-connections=0 sample#redis-keys=1371039 -->
