<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 03:25:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/cropped-fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Bulls Aim For Fresh Rally To $350</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bulls-aim-for-fresh-rally-to-350/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 03:28:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79286</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin cash is eyeing a fresh increase above the $300 resistance against the US Dollar. The price is now trading near the $275 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $285 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bulls-aim-for-fresh-rally-to-350/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Bulls Aim For Fresh Rally To $350</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin cash is eyeing a fresh increase above the $300 resistance against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading near the $275 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $285 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair must clear $285 and $300 to start a fresh increase in the near term.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin cash price is consolidating gains above $265 against the US Dollar, unlike <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-restart-rally-above-this-resistance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. BCH/USD could start a fresh surge if it clears the $285 level.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin cash price started a downside correction after it failed to clear the $330 zone. BCH formed a high near $329 before there was a bearish move.</p>
<p>The price declined below the $310 and $300 levels. There was a break below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $186 swing low to the $329 high. However, the bulls are protecting more losses below the $250 support zone.</p>
<p>Bitcoin cash is now trading near the $275 zone and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-fresh-rally-possible-to-330/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $285 level. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $285 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near $300, above which the price may perhaps start a strong increase. The next major resistance is near the $330 level. Any more gains above $330 could set the pace for a move toward the $350 level.</p>
<p>If not, the price might continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $255 level. The first major support sits near the $240 level or the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $186 swing low to the $329 high. The next major support is near $220, below which the bears might aim for $200.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79287" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79287" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-1.png"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-79287" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-1.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-1.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-1-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-1-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-1-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-1-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-1-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-Cash-1-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79287" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Cash Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BCHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, Bitcoin Cash’s price is now trading near the $275 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price must clear $285 and $300 to start a fresh increase in the near term.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for BCH/USD is losing pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BCH/USD is just below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $255 and $240.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $285 and $300.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bulls-aim-for-fresh-rally-to-350/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Bulls Aim For Fresh Rally To $350</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Texas Crypto Bill Seeks to Establish Safety for All Traders</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-crypto-bill-seeks-to-establish-safety-for-all-traders/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 17:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto bill]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Greg Abbott]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Texas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78561</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The state of Texas is looking to be one of the first in the American union to regulate cryptocurrency. Texas Looks to Create New Crypto Regulation Not long ago, House Bill 1666 made its way onto the desk of Greg Abbott, the state’s governor. The bill is a nod to the FTX debacle of last [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-crypto-bill-seeks-to-establish-safety-for-all-traders/">Texas Crypto Bill Seeks to Establish Safety for All Traders</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The state of Texas is looking to be one of the first in the American <a href="https://www.kvue.com/article/news/politics/texas-legislature/texas-cryptocurrency-regulation-hb1666/269-5543d20a-cabf-4e0e-aa9d-11c5f6d20a05">union to regulate cryptocurrency</a>.</p>
<h2>Texas Looks to Create New Crypto Regulation</h2>
<p>Not long ago, House Bill 1666 made its way onto the desk of Greg Abbott, the state’s governor. The bill is a nod to the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/">FTX debacle</a> of last year and will seek to ensure proper and safe trading environments for all residents of Texas that hold or trade digital currencies.</p>
<p>The goal is to make sure everybody’s money steers clear of fraud and other issues known to arise out of the crypto arena. Each year, all virtual currency companies that do business with citizens of Texas will be required to adhere to certain rules like ensuring all customers can withdraw funds whenever they wish.</p>
<p>Also, companies will need to provide proof of reserves to show that if there are ever any problems, executives can stay afloat and provide compensation and recompense to affected traders. Customers will also be able to garner information about the companies’ standing debts and see who they owe money to and how much.</p>
<p>Lastly, the firms in question would not be allowed to commingle funds (in other words, no mixing of company money with customer money), and they would be subjected to annual audits.</p>
<p>State representative Giovanni Capriglione, a republican, commented that he would like Texas to set an example to larger institutions like the federal government, and he hopes the regulation his region sets in place can provide rules and laws for surrounding areas as well. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>You will be comfortable knowing that when you invest online, when you&#8217;re buying cryptos, when you&#8217;re trading it, when you&#8217;re selling, those assets are being watched, that they are being managed, and that there&#8217;s an audit trail that protects those assets.</p></blockquote>
<p>Texas is widely considered a very crypto-friendly state. The region <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-is-still-a-crypto-mining-king/">opened itself to an influx</a> of miners from China after their native country declared that the practice was fully illegal in the summer of 2021. Seeing the opportunities for growth, jobs, innovation, and a rising economy, Texas leaders said, “Come on in” and have built one of the biggest mining arenas of the last ten years.</p>
<h2>Energy Issues Have Popped Up</h2>
<p>However, while this attitude has resulted in a strong economy and powerful job prospects, it has created problems for the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-texas-is-suffering-from-too-much-btc-mining/">state’s energy grid</a>. A new report by the Electric Reliability Council of Texas (ERCOT) states:</p>
<blockquote><p>Prospective crypto mining businesses have requested to put approximately 33,000 more megawatts in the ERCOT interconnection queue over the next few years (enough to power the whole state of Florida)… A single bitcoin transaction used nearly 1,452 kilowatt-hours (kWh) of electricity, equal to the power consumption of an average U.S. household for nearly 50 days.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-crypto-bill-seeks-to-establish-safety-for-all-traders/">Texas Crypto Bill Seeks to Establish Safety for All Traders</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Treasury is Set to Make Things Rough for Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-treasury-is-set-to-make-things-rough-for-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 15:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Treasury]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78558</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As both sides of the political spectrum have waged war on America’s debt ceiling and worked hard to formulate a deal, there’s growing concern that the Treasury is going to issue more than $1 trillion in new bills. Many analysts are worried about this as they say such a move could have atrocious effects on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-treasury-is-set-to-make-things-rough-for-bitcoin/">The Treasury is Set to Make Things Rough for Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As both sides of the political spectrum have waged war on America’s debt ceiling and worked hard to formulate a deal, there’s growing concern that the Treasury is <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/05/29/crypto-now-braced-for-a-11-trillion-fed-panic-after-bitcoin-and-ethereum-price-surge/?sh=34ddec114c08">going to issue more</a> than $1 trillion in new bills. Many analysts are worried about this as they say such a move could have atrocious effects on the market.</p>
<h2>The Treasury May Hurt BTC</h2>
<p>Alex Lennard – investment director at global asset manager Ruffer – explained in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Our concern is that if liquidity starts leaving the system, for whatever reason, this creates an environment where markets are crash prone.</p></blockquote>
<p>This was seconded by Mike Wilson, an equity strategist at Morgan Stanley. He claimed that while the Treasury is more than likely trying to refill “empty coffers,” the market may lose a heavy amount of liquidity should it move forward with its present plan, and thus a major correction could be heading our way.</p>
<p>There is also concern that the Fed could potentially seek to hike rates further in the coming weeks given inflation has not died down over the past few months the way financial analysts had initially hoped for. Yuga Hasegawa – crypto market analyst at Bit Bank in Tokyo – mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>The debt ceiling issue could soon be a thing of the past, but the future trajectory of the Fed funds rate will continue to weigh on the market sentiment, and bitcoin’s weekend rally could be hindered depending on the series of economic data slated for this week, such as ISM’s manufacturing PMI and May’s jobs report.</p></blockquote>
<p>Still, there is some good news in that economists anticipate a whopping 180,000 jobs to be added to the market in the coming future. However, this doesn’t change the fact that unemployment is expected to move up to close to four percent, and that 180K figure is nothing compared to the 250,000 jobs that were added as recently as April. Hasegawa explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>Economic data in the last month have indicated the resilience of the U.S. economy. Most of all, core indexes for CPI and PCE, as well as trimmed, mean PCE inflation rate for April did not show any significant improvements. The Fed Funds futures market now prices in [a] roughly 65% chance of another rate hike… and if the number keeps going up, it will likely be a headwind for bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Could There Be Price Dips?</h2>
<p>The Treasury and its department head Janet Yellen have made it <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-fans-may-want-to-wait-on-their-calls-for-regulation/">clear that crypto and other</a> assets are not their main priorities.</p>
<p>Thus, it would be a huge pity if they went ahead with the move anticipated above and it sucked further liquidity out of the market given how far tokens like bitcoin have come this year after enduring some of their most bearish conditions in 2022.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-treasury-is-set-to-make-things-rough-for-bitcoin/">The Treasury is Set to Make Things Rough for Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sam Bankman-Fried Likely to Face All Charges, Prosecutors Say</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-likely-to-face-all-charges-prosecutors-say/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 13:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charges]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78556</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, Sam Bankman-Fried – the former crypto billionaire behind the now fallen digital exchange FTX – said he was requesting that as many as ten separate criminal charges he’s facing be thrown out. However, prosecutors describe this motion as “meritless,” and say they’re not only going to pursue all charges, but that it’s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-likely-to-face-all-charges-prosecutors-say/">Sam Bankman-Fried Likely to Face All Charges, Prosecutors Say</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, Sam Bankman-Fried – the former crypto billionaire behind the now fallen digital exchange FTX – said he was requesting that as <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-wants-10-criminal-charges-tossed-out/">many as ten separate</a> criminal charges he’s facing be thrown out. However, prosecutors <a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/sam-bankman-frieds-bid-dismiss-cryptocurrency-charges-meritless-prosec-rcna86772">describe this motion</a> as “meritless,” and say they’re not only going to pursue all charges, but that it’s likely he’ll face penalties for many of them.</p>
<h2>Sam Bankman-Fried Isn&#8217;t Getting off that Easily</h2>
<p>Right now, among the many criminal accusations Bankman-Fried is facing are fraud, conspiracy, foreign bribery, and making illegal campaign contributions. In court documents, prosecutors explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>The indictment sufficiently alleges that the defendant and his co-conspirators made false and misleading representations to lenders relating to Alameda’s financial condition. No more specificity is required.</p></blockquote>
<p>FTX will likely go down as one of the biggest debacles of the digital currency space. The exchange – which first opened its doors for business in 2019 – rose to prominence three years later to become one of the top five digital currency trading platforms in the world. Its founder and chief executive Sam Bankman-Fried was lauded as a genius by many, and his net worth was in the billions towards the end of 2022.</p>
<p>Sadly, this reputation was short-lived as in mid-November, SBF complained of a liquidity crunch on social media. He said he <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>needed fast cash</strong></a> to keep his business in operation, and he eventually turned to his biggest rival Binance about a possible buyout. While things <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>appeared to be moving</strong></a> in that direction for some time, Binance eventually backed <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>away from the deal</strong></a>, claiming the problems FTX was facing were simply too big for it to handle.</p>
<p>From there, the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>company filed bankruptcy</strong></a> and SBF resigned from his post. Things would have been bad enough if they had stopped there, but the trash meter kept rising. It was later discovered that SBF had utilized customer funds to invest in luxury Bahamian real estate and to pay off loans taken out by his other company Alameda Research. He <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftxs-disgraced-founder-has-been-arrested/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>was eventually arrested</strong></a> and extradited back to the United States. He has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-ftx-exec-sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-fraud/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>entered a not guilty plea</strong></a> and is awaiting trial at his <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-to-await-trial-at-his-parents-house/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>parents’ California home</strong></a>.</p>
<h2>Looking for Someone to Blame?</h2>
<p>Sam Bankman-Fried has stated that while the risk management employed by the now bankrupt exchange was less than ideal, he continues to insist that he did not steal customer funds. He also says that the prosecutors in the case are simply looking for someone to blame for what happened and they were quick to rush in and tie him to all the issues that arose.</p>
<p>Many legal experts are saying that the chances of him getting any charges tossed are slim to none as there have been too many customers that lost money. His trial is set to begin in early October.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-likely-to-face-all-charges-prosecutors-say/">Sam Bankman-Fried Likely to Face All Charges, Prosecutors Say</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EOS Price Analysis: Key Uptrend Support Intact at $0.70</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-key-uptrend-support-intact-at-0-70/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 05:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EOS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79263</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>EOS price started a downside correction below the $0.765 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $0.745 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.714 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-key-uptrend-support-intact-at-0-70/">EOS Price Analysis: Key Uptrend Support Intact at $0.70</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>EOS price started a downside correction below the $0.765 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $0.745 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.714 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it stays below the $0.745 and $0.768 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>EOS price is declining below $0.768 against the US Dollar, unlike <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-restart-rally-above-this-resistance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. The price could attempt a fresh increase unless there is a break below $0.70.</em></p>
<h2>EOS Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Earlier this month, EOS price climbed higher above the $0.75 resistance zone against the US Dollar. The price surpassed the $0.80 level and settled above the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>A high was formed near $0.8070 before the price started a downside correction. The price declined below the $0.768 support zone. There was a drop below the 50% Fib retracement level of the key increase from the $0.6410 swing low to the $0.8070 high.</p>
<p>However, the bulls were active near the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bulls-protecting-key-support-at-0-70/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$0.70 support</a>. The price is also stable above the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the key increase from the $0.6410 swing low to the $0.8070 high.</p>
<p>More importantly, there is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.714 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair. The pair is now trading below $0.768 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>On the downside, immediate support is near the $0.714 level and the trend line. The next key support is near the $0.70 level. If there is a downside break below the $0.70 support, the price could revisit the $0.64 support. On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $0.745 level. The first major resistance is near the $0.768 level, above which the price could rise steadily toward the $0.80 level. Any more gains might send the price toward the $0.848 level.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79264" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79264" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-1.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-79264" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-1.png" alt="EOS Price " width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-1.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-1-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-1-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-1-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-1-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-1-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-1-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79264" class="wp-caption-text">EOS Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/EOSUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, EOS price is now trading below the $0.745 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $0.745 and $0.768 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for EOS/USD is losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $0.714 and $0.700.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $0.745 and $0.768.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-key-uptrend-support-intact-at-0-70/">EOS Price Analysis: Key Uptrend Support Intact at $0.70</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Key Breakout Resistance at $98</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-key-breakout-resistance-at-98/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 03:18:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79260</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin is consolidating losses near the $96 level against the US Dollar. LTC price is now trading below $98 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $97.00 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could gain [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-key-breakout-resistance-at-98/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Key Breakout Resistance at $98</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Litecoin is consolidating losses near the $96 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>LTC price is now trading below $98 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $97.00 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $97 and $98 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Litecoin price is showing positive signs above $92 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-restart-rally-above-this-resistance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. LTC price could climb again if there is a clear move above $98.</em></p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few sessions, there were mostly range moves in Bitcoin, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-aims-fresh-run-to-2000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a>, Ripple, and Litecoin against the US Dollar. Earlier, LTC started a downside correction from the $115 resistance.</p>
<p>The price traded below the $105 and $100 levels. However, the bulls were active near the $92 zone. The price is now consolidating losses and trading above $95. It even spiked a few times above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $114.98 swing high to the $91.88 low.</p>
<p>However, the bears were active near the $98 resistance zone. It is now consolidating below $98 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $97 level.</p>
<p>There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $97.00 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair. A clear move above the $98 level could push the price toward the $104 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $114.98 swing high to the $91.88 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance sits near the $110 level. Any more gains might send the price toward the $115 level. On the downside, initial support is near the $94 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $92 level. If there is a downside break below the $92 support, the price could accelerate lower toward the $82 level in the near term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79261" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79261" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-1.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-79261" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-1.png" alt="Litecoin (LTC) Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-1.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-1-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-1-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-1-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-1-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-1-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-1-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79261" class="wp-caption-text">Litecoin (LTC) Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, Litecoin’s price is trading below $98 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $97 and $98 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LTC/USD is now losing pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $94 and $92</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $97 and $98.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-key-breakout-resistance-at-98/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Key Breakout Resistance at $98</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DWP Executive John Chen Suspended After Engaging in Crypto Mining</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dwp-executive-john-chen-suspended-after-engaging-in-crypto-mining/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 17:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DWP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[John Chen]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78540</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>John Chen, an executive working with the Los Angeles Department of Water and Power (DWP), has been placed on administrative leave after he took part in crypto mining companies that allegedly go against the values and ethics of his agency. John Chen in Hot Water Chen reportedly earns more than $300K a year through his [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dwp-executive-john-chen-suspended-after-engaging-in-crypto-mining/">DWP Executive John Chen Suspended After Engaging in Crypto Mining</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>John Chen, an executive working with the Los Angeles Department of Water and Power (DWP), has been placed on <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/dwp-executive-placed-leave-amid-001223319.html">administrative leave after</a> he took part in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/crypto-mining/">crypto mining</a> companies that allegedly go against the values and ethics of his agency.</p>
<h2>John Chen in Hot Water</h2>
<p>Chen reportedly earns more than $300K a year through his job with the DWP. He has served, for the past few years, as the department’s director, though having been part of a crypto mining company in Colorado since 2018, his constituents say his outside business ventures don’t sit in line with those of the department. Thus, he’s no longer employed while the other executives further examine his activities.</p>
<p>It’s also alleged, through various court documents, that Chen is the manager of a mining data center in North Dakota. In the end, Chen was given an ultimatum… Either remain solely with the department and leave his outside ventures to others or be relieved of his duties… Chen chose the latter.</p>
<p>Cynthia McClain-Hill – president of the DWP board of commissioners – says she and her associates were shocked and displeased when they found out about Chen’s outside business dealings. In an interview, she stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I would expect that employees at DWP, and in particular employees at his level, would be giving their full-time attention to the city and the city’s business.</p></blockquote>
<p>Chen was quick to defend himself, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>It’s an investment. I’m not running it. There’s outside staff that are running it.</p></blockquote>
<p>To be fair, the associates of Chen aren’t displeased with him taking part in bitcoin. They acknowledge that this is a free country and people can pursue whatever makes them happy so long as their actions don’t hurt or disband others. Their concerns lie in the fact that he has a very demanding job, and thus taking part in other business ventures suggests he’s not devoting the proper amount of attention to his DWP duties.</p>
<p>Bob Stern – who worked to draft the public campaign and ethics laws of the city – said his main concern lies with Chen not being able to devote all he needs to the DWP job given he’s allegedly tied up with crypto mining. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Is he giving L.A. what he’s earning? Is he performing 40 hours a week?</p></blockquote>
<h2>Does This <em>Really</em> Warrant Concern?</h2>
<p>Further documentation surrounding the situation shows Chen allegedly partnered with companies in both Singapore and China to bring the Colorado firm to fruition. Also, he secured an economic development deal with Colorado Springs Utilities to garner lesser rates for electricity.</p>
<p>This all seems like an odd reason to get into a huff. If Chen is doing everything on his own time, like he clearly states, and he’s doing a good job with the DWP, what is the big deal?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/dwp-executive-john-chen-suspended-after-engaging-in-crypto-mining/">DWP Executive John Chen Suspended After Engaging in Crypto Mining</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tools for Humanity Garners More than $100 Million to Build Digital &#8220;World Coin&#8221;</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tools-for-humanity-garners-more-than-100-million-to-build-digital-world-coin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 15:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain capital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tools for Humanity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World Coin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78537</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tools for Humanity – a company that has introduced a new digital token known as World Coin – has recently garnered as much as $115 million in a new series C funding round led by Blockchain Capital. The company has announced that the funds will go towards growing the breadth of World Coin, as well [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tools-for-humanity-garners-more-than-100-million-to-build-digital-world-coin/">Tools for Humanity Garners More than $100 Million to Build Digital &#8220;World Coin&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tools for Humanity – a company that has introduced a new <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/tools-humanity-secures-115-million-130102805.html">digital token known</a> as World Coin – has recently garnered as much as $115 million in a new series C funding round led by Blockchain Capital. The company has announced that the funds will go towards growing the breadth of World Coin, as well as developing alternatives to CAPTCHA tests.</p>
<h2>Tools for Humanity Garners a Lot of Cash</h2>
<p>World Coin aims to be one of the few fully democratic digital tokens out there in that the executives behind it hope to distribute the token to as many people as possible (hopefully everyone in the world). In addition, all who hold the asset will share equally in the wealth, and nobody can hold more than other parties like they would with bitcoin, Ethereum, and mainstream digital coins.</p>
<p>Spencer Bogart – a general partner at Blockchain Capital – explained in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>It was this idea of creating a new primitive for the internet that can enable any application to easily and quickly distinguish between machines and humans, or bots and humans. That was something that took me working more closely with our engineering team to really appreciate how big of a problem that already is.</p></blockquote>
<p>He further stated that bots have been major problems for blockchain and crypto projects, and thus Tools for Humanity is working hard on making sure they never come about to prevent innovation in the industry again. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>[CAPTCHA] has been fairly effective for distinguishing between bots and humans. That&#8217;s no longer the case with more advanced automated systems, especially things being powered by AI.</p></blockquote>
<p>Not long ago, Blockchain Capital came <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blockchain-capital-plunks-money-into-eyeball-scanning-technology/">under fire for investing</a> in some rather questionable technology. To be exact, it was an eyeball-scanning orb built to give all users what are referred to as “World IDs.” Describing the venture, Bogart explained in a separate interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>The root of what defines humans is biometrics, and my first thought was, ‘Why create this custom hardware to go scan eyeballs?’ Like, billions of people are already walking around with an iPhone. Why don’t we use Face ID, right? The problem is that human facial structures do not have sufficient randomness or entropy to distinguish between unique humans at the scale of tens of millions or hundreds of millions of people… I didn’t think about the fact that once you get past one hundred million people, there are going to be a lot of people that look like Spencer Bogart.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Lot of Big Names at the Table</h2>
<p>Right now, it’s unclear how much money Blockchain Capital has invested in World Coin and the remaining ventures of Tools for Humanity.</p>
<p>However, the funding round was no doubt large and saw the participation of many big-name venture capital firms including Bain Capital Crypto and Distributed Global.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tools-for-humanity-garners-more-than-100-million-to-build-digital-world-coin/">Tools for Humanity Garners More than $100 Million to Build Digital &#8220;World Coin&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>&#8220;Tuttle Twins&#8221; Cartoon Features Entire Episode on Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tuttle-twins-cartoon-features-entire-episode-on-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 13:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Daniel Harmon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tuttle Twins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78534</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The “Tuttle Twins” – a conservative children’s cartoon series – recently featured an entire episode that discusses bitcoin and the notions of digital currency. &#8220;Tuttle Twins&#8221; Brings BTC to Children Normally, the “Tuttle Twins” is all about trying to teach children to think for themselves and develop critical skills that will help them in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tuttle-twins-cartoon-features-entire-episode-on-bitcoin/">&#8220;Tuttle Twins&#8221; Cartoon Features Entire Episode on Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The “Tuttle Twins” – a conservative children’s cartoon series – <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/tv/news/tuttle-twins-cartoon-about-life-and-liberty-goes-viral-with-bitcoin-and-the-beast-episode/ar-AA1bLsEH">recently featured an entire</a> episode that discusses bitcoin and the notions of digital currency.</p>
<h2>&#8220;Tuttle Twins&#8221; Brings BTC to Children</h2>
<p>Normally, the “Tuttle Twins” is all about trying to teach children to think for themselves and develop critical skills that will help them in the modern world. Thus, it makes perfect sense that bitcoin would be a major topic of the show. As we edge deeper into a digital age, there may be a time when the children watching the show, as adults, will be required to utilize bitcoin and other crypto assets for everyday purchases and transactions.</p>
<p>The bitcoin discussion came about during an episode called “Tuttle Twins: Bitcoin and the Beast.” It is currently making the rounds on several social platforms and garnering a lot of buzz. The show’s creator Daniel Harmon explained in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>People are really resonating with the message. We had one fan comment about how they were trying to explain bitcoin to someone for seven years. We did in 20 minutes what they couldn’t do in seven years. So, that’s really rewarding to see. People are understanding it, especially how money that’s hard to create is so beneficial to society.</p></blockquote>
<p>The episode – which describes bitcoin as “hard money” – recites the following about digital currency:</p>
<blockquote><p>Digital money that can be sent directly from one person to another without any bank or government involved, and the best part: it’s hard money. Bitcoin is very hard to make more of. Each new coin gets added to the supply only after a computer works very hard to solve a math problem where there’s no shortcut, and solving it costs a lot of energy and time.</p></blockquote>
<p>Harmon continued with:</p>
<blockquote><p>I don’t think they are hearing these kinds of messages in other forms of media, for the most part. They’re not getting it in schools, not getting it in culture, and for us to talk very clearly about things like rights to life, liberty, and property, about things like bitcoin, inflation, entrepreneurship in a way that kids can understand is very refreshing to parents. It’s something that they’ve been craving for a long time. They’re very much noticing that it doesn’t exist elsewhere. That’s why the show is having its success.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Money that Can&#8217;t Be Controlled</h2>
<p>Bitcoin is becoming a rough topic in that many countries – particularly the United States – are working hard to implement socialist, woke agendas into their societies along with poor economic tactics that have brought <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-provide-their-thoughts-on-latest-bitcoin-rally/">about the deaths of various</a> banks and caused inflation to rise through the roof.</p>
<p>Bitcoin is money that cannot be controlled by the government, which explains – according to Ron DeSantis – why Biden and his entourage of nation haters are <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/florida-governor-ron-desantis-defends-crypto-and-bashes-the-idea-of-cbdcs/">trying so hard to ruin</a> it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tuttle-twins-cartoon-features-entire-episode-on-bitcoin/">&#8220;Tuttle Twins&#8221; Cartoon Features Entire Episode on Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
