<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 11:12:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/cropped-fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Enhancing Security and Privacy with AI and Blockchain: A Synergistic Approach</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/enhancing-security-and-privacy-with-ai-and-blockchain-a-synergistic-approach/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 11:09:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79147</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In today&#8217;s digital landscape, the security of applications, software, data, and systems is a paramount concern for users and developers alike. With the rise of cyber threats and data breaches, organisations are seeking innovative solutions to safeguard their valuable assets. Blockchain and artificial intelligence (AI) are two transformative technologies that offer promising avenues to enhance [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/enhancing-security-and-privacy-with-ai-and-blockchain-a-synergistic-approach/">Enhancing Security and Privacy with AI and Blockchain: A Synergistic Approach</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In today&#8217;s digital landscape, the security of applications, software, data, and systems is a paramount concern for users and developers alike. With the rise of cyber threats and data breaches, organisations are seeking innovative solutions to safeguard their valuable assets. Blockchain and artificial intelligence (AI) are two transformative technologies that offer promising avenues to enhance security measures. By leveraging the power of blockchain and AI, developers can create secure applications and fortify the protection of sensitive information. These two new technologies are at the nexus of enhancing security and privacy in the digital world.</p>
<h4>AI and blockchain intersection for digital security</h4>
<p>Blockchain technology provides a decentralised and transparent platform for storing and managing data. Its immutability and consensus mechanisms ensure the integrity of data stored on the blockchain. By leveraging blockchain&#8217;s distributed nature, sensitive information can be stored across multiple nodes, making it extremely challenging for attackers to tamper with or manipulate the data. Moreover, blockchain&#8217;s cryptographic techniques enable secure data sharing and communication, protecting the privacy of users.</p>
<p>On the other hand, AI, particularly machine learning algorithms, play a crucial role in preserving privacy and enhancing system security. Machine learning models can analyse vast amounts of data to identify patterns and anomalies that may indicate security threats. By training these models on historical data, they can effectively detect and prevent unauthorised access, ensuring the security of applications and systems.</p>
<p>Combining AI and blockchain in the development of new applications helps unlock new levels of cybersecurity and data privacy, fortifying software, applications, and systems. These technologies aid the development of robust platforms that are continually evolving to meet the emerging security and privacy challenges while maintaining integrity of the systems in the following ways:</p>
<h4>AI-Driven Secure Blockchain Applications</h4>
<p>Integrating AI with blockchain can lead to the development of intelligent applications that autonomously detect and respond to security threats. AI algorithms can continuously monitor the blockchain network, identifying suspicious activities or anomalies. These applications can initiate security protocols automatically, notifying relevant stakeholders to take immediate action and minimise potential damages. By leveraging AI capabilities, blockchain applications can adapt and evolve in real-time to counter emerging security challenges.</p>
<h4>Trust Management</h4>
<p>Establishing trust is a critical aspect of securing applications, software, data, and systems. Blockchain technology, with its decentralised and transparent nature, provides a foundation for trust management. AI algorithms can analyse data stored on the blockchain, verifying the authenticity and integrity of transactions. By combining blockchain&#8217;s trust-building capabilities with AI&#8217;s data analysis and verification techniques, organisations can enable secure and trustworthy storage and exchange of digital assets.</p>
<h4>AI-Driven Secure Computing</h4>
<p>AI models often require significant computational power to perform complex tasks. Due to the decentralised and crowdsourced nature of blockchain networks they can provide the necessary computing resources while ensuring the security and privacy of AI computations. By leveraging blockchain&#8217;s distributed computing capabilities, organisations can securely execute AI algorithms without exposing sensitive data to potential risks. This integration enables secure and efficient AI-driven computing, safeguarding applications, software, data, and systems.</p>
<p>On the other hand, smart contracts, powered by AI, can automate and secure digital interactions, minimising human errors and potential security breaches. In this way, AI-empowered secure computing on blockchain ensures the privacy and security of computations, enabling trusted execution of smart contracts.</p>
<h4>Blockchain Recovery, and Auditing using AI</h4>
<p>Ensuring the availability and recovery of data in the event of a system failure or cyber-attack is crucial. Blockchain&#8217;s decentralised architecture and AI&#8217;s predictive capabilities can be leveraged to enhance availability and recovery mechanisms. The blockchain can store backup copies of critical data, enabling efficient recovery in case of data loss. AI algorithms can analyse system logs and detect anomalies, facilitating timely response and recovery measures. Furthermore, blockchain&#8217;s transparent nature allows for efficient auditing and accountability, ensuring the integrity of system operations.</p>
<p><a href="https://aiwork.io/">AIWORK</a> is leading the development of AI-driven blockchain applications by facilitating the creation, verification and validation of AI data sets to make AI smarter for human use. Through the platform, content creators can benefit from crowd-sourced computing resources and a decentralised community to transcribe and translate their content to reach diverse audiences. AIWORK harnesses the power of blockchain technology and novel AI tools to build better content metadata to improve better search and discoverability for its users. By combining these two ground-breaking technologies, AIWORK enables improved interactions and content consumption while maintaining a high degree of security and privacy for both creators and users in the digital space.</p>
<h4>Conclusion</h4>
<p>The secure application of blockchain and artificial intelligence offers a transformative approach to fortifying the security of applications, software, data, and systems. By leveraging blockchain&#8217;s decentralised and transparent platform and integrating AI&#8217;s data analysis and predictive capabilities, applications can establish secure environments, protect sensitive information, and mitigate security risks. As the digital landscape continues to evolve, embracing the combined potential of blockchain and AI will be crucial in safeguarding valuable assets and maintaining trust in the digital realm.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/enhancing-security-and-privacy-with-ai-and-blockchain-a-synergistic-approach/">Enhancing Security and Privacy with AI and Blockchain: A Synergistic Approach</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EOS Price Analysis: Bulls Protecting Key Support at $0.70</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bulls-protecting-key-support-at-0-70/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 05:08:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EOS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79144</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>EOS price started a downside correction from the $0.808 resistance against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $0.74 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key contracting triangle forming with support near $0.715 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bulls-protecting-key-support-at-0-70/">EOS Price Analysis: Bulls Protecting Key Support at $0.70</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>EOS price started a downside correction from the $0.808 resistance against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $0.74 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key contracting triangle forming with support near $0.715 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it stays below the $0.74 and $0.75 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>EOS price is declining from $0.808 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-more-upsides-above-31250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. The price could accelerate lower if there is a clear move below the $0.70 support.</em></p>
<h2>EOS Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This week, EOS price climbed further higher above the $0.75 resistance zone against the US Dollar. The price surpassed the $0.80 level and settled above the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>A high was formed near $0.8072 before the price started a downside correction. The price declined below the $0.765 support to move into a short-term bearish zone. There was a move below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.6412 swing low to the $0.8072 high.</p>
<p>The pair even tested the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.6412 swing low to the $0.8072 high. It is now trading below $0.75 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bears-in-control-below-0-80/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>On the downside, immediate support is near the $0.705 level. There is also a key contracting triangle forming with support near $0.715 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair. The next key support is near the $0.68 level. If there is a downside break below the $0.68 support, the price could revisit the $0.62 support.</p>
<p>On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $0.74 level. The first major resistance is near the $0.75 level, above which the price could rise steadily.</p>
<p>The main resistance is still near $0.808. A clear move above the $0.808 level might call for more upsides. In the stated case, it could rise toward the $0.880 level. Any more gains might send the price toward the $0.925 level.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79145" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79145" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS.png"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-79145" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS.png" alt="EOS Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/EOS-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79145" class="wp-caption-text">EOS Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/EOSUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, EOS price is now trading below the $0.75 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $0.74 and $0.75 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for EOS/USD is gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $0.705 and $0.700.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $0.740 and $0.808.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bulls-protecting-key-support-at-0-70/">EOS Price Analysis: Bulls Protecting Key Support at $0.70</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Uptrend Intact Above $100</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-uptrend-intact-above-100/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 03:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79141</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin started a downside correction from the $115 zone against the US Dollar. LTC price is now trading above $98 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $104.10 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-uptrend-intact-above-100/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Uptrend Intact Above $100</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Litecoin started a downside correction from the $115 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>LTC price is now trading above $98 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $104.10 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could start a fresh increase if it clears the $105 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Litecoin price is correcting gains from $115 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-more-upsides-above-31250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. LTC price could resume its increase if it remains well supported above the $98 level.</em></p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, there was a decent increase in Bitcoin, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-could-rally-above-2000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a>, Ripple, and Litecoin against the US Dollar. Earlier, LTC formed a base above the $80 level and started a fresh increase.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above the $85 and $95 resistance levels. The price even climbed above the $100 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). However, the bears were active near the $115 zone. The recent high was formed near $114.98 and the price started a downside correction.</p>
<p>There was a move below the $105 level. The price traded below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $81.77 swing low to the $114.98 high.</p>
<p>It is now trading above $98 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $105 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $104.10 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>The next major resistance sits near the $110 level. A clear move above the $110 level could pump the price toward the $115 level. Any more gains might call for a test of $120.</p>
<p>Immediate support is near the $98.80 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $81.77 swing low to the $114.98 high. The next major support is near the $95 zone. A downside break below the $95 support might start a strong decline.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79142" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79142" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-79142" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin.png" alt="Litecoin (LTC) Price " width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Litecoin-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79142" class="wp-caption-text">Litecoin (LTC) Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, Litecoin price is trading above $98 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could start a fresh increase if it clears the $105 resistance.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LTC/USD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $98 and $95</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $105 and $110.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-uptrend-intact-above-100/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Uptrend Intact Above $100</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leticia James and Coin Cafe Settle for More Than $4 Million</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leticia-james-and-coin-cafe-settle-for-more-than-4-million/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 17:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coin Cafe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Leticia James]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New York]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78455</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Leticia James – the attorney general of the state of New York – has sued ANOTHER digital currency company, and it appears she’s gotten her way. At the time of writing, Brooklyn-based cryptocurrency firm Coin Café has settled with James for roughly $4.3 million. Leticia James Sues Another Crypto Enterprise The money will serve as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leticia-james-and-coin-cafe-settle-for-more-than-4-million/">Leticia James and Coin Cafe Settle for More Than $4 Million</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Leticia James – the attorney general of the state of New York – has <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/cryptocurrency-company-defeated-new-york-attorney-general-recovers-4-3-million/ar-AA1bohUU">sued ANOTHER digital currency</a> company, and it appears she’s gotten her way. At the time of writing, Brooklyn-based cryptocurrency firm Coin Café has settled with James for roughly $4.3 million.</p>
<h2>Leticia James Sues Another Crypto Enterprise</h2>
<p>The money will serve as restitution for investors that James says were defrauded by the company. It was initially alleged that Coin Café was a free platform to use. However, James says that many of the investors were subjected to secret fees for its wallet storage services.</p>
<p>James seems to have made it her mission in life to go after crypto companies as of late. The head honcho of New York’s legal scene has attacked a wide array of crypto firms including <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-sues-crypto-lending-network-celsius-and-its-former-ceo/">Celsius</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-attorney-generals-office-now-suing-ku-coin-exchange/">Ku Coin</a>, and many of these companies are either still stuck in lawsuits with James or were subjected to her antics in the past.</p>
<p>It’s unclear if James is just hellbent on going after the crypto market or if there’s a true point to what she’s doing. The fact remains that New York has long held an anti-crypto attitude that is probably going to mar the digital currency environment in the region for some time.</p>
<p>For example, not long ago, the Empire State <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/some-want-the-crypto-moratorium-in-new-york-to-last-longer/">announced that it was imposing</a> a two-year crypto moratorium on all mining companies. Thus, no new firms could enter the state or set up shop there unless they were willing to fully operate on green energy, something that’s not quite possible right now.</p>
<p>Furthermore, New York has long made it difficult for crypto firms to establish headquarters within its borders given it’s been invoking <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitlicense/">BitLicense</a> requirements for the past eight years. The BitLicense is considered one of the most restrictive forms of crypto legislation in history. The document requires all crypto companies in New York to follow very strict guidelines and pay exorbitant fees to remain in business and engage in transactions with customers in the Big Apple.</p>
<p>Many crypto executives have said it’s not possible to adhere to the BitLicense’s requirements and that the program seeks to limit innovation in the crypto arena. Rather than follow the directions set forth by the legislation, many have simply packed up and left the state, never to return.</p>
<h2>Some Positive Steps</h2>
<p>Despite all this, James has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leticia-james-introduces-bill-that-would-birth-basic-crypto-regulation-in-new-york/">recently initiated a bill</a> that, if passed, would create a basic framework for crypto activity in the state of New York. While the bill is not perfect and doesn’t hit all the major points, it would be a positive step forward in many ways given how lacking crypto regulation is at this time.</p>
<p>In addition, the state has also explored the possibility of using bitcoin as a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-considers-crypto-as-a-method-of-payment/">method of payment</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/leticia-james-and-coin-cafe-settle-for-more-than-4-million/">Leticia James and Coin Cafe Settle for More Than $4 Million</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Venom Foundation Seeks to Bring Blockchain to Kenya</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-venom-foundation-seeks-to-bring-blockchain-to-kenya/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 15:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kenya]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Venom Foundation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78453</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Venom Foundation – a Web3, fintech, and blockchain company – has agreed to form a partnership with the government of Kenya in Africa as a means of bringing more blockchain and crypto capabilities to the continent. The company also said it’s hoping to establish more Web3 and blockchain applications in the coming months and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-venom-foundation-seeks-to-bring-blockchain-to-kenya/">The Venom Foundation Seeks to Bring Blockchain to Kenya</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Venom Foundation – a Web3, fintech, and blockchain company – has <a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/press-release/venom-to-launch-a-blockchain-hub-with-kenyan-government-2023-05-16">agreed to form a partnership</a> with the government of Kenya in Africa as a means of bringing more blockchain and crypto capabilities to the continent. The company also said it’s hoping to establish more Web3 and blockchain applications in the coming months and years to ensure Kenyans have access to up-to-date technology.</p>
<h2>Kenya Is Getting Access to Blockchain</h2>
<p>Christopher Louis Tsu – CTO for the Venom Foundation – commented in a recent interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Africa is already rich in natural resources and human capital. By bringing next generation blockchain technology to the continent, it will empower the people and help not only Kenya, but many other African nations to capitalize on their assets and participate in new global markets competitively.</p></blockquote>
<p>There has been a running theme over the past several years that if any region can benefit from blockchain and crypto, it’s Africa. The continent has long suffered from both political and financial corruption, and it’s long been believed that <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/could-btc-revamp-the-financial-industry-of-africa/">digital currencies can ultimately</a> bring about a new world for many of the continent’s native residents.</p>
<p>There are many entrepreneurs that have worked hard to bring the joys and magic of blockchain and digital currencies to Africa. For example, Jack Dorsey – the former CEO of Twitter – initially announced that <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/jack-dorsey-i-will-bring-btc-to-africa/">he was going to spend</a> several months touring through Africa and doing what he could to ensure the people had proper access to bitcoin and blockchain technology.</p>
<p>Sadly, this was about a year prior to the start of the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/coronavirus/">COVID-19 pandemic</a>, and thus it’s unclear if Dorsey ever fulfilled those plans. In any case, the idea still stands that crypto and blockchain can help Africa in ways no other technology can. Moses Kuria – the Cabinet Secretary for Investments, Trade, and Industry – commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>We are excited to work together with the Venom Foundation. This collaboration signifies the stance that we are taking towards next-generation technology and financial and technological developments in the world. We believe that the establishment of this blockchain hub will catalyze further innovations in various industries, benefitting our people both nationally and globally.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Trying to Help Africa</h2>
<p>Kenya is a unique country in that at the present time, roughly 84 percent of the people have normal access to banks. This is odd given the number of unbanked souls living in Africa. Thus, Kenya is a little more ahead of the game. However, with the integration of blockchain into the nation’s financial space, further value is likely to be implemented for the people who live there.</p>
<p>They will thus enjoy more opportunities and see their economy boom in ways nobody thought possible. There will also be new trade routes established through blockchain, which analysts believe will lead to a solid, long-term financial plan for the people of Kenya.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-venom-foundation-seeks-to-bring-blockchain-to-kenya/">The Venom Foundation Seeks to Bring Blockchain to Kenya</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The ASX Has Ended All Its Blockchain-Related Plans</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-asx-has-ended-all-its-blockchain-related-plans/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 13:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ASX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tim Whiteley]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78450</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Australian Stock Exchange (ASX) recently engaged in an ambitious new plan to completely rebuild and revamp itself with blockchain technology, but sadly, those plans have come to a sudden end. The ASX &#8220;Breaks Up&#8221; with Blockchain A review of the agenda has suggested that for the ASX to be successful in its attempts, it [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-asx-has-ended-all-its-blockchain-related-plans/">The ASX Has Ended All Its Blockchain-Related Plans</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Australian Stock Exchange (ASX) recently engaged in an <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/australian-stock-exchange-says-software-overhaul-wont-involve-blockchain/ar-AA1bondT">ambitious new plan to completely</a> rebuild and revamp itself with <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/blockchain/">blockchain</a> technology, but sadly, those plans have come to a sudden end.</p>
<h2>The ASX &#8220;Breaks Up&#8221; with Blockchain</h2>
<p>A review of the agenda has suggested that for the ASX to be successful in its attempts, it would need to completely rework itself over a seven-year period. Executives behind the exchange say the plan is not feasible, and would thus not only require too much time, but also too much money and other resources to get things done appropriately.</p>
<p>The problem remains, however, that the ASX is still running on software that is approximately 30 years old. Since 1993, the technicals of the exchange haven’t been altered or adapted, but those behind the platform say blockchain is now completely and totally out of the question.</p>
<p>In a recent interview, Tim Whiteley – the exchange project director – was asked if the platform would choose to walk a more “conventional route.” He responded with:</p>
<blockquote><p>While we continue to explore all the options, certainly we will need to use a more conventional technology than in the original solution in order to achieve the business outcomes.</p></blockquote>
<p>The announcement has brought about the end of what would likely have been one of the most prominent use cases of blockchain technology ever recorded in the annals of history. For many years, it’s been argued that blockchain technology could only become more mainstream and legitimate granted companies and platforms outside the crypto arena chose to utilize it.</p>
<p>Right now, while the technology has indeed come a long way and has built up a solid reputation for itself, it’s also very saturated, and while there have been instances in the past of blockchain being used in industries such as healthcare or in supply-chain manufacturing, these instances are rare and far from being the norm.</p>
<p>Blockchain is rather revolutionary because it’s widely believed it can prevent all fraud from occurring. Everything recorded to the blockchain is recorded in real-time. This ensures that all transactions are clear and unaltered from third parties. They involve the transactors only, and thus there’s no worries about what will go on behind closed doors.</p>
<p>However, it’s not likely blockchain will reach the breadth of its potential unless outside firms see it for what it is: something that can aid all kinds of companies, not just those in the financial circle. With everything recorded to a distributed ledger, all the information becomes verifiable and provable, thus ensuring illicit activity is kept to a minimum.</p>
<h2>Getting the Right Commentary</h2>
<p>Whiteley said that the ASX has sent out requests for feedback to potential software vendors to see what alternatives exist to blockchain. Several have already gotten back to him, and he commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Feedback has been taken into the implementation planning.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-asx-has-ended-all-its-blockchain-related-plans/">The ASX Has Ended All Its Blockchain-Related Plans</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: More Gains Possible Above $0.08</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-more-gains-possible-above-0-08/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 06:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79118</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tron price started a fresh increase above the $0.0725 level against the US Dollar. TRX price is now trading above $0.0750 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.0762 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could continue to move [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-more-gains-possible-above-0-08/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: More Gains Possible Above $0.08</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Tron price started a fresh increase above the $0.0725 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>TRX price is now trading above $0.0750 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.0762 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move up if it breaks the $0.0785 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>TRON price started a fresh increase above $0.0750 against the US Dollar, outpacing <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-more-upsides-above-31250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. TRX’s price could rise further if it clears the $0.0785 resistance.</em></p>
<h2>Tron Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, Tron price started a steady increase from the $0.0682 support zone against the US Dollar. TRX’s price remained well-bid and was able to climb above the $0.0725 zone.</p>
<p>It traded above the $0.0750 and $0.0765 levels to move further into a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bulls-aim-fresh-move-to-0-082/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">positive zone</a>. Finally, the bears appeared near the $0.0785 level. A high is formed near $0.0783 and the price is now consolidating gains. It is trading well above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward wave from the $0.0680 swing low to the $0.0783 high.</p>
<p>It is trading above $0.0750 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, TRX is facing resistance near the $0.0785 level. The next major resistance is near the $0.080 level.</p>
<p>A close above $0.080 could send the price toward the $0.0820 resistance zone. Any more gains might send TRX price toward $0.0850, above which the price could even rise toward $0.088. On the downside, initial support is near the $0.0762 level.</p>
<p>There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.0762 on the 4-hours chart. The next major support is now forming near $0.0750, below which it could test the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward wave from the $0.0680 swing low to the $0.0783 high.</p>
<p>If there is a downside break below the $0.0732 support, the price might revisit the $0.0720 support. Any more losses might call for a move toward the $0.0682 zone in the near term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79119" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79119" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/TRON-TRX.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-79119" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/TRON-TRX.png" alt="Tron (TRX) Price Analysis" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/TRON-TRX.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/TRON-TRX-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/TRON-TRX-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/TRON-TRX-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/TRON-TRX-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/TRON-TRX-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/TRON-TRX-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79119" class="wp-caption-text">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis</figcaption></figure>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/TRXUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a> indicates that TRX’s price is now trading above $0.0750 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move up if it breaks the $0.0785 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for TRX/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for TRX/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.0762 and $0.0750.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.0785, $0.080, and $0.0820.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-more-gains-possible-above-0-08/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: More Gains Possible Above $0.08</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Eyes More Upsides Above $31,250</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-more-upsides-above-31250/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 04:48:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79115</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price is trading below the $31,250 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above $30,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a connecting bullish trend line forming with support near $30,300 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could continue [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-more-upsides-above-31250/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Eyes More Upsides Above $31,250</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin price is trading below the $31,250 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $30,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a connecting bullish trend line forming with support near $30,300 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to rise if it stays above the $30,000 support zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin price is showing positive signs above $30,000 against the US Dollar. BTC might correct lower but dips could be limited below the $29,850 zone.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price started a decent increase above the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-bulls-in-control-above-29500/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$29,000 resistance zone</a>. The price remained stable above the $30,000 level and traded in a positive zone.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above the $30,500 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). The price even rallied above the $31,000 resistance zone. However, the price seems to be struggling near the $31,450 zone. A high was formed near $31,445 and the price is now consolidating gains.</p>
<p>The price traded below $30,850 and tested the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $24,750 swing low to the $31,445 high. The price is now trading above $30,500 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-bulls-aim-fresh-uptrend/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>Immediate resistance on the upside is near the $31,000 level. The first major resistance is near the $31,250 level, above which the price could rise toward the $32,000 zone.</p>
<p>Any more gains might send the price toward the $32,850 zone. If there is no upside break, the price might start a downside correction below $30,500. There is also a connecting bullish trend line forming with support near $30,300 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>The next key support is near the $29,200 level. Any more losses might call for a move toward the $28,000 support zone or the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $24,750 swing low to the $31,445 high.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79116" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79116" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-79116" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-600x276.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-1100x507.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-768x354.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-750x345.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Bitcoin-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79116" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XBTUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, Bitcoin price is trading above $30,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to rise if it stays above the $30,000 support zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD is now losing momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $30,500 and $30,000.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $31,000, $31,250, and $32,000.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-more-upsides-above-31250/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Eyes More Upsides Above $31,250</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Winter to Blame for Miami BTC Conference Attendance Dips? Analysts Think So</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-winter-to-blame-for-miami-btc-conference-attendance-dips-analysts-think-so/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 17:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto winter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Bitcoin Conference]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robert Kennedy Jr.]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78448</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The crypto winter of 2022 may be technically over, but the effects are still being felt. This year, the Miami Bitcoin Conference saw a whopping 50 percent dip in its attendance rate. The Crypto Winter Is Still a Powerful Enemy That means roughly half of last year’s crowd showed up this year, and many are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-winter-to-blame-for-miami-btc-conference-attendance-dips-analysts-think-so/">Crypto Winter to Blame for Miami BTC Conference Attendance Dips? Analysts Think So</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto winter of 2022 may be technically over, but the <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/bitcoin-miami-conference-drop-attendance-crypto-094208644.html">effects are still being</a> felt. This year, the Miami Bitcoin Conference saw a whopping 50 percent dip in its attendance rate.</p>
<h2>The Crypto Winter Is Still a Powerful Enemy</h2>
<p>That means roughly half of last year’s crowd showed up this year, and many are blaming the crypto winter for the drops.</p>
<p>Some analysts believe the number may be lower than what’s being reported. For example, this year, roughly 15,000 people were in attendance. However, there are records suggesting last year’s attendance rate exceeded 35,000.</p>
<p>Despite this, the event still featured some relatively high-ranking individuals, one of which was democratic candidate for the White House Robert F. Kennedy Jr.</p>
<p>Kennedy is <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-candidate-robert-kennedy-jr-has-big-plans-for-the-crypto-space/">clearly a bitcoin fanatic</a>. He mentioned he is going to be accepting bitcoin and crypto donations for his campaign, and he also stated that should he become president, the government will never get in the way of investing in and holding digital assets. He commented during a speech:</p>
<blockquote><p>As president, I will make sure that your right to hold and use bitcoin is inviolable. I am an ardent defender and lifelong defender of civil liberties, and bitcoin is both an exercise and a guarantee of those freedoms.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also took serious issue with the situation involving Canadian truckers in 2022. During that time, several of these men took to protesting after their government announced they were required to take the COVID-19 vaccine. When their bank accounts and other <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-fund-set-up-for-canadian-truckers/">financial tools were shut</a> off, they sought to gain access to crypto so they could continue their actions.</p>
<p>From there, the Canadian government got in the way and sought to freeze whatever digital assets they got their hands on. Kennedy said he would make sure the government could take no action like that in the future and commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>None of these lawful and peaceful protestors had violated any law, but suddenly, they found that they could not access their money [or] their bank accounts to pay their mortgages or feed their families. When I witnessed this devastating use of government repression, I realized for the first time how free money is as important as free expression.</p></blockquote>
<h2>So Many Losses</h2>
<p>The crypto winter of 2022 was arguably the worst period for bitcoin and its digital cousins. BTC – the world’s number one digital currency by market cap – was trading at a new all-time high of $68,000 per unit during November of 2021. However, roughly one year later, the asset had lost more than 70 percent of its value and was trading in the mid-$16K range. It was a sad and ugly sight to see.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, things didn’t quite stop there, and many cryptocurrencies followed in BTC’s footsteps, thus causing the arena to lose more than $2 trillion in overall value.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-winter-to-blame-for-miami-btc-conference-attendance-dips-analysts-think-so/">Crypto Winter to Blame for Miami BTC Conference Attendance Dips? Analysts Think So</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
