<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 09:30:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/cropped-fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Cynthia Lummis: BTC Can Make the Planet Clean Again</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cynthia-lummis-btc-can-make-the-planet-clean-again/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 17:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cynthia Lummis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[national security]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78512</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cynthia Lummis – the republican senator of Wyoming – has proven herself to be a major bitcoin bull. During the recent Miami Bitcoin Conference, Lummis made an appearance and commented that bitcoin and cryptocurrencies could help clean up the environment. Cynthia Lummis on the Power of Crypto She explained: One of the advantages of bitcoin [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cynthia-lummis-btc-can-make-the-planet-clean-again/">Cynthia Lummis: BTC Can Make the Planet Clean Again</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cynthia Lummis – the republican senator of Wyoming – has proven herself to be a major bitcoin bull. During the recent Miami Bitcoin Conference, Lummis <a href="https://www.thestreet.com/cryptocurrency/news/cynthia-lummis-bitcoin-environment-miami">made an appearance and</a> commented that bitcoin and cryptocurrencies could help clean up the environment.</p>
<h2>Cynthia Lummis on the Power of Crypto</h2>
<p>She explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>One of the advantages of bitcoin mining is that when you drill an oil and gas well, and it is distant from other oil and gas wells, you vent the gas into the atmosphere until you can bring in a pipeline to hook it up. Well, while that’s being vented, you can pull a bitcoin mining operation in a trailer, use the vented methane gas to mine your bitcoin, and you are preventing that gas from being vented into the atmosphere. Bitcoin is cleaning up the environment.</p></blockquote>
<p>The news is interesting given that for the past several years, many environmentalists have stepped in to say that bitcoin and crypto are doing incredible harm to the environment – the <em>exact opposite</em> of what Lummis is stating. There have been many reports, for example, for some time, that bitcoin and crypto mining <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-bitcoin-mining-may-require-more-energy-than-180-countries/">uses more energy than</a> most developing nations such as Iceland.</p>
<p>Also, in April of 2023, reports from the Environmental Working Group linked bitcoin and crypto mining to higher air, noise, and water pollution. Many industry heads – from Kevin O’Leary to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-has-taken-a-nasty-stumble-many-are-blaming-elon-musk/">Elon Musk</a> – have also expressed concerns about how the mining industry has affected Earth’s atmosphere and resources.</p>
<p>Continuing her speech, Lummis further stated that bitcoin is also a national security issue. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I’m actually worried as we go into another debt ceiling debate that we will eventually increase the debt ceiling to the point where our interest payments will exceed how much money we spend on national defense, so it is a national security issue.</p></blockquote>
<p>She also criticized other lawmakers in Washington for not doing enough to know more about the crypto industry. She said that many of her constituents in Congress do not recognize the differences between bitcoin and its many altcoin cousins, a scary fact in her opinion. She commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Even though you all know that when FTX failed, they held zero bitcoin, there are a lot of people in Washington D.C. that conflate companies with digital assets. They conflate bitcoin with other cryptocurrencies.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Major Bull</h2>
<p>Since she first entered Congress <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/wyoming-bitcoin-advocate-heads-for-the-senate/">in January of 2021</a>, Lummis has shown herself to be a major bitcoin and crypto advocate, as she was very clear that she had invested in bitcoin multiple times prior.</p>
<p>She also introduced a crypto bill in mid-2022 that would allegedly carve <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/wyomings-cynthia-lummis-is-drafting-a-new-crypto-bill/">out rules and structures</a> for all future crypto legislation. The move was alleged proof that crypto innovation in America was an important talking point for Lummis and her staff.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cynthia-lummis-btc-can-make-the-planet-clean-again/">Cynthia Lummis: BTC Can Make the Planet Clean Again</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Gemini Exchange is Relocating to Ireland</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-gemini-exchange-is-relocating-to-ireland/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 15:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dublin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ireland]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78510</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Gemini exchange in New York is relocating to Dublin, Ireland, and joins a growing list of digital currency exchanges and related companies leaving the U.S. either due to complicated regulations or persecution from agencies like the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The Gemini Sets Its Sights on the Emerald Isle The crypto industry in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-gemini-exchange-is-relocating-to-ireland/">The Gemini Exchange is Relocating to Ireland</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Gemini exchange in New York <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/cryptocurrency-platform-founded-by-us-entrepreneurs-chooses-ireland-as-european-hq/ar-AA1bJfyA">is relocating to</a> Dublin, Ireland, and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-is-now-active-in-bermuda/">joins a growing list</a> of digital currency exchanges and related companies leaving the U.S. either due to complicated regulations or persecution from agencies like the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<h2>The Gemini Sets Its Sights on the Emerald Isle</h2>
<p>The crypto industry in the U.S. has been under heavy scrutiny from organizations like the one mentioned above. Its head, Gary Gensler, has gone after several leading digital currency companies over the past few months. Among the big names he’s attacked are Kraken, a crypto exchange based in Northern California, and Coinbase, arguably the largest and most dominant digital trading platform in the country.</p>
<p>Kraken was forced to end <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/">all its staking activities</a> and services while also parting with a $30 million penalty fee. Coinbase, on the other hand, was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/">served what’s called</a> a Wells notice that informed executives that financial charges were likely coming in the future. The group’s leaders took issue with the notice on account of they had allegedly met with representatives of the SEC several times over a nine-year period to ensure the company was fully compliant.</p>
<p>Gemini services have only been available in Europe for about a year, though in a statement, the company’s founders Tyler and Cameron Winklevoss made it clear they have a positive view of the Irish regulatory landscape. They’re also thrilled by how far the nation has come in terms of technology adoption and innovation. They commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>We look forward to being a part of and adding to the vibrant tech community in Dublin. Crypto is as transformative as the internet, and we are committed to unlocking the opportunities it represents.</p></blockquote>
<p>Irish politician Taoiseach Leo Varadkar TD commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>This is significant for Ireland as the government focuses on innovation as a driver of growth. Gemini&#8217;s decision to locate in Ireland highlights our competitive offering for the international financial services sector. We take pride in how it has grown from 60 staff in Dublin 30 years ago, to approximately 56,000 people around the country working in finance today. I wish Gemini every success as they build their team in Ireland.’</p></blockquote>
<p>Gillian Lynch – head of Ireland and Europe at Gemini – also threw her two cents in, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>As we continue to expand our global footprint, we’re excited to tap into the talent and innovation that Dublin and the Irish market have to offer. Dublin has long been a hub for innovation and technology, with a thriving startup scene and deep talent pool. We continue to be encouraged by the city’s commitment to fostering innovation, by a policy environment which encourages entrepreneurship.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Great Landscape?</h2>
<p>Michael Lohan – CEO of IDA Ireland – said:</p>
<blockquote><p>This investment will act as a strong reference case in seeking to further develop the digital assets sector.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-gemini-exchange-is-relocating-to-ireland/">The Gemini Exchange is Relocating to Ireland</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ron DeSantis is Running for President, Appears to Be Very Pro Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ron-desantis-is-running-for-president-appears-to-be-very-pro-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 13:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[President]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ron DeSantis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78504</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Republican governor of Florida Ron DeSantis has thrown his hat into the presidential ring. He has filed the necessary paperwork with the Federal Election Commission (FEC) and has officially launched his 2024 campaign on Twitter. Ron DeSantis Has Entered the White House Race Like several of this year’s candidates, DeSantis appears to be very pro [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ron-desantis-is-running-for-president-appears-to-be-very-pro-crypto/">Ron DeSantis is Running for President, Appears to Be Very Pro Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Republican governor of Florida Ron DeSantis has thrown his <a href="https://www.thestreet.com/cryptocurrency/news/ron-desantis-bitcoin-elon-musk-twitter-spaces">hat into the presidential</a> ring. He has filed the necessary paperwork with the Federal Election Commission (FEC) and has officially launched his 2024 campaign on Twitter.</p>
<h2>Ron DeSantis Has Entered the White House Race</h2>
<p>Like several of this year’s candidates, DeSantis appears to be very pro crypto, and is arguably hoping to garner some extra votes by saying a thing or two about the industry. In a recent interview, he claimed that Biden and his group of nation haters are likely to end the bitcoin reign in America should they win another four years in office as they’re doing all they can to outlaw it. DeSantis said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The current regime, clearly, they have it out for bitcoin, and if it continues for another four years, they’ll probably end up killing it. Bitcoin represents a threat to them. They’re trying to regulate it out of existence. You have every right to… bitcoin. The only reason these people in Washington don’t like it is because they don’t control it.</p></blockquote>
<p>There have been a wide array of politicians and presidential hopefuls this year that have spoken positively about bitcoin. Among them are democratic hopeful Robert F. Kennedy Jr., who in a speech at this <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/presidential-candidate-robert-kennedy-jr-has-big-plans-for-the-crypto-space/">year’s bitcoin conference</a> stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Our campaign will be the first presidential campaign in history to accept bitcoin donations through the Lightning Network, and today, we move one step closer to the future. Today, we show the world the power, durability, and flexibility of bitcoin.</p></blockquote>
<p>His love for crypto-based enterprises was seconded by another White House contender in republican Vivek Ramaswamy, who <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/vivek-ramaswamy-is-making-crypto-a-big-part-of-his-white-house-campaign/">during a campaign discussion</a> said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The thriving bitcoin universe should actually better empower me to do what I want to do as the U.S. president, which is to stabilize the U.S. dollar as a unit of measurement and put the Federal Reserve back in its place with that as its single mandate.</p></blockquote>
<p>Ron DeSantis recently <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ron-desantis-signs-anti-cbdc-crypto-bill-into-law/">took measures against</a> a central bank digital currency (CBDC) and signed a law in Florida disallowing the creation of such a tool. He says that a digital dollar of CBDC will undoubtedly be used by the federal government to spy on users. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Anyone with their eyes open could see the danger this type of an arrangement would mean for Americans who want to exercise their financial independence and would like to be able to conduct business without having the government know every single transaction they’re making in real time.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Will Bitcoin Decide the President in 2024?</h2>
<p>As mentioned in a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-bitcoin-could-be-a-big-topic-in-next-years-presidential-election/">previous opinion piece</a>, bitcoin and crypto are shaping up to be major talking points in next year’s presidential election.</p>
<p>Now, with the recent stance being taken by new contender Ron DeSantis, it looks like this sentiment is correct.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ron-desantis-is-running-for-president-appears-to-be-very-pro-crypto/">Ron DeSantis is Running for President, Appears to Be Very Pro Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alaya：High-quality data is the future of AI</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/alaya%ef%bc%9ahigh-quality-data-is-the-future-of-ai/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 09:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79175</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As the field of artificial intelligence continues to evolve, security and stability have improved, and so have the requirements for data quality. If the former algorithm model using the general data set is the rough food, then now the algorithm model needs to be customized nutritional meal. If companies want to further improve the ability [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/alaya%ef%bc%9ahigh-quality-data-is-the-future-of-ai/">Alaya：High-quality data is the future of AI</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As the field of artificial intelligence continues to evolve, security and stability have improved, and so have the requirements for data quality. If the former algorithm model using the general data set is the rough food, then now the algorithm model needs to be customized nutritional meal. If companies want to further improve the ability to implement the model, they must gradually move away from the original common data set and Internet data, and actively engage in customized data collection to create a core data barrier. At present, the world-wide Alaya data labeling platform has been known for its pursuit of data quality.</p>
<p>In a talk titled &#8220;AI is the new electricity&#8221;, the international authority on artificial intelligence, Enda Wu, highlighted the importance of data &#8220;The rise of AI is changing the competitive landscape for companies. The barrier for companies is no longer algorithms, but data, so that the algorithm can use enough data to make the product work&#8230;&#8221;</p>
<p>So why do people in artificial intelligence continue to seek high quality data?</p>
<p>When faced with a poorly performing model, engineers spend months tinkering with product features and new algorithms, not realizing that the problem exists in their data. High-quality data can lead to greater breakthroughs for humans.</p>
<h4>High quality data that is capable of understanding the problem you are trying to solve.</h4>
<p>While AI systems are becoming more complex, we need advanced and clever human marker systems to teach and measure their performance. Models that currently know enough about the world to identify and classify misleading information will not increase in complexity by using more low-skilled workers. To identify algorithmic biases, we need high-quality data to identify the right world.</p>
<h4>High-quality data can drive target functions consistent with human values</h4>
<p>Models are often trained on datasets that are only approximations of their true goals, leading to unexpected divergences. Machine learning is about teaching computers to work the way we want them to, and we achieve our goals by showing positive examples. So in order to build high-quality models, the most important skill a machine learning engineer needs to master should be building high-quality datasets and making sure they match the problem at hand.</p>
<p>If we want AI to solve our own real-world needs, we need to think deeply about the datasets that define our models and give them a certain human touch.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-79177 aligncenter" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture40-600x342.jpg" alt="" width="600" height="342" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture40-600x342.jpg 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture40-1100x628.jpg 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture40-768x438.jpg 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture40-750x428.jpg 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture40-1140x650.jpg 1140w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture40.jpg 1241w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></p>
<p>Alaya is always innovating and seeking world-wide growth when it comes to data quality.Alaya is a distributed AI data platform that integrates collection and labeling, that originated from Swarm Intelligence and connects communities, data, and AI through Social Commerce, providing the AI industry with high quality scalable data and full protection of its ownership and privacy. Provide high quality bid collection data for AI industry and  has achieved exponential growth through its built-in social recommendation mechanism. The community is used to solve the pain point of lack of data and scarcity of labor for AI practitioners and to bring group intelligence together across time and space and reorganize it efficiently.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-79178 aligncenter" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture41-600x489.jpg" alt="" width="600" height="489" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture41-600x489.jpg 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture41-1100x896.jpg 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture41-768x625.jpg 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture41-750x611.jpg 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture41-1140x928.jpg 1140w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/Picture41.jpg 1292w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></p>
<p>In terms of data quality, Alaya has achieved the following three things:</p>
<ol>
<li>The theoretical guidance of the discipline of community intelligence, linking global communities, using the community economy to constantly link to everyone in the world, so that the collection of data is no longer constrained by space, and global data collection and labeling can better highlight the quality of data;</li>
<li>With a built-in hierarchy and a unique intelligent recommendation algorithm, alaya accurately assigns needs to users with the same attribute tags, ensuring that needs are addressed by professional groups and improving data quality. User data will be an important part of the industry&#8217;s best quality data;</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>Alaya&#8217;s unique data quality assessment system ensures the accuracy and consistency of data after it is collected and labeled, and addresses errors and inconsistencies to guarantee customers the highest quality data sets.</li>
</ul>
<p>Alaya was founded on the idea of providing high quality data to help the industry grow. In the field of artificial intelligence, which is increasingly pursuing data quality, companies like Alaya will be the future of the industry.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/alaya%ef%bc%9ahigh-quality-data-is-the-future-of-ai/">Alaya：High-quality data is the future of AI</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CFTC Commissioner: We Can&#8217;t Stop All the Crypto Fraud</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cftc-commissioner-we-cant-stop-all-the-crypto-fraud/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 17:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CFTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christy Goldsmith Romero]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto fraud]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78494</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) has warned that while it’s doing all it can to end crypto fraud, it admitted that there’s nothing it can do about all the illicit activity out there, and thus there’s likely to be things here and there that vanish from its radar or go unnoticed. The CFTC Doesn&#8217;t [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cftc-commissioner-we-cant-stop-all-the-crypto-fraud/">CFTC Commissioner: We Can&#8217;t Stop All the Crypto Fraud</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) has <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/no-way-to-police-all-cryptocurrency-fraud-cftc-commissioner-says/ar-AA1bCRU5">warned that while it’s doing</a> all it can to end crypto fraud, it admitted that there’s nothing it can do about all the illicit activity out there, and thus there’s likely to be things here and there that vanish from its radar or go unnoticed.</p>
<h2>The CFTC Doesn&#8217;t Have that Much Power</h2>
<p>Christy Goldsmith Romero – one of five commissioners at the CFTC – announced in a recent interview that crypto cases account for roughly 20 percent (one fifth) of all the fraud cases the organization is overseeing. Among the present items it’s looking at include civil cases against both Binance and FTX, which are (or were) major digital trading platforms. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>There&#8217;s just a lot of fraud in the space. There&#8217;s no way we can police all the fraud, but we&#8217;ve got to do something.</p></blockquote>
<p>She also mentioned that she takes serious issue with the idea that the CFTC is somehow considered lighter or “friendlier” than its rival the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), which is presently run by head Gary Gensler. Over the past several months, the SEC has been more involved in policing crypto activity. Not long ago, the agency went after Kraken and Coinbase.</p>
<p>In the case of the former, the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/is-the-sec-trying-to-kill-crypto-for-good/">company was forced to end</a> all its staking activities and part with a $30 million penalty fee. With the latter, a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-receives-wells-notice-from-the-sec/">Wells notice was sent</a> to executives, informing them that formal charges were likely on their way. The executives took serious issue with these threats because they allegedly met with representatives of the SEC many times over a nine-year period to ensure the company was fully compliant.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, Romero doesn’t want to be seen as the easier of the two agencies. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I don&#8217;t like the idea that somehow the CFTC is light touch. &#8216;Light touch regulator&#8217; would never be written on my tombstone.</p></blockquote>
<p>Right now, the CFTC <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cftc-sues-binance-alleging-financial-violations/">is suing Binance</a> – one of the largest and most popular crypto exchanges in the world – because it allegedly violated the Commodity Exchange Act. CFTC chair Rostin Behnam claimed:</p>
<blockquote><p>For years, Binance knew they were violating CFTC rules, working actively to both keep the money flowing and avoid compliance. This should be a warning to anyone in the digital asset world that the CFTC will not tolerate willful avoidance of U.S. law.</p></blockquote>
<h2>So Many Types of Fraud</h2>
<p>Crypto fraud has taken on many forms in recent years. One of the most common (and more modern) forms has been <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/romance-scams/">romance scams</a>, which usually involve people chasing down others looking for love online.</p>
<p>Once they narrow in on a victim and garner their trust, they get them to invest in a phony crypto platform that’s controlled by their malicious brethren. They then block them from making withdrawals.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cftc-commissioner-we-cant-stop-all-the-crypto-fraud/">CFTC Commissioner: We Can&#8217;t Stop All the Crypto Fraud</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mathew McDermott: Blockchain Is an Unrivaled Technology</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mathew-mcdermott-blockchain-is-an-unrivaled-technology/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 15:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mathew McDermott]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78492</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mathew McDermott – a managing director of Goldman Sachs, one of the biggest financial companies in the world – says he thinks blockchain technology is well on its way to creating a sound new financial system that will never be rivaled or overshadowed. Mathew McDermott on the Future of Blockchain In a recent interview, McDermott [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mathew-mcdermott-blockchain-is-an-unrivaled-technology/">Mathew McDermott: Blockchain Is an Unrivaled Technology</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mathew McDermott – a managing director of Goldman Sachs, one of the biggest financial companies in the world – says he thinks blockchain technology is well <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/savingandinvesting/future-of-finance-goldmans-mcdermott-on-how-blockchain-tech-will-produce-a-profoundly-different-financial-system/ar-AA1bDbpS">on its way to creating</a> a sound new financial system that will never be rivaled or overshadowed.</p>
<h2>Mathew McDermott on the Future of Blockchain</h2>
<p>In a recent interview, McDermott explained his thoughts and feelings towards blockchain and how Goldman plans to integrate the technology into its systems in the coming future. As the head of the company’s digital assets division, McDermott stated that <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/blockchain/">blockchain</a> is likely to really help people do their jobs better. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>We&#8217;ve spent a lot of time recently talking in closed sessions with regulators and central bankers and the like, but I think commercially that sometimes it gets a little lost on people, but there are two real core areas. First, the tokenization and digitizing the lifecycle of different asset classes. It’s about creating efficiencies from inception (from issuance through post-trade), and we see a huge value opportunity there when it manifests itself at scale. The second area… is collateral mobility. A lot of the systems we use are probably as old as me and there are inefficiencies in those. In the movement of collateral from one custodian to another, you can’t be as precise as one would like, in terms of liquidity, which creates inefficiencies. There are certain risk profiles and trades you can totally transform [using] DLT [distributed ledger technology] because of that precision, that settlement finality.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Providing Benefits to Customers</h2>
<p>He also said that there are a multitude of financial companies and banks out there doing all they can to integrate blockchain in some way given that they see the benefits of the technology and what it can do for customers. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>For what [it is] worth, U.S. banks are typically focused on the private blockchains [now]. In client discussions, that tends to be where they want to play because of the control, privacy, security, KYC, all the things you’d expect. I think as people get more familiar with the technology, they’ll see the value that it adds. Web3 is all about empowering the individual, and I genuinely believe one of the biggest beneficiaries of this technology is going to be wealth management clients and family offices because they’re going to get greater access to investment opportunities. There will just be more liquidity in the market because you’re going to start seeing different marketplaces emerge. As public blockchains improve (there’s probably a nicer way to put it, as they <em>mature</em>), and people get more comfortable with them, opportunities will present themselves. I do think it’s probably a few years away, but I think that’s the way it really [must] evolve for regulators and institutions to be completely comfortable with it.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/mathew-mcdermott-blockchain-is-an-unrivaled-technology/">Mathew McDermott: Blockchain Is an Unrivaled Technology</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Arguments Against Crypto Mining May Be Based on Untrue Facts</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-arguments-against-crypto-mining-may-be-based-on-untrue-facts/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 13:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Greenidge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[William Hall]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78482</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The crypto mining debate has raged for years, but it appears the fight is taking stronger precedence in recent weeks. Is Crypto Mining a Damaging Enterprise? Maybe Not&#8230; There have been many reports published, over some time, claiming that crypto mining is putting the planet in harm’s way. They say there are several developing nations [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-arguments-against-crypto-mining-may-be-based-on-untrue-facts/">The Arguments Against Crypto Mining May Be Based on Untrue Facts</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto mining debate has raged for years, but it appears the fight is <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/the-bitcoin-mining-debate-is-ignoring-the-people-most-affected-1032346362">taking stronger precedence</a> in recent weeks.</p>
<h2>Is Crypto Mining a Damaging Enterprise? Maybe Not&#8230;</h2>
<p>There have been many reports published, over some time, claiming that crypto mining is putting the planet in harm’s way. They say there are <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-bitcoin-mining-may-require-more-energy-than-180-countries/">several developing nations that</a> do not use the same amount of energy as crypto mining facilities. In addition, there are several arguments that say the pollution caused by these companies is doing a lot of damage to the environment.</p>
<p>New York Assemblywoman Anna Kelles is one of the politicians today that supported her home state’s <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/some-want-the-crypto-moratorium-in-new-york-to-last-longer/">implementation of a crypto moratorium</a>. The law is disallowing all digital currency mining companies from setting up shop in the Empire State granted they do not use renewable energy.</p>
<p>Kelles explained in a recent testimony to Congress the damages that are allegedly caused by crypto mining firms. She has taken issue with the many mining companies that currently call New York home, in particular large ones like Greenidge, and she believes they’re making life difficult for residents. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Facilities like Greenidge also negatively impact aquatic life, killing thousands of fish every year and increasing the risk of harmful algal bloom outbreaks that are toxic for both wildlife and humans.</p></blockquote>
<p>The problem with arguments like these, however, is that they are largely based on information that has either been proven untrue at this stage, or instead stem from things that are not fully verified or even understood.</p>
<p>Steve Griffin – a native of New York’s Yates County and the CEO Of the Finger Lake Economic Development Center – recently stated that many of the arguments being made by individuals like Kelles are completely overblown. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>We know the value and the importance of the lakes&#8217; worth and in our environment or climate. I mean, we&#8217;re a big agricultural community. We know what the value is of the climate. We wouldn&#8217;t want to incentivize anything that was going to clearly negatively impact that.</p></blockquote>
<p>William Hall is the mayor of a town called Dresden, where Greenidge has set up its headquarters. He says that nobody has come out to see the company in action, and thus they cannot say for sure that the company is doing tons of damage to the atmosphere.</p>
<h2>Come and See!</h2>
<p>He also said that he’s tired of the ongoing negative reports that people are creating about crypto mining companies and says he would like to see something positive mentioned occasionally. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>Nobody has ever come to talk to us about it. We need people from somewhere to take an interest, to come talk to the people that are benefitting [from Greenidge’s presence], not the anti-[Greenidge] people that don’t even live here.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-arguments-against-crypto-mining-may-be-based-on-untrue-facts/">The Arguments Against Crypto Mining May Be Based on Untrue Facts</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Faces Accusations that It Mixed Customer and Company Funds</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-faces-accusations-that-it-mixed-customer-and-company-funds/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 17:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CFTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78479</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance – the largest and most popular digital currency exchange – is in hot water again after former insiders alleged that the exchange combined funds from customers with those of the company. What Did Binance Do? In what could be argued as taking a page out of the FTX playbook, Binance is accused of not [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-faces-accusations-that-it-mixed-customer-and-company-funds/">Binance Faces Accusations that It Mixed Customer and Company Funds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance – the largest and most popular digital currency exchange – is in <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/23/crypto-giant-binance-commingled-customer-funds-and-company-revenue-former-insiders-say.html">hot water again after former</a> insiders alleged that the exchange combined funds from customers with those of the company.</p>
<h2>What Did Binance Do?</h2>
<p>In what could be argued as taking a page out of the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/">FTX</a> playbook, Binance is accused of not keeping customer and company funds separate. This would be a breach of U.S. financial rules. Binance has denied any wrongdoing.</p>
<p>One of the insiders claims that the total of the commingled money is in the billions, and that this occurred almost daily through accounts the company had with the now <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-provide-their-thoughts-on-latest-bitcoin-rally/">defunct Silvergate Bank</a>. As it stands, various news platforms such as Reuters have conducted analyses of Binance’s financial transactions, yet they cannot find (at least for now) evidence suggesting that what the insiders say is true.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the claims arouse suspicion and concern in digital currency traders given this is exactly what FTX is accused of having done, and for some time, Binance and FTX <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/">were working together</a>. One needs to wonder if perhaps the latter’s bad business protocols didn’t rub off on the former.</p>
<p>In a statement, SEC commissioner Gary Gensler says many crypto exchanges are guilty of offering securities after they failed to register as broker-dealers, thus ensuring that their clients’ money would be protected and separated from all corporate assets and profit funds. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Their business models tend to be built on taking customer funds, commingling it.</p></blockquote>
<p>Binance spokesperson Brad Jaffe came out to say that Binance has not committed any crimes, nor is it guilty of what it’s being accused of. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>These accounts were not used to accept user deposits. They were used to facilitate user purchases. There was no commingling at any time because these are 100 percent corporate funds.</p></blockquote>
<p>Indeed, the situation is very reminiscent of FTX, a crypto exchange that fell into a heaping pile of bankruptcy and fraud last November. Following the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/">announcement of its bankruptcy</a>, the company’s head honcho Sam Bankman-Fried was <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftxs-disgraced-founder-has-been-arrested/">arrested in the Bahamas</a> after he was accused of commingling his firm’s money with that of customers. He was also charged with using customer funds to pay off loans with his other firm Alameda Research and to invest in luxury Bahamian real estate.</p>
<p>At the present time, Binance is <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cftc-sues-binance-alleging-financial-violations/">also facing scrutiny from</a> the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), which is suing the exchange for allegedly violating the Commodity Exchange Act.</p>
<h2>Further Legal Issues</h2>
<p>CFTC chair Rostin Behnam said:</p>
<blockquote><p>For years, Binance knew they were violating CFTC rules, working actively to both keep the money flowing and avoid compliance. This should be a warning to anyone in the digital asset world that the CFTC will not tolerate willful avoidance of U.S. law.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/binance-faces-accusations-that-it-mixed-customer-and-company-funds/">Binance Faces Accusations that It Mixed Customer and Company Funds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Michael Saylor Hints at Potential Bull Run for BTC</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-hints-at-potential-bull-run-for-btc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 15:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Saylor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroStrategy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78476</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Saylor – the former CEO of software giant MicroStrategy – is predicting big things for bitcoin. Michael Saylor Is Still a BTC Fan Not long ago, Saylor issued a separate interview that clearly showed him to be a full bitcoin maximalist. He insinuated that he would never live it down, nor would he ever [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-hints-at-potential-bull-run-for-btc/">Michael Saylor Hints at Potential Bull Run for BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Michael Saylor – the former CEO of software giant MicroStrategy – is predicting big <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-has-bottomed-and-the-worlds-biggest-cryptocurrency-is-on-a-new-bull-run-microstrategys-michael-saylor-says/ar-AA1bx3Ui">things for bitcoin</a>.</p>
<h2>Michael Saylor Is Still a BTC Fan</h2>
<p>Not long ago, Saylor issued a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-bitcoin-is-the-future/">separate interview</a> that clearly showed him to be a full bitcoin maximalist. He insinuated that he would never live it down, nor would he ever lose hope that the world’s number one digital currency by market capitalization would amount to something. In this more recent interview, he took his ideas and comments to the next level.</p>
<p>He stated that he thinks a regulatory crackdown on digital markets will ultimately work well for the asset. In addition, he said that the next halving – currently scheduled for 2024 – will help bring BTC to a new level of trading and appreciation. Saylor commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think the crypto tokens and crypto securities are going to be regulated, perhaps out of existence. Bitcoin is the most secure network. It&#8217;s the most secure asset. Everything else has got a black cloud hanging over it. You&#8217;re going to see a consistent flow of capital flowing from the rest of the crypto ecosystem [into] bitcoin.</p></blockquote>
<p>Saylor has had a very long (and up and down) history with crypto. First catching the bitcoin bug in late 2020, he began investing his company’s reserves in the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-microstrategy-bitcoin-bet-is-already-paying-off-big-time/">asset in August of that</a> year. When he first started to make profits, additional investments came, and at first, it looked like everything was going his way.</p>
<p>However, in early 2022, when the market began to crash, Saylor continued to invest in BTC even though losses were beginning to pile up, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-buys-more-btc-despite-ongoing-crash/">and this behavior continued</a> despite what has come to be known as one of the worst bear markets in the history of crypto. Before long, he had put his company into billions of dollars and debt, and the world saw him <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-btc-bull-and-microstrategy-chief-executive-steps-down/">resigning from the CEO</a> post he had held for over 30 years.</p>
<p>Despite all the issues he’s endured, Saylor still believes in BTC. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The FASB initiative to adopt fair value accounting is a very auspicious development.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Working Out the Kinks</h2>
<p>He further commented that while the industry is enduring “growing pains,” here and there, this is to be expected from something that’s still very much in an infant-like state. He mentioned that bitcoin and crypto need to go through these hindrances to be developed into lasting, strong tools that investors can truly benefit from. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Nearly all of the bad leverage has been squeezed out. Everyone in the business of shorting bitcoin, rehypothecating bitcoin, loaning bitcoin, they&#8217;ve all [gone] bankrupt. The remaining exchanges where you can short it are under a massive amount of regulatory pressure. I think bitcoin [has] found the bottom. I think the leverage is out of it. I think we&#8217;re on a bull run.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/michael-saylor-hints-at-potential-bull-run-for-btc/">Michael Saylor Hints at Potential Bull Run for BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
