<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 03:04:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>FTX Has, Thus Far, Recovered More Than $7 Billion in Assets</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-has-thus-far-recovered-more-than-7-billion-in-assets/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-has-thus-far-recovered-more-than-7-billion-in-assets/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 17:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[John Ray III]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77933</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At a recent hearing in Delaware, it was announced the now defunct crypto exchange FTX – which fell apart in November of last year – has recovered more than $7.3 billion in assets at the time of writing. This is an increase of more than $800 million since the month of January. FTX Is Trying<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-has-thus-far-recovered-more-than-7-billion-in-assets/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-has-thus-far-recovered-more-than-7-billion-in-assets/">FTX Has, Thus Far, Recovered More Than $7 Billion in Assets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>At a recent hearing in Delaware, it was <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-in/news/world/bankrupt-cryptocurrency-exchange-ftx-has-recovered-7-3-billion-in-cash-liquid-crypto-assets/ar-AA19MwSv" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced the now</a> defunct crypto exchange FTX – which fell apart in November of last year – has recovered more than $7.3 billion in assets at the time of writing. This is an increase of more than $800 million since the month of January.</p>
<h2>FTX Is Trying to Pick Itself Up</h2>
<p>The company is working to garner as many funds as it can to pay off some of its loans as part of its bankruptcy proceedings, which it first entered roughly six months ago. The company is fully down in the dumps and is considering reopening in the future at some point according to FTX attorney Andy Dietderich. In a recent interview, he stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>The situation has stabilized, and the dumpster fire is out.</p></blockquote>
<p>First coming to fruition in the year 2019, FTX required only three years to come out as one of the world’s top five digital currency trading platforms. The company was overseeing billions in trades, and Sam Bankman-Fried – the main executive behind it – was lauded as a genius by many (his net worth was also in the billions towards the end of 2022).</p>
<p>Sadly, this reputation was short-lived as in mid-November, SBF complained of a liquidity crunch on social media. He said he <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>needed fast cash</strong></a> to keep his business in operation, and he eventually turned to his biggest rival Binance about a possible buyout. While things <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-ii-binance-said-it-would-buy-the-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>appeared to be moving</strong></a> in that direction for some time, Binance eventually backed <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>away from the deal</strong></a>, claiming the problems FTX was facing were simply too big for it to handle.</p>
<p>From there, the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>company filed bankruptcy</strong></a> and SBF resigned from his post. Things would have been bad enough if they had stopped there, but the trash meter kept rising. It was later discovered that SBF had utilized customer funds to invest in luxury Bahamian real estate and to pay off loans taken out by his other company Alameda Research. He <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftxs-disgraced-founder-has-been-arrested/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>was eventually arrested</strong></a> and extradited back to the United States. He has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-ftx-exec-sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-fraud/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>entered a not guilty plea</strong></a> and is awaiting trial at his <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-to-await-trial-at-his-parents-house/" data-wpel-link="internal"><strong>parents’ California home</strong></a>.</p>
<h2>Rising Prices Have Helped</h2>
<p>One of the big things that has helped FTX in the long run is how much crypto prices have come along in just the past few weeks. For example, BTC rose to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">a whopping $30K some</a> time ago, a big improvement from where it was at the end of last year (during that time, it was trading in the mid-$16K range).</p>
<p>Should the company decide to open its doors once again for business, the choice will be left up to the new CEO John Ray III, though Dietderich mentioned that it’s going to be a while before the enterprise can come back in such a way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-has-thus-far-recovered-more-than-7-billion-in-assets/">FTX Has, Thus Far, Recovered More Than $7 Billion in Assets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-has-thus-far-recovered-more-than-7-billion-in-assets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Howard Marks: Bitcoin Is an &#8220;Anti-Bank Play&#8221;</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/howard-marks-bitcoin-is-an-anti-bank-play/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/howard-marks-bitcoin-is-an-anti-bank-play/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 15:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Howard Marks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77931</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Howard Marks, a billionaire investor, is confident bitcoin has a lot to offer. Howard Marks Feels Bitcoin Has a Solid Future Over the past several weeks, Marks said bitcoin is becoming a huge power play for those losing faith in the American banking system, which has been in trouble as of late. At press time,<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/howard-marks-bitcoin-is-an-anti-bank-play/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/howard-marks-bitcoin-is-an-anti-bank-play/">Howard Marks: Bitcoin Is an &#8220;Anti-Bank Play&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Howard Marks, a billionaire investor, is confident <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/howard-marks-says-rock-bottom-rates-are-history-bitcoin-has-its-uses-and-ai-won-t-replace-the-best-investors-here-are-his-8-best-quotes-from-a-new-interview/ar-AA19TEfm" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">bitcoin has a lot</a> to offer.</p>
<h2>Howard Marks Feels Bitcoin Has a Solid Future</h2>
<p>Over the past several weeks, Marks said bitcoin is becoming a huge power play for those losing faith in the American banking system, which has <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-provide-their-thoughts-on-latest-bitcoin-rally/" data-wpel-link="internal">been in trouble as</a> of late. At press time, about three banks in the U.S. have completely fallen apart, largely due to the ballooning debt the Fed has taken on.</p>
<p>In a recent interview, Marks commented on bitcoin:</p>
<blockquote><p>There are people who believe that when you have a bank crisis, like we did with Silicon Valley Bank and some of the others, that the weakness of the banks shows the strength of bitcoin. It&#8217;s in many ways an anti-bank play. It does seem that there are good uses for some coins, and bitcoin seems to be the one in the lead so far.</p></blockquote>
<p>He said that up to this point, interest rates have been relatively low, and they’re largely responsible for all the money U.S. investors have made over the past four and a half decades. He also said that while the present rate hikes aren’t likely to last much longer, he does think the days of super-low rates are dead and gone. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>The declining interest rates were responsible for the majority of all the money that&#8217;s been made in the last 45 years… The rates are high today to fight inflation. I don&#8217;t think they&#8217;re going to stay this high, but they&#8217;re through coming down in any major way, and they&#8217;re through being ultra-low.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also stated that the present situation presents opportunities for both investors and the Fed to show some humility, which has been missing from the financial landscape in the U.S. for years. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Humility is a really important thing, especially in the market, which humbles us all. Anybody who doesn&#8217;t allow for humility, in a field where there&#8217;s randomness and uncertainty, and qualitative and subjective things are important, is riding for a fall.</p></blockquote>
<p>In the long run, he doesn’t think the Fed has done a good job in ensuring the cogs of the monetary machine keep running smoothly. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>People used to talk about the factory of the future, which would have one man and one dog, and it was the dog&#8217;s job to keep the man from touching the equipment. It was the man&#8217;s job to feed the dog. I would like to have the Fed keep its hands off the machinery most of the time.</p></blockquote>
<h2>AI Will Present Problems</h2>
<p>In closing, he said advancements in AI could cause problems for a lot of workers in the future, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>AI, just like passive investing and machine learning, even maybe to a greater extent, will knock out everybody who doesn&#8217;t add value.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/howard-marks-bitcoin-is-an-anti-bank-play/">Howard Marks: Bitcoin Is an &#8220;Anti-Bank Play&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/howard-marks-bitcoin-is-an-anti-bank-play/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Report: Texas Is Suffering from too Much BTC Mining</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-texas-is-suffering-from-too-much-btc-mining/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-texas-is-suffering-from-too-much-btc-mining/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 13:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Texas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wood Mackenzie]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77929</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is bitcoin mining running the state of Texas into the ground? Texas Could Wind Up on the Wrong Side Texas declared itself open for bitcoin mining about two years ago. During that time, the nation of China said the practice would be declared illegal, meaning those taking part in crypto mining within its borders had<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-texas-is-suffering-from-too-much-btc-mining/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-texas-is-suffering-from-too-much-btc-mining/">Report: Texas Is Suffering from too Much BTC Mining</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is bitcoin mining <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/voracious-bitcoin-mining-messing-texans-090846053.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">running the state</a> of Texas into the ground?</p>
<h2>Texas Could Wind Up on the Wrong Side</h2>
<p>Texas declared itself open for bitcoin mining about two years ago. During that time, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-crypto-mining-clampdown-in-china-is-not-over/" data-wpel-link="internal">the nation of China</a> said the practice would be declared illegal, meaning those taking part in crypto mining within its borders had to find a new place to set up shop, and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-is-still-a-major-crypto-mining-hub/" data-wpel-link="internal">the Lone Star State seemed</a> like a good area given it had vast open land and cheap electricity.</p>
<p>However, according to a new report by the Electric Reliability Council of Texas (ERCOT), things are beginning to move in a negative direction. The document states:</p>
<blockquote><p>Prospective crypto mining businesses have requested to put approximately 33,000 more megawatts in the ERCOT interconnection queue over the next few years (enough to power the whole state of Florida)… A single bitcoin transaction used nearly 1,452 kilowatt-hours (kWh) of electricity, equal to the power consumption of an average U.S. household for nearly 50 days.</p></blockquote>
<p>A separate news outlet says:</p>
<blockquote><p>Their massive energy consumption combined with their ability to shut off almost instantly allows some companies to save money and make money by deftly pulling the levers of U.S. power markets… In practice, they rarely are asked to shut down. Several of the companies are being paid through these agreements [most] of the time they operate. Most years, they are asked to turn off for only a few hours, at which point they are paid even more.</p></blockquote>
<p>Not long ago, it was reported that <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/texas-paid-crypto-mining-firm-bit-deer-a-lot-of-money-to-shut-its-machines-off/" data-wpel-link="internal">Texas paid a specific bitcoin</a> mining company to shut down its systems during a time of heavy winter storms. Overall, that company made millions of dollars doing nothing over the course of several weeks. ERCOT says it’s not looking to discriminate against the types of companies looking to set up in Texas, nor does it have problems with firms looking to offer specific kinds of services. It said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We want to be able to serve any business that wants to do business in Texas, and that includes crypto miners.</p></blockquote>
<p>Ed Hirs – a University of Houston energy economist – believes that a lot of these excessive electricity practices seen in the mining industry in Texas are going to fall onto the shoulders of everyday citizens. He mentioned in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>Ironically, when people are paying the most for their power, or losing it altogether, the miners are making money selling energy back to Texans at rates 100 times what they paid.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Ordinary Citizens Bearing the Burden?</h2>
<p>A study performed by research firm Wood Mackenzie seconds this, stating:</p>
<blockquote><p>Increased demand has caused electric bills for power customers to rise nearly five percent, or $1.8 billion per year. In West Texas, where several bitcoin mines have settled, bills have increased by nearly nine percent.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-texas-is-suffering-from-too-much-btc-mining/">Report: Texas Is Suffering from too Much BTC Mining</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-texas-is-suffering-from-too-much-btc-mining/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Risk of Fresh Drop to $105</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-105-2/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-105-2/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 03:08:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78506</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline below the $115 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below the $115 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $115 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-105-2/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-105-2/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Risk of Fresh Drop to $105</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline below the $115 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below the $115 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $115 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it stays below the $115 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin cash price is declining below the $115s zone against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-another-increase-to-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. BCH/USD could extend losses if there is a close below $110.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin cash price struggled to gain pace for a move above the $117 and $118 resistance levels. BCH formed a high near $117.41 and started a fresh decline.</p>
<p>There was a clear move below the $116.00 and $115.00 support levels. The pair even declined below the $112 support. It tested the $110 zone. A low is formed near $109.30 and the price is now consolidating losses. It is now trading above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $117.41 swing high to the $109.30 low.</p>
<p>Besides, it is trading below the $115 zone and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-105/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. Immediate resistance is near the $113.50 level.</p>
<p>The 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $117.41 swing high to the $109.30 low is also near the $113.50 level. The next key resistance is near $115 and the trend line. Any more gains above $115 could set the pace for a move toward the $118 level.</p>
<p>If there is a move above the $118 resistance, the price could rise toward the $122 zone. If not, the price might continue lower below $111.</p>
<p>Immediate support on the downside is near the $110 zone. The next major support is near the $105 level, below which the bears might aim for $100.</p>
<div id="attachment_78507" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Bitcoin-Cash-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78507" class="size-full wp-image-78507" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Bitcoin-Cash-3.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash Price " width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78507" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Cash Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BCHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Bitcoin cash price is now trading below the $115 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $115 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for BCH/USD is losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BCH/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $110 and $105.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $115 and $118.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-105-2/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Risk of Fresh Drop to $105</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-risk-of-fresh-drop-to-105-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Small Nation of Bhutan Has Been Hoarding a Lot of Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-small-nation-of-bhutan-has-been-hoarding-a-lot-of-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-small-nation-of-bhutan-has-been-hoarding-a-lot-of-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 17:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bhutan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Duncan Bonfield]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77920</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bhutan is a small country lodged between India, Nepal, and China on the continent of Asia. Its biggest claims to fame are its architecture, its vast open landscapes… and the big crypto stash that the nation has allegedly been hiding from the world all this time. Bhutan Has Been Hiding a Lot of Crypto Bhutan<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-small-nation-of-bhutan-has-been-hoarding-a-lot-of-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-small-nation-of-bhutan-has-been-hoarding-a-lot-of-crypto/">The Small Nation of Bhutan Has Been Hoarding a Lot of Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bhutan is a small country lodged between India, Nepal, and China on the continent of Asia. Its biggest claims to fame are its architecture, its vast open landscapes… and the big crypto stash that the nation has <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/iainmartin/2023/04/15/the-tiny-kingdom-of-bhutan-secretly-held-millions-of-dollars-in-cryptocurrency/?sh=275021ab7f1d" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">allegedly been hiding from</a> the world all this time.</p>
<h2>Bhutan Has Been Hiding a Lot of Crypto</h2>
<p>Bhutan is a miniscule and obscure nation. It also doesn’t appear to have all the technological advancements of its neighbors. The region only began supporting cell phone usage about 20 years ago, and in many areas, traffic lights are still absent or in the process of being put up. One wouldn’t assume that a country like Bhutan would be all that into crypto or the technology that supports it, but new court documents suggest otherwise.</p>
<p>These papers revealed that the sovereign investment arm of Bhutan was a big customer of both Block Fi and Celsius, two crypto lending platforms that <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-crypto-in-the-age-of-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">went bust in 2022</a> (arguably the most bearish year on record for the crypto industry). The losses of the nation were never disclosed up until now. It is estimated that this investment division is worth just shy of $3 billion, meaning the country has more money stashed away than it’s been letting on all this time.</p>
<p>The investment firm is known as Druk Holding &amp; Investments. It’s believed the institution has been accumulating crypto since 2022, which is interesting because while the country was clearly able to gather millions of dollars in digital currency units over the course of a single year, it clearly chose the worst time to do so given how badly everything crashed during that time.</p>
<p>Right now, Druk says it’s sworn to secrecy about the matter of how much it’s lost, though it did say it engaged in a court battle with Block Fi that has since been settled. It’s not known how the money accumulated nor what the company was planning to do with all the funds. Druk’s CEO Ujjwal Deep Dahal commented in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>We do not have any comments as the matter with Block Fi has been settled. We are not able to comment due to confidentiality.</p></blockquote>
<p>Duncan Bonfield – chief executive of the International Forum of Sovereign Wealth Funds – also threw his two cents into the mix, stating:</p>
<blockquote><p>We have seen no real interest in cryptocurrency as an asset class, and we do not believe any of our members have an allocation to crypto in their portfolios.</p></blockquote>
<h2>You Couldn&#8217;t Even Visit</h2>
<p>Bhutan is a relative newcomer to “modern society” and visitors in many ways. The nation could not be traveled to until 1974, and that only occurred as a means of building its economy through tourism.</p>
<p>Prior to that, the nation had fallen victim to a pandemic that prohibited all foreigners from entering.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-small-nation-of-bhutan-has-been-hoarding-a-lot-of-crypto/">The Small Nation of Bhutan Has Been Hoarding a Lot of Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-small-nation-of-bhutan-has-been-hoarding-a-lot-of-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Anthony Scaramucci is Still a Big Bitcoin Fan</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/anthony-scaramucci-is-still-a-big-bitcoin-fan/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/anthony-scaramucci-is-still-a-big-bitcoin-fan/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 15:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthony Scaramucci]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jamie dimon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77917</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Anthony Scaramucci of Skybridge Capital says he’s never been more bullish on bitcoin as he is now. Scaramucci Has Good Reason to Love BTC In many ways, his words make sense, and Scaramucci has a big, giant reason to be bullish. After all, the world’s number one digital currency by market cap recently hit $30K<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/anthony-scaramucci-is-still-a-big-bitcoin-fan/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/anthony-scaramucci-is-still-a-big-bitcoin-fan/">Anthony Scaramucci is Still a Big Bitcoin Fan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Anthony Scaramucci of Skybridge Capital says <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/anthony-scaramucci-says-he-is-more-bullish-on-bitcoin-now-than-ever-before-incredibly-sturdy-bizarrely-anti-fragile-asset-class/ar-AA19UgZq" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">he’s never been more</a> bullish on bitcoin as he is now.</p>
<h2>Scaramucci Has Good Reason to Love BTC</h2>
<p>In many ways, his words make sense, and Scaramucci has a big, giant reason to be bullish. After all, the world’s number one digital currency by market cap <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-rose-to-30k-in-mid-april-analysts-discuss-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">recently hit $30K for</a> the first time in about 11 months, and 2023 appears to be directing bitcoin on a healing path that’s likely to reverse all the damage done during the previous year, which was arguably the worst on record for BTC.</p>
<p>In a recent discussion, Scaramucci commented that bitcoin has been enduring some hardcore boom-bust cycles in which it goes up quite high then crashes down very low. He says this all coincides with the halving process, and how interesting (and coincidental, in many ways) bitcoin is going to endure another halving event next year in 2024.</p>
<p>He also says that the mainstream media has been giving bitcoin and crypto a lot more attention as of late. He commented that this is likely leading to a lot of the rising and falling we’re seeing in the BTC cycles. In addition, he says bitcoin wallets have never been available on such a large scale.</p>
<p>This, in turn, has led to a bit of an issue in that many fraud schemes have emerged in recent months and years, something that he feels has brought down the reputation and the legitimacy of the space. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>What happened almost right on time is the intersection of fraud and over-leverage, which always happens in the age of new technology… The technology that we have now can create a bee swarm.</p></blockquote>
<p>He says that there have been many elements leading up to the present anti-crypto stance taken by Gary Gensler, who heads the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Among them are the many crypto companies collapsing in America such as <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/celsius-network-is-next-crypto-company-to-file-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">Celsius</a>, and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/block-fi-is-the-latest-crypto-company-to-go-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">Block Fi</a>.</p>
<p>Despite this, however, he’s convinced bitcoin is an “incredibly sturdy” and “anti-fragile asset class,” and he believes the currency is going to end the year in the $40,000 or $50,000 price range.</p>
<h2>Some Things Remain in the Way</h2>
<p>He further said that there are individuals out there that are going to do everything they can to bring bitcoin down. Among them are people like Charlie Munger – Warren Buffett’s right hand man – and Jamie Dimon, who’s the head of JPMorgan, arguably one of the biggest financial institutions in the world. Speaking about the latter, Scaramucci said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Jamie Dimon is probably the smartest person in financial services history since the original J.P. Morgan, and there&#8217;s no way if you got him unplugged and you got him with truth serum in him that he would say to you that bitcoin is a decentralized bedrock.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/anthony-scaramucci-is-still-a-big-bitcoin-fan/">Anthony Scaramucci is Still a Big Bitcoin Fan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/anthony-scaramucci-is-still-a-big-bitcoin-fan/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New York Town of Brasher Implements Crypto Moratorium</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-town-of-brasher-implements-crypto-moratorium/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-town-of-brasher-implements-crypto-moratorium/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 13:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brasher]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New York]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77914</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Right when we thought New York was going to become a more crypto-friendly state, the region of Brasher announced it is implementing a six-month cryptocurrency moratorium on all digital currency mining and related activities. Brasher Ain&#8217;t Too Keen on Crypto Mining The moratorium is set to go into effect on April 30 and will expire<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-town-of-brasher-implements-crypto-moratorium/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-town-of-brasher-implements-crypto-moratorium/">New York Town of Brasher Implements Crypto Moratorium</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Right when we thought New York was going to become a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-to-allow-crypto-mining-firm-block-fusion-to-set-up-shop/" data-wpel-link="internal">more crypto-friendly state</a>, the region of Brasher announced it is implementing a six-month cryptocurrency moratorium <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/brasher-town-board-places-six-221900643.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">on all digital currency</a> mining and related activities.</p>
<h2>Brasher Ain&#8217;t Too Keen on Crypto Mining</h2>
<p>The moratorium is set to go into effect on April 30 and will expire on October 31 unless it gets renewed by city council members. Representatives of the town of Brasher issued the following statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>The town board believes that such a moratorium will protect the public interest and welfare of the residents of the town until such comprehensive regulations are adopted. There are currently no regulations regulating cryptocurrency mining operations except the current moratorium within the town.</p></blockquote>
<p>Town Supervisor Mark A. Peets said Brasher currently doesn’t house any specific digital currency companies, though he mentioned they don’t want to let anyone in without proper regulation in place. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We&#8217;re not allowing cryptocurrency until we have regulations. Before we allow people to go into that business, we want to be able to come up with some rules and regulations.</p></blockquote>
<p>Right now, he believes there’s too much concern surrounding the amount of electricity that such operations often require. For the past several years, we <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/report-bitcoin-mining-may-require-more-energy-than-180-countries/" data-wpel-link="internal">have seen many reports</a> come out saying that bitcoin and crypto mining often uses more energy than third-world countries, and that this is putting Mother Earth on a deadly path. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>They&#8217;d be using a whole lot of electricity. It&#8217;s going to put a burden on the electric system that we are now supposed to use for other things. So, until we can regulate it properly in the town of Brasher through our zoning laws, we&#8217;re just not going to allow people to come because there&#8217;s a section in the town of Brasher where folks get their electricity from the Massena Electric Department, which is a cheap rate… In the MED section of the town, we want to have some regulations put in place before we allow something like that to happen within the town.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also said that while one company (which is unnamed at the time of writing) inquired about setting up shop within the region’s borders, he’s not even sure if Brasher has the kind of resources this enterprise is looking for. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>It&#8217;s not set up for what they want. They want three-phase power, and there is no three-phase power in that area. So, they can&#8217;t just put something in without us being able to look at our zoning laws before we even allow something.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Too Many Environmental Issues?</h2>
<p>Regarding further environmental impacts, Peets said:</p>
<blockquote><p>These devices pull off a lot of heat, so much that they would need air conditioning, or they would vent it out into the atmosphere.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-town-of-brasher-implements-crypto-moratorium/">New York Town of Brasher Implements Crypto Moratorium</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-town-of-brasher-implements-crypto-moratorium/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EOS Price Analysis: Bears In Control Below $0.90</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bears-in-control-below-0-90/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bears-in-control-below-0-90/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 05:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EOS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78500</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>EOS price started a fresh decline below the $0.880 level against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $0.850 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.851 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bears-in-control-below-0-90/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bears-in-control-below-0-90/">EOS Price Analysis: Bears In Control Below $0.90</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>EOS price started a fresh decline below the $0.880 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $0.850 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.851 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to decline if it stays below the $0.850 and $0.875 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>EOS price is struggling below $0.90 against the US Dollar, unlike <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-another-increase-to-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. The price might attempt to recover if there is a clear move above $0.875.</em></p>
<h2>EOS Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, EOS price saw a steady decline from the $0.912 resistance against the US Dollar. The price traded below the $0.90 and $0.88 levels to move into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>The decline gained pace below the $0.850 level. It even spiked below $0.820. A low is formed near $0.817 and the price is now consolidating losses. EOS is trading well below $0.850 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-signs-of-recovery-toward-1-0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $0.840 level. It is near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.9118 swing high to the $0.8170 low. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.851 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair.</p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $0.875 level or the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.9118 swing high to the $0.8170 low.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $0.875 level could start a steady increase toward the $0.90 level. The next major resistance might be $0.912. Any more gains might send the price toward the $1.00 level. On the downside, immediate support is near $0.820.</p>
<p>The next key support is near the $0.812 level. If there is a downside break below the $0.812 support, the price could test the $0.800 support in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_78501" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/EOS-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78501" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78501" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/EOS-3.png" alt="EOS Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78501" class="wp-caption-text">EOS Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/EOSUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, EOS price is now trading below the $0.850 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to decline if it stays below the $0.850 and $0.875 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for EOS/USD is gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $0.820 and $0.800.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $0.850 and $0.875.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bears-in-control-below-0-90/">EOS Price Analysis: Bears In Control Below $0.90</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bears-in-control-below-0-90/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Might Protect $80</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-might-protect-80/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-might-protect-80/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 03:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78497</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin started a downside correction from the $95 zone against the US Dollar. LTC price is now trading below $90 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $85 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-might-protect-80/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-might-protect-80/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Might Protect $80</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Litecoin started a downside correction from the $95 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>LTC price is now trading below $90 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $85 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair remains supported for a fresh increase unless there is a clear move below $80.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Litecoin price is correcting gains from $95 against the US Dollar, similar to bitcoin. LTC price could resume its increase if it remains well supported above the $80 level.</em></p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, there was a decent increase in <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-eyes-another-increase-to-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-aims-fresh-increase-above-1850/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Ethereum</a>, Ripple, and Litecoin against the US Dollar. Earlier, LTC formed a base above the $80 level and started a fresh increase.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above the $85 and $90 resistance levels. The price even climbed above the $92 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). However, the bears were active near the $95 zone. A high was formed near $95.00 and the price started a downside correction.</p>
<p>There was a move below the $90 level. The price traded below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $75.32 swing low to the $95.00 high. Besides, there was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $85 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>It is now trading below $90 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $85 level.</p>
<p>The next major resistance sits near the $90 level. A clear move above the $90 level could pump the price toward the $95 level. Any more gains might call for a test of $100. Immediate support is near the $82.80 level or the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $75.32 swing low to the $95.00 high.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $80 zone. A downside break below the $80 support might start a strong decline.</p>
<div id="attachment_78498" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Litecoin-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78498" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78498" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Litecoin-3.png" alt="Litecoin (LTC) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78498" class="wp-caption-text">Litecoin (LTC) Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Litecoin price is trading below $90 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price remains supported for a fresh increase unless there is a clear move below $80.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LTC/USD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $82.80 and $80.00</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $85 and $90.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-might-protect-80/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Might Protect $80</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-might-protect-80/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
