<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 03:24:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Bears Aim Fresh Drop To $100</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bears-aim-fresh-drop-to-100/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bears-aim-fresh-drop-to-100/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 03:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78304</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline below the $120 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below the $120 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a short-term rising channel forming with support at $112.80 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bears-aim-fresh-drop-to-100/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bears-aim-fresh-drop-to-100/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Bears Aim Fresh Drop To $100</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin cash price started a fresh decline below the $120 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below the $120 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a short-term rising channel forming with support at $112.80 on the 4-hour chart of the BCH/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it stays below the $118 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin cash price is declining below the $120 zone against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-29k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. BCH/USD could extend losses if there is a close below $110.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin cash price struggled to gain pace for a move above the $124 and $124 resistance levels. BCH formed a high near $123.94 and started a fresh decline.</p>
<p>There was a clear move below the $122.00 and $120.00 support levels. The pair even declined below the $115 support. It tested the $110 level. A low is formed near $110.16 and the price is now consolidating losses. It is now trading near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $123.94 swing high to the $110.16 low.</p>
<p>Besides, it is trading below the $120 zone and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-key-breakout-resistance-sits-at-120/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. Immediate resistance is near the $117.00 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>The 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $123.94 swing high to the $110.16 low is also near $117. The next key resistance is near $120. Any more gains above $117 and $120 could set the pace for a move toward the $125 level.</p>
<p>If there is a move above the $125 resistance, the price could rise toward the $132 zone. If not, the price might continue lower below $110. Immediate support on the downside is near the $108 zone. The next major support is near the $100 level, below which the bears might aim for $92.</p>
<div id="attachment_78305" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Bitcoin-Cash-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78305" class="size-full wp-image-78305" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Bitcoin-Cash-1.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78305" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Cash Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BCHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Bitcoin cash price is now trading below the $118 zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $118 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for BCH/USD is gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BCH/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $110 and $108.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $118 and $120.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bears-aim-fresh-drop-to-100/">Bitcoin Cash Analysis: Bears Aim Fresh Drop To $100</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-cash-analysis-bears-aim-fresh-drop-to-100/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FUNToken listed on a top tier exchange, MEXC</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/funtoken-listed-on-a-top-tier-exchange-mexc/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/funtoken-listed-on-a-top-tier-exchange-mexc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 18:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78296</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FUNToken is excited to announce that it has been listed on MEXC, a top-tier cryptocurrency exchange. This is a significant milestone for FUNToken, giving users more options to trade and buy FUN on different exchanges. The FUN/USDT trading pair is available on MEXC as of May 9th, providing users with a fast, secure, and reliable<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/funtoken-listed-on-a-top-tier-exchange-mexc/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/funtoken-listed-on-a-top-tier-exchange-mexc/">FUNToken listed on a top tier exchange, MEXC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FUNToken is excited to announce that it has been listed on MEXC, a top-tier cryptocurrency exchange. This is a significant milestone for FUNToken, giving users more options to trade and buy FUN on different exchanges.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.mexc.com/exchange/FUN_USDT" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">FUN/USDT</a> trading pair is available on MEXC as of May 9th, providing users with a fast, secure, and reliable platform to trade FUN. The listing on MEXC is an important step for FUNToken, as it enables users to access <a href="https://funtoken.io/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">FUNToken</a> more easily and efficiently.</p>
<p>The listing on MEXC is part of FUNToken&#8217;s strategic plan to expand its presence and make its token more accessible to users worldwide. FUNToken is committed to providing its users with the best trading experience, and MEXC is one of the most trusted and reliable exchanges in the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p>MEXC is known for its user-friendly interface, high liquidity, and advanced trading features. With over 5 million registered users, MEXC is one of the top 10 cryptocurrency exchanges in the world, providing a wide range of trading pairs and a secure trading environment.</p>
<p>In conclusion, FUNToken&#8217;s listing on MEXC is a significant step, providing users with more options to trade and buy FUN on different exchanges. By trading FUNToken on multiple top-tier exchanges now, users can take advantage of the various features offered by each exchange and enhance their overall trading experience. So, start trading FUNToken on exchanges like  MEXC, Binance, Gate.io, XT.com, LAToken, Uniswap, and BitYard.</p>
<p><strong>About FUNToken</strong></p>
<p>With over 350,000 investors and staking users worldwide and counting, FUN Token is the leading iGaming token globally. Based on the Ethereum blockchain, it was created as a fast, transparent, and genuinely fair transactional solution for iGaming ecosystems and players. Harnessing the power of blockchain technology, it creates &#8220;trustless&#8221; gaming ecosystems that users can rely on and operators can implement seamlessly.</p>
<p>FUN Token is backed by the best in the business – FreeBitco.in is committed to fueling FUN Token’s efforts of making non-custodial gaming an industry standard.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/funtoken-listed-on-a-top-tier-exchange-mexc/">FUNToken listed on a top tier exchange, MEXC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/funtoken-listed-on-a-top-tier-exchange-mexc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eurexcoin.com Seeks to Become the Safest Crypto Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eurexcoin-com-seeks-to-become-the-safest-crypto-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eurexcoin-com-seeks-to-become-the-safest-crypto-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 17:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Eurexcoin.com]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77747</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Eurexcoin.com, a leading digital currency trading platform on the European continent, just announced that it’s going to be enhancing its security and protection methods tenfold. Eurexcoin.com Seeks to Enhance Its Security The crypto space is wrought with fraud and illicit attacks carried out on crypto exchanges. Often, it’s either the exchanges themselves losing tons of<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eurexcoin-com-seeks-to-become-the-safest-crypto-exchange/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eurexcoin-com-seeks-to-become-the-safest-crypto-exchange/">Eurexcoin.com Seeks to Become the Safest Crypto Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Eurexcoin.com, a leading digital currency trading platform on the European continent, just announced that it’s going to be <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/pressreleases/23/04/ab31621305/eurexcoin-com-announces-high-end-security-measures-and-innovative-trading-protocol-for-its-crypto" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">enhancing its security and</a> protection methods tenfold.</p>
<h2>Eurexcoin.com Seeks to Enhance Its Security</h2>
<p>The crypto space is wrought with fraud and illicit attacks carried out on crypto exchanges. Often, it’s either the exchanges themselves losing tons of reserve money, or it’s individual customers that wake up one day to see their wallets have been drained and are empty. Either situation is ugly and rough to contend with, and many companies are working hard to make sure these kinds of attacks end.</p>
<p>There are also plenty of concerns out there regarding crypto exchanges following the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">collapse of FTX</a> in November. The protection of individual customer information was practically thrown out the window when the company went under, and the funds of individual traders were utilized (allegedly) to purchase luxury Bahamian real estate and pay off loans for an entirely separate firm.</p>
<p>Up to that point, such a degree of fraud was virtually unprecedented in the crypto arena, and it wasn’t long before FTX’s reputation as a leading trading platform transformed into one of filth and criminality.</p>
<p>John Smith – the CEO of Eurexcoin.com – explained in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>We understand that security is a top concern for our customers, and we take this responsibility very seriously. We have invested heavily in our security infrastructure to ensure that our customers can trade with peace of mind. We are constantly looking for ways to improve our platform and provide a better trading experience for our users. Our new trading protocol is the result of extensive research and development, and we are confident that it will be a game-changer in the cryptocurrency industry.</p></blockquote>
<p>Among the tools the company will be utilizing to ensure its customers remain safe are multi-factor authentication, cold storage, and advanced crypto algorithms. In addition, Eurexcoin.com will also regularly engage in security audits to ensure its systems are never subjected to any loopholes or vulnerabilities.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the enterprise is implementing a new innovative trading protocol designed to boost the speed of trades and limit opportunities for price manipulation down the line. The company explained in a separate statement that it’s consistently looking to evolve and meet the needs of all its users.</p>
<h2>Should All Exchanges Become Decentralized?</h2>
<p>While this certainly sounds positive, there’s <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/should-every-crypto-exchange-become-decentralized-analysts-weigh-in/" data-wpel-link="internal">still a prevalent argument</a> making its way through the crypto space following incidents like FTX. Many are wondering if all exchanges should enter the defi realm and thus give traders full access and control of their digital tokens. Crypto journalist Tracy Wang said:</p>
<blockquote><p>A company like FTX was supposed to hold your assets, but they ended up lending them out. This is like taking power back and being… in charge of your own money.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eurexcoin-com-seeks-to-become-the-safest-crypto-exchange/">Eurexcoin.com Seeks to Become the Safest Crypto Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eurexcoin-com-seeks-to-become-the-safest-crypto-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Look at Crypto Regulation Ideas Across the Globe</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/a-look-at-crypto-regulation-ideas-across-the-globe/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/a-look-at-crypto-regulation-ideas-across-the-globe/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 15:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christopher Mitchell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Do Kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77745</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How does crypto regulation work around the world? It appears to be different in every country, and the goal is to try and find the best approaches and take the best points from each to form a solid roadmap for traders everywhere. Crypto Regulation Differs Depending on the Country There has been a huge call<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/a-look-at-crypto-regulation-ideas-across-the-globe/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/a-look-at-crypto-regulation-ideas-across-the-globe/">A Look at Crypto Regulation Ideas Across the Globe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How does crypto regulation work around the world? It appears <a href="https://www.forbes.com/advisor/investing/cryptocurrency/cryptocurrency-regulations-around-the-world/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">to be different in every country</a>, and the goal is to try and find the best approaches and take the best points from each to form a solid roadmap for traders everywhere.</p>
<h2>Crypto Regulation Differs Depending on the Country</h2>
<p>There has been a huge call for crypto regulation since the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">collapse of FTX</a> last November. In the U.S., agencies like the Federal Reserve and the Office of the Comptrollers of the Currency (OCC) released a joint statement explaining that crypto trading is extremely risky, and thus taking part in the arena goes against “sound banking practices.” The statement reads:</p>
<blockquote><p>Issuing or holding as principal crypto-assets that are issued, stored, or transferred on an open, public and/or decentralized network or similar, is highly likely to be inconsistent with safe and sound banking practices.</p></blockquote>
<p>Christopher Mitchell – founder and principal of Keala Advisors – says the U.S. has it all wrong when it comes to crypto regulation. He commented that the big problem is that while crypto is part of a whole new technology trend, officials want to regulate it like it’s part of the standard financial industry. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The government wants to treat cryptocurrencies as traditional securities while also working to restrict their ability to be treated and function within financial markets like traditional securities.</p></blockquote>
<p>UK prime minister Rishi Sunak, by contrast, wants his country to become a huge crypto haven in the coming years. He recently stated that he’d like to regulate stable coins so they can become valid methods of payment in the future:</p>
<blockquote><p>It’s my ambition to make the U.K. a global hub for crypto asset technology, and the measures we’ve outlined today will help to ensure firms can invest, innovate, and scale up in this country.</p></blockquote>
<p>Discussing crypto regulation in Brazil, Bruno Sousa – head of U.S. and new markets at Hashdex – said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Brazil has been a frontrunner in crypto policy. The Real Digital project, led by the Brazilian Central Bank, is a very interesting project in terms of regulation because it is flexible in terms of adopting the new technology but maintaining current regulation for deposits… and making the large banks the ones who issue the stablecoins instead of bypassing the banks.</p></blockquote>
<h2>We Don&#8217;t Want People Like Do Kwon in the Mix</h2>
<p>He also stated that in general terms, crypto regulation is far more needed today, and he used the current situation <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-executive-do-kwon-arrested-in-montenegro/" data-wpel-link="internal">surrounding Do Kwon</a> and his recent arrest as the reason why. He says that men like Kwon are running rampant throughout the space, and regulation will have a hand in stopping this:</p>
<blockquote><p>Strong regulations are not only important, but necessary to foster the industry’s growth. From the investor’s standpoint, having access to this new asset class through regulated entities and investment funds helps mitigate the risks.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/a-look-at-crypto-regulation-ideas-across-the-globe/">A Look at Crypto Regulation Ideas Across the Globe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/a-look-at-crypto-regulation-ideas-across-the-globe/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Scammers Are Pretending to Be Part of Best Buy&#8217;s Geek Squad</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-scammers-are-pretending-to-be-part-of-best-buys-geek-squad/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-scammers-are-pretending-to-be-part-of-best-buys-geek-squad/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 13:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto scammer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geek Squad]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Woodbury]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77743</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto scammers have a new way of getting money out of their intended victims. They are now pretending to be members of Best Buy’s infamous Geek Squad team. You know… The alleged computer geniuses that know everything about fixing your laptop or desktop. Is That the Real Geek Squad Contacting You? This was recently witnessed<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-scammers-are-pretending-to-be-part-of-best-buys-geek-squad/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-scammers-are-pretending-to-be-part-of-best-buys-geek-squad/">Crypto Scammers Are Pretending to Be Part of Best Buy&#8217;s Geek Squad</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/scam/" data-wpel-link="internal">scammers</a> have a new way of <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/once-it-s-gone-there-s-no-getting-it-back-scammers-sending-victims-to-cryptocurrency-atms/ar-AA19nsAU" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">getting money out of their</a> intended victims. They are now pretending to be members of Best Buy’s infamous Geek Squad team. You know… The alleged computer geniuses that know everything about fixing your laptop or desktop.</p>
<h2>Is That the <em>Real</em> Geek Squad Contacting You?</h2>
<p>This was recently witnessed in a recent situation involving a woman living in Woodbury. In her inbox on Valentine’s Day last year, she received an email from Geek Squad saying her account would be renewed, and that she was going to be charged $1,145. Not thinking much of the email (she had a legitimate Geek Squad account), she ignored it at first, though she took note of the later verbiage that said if she was interested in cancelling, she had roughly 48 hours to do so.</p>
<p>The woman – who remains unnamed at the time of writing – stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Years ago, we had a service contract with Geek Squad, so I didn’t think much about it. The email said if I didn’t want to renew, I had 48 hours to cancel it, but that 48-hour period had already passed.</p></blockquote>
<p>While details are scarce at this time, she called the phone number listed on what turned out to be a fake invoice and said she wanted to end her account. The man on the other side of the call said he could take care of everything for her, though the situation escalated, and on many occasions, she was required to travel to a nearby bitcoin ATM to make transfers of anywhere between $7,000 and $8,000. Overall, the 78-year-old victim was cheated out of $70,000. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>By the end, they had me so wrapped up and so scared and intimidated that I probably would have sold my house. It’s just crazy.</p></blockquote>
<p>Lynn Lawrence – a Woodbury police detective – commented on the situation, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>It’s sad, but there’s not much we can do. The money is gone within seconds, and once it’s gone, there’s no getting it back… It’s much different if we have a victim who has transferred money from one bank account to another bank account. Sometimes we can intercept those funds with the receiving bank and stop that kind of stuff, but with bitcoin, we don’t have those abilities, so really prevention and education are our only options at this point.</p></blockquote>
<h2>No Way to Track Things</h2>
<p>Marty Fleischhacker – senior financial fraud ombudsman for the Minnesota Department of Commerce – also threw his two cents into the mix, mentioning:</p>
<blockquote><p>The thing about cryptocurrency is you really can’t trace it, so you have no real ability to find the perpetrators at any point by following the money trail, so how do you stop it? That’s the problem… The old saying used to be, ‘Trust, but verify.’ Now it’s, ‘Verify before you trust.’</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-scammers-are-pretending-to-be-part-of-best-buys-geek-squad/">Crypto Scammers Are Pretending to Be Part of Best Buy&#8217;s Geek Squad</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/crypto-scammers-are-pretending-to-be-part-of-best-buys-geek-squad/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>TABOO Gains Bullish Momentum With $10M Funding at $250M Valuation</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/taboo-gains-bullish-momentum-with-10m-funding-at-250m-valuation/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/taboo-gains-bullish-momentum-with-10m-funding-at-250m-valuation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 08:07:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78289</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TABOO recently secured $10 million in funding at a valuation of $250 million. TABOO token is now available for trading on major exchanges, including Binance and Coinbase. Recently, the TABOO token has been gaining attention from investors and traders as it has been making bold moves in the cryptocurrency market, where its price has increased<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/taboo-gains-bullish-momentum-with-10m-funding-at-250m-valuation/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/taboo-gains-bullish-momentum-with-10m-funding-at-250m-valuation/">TABOO Gains Bullish Momentum With $10M Funding at $250M Valuation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>TABOO recently secured $10 million in funding at a valuation of $250 million.</li>
<li>TABOO token is now available for trading on major exchanges, including Binance and Coinbase.</li>
</ul>
<p>Recently, the <a href="https://taboo.io/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">TABOO</a> token has been gaining attention from investors and traders as it has been making bold moves in the cryptocurrency market, where its price has increased steadily.</p>
<p>TABOO has completed its latest investment, securing $10 million at a valuation of $250 million. Leading the investment is a private family office helmed by a former senior executive from J.P. Morgan. The raised funds will drive growth, enhance product offerings, bolster security measures, strengthen marketing efforts, and pursue potential acquisitions.</p>
<h2>TABOO Bullish Q1 2023</h2>
<p>According to data obtained from <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/converter/taboo/usd" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">Coinbase</a>, the exchange rate of TABOO has experienced a noteworthy increase of 18.62% over the past 7 days. The project is expected to list in top tier centralized exchanges.</p>
<p>TABOO&#8217;s CEO, James, expressed his excitement for the investment, stating that it would enable the platform to take TABOO to the next level. He added that blockchain and NFTs were the future of adult entertainment and media platform, and TABOO was determined to lead the way.</p>
<p>Furthermore, TABOO’s latest investment of $10 million at a $250 million valuation marks a significant milestone for the platform. With this new funding, TABOO is well-positioned to continue its rapid expansion and establish itself as a key player in the adult entertainment industry.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/taboo-gains-bullish-momentum-with-10m-funding-at-250m-valuation/">TABOO Gains Bullish Momentum With $10M Funding at $250M Valuation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/taboo-gains-bullish-momentum-with-10m-funding-at-250m-valuation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EOS Price Analysis: More Losses Seem Likely Below $0.92</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-more-losses-seem-likely-below-0-92/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-more-losses-seem-likely-below-0-92/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 05:08:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EOS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78286</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>EOS price started a fresh decline below the $1.00 level against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $1.00 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.920 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-more-losses-seem-likely-below-0-92/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-more-losses-seem-likely-below-0-92/">EOS Price Analysis: More Losses Seem Likely Below $0.92</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>EOS price started a fresh decline below the $1.00 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $1.00 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.920 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to decline if it stays below the $0.920 and $0.950 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>EOS price is struggling below $1.00 against the US Dollar, unlike <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-29k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. The price might attempt to recover if there is a clear move above $0.950.</em></p>
<h2>EOS Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, EOS price saw a steady decline from the $1.05 resistance against the US Dollar. The price traded below the $1.02 and $1.00 levels to move into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>The decline gained pace below the $0.950 level. It even spiked below $0.900. A low is formed near $0.8708 and the price is now consolidating losses. EOS is trading well below $1.00 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-signs-of-recovery-above-1-05/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $0.920 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.920 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair. It is near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $1.038 swing high to the $0.8708 low.</p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $0.955 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $1.038 swing high to the $0.8708 low.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $0.955 level could start a steady increase toward the $1.00 level. The next major resistance might be $1.05. Any more gains might send the price toward the $1.10 level. On the downside, immediate support is near $0.880.</p>
<p>The next key support is near the $0.870 level. If there is a downside break below the $0.870 support, the price could test the $0.820 support in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_78287" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/EOS-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78287" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78287" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/EOS-1.png" alt="EOS Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78287" class="wp-caption-text">EOS Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/EOSUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, EOS price is now trading below the $0.950 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to decline if it stays below the $0.920 and $0.950 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for EOS/USD is gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $0.880 and $0.820.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $0.920 and $0.950.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-more-losses-seem-likely-below-0-92/">EOS Price Analysis: More Losses Seem Likely Below $0.92</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-more-losses-seem-likely-below-0-92/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Face Uphill Task</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-face-uphill-task-2/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-face-uphill-task-2/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 03:18:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=78283</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin is showing bearish signs and trading above $75 against the US Dollar. LTC price is now trading below $85 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $84.8 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-face-uphill-task-2/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-face-uphill-task-2/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Face Uphill Task</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Litecoin is showing bearish signs and trading above $75 against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>LTC price is now trading below $85 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $84.8 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could start a decent increase if it clears the $85 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Litecoin price is struggling below $85 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-29k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a>. LTC price could continue to decline if it stays below the $85 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few hours, there was a short-lived recovery in Bitcoin, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-at-risk-of-downside-break/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Ethereum</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-xrp-turns-red-and-at-risk-below-0-45/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Ripple</a>, and Litecoin against the US Dollar. Earlier, LTC settled below the $85 resistance zone to move into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>The price broke the $80 support zone and tested the $75 support. A low is formed near $75.32 and the price is now attempting a recovery wave. There was a move above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $79.76 swing high to the $75.32 low.</p>
<p>It is now trading below $85 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $82.50 zone.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $85 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $84.8 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair. The trend line is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $79.76 swing high to the $75.32 low.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $85 level could pump the price toward the $92 level or even $95. The next major resistance could be $100.</p>
<p>On the downside, immediate support is near the $78 level. The next key support is near the $75 level. If there is a downside break below the $75 support, the price could accelerate lower toward the $70 level in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_78284" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Litecoin-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-78284" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-78284" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/05/Litecoin-1.png" alt="Litecoin (LTC) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-78284" class="wp-caption-text">Litecoin (LTC) Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, Litecoin price is clearly trading below $85 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $85 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LTC/USD is now losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $78.00 and $75.00.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $82.50 and $85.00.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-face-uphill-task-2/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Bulls Face Uphill Task</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-bulls-face-uphill-task-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk Asks Judge to Toss Out Dogecoin-Centered Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-asks-judge-to-toss-out-dogecoin-centered-lawsuit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-asks-judge-to-toss-out-dogecoin-centered-lawsuit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 17:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lawsuit]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=77740</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At the time of writing, South African billionaire and entrepreneur Elon Musk – the man who brought companies like Tesla and SpaceX to the forefront – is currently trapped in the middle of a $258 billion lawsuit centering on his promotion of digital currencies like Dogecoin. Elon Musk Requests Dismissal of Court Case Musk is<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-asks-judge-to-toss-out-dogecoin-centered-lawsuit/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-asks-judge-to-toss-out-dogecoin-centered-lawsuit/">Elon Musk Asks Judge to Toss Out Dogecoin-Centered Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>At the time of writing, South African billionaire and entrepreneur Elon Musk – the man who brought companies like Tesla and SpaceX to the forefront – is <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-i-never-forced-anyone-to-invest-in-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">currently trapped in the middle</a> of a $258 billion lawsuit centering on his promotion of digital currencies like Dogecoin.</p>
<h2>Elon Musk Requests Dismissal of Court Case</h2>
<p>Musk is now asking the judge <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/04/02/a-legitimate-cryptocurrency-dogecoin-price-suddenly-soars-after-elon-musk-hits-back-at-258-billion-lawsuit/?sh=4de179fb3185" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">overseeing the case to toss</a> it out. The lawsuit stems from a group of defendants that invested in Dogecoin last year following heavy promotion and praise from Musk, who’s had a lot of nice things to say about Dogecoin in the past. Not long ago, he referred to the asset as “the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-affirms-his-position-on-doge-its-the-peoples-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">people’s crypto</a>.”</p>
<p>Sadly, 2022 was marred by a heavy bear run that saw many digital currencies drop into the doldrums and lose 70 percent or more of their values. Bitcoin, for example, was trading at a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit in November of 2021, though 12 months later, it had fallen into the $16,000 range. It was a sad and ugly sight to see.</p>
<p>Dogecoin also suffered heavily during this time, and many people lost all their money after making investments in the popular meme currency co-invented by Jackson Palmer. They are now suing Musk, saying he’s responsible for their losses and that they never would have invested in the asset had they not seen Musk praise it so much.</p>
<p>Over the past few weeks, Dogecoin has jumped up in price by about ten percent. In a statement, lawyers for Musk said there’s no base to the lawsuit, as their client did not force anyone to engage in crypto trading. They commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>There is nothing unlawful about tweeting words of support for, or funny pictures about, a legitimate cryptocurrency that continues to hold a market cap of nearly $10 billion. This court should put a stop to [the] plaintiffs&#8217; fantasy and dismiss the complaint.</p></blockquote>
<p>At first glance, this appears like a one-and-done case that will be dismissed outright. After all, what Musk’s lawyers say is true. It’s not like the South African billionaire held a gun to anyone’s head and said to them, “Either invest in Dogecoin or I pull the trigger.” At the end of the day, there’s certainly sympathy for their losses, but those who invested in Dogecoin chose to do so on their own accord, and they were not forced into action by any outside party.</p>
<h2>Nefariously Pumping Up the Price?</h2>
<p>Still, lawyers for the defendants are not giving up. A member of the legal team recently said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We are more confident than ever that our case will be successful.</p></blockquote>
<p>The lawsuit says Musk is responsible for pumping up the Dogecoin price over the course of two years by about 36,000 percent, then allowing it to crash.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-asks-judge-to-toss-out-dogecoin-centered-lawsuit/">Elon Musk Asks Judge to Toss Out Dogecoin-Centered Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/elon-musk-asks-judge-to-toss-out-dogecoin-centered-lawsuit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
