<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 03:56:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/07/cropped-fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ark Fi Introduces Ramp, a New Way to Purchase Digital Currency</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ark-fi-introduces-ramp-a-new-way-to-purchase-digital-currency/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 13:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ark Fi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ramp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79164</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Leading fiat-to-crypto firm Ark Fi is introducing Ramp, a secondary platform that will allow customers to purchase digital assets with their credit cards. Ramp Will Make Crypto Buying Easy The whole idea of purchasing bitcoin and its altcoin cousins should be easy. One pulls out their credit card, enters the information, and done! The money [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ark-fi-introduces-ramp-a-new-way-to-purchase-digital-currency/">Ark Fi Introduces Ramp, a New Way to Purchase Digital Currency</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Leading fiat-to-crypto firm Ark Fi is introducing Ramp, a <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/pressreleases/23/07/ab33103238/ark-fi-launches-ramp-a-new-platform-to-buy-cryptocurrency-with-credit-or-debit-cards">secondary platform that</a> will allow customers to purchase digital assets with their credit cards.</p>
<h2>Ramp Will Make Crypto Buying Easy</h2>
<p>The whole idea of purchasing bitcoin and its altcoin cousins should be easy. One pulls out their credit card, enters the information, and done! The money should be transferred to their digital wallet for use and investment purposes. Unfortunately, there are some companies out there that make things more complicated than they need to be.</p>
<p>This is rough for many reasons, a big one being that digital currency was designed to be accessible to all. If there are individuals out there that cannot access crypto, then the network and the system has failed, and they will not be able to take advantage of the benefits available to them. Thus, they are stuck in a traditional world of finance where third parties and middlemen have more say over their money than they do.</p>
<p>The big thing about Ramp is it offers a wide array of crypto including bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin, Binance Coin, and others. In addition, the platform charges low fees and is compliant with all present financial regulations (so users can rest assured the SEC probably won’t come after the firm anytime soon).</p>
<p>Lastly, KYC (know your customer) protocols are not in place for most transactions, meaning the buys should be quick and painless for most, and there are no lock periods, so the money can be used right away if need be. The CEO of Ark Fi – a person simply known as “Atlas” – explained in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>We are excited to launch Ramp and make it easier for consumers to buy cryptocurrency. Ramp is a valuable resource for anyone who wants to get started in decentralized finance, despite the recent restrictions by some banks and centralized exchanges.</p></blockquote>
<p>While talking, he threw in his two cents regarding the digital currency lawsuits against both <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sues-binance-alleges-selling-of-illegal-securities/">Binance</a> and <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-hit-with-sec-lawsuit-says-it-operated-as-an-exchange-broker/">Coinbase</a>. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We believe these restrictions are misguided. Cryptocurrency is a legitimate asset class, and consumers should have the freedom to buy and sell it.</p></blockquote>
<p>Among the payment methods that Ramp accepts are credit and debit cards, Astro Pay, Neteller, and Skrill. It also boasts a user-friendly interface, meaning those with little to no crypto-buying experience shouldn’t find the platform too difficult to operate. The company also offers 24/7 customer service to help users with any issues they should encounter (a real clincher considering <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/opinion-lagging-customer-service-is-hurting-the-crypto-space/">how many crypto firms</a> have gotten rid of their customer service departments).</p>
<h2>A Proud Addition to the Industry</h2>
<p>Atlas concluded with:</p>
<blockquote><p>We are committed to providing consumers with a safe and easy way to buy cryptocurrency. Ramp is the perfect solution for anyone who wants to quickly get started in the crypto world.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ark-fi-introduces-ramp-a-new-way-to-purchase-digital-currency/">Ark Fi Introduces Ramp, a New Way to Purchase Digital Currency</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EOS Price Analysis: Risk of Drop To $0.60</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-risk-of-drop-to-0-60/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 04:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EOS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79770</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>EOS price started a fresh decline from the $0.730 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $0.70 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.6720 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-risk-of-drop-to-0-60/">EOS Price Analysis: Risk of Drop To $0.60</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>EOS price started a fresh decline from the $0.730 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $0.70 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.6720 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to decline if it stays below the $0.672 and $0.700 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>EOS price is struggling below $0.700 against the US Dollar, unlike <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-at-risk-below-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. The price might attempt to recover if there is a clear move above $0.672.</em></p>
<h2>EOS Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, EOS price saw a fresh decline from the $0.730 resistance against the US Dollar. The price traded below the $0.72 and $0.70 levels to move into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>The pair even spiked below the $0.650 support. A low is formed near $0.6140 and the price is now consolidating losses. EOS is trading well below $0.700 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-bears-aim-for-0-65-or-lower/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $0.642 level.</p>
<p>The 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.7302 swing high to the $0.6140 low is also near $0.642. The first major resistance is near the $0.672 level.</p>
<p>There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.6720 on the 4-hour chart of the EOS/USD pair. The trend line is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.7302 swing high to the $0.6140 low.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $0.672 level could start a steady increase toward the $0.70 level. The next major resistance might be $0.732. Any more gains might send the price toward the $0.78 level.</p>
<p>On the downside, immediate support is near $0.625. The next key support is near the $0.615 level. If there is a downside break below the $0.615 support, the price could test the $0.60 support in the near term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79771" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79771" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/EOS-1.png"><img decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" class="size-full wp-image-79771" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/EOS-1.png" alt="EOS Price" width="1835" height="839" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/EOS-1.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/EOS-1-600x274.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/EOS-1-1100x503.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/EOS-1-768x351.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/EOS-1-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/EOS-1-750x343.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/EOS-1-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79771" class="wp-caption-text">EOS Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/EOSUSD/">chart</a>, EOS price is now trading below the $0.700 level and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to decline if it stays below the $0.672 and $0.700 resistance levels.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for EOS/USD is losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $0.625 and $0.615.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $0.672 and $0.700.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/eos-price-analysis-risk-of-drop-to-0-60/">EOS Price Analysis: Risk of Drop To $0.60</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Upsides Could Be Attractive To Sellers</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-upsides-could-be-attractive-to-sellers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 03:48:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79767</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin is showing bearish signs and trading below $80 against the US Dollar. LTC price is now trading below $78 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $79.00 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-upsides-could-be-attractive-to-sellers/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Upsides Could Be Attractive To Sellers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Litecoin is showing bearish signs and trading below $80 against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>LTC price is now trading below $78 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $79.00 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could start a decent increase if it clears the $80 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Litecoin price is struggling below $80 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-at-risk-below-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. LTC price could continue to decline if it stays below the $80 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few days, there was a short-lived recovery in Bitcoin, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-eth-revisits-key-support/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a>, Ripple, and Litecoin against the US Dollar. Earlier, LTC settled below the $85 resistance zone to move into a bearish zone.</p>
<p>The price broke the $80 support zone and started a fresh decline. It even traded below the $75 support. A low is formed near $72.72 and the price is now consolidating losses. It is now trading below $80 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>Immediate resistance is near the $75.80 level. It is close to the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $85.40 swing high to the $72.72 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $79 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $79.00 on the 4-hour chart of the LTC/USD pair. The trend line is near the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $85.40 swing high to the $72.72 low.</p>
<p>A clear move above the $80 level could pump the price toward the $85 level. The next major resistance could be $92. On the downside, immediate support is near the $72.75 level. The next key support is near the $70 level.</p>
<p>If there is a downside break below the $70 support, the price could accelerate lower toward the $65 level in the near term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79768" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79768" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Litecoin-1.png"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-79768" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Litecoin-1.png" alt="Litecoin (LTC) Price" width="1835" height="839" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Litecoin-1.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Litecoin-1-600x274.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Litecoin-1-1100x503.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Litecoin-1-768x351.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Litecoin-1-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Litecoin-1-750x343.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Litecoin-1-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79768" class="wp-caption-text">Litecoin (LTC) Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/">chart</a>, Litecoin price is clearly trading below $80 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it stays below the $80 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LTC/USD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $72.75 and $70.00.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $79.00 and $80.00.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-upsides-could-be-attractive-to-sellers/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Upsides Could Be Attractive To Sellers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tapbit Introduces Contract Copy Trading: Unlocking Profits for All Investors in the Cryptocurrency Market</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tapbit-introduces-contract-copy-trading-unlocking-profits-for-all-investors-in-the-cryptocurrency-market/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Live Bitcoin News]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 17:22:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79763</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency industry had a number of noteworthy events in the first half of 2023, reaffirming its status as a top global risk asset. Investors sought solutions to handle the highly unpredictable market and secure larger returns in the face of the hurdles offered by significant market changes. As a result, many people began trading [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tapbit-introduces-contract-copy-trading-unlocking-profits-for-all-investors-in-the-cryptocurrency-market/">Tapbit Introduces Contract Copy Trading: Unlocking Profits for All Investors in the Cryptocurrency Market</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency industry had a number of noteworthy events in the first half of 2023, reaffirming its status as a top global risk asset. Investors sought solutions to handle the highly unpredictable market and secure larger returns in the face of the hurdles offered by significant market changes. As a result, many people began trading high-leverage contracts, exposing themselves to potential liquidation and trading failures owing to a lack of experience and risk management.</p>
<p>In response to these obstacles, Tapbit provides a breakthrough contract copy trading platform that enables traders, both rookie and experienced, to earn like pros while lowering the likelihood of losses.</p>
<h4>Copy Trading: A Game-Changing Opportunity for Investors</h4>
<p>Copy trading is an effective approach that allows users to mimic the trading activities of experienced and successful traders. Investors can benefit from skilled traders&#8217; skills, get useful insights, and minimise potential risks during market volatility by following them for at least six months.</p>
<h4>Why Should You Use Tapbit Copy Trading?</h4>
<p>Tapbit stands out as a trustworthy and respectable contract trading platform, with a user-friendly interface and a wide range of games and investing options. Tapbit&#8217;s revolutionary features let users to customise their copy trading tactics, such as preset follow ratios, preset TP/SL (take-profit/stop-loss) and customizable initial position options. This adaptability reduces copy trading hazards while adapting to consumers&#8217; individual trading behaviours.</p>
<p>With over 300 top traders and well-known Key Opinion Leaders (KOLs) already on board, Tapbit&#8217;s copy trading ecosystem provides a wide choice of solutions to meet the demands of any investor.</p>
<h4>Pursuing Excellence</h4>
<p>Tapbit, as a new cryptocurrency exchange, is dedicated to providing a secure, smooth, and profitable contract trading experience. Tapbit aspires to improve security, liquidity, and user simplicity to offer a pleasurable trading trip through strong technology support, devoted product development, and user-centric services.</p>
<p>Visit Tapbit&#8217;s official website at <a href="https://www.tapbit.com/">https://www.tapbit.com/ </a>to learn more and start profiting like a pro.</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/Tapbitglobal"><strong>Twitter</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://t.me/tapbitglobal"><strong>Telegram</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://www.facebook.com/tapbitglobal"><strong>Facebook</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCj4ocBlVoduelyFApLhQNxg"><strong>YouTube</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://www.instagram.com/tapbit_global/"><strong>Instagram</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/tapbit/"><strong>LinkedIn</strong></a></p>
<p><strong>Contact Information:</strong></p>
<p>Website: <a href="https://www.tapbit.com/">https://www.tapbit.com/</a><br />
Contact person: Zora Chia<br />
Company Name: Tapbit<br />
Company Email: contact@tapbit.com<br />
Country: Seychelles, US</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tapbit-introduces-contract-copy-trading-unlocking-profits-for-all-investors-in-the-cryptocurrency-market/">Tapbit Introduces Contract Copy Trading: Unlocking Profits for All Investors in the Cryptocurrency Market</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Matrix Port: Bitcoin Will Hit $125K in 18 Months</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/matrix-port-bitcoin-will-hit-125k-in-18-months/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 17:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Matrix Port]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79159</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Matrix Port – a provider of crypto and blockchain services – is confident that in a year and a half from now (at the end of 2024), the price of bitcoin will rise to a whopping $125,000. Matrix Port: Bitcoin Is Going to Rise, Rise, Rise The company is basing its hypothesis on historical data, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/matrix-port-bitcoin-will-hit-125k-in-18-months/">Matrix Port: Bitcoin Will Hit $125K in 18 Months</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Matrix Port – a provider of crypto and blockchain services – is <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/technology/bitcoin-to-potentially-climb-to-125-000-by-end-of-2024-predicts-cryptocurrency-services-provider/ar-AA1dwjun">confident that in a year</a> and a half from now (at the end of 2024), the price of bitcoin will rise to a whopping $125,000.</p>
<h2>Matrix Port: Bitcoin Is Going to Rise, Rise, Rise</h2>
<p>The company is basing its hypothesis on historical data, which includes former bullish trends and significant increases in market value. Matrix Port believes that these little points will repeat themselves and ultimately bring the world’s number one digital asset to a point where it nearly doubles its end-of-year 2021 high.</p>
<p>Matrix Port is also considering that bitcoin has shot up to about $31,000 per unit at the time of writing, the highest it’s been in about 13 months. Right now, the signals being witnessed on bitcoin-centered technical charts have also been seen in charts during August of 2012, December of 2015, May of 2019, and August of 2020. All these periods were followed by huge price rallies.</p>
<p>Markus Thielen – the head of research and strategy at Matrix Port – explained in a recent note:</p>
<blockquote><p>On June 22, 2023, bitcoin recorded a new one-year high, marking the first such instance in a year. Historically, this signal has signified the conclusion of bear markets and the commencement of new crypto bull markets. If we take history as a reference, bitcoin prices could rise by +123 percent over 12 months and by +310 percent over 18 months based on the average return of the signals triggered in 2015, 2019, and 2020. This could push prices to $65,539 in 12 months and $125,731 over 18 months.</p></blockquote>
<p>It feels as though so long as bitcoin remains in existence, there will be people and companies alike working to predict where its price will go, though to be fair, the $125,000 prediction from Matrix Port is nothing compared to some of the other predictions that have arisen over the past few weeks and months.</p>
<p>For example, Tom Lee of Fundstrat fame <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tom-lee-sees-btc-rising-to-200k/">recently concluded</a> that bitcoin could somehow make it all the way to $200K, while Cathie Wood of ARK Invest thinks that <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/cathie-wood-btc-will-be-priced-at-1-5-million-in-2030/">over the next seven</a> years, bitcoin could cross the $1 million mark.</p>
<h2>We Can All Be Thankful that 2022 is Over</h2>
<p>In any case, one thing that needs to be mentioned is that while bitcoin is still only trading for around $30K, this is still miles better than where it stood at the end of last year. 2022 was arguably the worst period on record for the world’s primary cryptocurrency. The asset – which as mentioned, was trading in the high $60K range at the end of 2021 – finished the following 12-month stint trading in the mid-$16K range, thus meaning the asset had lost more than 70 percent of its overall value.</p>
<p>This contributed to the crypto industry falling below the $1 trillion valuation line when it had been standing beyond $3 trillion at the beginning of 2022.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/matrix-port-bitcoin-will-hit-125k-in-18-months/">Matrix Port: Bitcoin Will Hit $125K in 18 Months</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Analysts Think Coinbase Will Succeed in the SEC Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-think-coinbase-will-succeed-in-the-sec-lawsuit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 15:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79156</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Could the new BlackRock bitcoin-based exchange-traded fund (ETF) application help pave the way for a Coinbase and SEC settlement or relationship? According to some analysts, the answer is “yes.” Coinbase Could Be Successful Coinbase was recently listed as a custody provider in the application submitted by BlackRock. This, according to several industry experts, is a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-think-coinbase-will-succeed-in-the-sec-lawsuit/">Analysts Think Coinbase Will Succeed in the SEC Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Could the new BlackRock bitcoin-based exchange-traded fund (ETF) application <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/blackrock-s-bitcoin-etf-filing-is-a-vote-of-confidence-in-coinbase-one-analyst-says-here-s-why/ar-AA1dwErz">help pave the way</a> for a Coinbase and SEC settlement or relationship? According to some analysts, the answer is “yes.”</p>
<h2>Coinbase Could Be Successful</h2>
<p>Coinbase was recently listed as a custody provider in the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blackrock-etf-application-causes-btc-eth-to-surge/">application submitted</a> by BlackRock. This, according to several industry experts, is a huge vote of confidence for the firm given Coinbase is currently under the scrutiny of the SEC, which <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-hit-with-sec-lawsuit-says-it-operated-as-an-exchange-broker/">has filed a lawsuit</a> against the exchange for allegedly operating as an unlicensed broker.</p>
<p>This was a move that really shocked many executives, who claim to have met with members of the SEC several times over a period of nine years to ensure they were fully compliant. In any case, Coinbase is denying it engaged in any wrongdoing at the time of writing.</p>
<p>If the BlackRock application were to somehow garner approval from the SEC, could this pave the way for an easy outcome for Coinbase? Several analysts weighed in on the situation, with Matt Kunke – a research analyst at GSR – saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>While the exact catalyst for BlackRock’s first-time filing remains unknown, it may be due in part to Grayscale’s progress in its lawsuit with the SEC, [BlackRock’s] perceived ability to maneuver the current regulatory climate, and/or its ability to procure a new surveillance sharing agreement with Coinbase.</p></blockquote>
<p>Mark Connors – head of research at digital asset manager 3iQ – also threw his two cents into the mix, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>In my opinion, [the asset managers] are downplaying the risk of a successful lawsuit against Coinbase. BlackRock’s filing means that they vote that the SEC will not prevail in their case against Coinbase.</p></blockquote>
<p>Jeff Feng – co-founder at Sei Labs – offered a similar sentiment. He mentioned:</p>
<blockquote><p>This choice suggests that these institutions believe that Coinbase has a robust legal defense in its operations, further fueling the optimism around the potential for approval. Given the current circumstances, there are indeed strong signals suggesting that approval of these spot bitcoin ETFs could be on the horizon. However, it’s vital to remember that in this rapidly evolving regulatory landscape, an elevated probability doesn’t necessarily translate into a guaranteed outcome.</p></blockquote>
<h2>This is an Entirely Different Situation</h2>
<p>In a note to investors, analysts at Alliance Bernstein said now that BlackRock has entered the picture, the SEC is “fairly” likely to approve a spot bitcoin ETF application given it’s coming from a licensed and registered (traditional) financial company with a long history of operating on Wall Street.</p>
<p>Prior to this, the bitcoin ETF applications that made headlines have all come from companies that didn’t have BlackRock’s reputation or standing, nor had they been around as long. Also, they were not registered and were part of an industry that at that point, was still considered taboo or illegitimate.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/analysts-think-coinbase-will-succeed-in-the-sec-lawsuit/">Analysts Think Coinbase Will Succeed in the SEC Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Larry Fink: Bitcoin Can Do a Lot for the Financial Space</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/larry-fink-bitcoin-can-revolutionize-the-financial-arena/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 13:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Larry Fink]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79152</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Larry Fink – the CEO of BlackRock, which recently applied to the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for a bitcoin-based exchange-traded fund (ETF) – said he thinks bitcoin is akin to digital gold, and he feels it has the power to truly revolutionize the financial arena. Larry Fink Thinks Highly of BTC The application was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/larry-fink-bitcoin-can-revolutionize-the-financial-arena/">Larry Fink: Bitcoin Can Do a Lot for the Financial Space</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Larry Fink – the CEO of BlackRock, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/blackrock-etf-application-causes-btc-eth-to-surge/">which recently applied</a> to the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for a bitcoin-based exchange-traded fund (ETF) – said he <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/crypto-digitizing-gold-bitcoin-can-revolutionize-finance-blackrock-larry-fink-2023-7">thinks bitcoin is akin</a> to digital gold, and he feels it has the power to truly revolutionize the financial arena.</p>
<h2>Larry Fink Thinks Highly of BTC</h2>
<p>The application was initially rejected by Gary Gensler and the SEC, who claimed the details in the document <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sec-sends-blackrock-btc-etf-application-back-for-revisions/">were not comprehensive</a> enough. However, a ray of light appeared in the form of the SEC not giving a flat-out “no,” which it’s done to other companies in the past. The financial agency said if Fink and BlackRock were willing to make certain changes to the application, it could be submitted again for a second look.</p>
<p>On this front, Fink said he’s willing to do all he can to cooperate. He commented in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>We work really closely with our regulators, and we want to hear from our regulators. What are their issues, and can we fix those issues around that? We do believe if we can create more tokenization of assets and securities, and that&#8217;s what bitcoin is, it could revolutionize finance again. We look at this as an opportunity to move one step further in terms of providing investors fractions of shares, fractions of this, democratizing the cost of investing.</p></blockquote>
<p>Fink is not the only one excited about the prospects of a BTC ETF. Changpeng Zhao – the man behind the Binance crypto exchange – recently <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/larger-better-says-binance-ceo-185718318.html">engaged in a discussion</a> regarding the power the tool might have and how much it could potentially do for the industry. He commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>We welcome more players. The larger the better. It will offer more coverage.</p></blockquote>
<p>One of the big issues that has been discussed lately is whether traditional financial companies – like BlackRock – pose threats to companies like Binance should they decide to enter the crypto industry as they’re doing now. Zhao doesn’t think so, mentioning:</p>
<blockquote><p>Short answer is no. It would be hugely beneficial to crypto for large entities to come into the space… It will help us improve.</p></blockquote>
<p>Fink continued his discussion of bitcoin and crypto, saying he was skeptical of both in the past on account of their associations with “illicit activities,” as he put it. However, he has since warmed up to the digital currency arena and said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I do believe the role of crypto is digitizing gold in many ways.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Convincing the SEC</h2>
<p>Fink concluded by commenting that he thinks BlackRock will <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/07/06/shock-flip-reveals-unprecedented-9-trillion-revolution-could-be-about-to-hit-the-price-of-bitcoin-and-major-cryptos-ethereum-bnb-and-xrp/?sh=53a5d55ac740">not have any issues</a> when it comes to convincing the SEC of the power of its bitcoin ETF given the firm’s longstanding track record. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We have a good track record working with our regulators and trying to make sure we&#8217;re thinking about all the issues around any filing.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/larry-fink-bitcoin-can-revolutionize-the-financial-arena/">Larry Fink: Bitcoin Can Do a Lot for the Financial Space</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Bears Aim Breakdown Below $0.075</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bears-aim-breakdown-below-0-075/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 06:08:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79759</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tron price started a fresh decline below the $0.080 level against the US Dollar. TRX price is now trading below $0.0785 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key contracting triangle forming with resistance near $0.0775 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could continue to move down [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bears-aim-breakdown-below-0-075/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Bears Aim Breakdown Below $0.075</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Tron price started a fresh decline below the $0.080 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>TRX price is now trading below $0.0785 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key contracting triangle forming with resistance near $0.0775 on the 4-hour chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it breaks the $0.0750 support zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>TRON price started a fresh decline below the $0.0820 zone against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-at-risk-below-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. TRX price could accelerate lower if there is a move below $0.0750.</em></p>
<h2>Tron Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, Tron price started a steady decline from well above the $0.0820 resistance level against the US Dollar. TRX price struggled to gain pace for more gains and formed a top near $0.085.</p>
<p>The price started a fresh decline below the $0.0800 level. There was a clear move below the $0.0780 level. A low is formed near $0.0754 and the price is now consolidating losses. The price is now trading below $0.0785 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-indicators-suggest-fresh-rally-to-0-085/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>.</p>
<p>On the upside, TRX is facing resistance near the $0.0775 level. It is near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.0854 swing high to the $0.0754 low.</p>
<p>There is also a key contracting triangle forming with resistance near $0.0775 on the 4-hour chart. The next major resistance is near the $0.080 level. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.0854 swing high to the $0.0754 low.</p>
<p>A close above $0.0785 and $0.080 is a must for a fresh increase. In the stated case, the price could rise toward the $0.085 resistance in the near term.</p>
<p>On the downside, initial support is near the $0.0758 level. The next major support is now forming near $0.0750. If there is a downside break below the $0.075 support, the price might revisit the $0.0720 support. Any more losses might call for a move toward the $0.070 zone in the near term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79760" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79760" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/TRON-TRX.png"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-79760" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/TRON-TRX.png" alt="Tron (TRX) Price" width="1835" height="839" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/TRON-TRX.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/TRON-TRX-600x274.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/TRON-TRX-1100x503.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/TRON-TRX-768x351.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/TRON-TRX-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/TRON-TRX-750x343.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/TRON-TRX-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79760" class="wp-caption-text">Tron (TRX) Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/TRXUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a> indicates that TRX price is now trading below $0.0785 and near the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it breaks the $0.0750 support zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for TRX/USD is slowly gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for TRX/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.0758 and $0.0750.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.0785, $0.080, and $0.085.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bears-aim-breakdown-below-0-075/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Bears Aim Breakdown Below $0.075</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC At Risk Below $30K</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-at-risk-below-30k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 04:08:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=79756</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price started a fresh decline below the $29,600 level against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $29,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $29,320 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-at-risk-below-30k/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC At Risk Below $30K</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin price started a fresh decline below the $29,600 level against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $29,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $29,320 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could extend its decline toward the $28,650 and $28,000 levels.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin price is declining below $29,600 against the US Dollar. BTC might extend losses if it stays below the $29,500 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price started a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-faces-uphill-task-near-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">fresh decline</a> below the $29,600 zone. A high was formed near $30,222 before the price started a steady decline. There was a clear move below the $30,000 and $29,600 support levels.</p>
<p>The price declined below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $28,660 swing low to the $30,222 high. The bears even pushed the price below the $29,320 support zone and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>The price is now trading below $29,500 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-turns-red-below-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">55 simple moving average (4 hours)</a>. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $29,320 on the 4-hour chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>Immediate resistance on the upside is near the $29,320 level and the trend line. The next major resistance might be near the $29,500 zone. A clear move above the $29,500 level might send the price toward $29,750, above which the price might rise toward the $30,000 level. Any more gains might push the price toward the $31,200 zone.</p>
<p>If there is no upside break, the price might decline below the $29,000 level or the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $28,660 swing low to the $30,222 high.</p>
<p>The first major support is near $28,660. The next key support is near the $28,500 level, below which the price might accelerate lower. In the stated case, the price could decline toward the $28,000 level. Any more losses might send the price toward the $27,400 level.</p>
<figure id="attachment_79757" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-79757" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Bitcoin-1.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-79757" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Bitcoin-1.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1835" height="839" srcset="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Bitcoin-1.png 1835w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Bitcoin-1-600x274.png 600w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Bitcoin-1-1100x503.png 1100w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Bitcoin-1-768x351.png 768w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Bitcoin-1-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Bitcoin-1-750x343.png 750w, https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/08/Bitcoin-1-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-79757" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Price</figcaption></figure>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XBTUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chart</a>, Bitcoin price is clearly trading below $29,500 and the 55 simple moving average (4 hours). Overall, the price could extend its decline toward the $28,650 and $28,000 levels.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD is now losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $29,000 and $28,660.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $29,320, $29,500, and $30,000.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-at-risk-below-30k/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC At Risk Below $30K</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
