<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<description>Live Bitcoin News is one of the world’s leading bitcoin networks where you will get all the latest news, charts, guides and analysis about bitcoin.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 03:49:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2018/05/cropped-favicon-80x80.png</url>
	<title>Live Bitcoin News</title>
	<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Uptrend Intact Above $85</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-uptrend-intact-above-85/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-uptrend-intact-above-85/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 03:58:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76678</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin started a strong increase above $85 against the US Dollar. LTC price is now trading above $82 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a connecting bullish trend line forming with support near $88.00 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair remains supported for more<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-uptrend-intact-above-85/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-uptrend-intact-above-85/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Uptrend Intact Above $85</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Litecoin started a strong increase above $85 against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>LTC price is now trading above $82 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a connecting bullish trend line forming with support near $88.00 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair remains supported for more gains unless there is a clear move below $85.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Litecoin price is rising steadily above $85 against the US Dollar, similar to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-more-gains-above-23k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. LTC price could continue to move up if it remains well supported above the $85 level.</em></p>
<h2>Litecoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>In the past few sessions, there was a decent increase in bitcoin, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ethereum-price-analysis-bulls-aim-1800-or-higher/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">ethereum</a>, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ripple-price-analysis-bulls-in-control-above-0-38/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">ripple</a>, and litecoin against the US Dollar. Earlier, LTC formed a base above the $82 level and started a fresh increase.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above the $85 and $88 resistance levels. The price even climbed above the $90 level and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). However, the bears were active near the $95 zone. A high was formed near $93.16 and the price started a downside correction.</p>
<p>There was a move below the $90 level. The price declined below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $81.67 swing low to $93.16 high.</p>
<p>The price is now trading above $85 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $88.00 on the 4-hours chart of the LTC/USD pair. The pair is also supported above the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $81.67 swing low to $93.16 high.</p>
<p>The first major support is near the $88 level and the trend line. If there is a downside break below the $88 support, the price could accelerate lower towards the $85 level in the near term.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $92 and $93 levels. A clear move above the $93 level could pump the price towards the $100 level. The next major resistance sits near the $108 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_76679" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Litecoin-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76679" class="size-full wp-image-76679" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Litecoin-2.png" alt="Litecoin (LTC) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76679" class="wp-caption-text">Litecoin (LTC) Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, litecoin price is clearly trading above $85 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price remains supported for more gains unless there is a clear move below $85.</p>
<h2>Technical indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LTC/USD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LTC/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $88 and $85</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $93 and $100.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-uptrend-intact-above-85/">Litecoin (LTC) Price Analysis: Uptrend Intact Above $85</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/litecoin-ltc-price-analysis-uptrend-intact-above-85/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana Praised Again By Buterin, Price Surges 10%</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/solana-praised-again-by-buterin-price-surges-10/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/solana-praised-again-by-buterin-price-surges-10/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 17:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vitalik buterin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76332</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, Live Bitcoin News published an article talking about how poorly the Solana cryptocurrency was doing. The asset was crashing and burning likely due to its ties to the now fallen crypto exchange FTX and its disgraced head executive Sam Bankman-Fried, and while things aren’t fully looking up for the currency just yet,<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/solana-praised-again-by-buterin-price-surges-10/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/solana-praised-again-by-buterin-price-surges-10/">Solana Praised Again By Buterin, Price Surges 10%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, <em>Live Bitcoin News</em> published an article <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/solana-continues-to-crash-due-to-ftx-ties/" data-wpel-link="internal">talking about how poorly</a> the Solana cryptocurrency was doing. The asset was crashing and burning likely due to its ties to the now fallen crypto exchange FTX and its disgraced head executive Sam Bankman-Fried, and while things aren’t fully looking up for the currency just yet, it’s garnering a heavy load of support <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/billybambrough/2023/01/02/ethereum-founder-suddenly-powers-a-shock-ftx-crypto-price-rally-as-bitcoin-struggles/?sh=5a31ee5a22bb" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">from crypto developers</a> such as Vitalik Buterin, the co-creator of popular crypto network Ethereum.</p>
<h2>Solana Has Recorded a Price Jump</h2>
<p>In the previous article, it was discussed that Solana has deep ties to the fallen exchange and has since crashed by more than 96 percent since reaching an all-time high during the month of November 2021. During that time, it was trading for just shy of $260 per unit. At the time of the FTX bankruptcy, the currency had fallen to less than ten dollars.</p>
<p>Solana’s ties to FTX are so thick that it’s often dubbed “Sam Coin” in <em>honor</em> of Sam Bankman-Fried (not such a big honor anymore). The asset has links to an on-chain crypto exchange known as Serum, which was also created by Bankman-Fried. Solana is issued by the Solana blockchain, which presently engages in decentralized finance (defi) protocols and offers monetary products such as loans and mortgages.</p>
<p>Things do appear to be changing for the currency, however. At least on a temporary basis. At the time of writing, the altcoin has recorded a surge of approximately ten percent thanks to some positive words delivered on its behalf by Vitalik Buterin. In a recent tweet, the Ethereum front man said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Some smart people tell me there is an earnest smart developer community in Solana, and now that the awful opportunistic money people have been washed out, the chain has a bright future. Hard for me to tell from [the] outside, but I hope the community gets its fair chance to thrive.</p></blockquote>
<p>During its peak, Solana had a market capitalization of about $80 billion, and while this is not comparable to bitcoin or even Ethereum, the number is considered relatively impressive for a secondary altcoin.</p>
<p>Sadly, given the bear market conditions the crypto world is facing and the sudden problems surrounding FTX, that market cap has since fallen to about $4 billion. This is a dip of more than 90 percent at press time. Overall, the crypto space has lost more than $2 trillion in valuation in the last several months.</p>
<h2>Additional Support</h2>
<p>Solana has also gotten support from the likes of tech and crypto moguls Chamath Palihapitiya and David Sacks. On a recent podcast episode, Palihapitiya said of Solana:</p>
<blockquote><p>I was able to see a little bit under the hood of Solana Pay, and that&#8217;s really exciting. [Solana and blockchain] is like a swarm of activity to dismantle these payments businesses.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/solana-praised-again-by-buterin-price-surges-10/">Solana Praised Again By Buterin, Price Surges 10%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/solana-praised-again-by-buterin-price-surges-10/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Connecticut Police Get $23K in Stolen Crypto Funds Back</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/connecticut-police-recover-23k-in-stolen-crypto-funds/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/connecticut-police-recover-23k-in-stolen-crypto-funds/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 15:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security & Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Connecticut]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Police]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76329</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Members of a local police force in the state of Connecticut have helped a theft victim recover roughly $23,000 in stolen crypto funds. Police Are on the Case! The money was deposited under false pretenses to several nearby bitcoin ATMs after a complaint was filed in September of last year. The victim had allegedly been<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/connecticut-police-recover-23k-in-stolen-crypto-funds/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/connecticut-police-recover-23k-in-stolen-crypto-funds/">Connecticut Police Get $23K in Stolen Crypto Funds Back</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Members of a local police force in the state of Connecticut <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/ct-state-police-recover-23k-181600011.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">have helped a theft victim</a> recover roughly $23,000 in stolen crypto funds.</p>
<h2>Police Are on the Case!</h2>
<p>The money was deposited under false pretenses to several nearby bitcoin ATMs after a complaint was filed in September of last year. The victim had allegedly been scammed into depositing the money into various machines around the state, and the case was noted by the Milford Police Department. It was stated that more than $41,000 had been taken from the victim.</p>
<p>In a statement, the police agency explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>The funds were traced to two major cryptocurrency exchanges located in both the United States and the Cayman Islands. During the month of September, SOCITF investigators were able to recover a portion of the bitcoin from the two exchanges. Investigators learned that the suspects reside outside of the United States and no arrest is anticipated at this time.</p></blockquote>
<p>Situations like these have become increasingly common in the crypto space, and it looks like bitcoin and crypto-based ATMs are now widely used for fraudulent purposes. Typically, situations like these arise when a scammer contacts a potential victim – usually by phone (a huge red flag because crypto companies often don’t call their customers) – and says that there is a problem with their bank account or with some other financial tool they’ve been utilizing, and that their money is in danger.</p>
<p>From there, the crypto scammer tells the victim that to make sure their accounts are not vulnerable, they should download a bitcoin app and purchase the asset. From there, they need to make deposits into various machines so that the money can be monitored while being transferred. What the victim likely doesn’t know is that their digital money is going to an address that the scammer controls. When they give them the money, it’s likely they’ll never see it again, as it’s now in the hands of the cyberthief and crypto funds can be notoriously difficult to take back.</p>
<p>Other incidents involve <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/romance-scam/" data-wpel-link="internal">romance scams</a>, in which those looking for love online are tricked into making deposits into thief-controlled crypto platforms.</p>
<h2>Much of the Money Has Been Returned</h2>
<p>In this case, the victim was lucky in that police were able to seize back roughly $23,000 of the stolen money on December 30 and have it transferred back to the person. While not all the funds have been recovered, the move is considered a win for the scammed individual and a potential step forward in the world’s fight against crypto.</p>
<p>Police in the area are warning residents that these kinds of incidents are becoming increasingly common, and that all traders need to be on the lookout. If anything smells or looks fishy, they should report it to local law enforcement right away.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/connecticut-police-recover-23k-in-stolen-crypto-funds/">Connecticut Police Get $23K in Stolen Crypto Funds Back</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/connecticut-police-recover-23k-in-stolen-crypto-funds/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase to Pay Hefty Penalty Fees to New York Lawmakers</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-to-pay-hefty-penalty-fees-to-new-york-lawmakers/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-to-pay-hefty-penalty-fees-to-new-york-lawmakers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 13:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New York]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76327</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase – one of the largest and most popular digital currency exchanges in the world – has announced it will pay roughly $50 million in settlement fees to New York regulators for allegedly failing to comply with the Empire State’s anti-money laundering laws. Coinbase Allegedly Did Not Comply with Anti-Money Laundering Laws Regulators say that<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-to-pay-hefty-penalty-fees-to-new-york-lawmakers/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-to-pay-hefty-penalty-fees-to-new-york-lawmakers/">Coinbase to Pay Hefty Penalty Fees to New York Lawmakers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase – one of the largest and most popular digital currency exchanges in the world – has announced it will <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/coinbase-to-pay-regulators-7091279" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">pay roughly $50 million in settlement</a> fees to New York regulators for allegedly failing to comply with the Empire State’s anti-money laundering laws.</p>
<h2>Coinbase Allegedly Did Not Comply with Anti-Money Laundering Laws</h2>
<p>Regulators say that Coinbase has several older accounts that it hasn’t bothered to apply anti-money laundering laws to. There have been several thousand transactions with these accounts over the past four years that raised several red flags that Coinbase has allegedly done nothing about. The company must provide $50 million in penalties to New York as well as an additional $50 million to boost its compliance efforts.</p>
<p>The chief legal officer of the exchange, Paul Grewal, said in an email that Coinbase is now working hard to ensure it always remains in compliance with the state. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Coinbase has taken substantial measures to address these historical shortcomings.</p></blockquote>
<p>Coinbase obtained a BitLicense back in 2017. New York is the only region in the United States to impose such a will on crypto firms, and it’s rare when a company is willing to go as far as it does to please customers and legislators alike within the state’s borders, though a few – such as the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/gemini/" data-wpel-link="internal">Gemini exchange</a> – have had the initiative to do so.</p>
<p>Adrienne A. Harris – the state superintendent of financial services – says Coinbase’s issues go back as far as 2018. She said in a statement:</p>
<blockquote><p>We found failures that really warranted putting in place an independent monitor rather than wait for a settlement. We have been very outspoken about illicit financing concerns in the space. It is why our framework holds crypto companies to the same standard as for banks.</p></blockquote>
<p>It’s been a rough several months for the Coinbase exchange. 2022 was initially going to be a year when the company expanded its staff by as many as 5,000 people, though the subsequent bear market that struck the crypto space put these <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-says-its-freezing-all-2022-hiring-plans/" data-wpel-link="internal">plans largely out of commission</a>. Things eventually got so bad that Coinbase – like many other crypto companies – was forced to let go of several employees, and as many as 18 percent of the individuals it had <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-says-its-laying-off-several-employees/" data-wpel-link="internal">hired were forced</a> to step away.</p>
<h2>Everyone&#8217;s on Edge Because of FTX</h2>
<p>Regulators have been coming down hard on crypto exchanges for the past few months, likely in response <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">to the collapse of FTX</a>, which at one time, was one of the world’s top five crypto exchanges.</p>
<p>The company came to fruition in 2019 and quickly rose through the ranks, but it eventually collapsed into a heap of bankruptcy filings and fraud charges when it was alleged that its founder and chief executive – Sam Bankman-Fried – had misused customer funds for his own personal gain and to purchase Bahamian real estate.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-to-pay-hefty-penalty-fees-to-new-york-lawmakers/">Coinbase to Pay Hefty Penalty Fees to New York Lawmakers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/coinbase-to-pay-hefty-penalty-fees-to-new-york-lawmakers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Decline Could Extend To $0.055</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-decline-could-extend-to-0-055/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-decline-could-extend-to-0-055/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 07:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76666</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tron price started a fresh downside correction from the $0.064 zone against the US Dollar. TRX price is now trading below $0.0620 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $0.0620 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken). The pair could continue<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-decline-could-extend-to-0-055/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-decline-could-extend-to-0-055/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Decline Could Extend To $0.055</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Tron price started a fresh downside correction from the $0.064 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>TRX price is now trading below $0.0620 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $0.0620 on the 4-hours chart (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it breaks the $0.0585 support zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>TRON price started a downside correction below the $0.0620 against the US Dollar, similar <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-more-gains-above-23k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bitcoin</a>. TRX price could accelerate lower if there is a move below $0.0585.</em></p>
<h2>Tron Price Analysis</h2>
<p>This past week, tron price started a steady increase above the $0.0600 resistance level against the US Dollar. TRX price struggled to gain pace for more gains and formed a top near $0.0640.</p>
<p>The price started a fresh decline below the $0.0620 level. There was a move below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.0589 swing low to $0.0636 high. Besides, there was also a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $0.0620 on the 4-hours chart.</p>
<p>The price is now trading below $0.0620 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-bulls-in-control-above-0-06/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. On the upside, TRX is facing resistance near the $0.0620 level.</p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $0.0635 level. A close above $0.0635 and $0.0640 is a must for a fresh increase. In the stated case, the price could rise towards the $0.0680 resistance in the near term.</p>
<p>On the downside, an initial support is near the $0.0600 level. It is near the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $0.0589 swing low to $0.0636 high. The next major support is now forming near $0.0585. If there is a downside break below the $0.0585 support, the price might revisit the $0.0550 support. Any more losses might call for a move towards the $0.0520 zone in the near term.</p>
<div id="attachment_76667" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/TRON-TRX-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76667" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-76667" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/TRON-TRX-3.png" alt="Tron (TRX) Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76667" class="wp-caption-text">Tron (TRX) Price</p></div>
<p>The <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/TRXUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a> indicates that TRX price is now trading below $0.0620 and near the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could continue to move down if it breaks the $0.0585 support zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for TRX/USD is slowly gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI &#8211; The RSI for TRX/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $0.0585 and $0.0550.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $0.0620, $0.0635 and $0.0680.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-decline-could-extend-to-0-055/">Tron (TRX) Price Analysis: Decline Could Extend To $0.055</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tron-trx-price-analysis-decline-could-extend-to-0-055/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Aims More Gains above $23K</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-more-gains-above-23k/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-more-gains-above-23k/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 05:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76662</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price started a fresh increase from the $20,400 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading above $22,000 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $22,450 on the 4-hours chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase). The pair could<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-more-gains-above-23k/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-more-gains-above-23k/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Aims More Gains above $23K</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin price started a fresh increase from the $20,400 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $22,000 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $22,450 on the 4-hours chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Coinbase).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move up if it stays above the $21,500 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Bitcoin price is rising above $22,000 against the US Dollar. BTC might extend gains if there is a clear move above the $23,375 resistance zone.</em></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price started a <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-rally-could-extend-above-22k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">fresh increase</a> from the $20,400 support zone. A base was formed and the price climbed higher above the $21,500 resistance zone.</p>
<p>The bulls pushed the price above the $22,000 resistance and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). The upward move was such that the price climbed towards the $23,400 resistance zone. A high is formed near $23,375 and the price is now consolidating gains.</p>
<p>There was a minor move below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $20,370 swing low to $23,375 high. It is now trading above $22,000 and the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-climbs-and-aims-steady-increase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">55 simple moving average (4-hours)</a>. There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support near $22,450 on the 4-hours chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>An immediate resistance on the upside is near the $22,850 level. The next major resistance might near the $23,000 zone. The first major resistance is near the $23,400 level. A clear move above the $23,400 level might send the price towards $24,000, above which the price might rise towards the $25,000 level.</p>
<p>Any more gains might push the price towards the $26,200 zone. If there is no upside break, the price might decline below the $22,500 level. The first major support is near $22,000 or the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $20,370 swing low to $23,375 high.</p>
<p>The next key support is near the $21,500 level, below which the price might accelerate lower. In the stated case, the price could decline towards the $20,400 level. Any more losses might send the price towards the $20,000 level.</p>
<div id="attachment_76663" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Bitcoin-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-76663" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-76663" src="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/https://s3.amazonaws.com/lbn-s3/2023/01/Bitcoin-3.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" /></a><p id="caption-attachment-76663" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Price</p></div>
<p>Looking at the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XBTUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener follow" data-wpel-link="exclude">chart</a>, bitcoin price is clearly trading above $22,000 and the 55 simple moving average (4-hours). Overall, the price could continue to move up if it stays above the $21,500 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Indicators</h2>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Key Support Levels – $22,400 and $21,500.</p>
<p>Key Resistance Levels – $22,850, $23,400 and $25,000.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-more-gains-above-23k/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Aims More Gains above $23K</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-aims-more-gains-above-23k/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Federal Reserve and Other Agencies Are Warning Banks About Crypto</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-federal-reserve-and-other-regulators-are-warning-banks-about-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-federal-reserve-and-other-regulators-are-warning-banks-about-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 17:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[federal reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76323</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>U.S. regulators like the Federal Reserve, the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, and the Office of the Comptroller of the Currency have established a joint statement warning banks all over the world about the alleged risks and problems that come with crypto trading. The Federal Reserve Feels Crypto Is Problematic These agencies say that banks need<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-federal-reserve-and-other-regulators-are-warning-banks-about-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-federal-reserve-and-other-regulators-are-warning-banks-about-crypto/">The Federal Reserve and Other Agencies Are Warning Banks About Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>U.S. regulators like the Federal Reserve, the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, and the Office of the Comptroller of the Currency have <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/personalfinance/us-regulators-warn-banks-over-cryptocurrency-risks/ar-AA15WYvb" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">established a joint statement</a> warning banks all over the world about the alleged risks and problems that come with crypto trading.</p>
<h2>The Federal Reserve Feels Crypto Is Problematic</h2>
<p>These agencies say that banks need to take these risks seriously and implement the necessary security measures to keep themselves and their customers safe. The statement read:</p>
<blockquote><p>The events of the past year have been marked by significant volatility and the exposure of vulnerabilities in the crypto asset sector… It is important that risks related to the crypto asset sector that cannot be mitigated or controlled do not migrate to the banking system.</p></blockquote>
<p>The events of the past year have got plenty of traders, and above all, legislators a little spooked. For one thing, 2022 was marred by some of the worst volatility the crypto arena has ever seen, with assets like bitcoin losing more than 70 percent of their value. BTC hit a new all-time high of about $68,000 per unit in November of 2021, though it entered the new year on a down note, and by the time 2022 was over, it had fallen into the mid-$16K range.</p>
<p>Things didn’t stop there, however. The rest of the crypto industry followed in BTC’s footsteps, and the space has lost more than $2 trillion in valuation in under a year. It’s a sad and ugly sight to see.</p>
<p>In addition, 2022 saw several <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">bankruptcies</a> and elements of fraud. While criminal activity has always been a problem in the crypto arena, nothing could have prepared the world for what would happen with FTX, the now fallen crypto exchange that rose to fruition in just three short years.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, the company’s chief executive Sam Bankman-Fried <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-ftx-exec-sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-fraud/" data-wpel-link="internal">has been charged with</a> eight counts of fraud and conspiracy, though he has recently entered a plea of not guilty. It is alleged he used customer funds to purchase lavish Bahamian real estate.</p>
<h2>You Caused a Lot of These Issues!</h2>
<p>At the same time, there is irony in that some of the agencies issuing the statement – such as the Federal Reserve – are responsible for the very crypto problems they’re pointing out. While many contributing factors led to bitcoin’s demise in 2022, one big one was the fact that the Federal Reserve continued to <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/bitcoin-slated-to-suffer-in-2022-thanks-to-federal-reserve-rate-hikes/" data-wpel-link="internal">hike rates as a means</a> of dealing with inflation.</p>
<p>The tactic proved relatively useless, as everyday Americans are still witnessing higher prices at grocery stores and they can no longer afford homes. The side effect of these ongoing rate hikes is that bitcoin has ultimately taken a turn for the worse and will need a lot of recovery time if it’s ever to achieve its previous all-time high again.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-federal-reserve-and-other-regulators-are-warning-banks-about-crypto/">The Federal Reserve and Other Agencies Are Warning Banks About Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/the-federal-reserve-and-other-regulators-are-warning-banks-about-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Some Want the Crypto Moratorium in New York to Last Longer</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/some-want-the-crypto-moratorium-in-new-york-to-last-longer/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/some-want-the-crypto-moratorium-in-new-york-to-last-longer/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 15:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mine Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Moratorium]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New York]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76319</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, the state of New York imposed a moratorium on crypto mining, thus barring any firms that did not fully rely on clean energy from entering its borders and setting up shop. Initially, the ban was set to last a total of two years, though now, local legislators are considering extending the ban.<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/some-want-the-crypto-moratorium-in-new-york-to-last-longer/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/some-want-the-crypto-moratorium-in-new-york-to-last-longer/">Some Want the Crypto Moratorium in New York to Last Longer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Not long ago, the state of New York <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/new-york-signs-crypto-moratorium-into-law/" data-wpel-link="internal">imposed a moratorium on</a> crypto mining, thus barring any firms that did not fully rely on clean energy from entering its borders and setting up shop. Initially, the ban was set to last a total of two years, though now, local legislators are <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/massena-town-board-holding-hearing-232100463.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="follow noopener">considering extending the ban</a>.</p>
<h2>The New York Crypto Moratorium Could Be Extended</h2>
<p>A town board meeting has been put on the calendar regarding the moratorium in the region of Massena. Town supervisor Susan J. Bellor explained in an interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>We have a public hearing scheduled for next Tuesday when we have our organizational meeting. After our installation of both Francis and Debra, we&#8217;ll get right to the public hearing on that.</p></blockquote>
<p>The goal is to keep the moratorium in place until official crypto regulation can be introduced. Bellor and her fellow council members believe local laws need to be established that can fully monitor the crypto space in New York and preside over statewide operations. She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>It was good to hear that panel of speakers talking about the pros and cons and how they want to get those regulations done.</p></blockquote>
<p>She has also invited members of the public to address her with their thoughts and concerns, claiming:</p>
<blockquote><p>Some show up, some send me an email, some send me regular mail. Whatever works.</p></blockquote>
<p>Resident David Felton says he’s concerned about all the crypto bankruptcies that have been occurring as of late. He says crypto laws need to be in place to not only protect the companies, but to ensure users or customers of these companies receive their dues should the enterprises decide to close their doors and go bankrupt themselves. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think that is a major problem. You&#8217;re taking the risk where right now there&#8217;s no government regulations. You&#8217;re perpetuating an industry that doesn&#8217;t have any protection. They can go bankrupt very easily. You&#8217;re supporting that. I do not think it&#8217;s a very good idea.</p></blockquote>
<p>Town attorney Eric J. Gustafson also commented that regulations are close to being established, suggesting:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think we&#8217;re just about there. We&#8217;ve got some work to do. They&#8217;re waiting for a draft of cryptocurrency mining operations from me. I have a draft that I think is almost ready for their consideration. I&#8217;m just not quite ready, but we&#8217;re close. I think the January timeframe will give us enough time to finalize the regulations, have the committee review it, and then have it out for public hearing sometime… so that it can be adopted.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A State That&#8217;s Always Been Against Crypto?</h2>
<p>New York is the first state to impose such a ban. The Empire State has long had a strained relationship with crypto beginning with the implementation of its <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/tag/bitlicense/" data-wpel-link="internal">BitLicense</a> in 2015.</p>
<p>This caused several digital asset firms to pack up and leave the region.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/some-want-the-crypto-moratorium-in-new-york-to-last-longer/">Some Want the Crypto Moratorium in New York to Last Longer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/some-want-the-crypto-moratorium-in-new-york-to-last-longer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former FTX Exec Sam Bankman-Fried Enters Not Guilty Plea</title>
		<link>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-ftx-exec-sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-fraud/</link>
					<comments>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-ftx-exec-sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-fraud/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nick Marinoff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 13:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Wang]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/?p=76315</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sam Bankman-Fried – the former head executive of the now fallen crypto exchange FTX – has pleaded not guilty to all counts of fraud. This means his case will potentially be heard by a jury. Sam Bankman-Fried Says He&#8217;s Not Guilty During a recent testimony, Bankman-Fried refused to speak for himself. Instead, it was his<a class="read-more" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-ftx-exec-sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-fraud/" data-wpel-link="internal">...</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-ftx-exec-sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-fraud/">Former FTX Exec Sam Bankman-Fried Enters Not Guilty Plea</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sam Bankman-Fried – the former head executive of the now fallen crypto exchange FTX – has pleaded not guilty to all <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/ftx-crypto-ceo-sam-bankman-fried-expected-to-plead-not-guilty-in-court-tuesday/ar-AA15UZpS" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">counts of fraud</a>. This means his case will potentially be heard by a jury.</p>
<h2>Sam Bankman-Fried Says He&#8217;s Not Guilty</h2>
<p>During a recent testimony, Bankman-Fried refused to speak for himself. Instead, it was his lawyer Mark Cohen who entered the not guilty plea on his behalf. Bankman-Fried’s mother was in attendance and sitting behind her son as the <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/lewis-kaplan-will-be-the-judge-to-oversee-ftx-court-case/" data-wpel-link="internal">judge who will preside</a> over the former crypto head’s case – Lewis Kaplan – monitored the courtroom.</p>
<p>Sam Bankman-Fried currently faces eight separate charges of fraud and conspiracy. Federal prosecutors say the crypto executive engaged in one of the biggest digital currency fraud schemes in the history of the space.</p>
<p>It is alleged that billions of dollars in customer funds were taken from the exchange and moved to Alameda Research, another company founded by SBF. Both enterprises were supposed to remain separate. By conjoining them through financial procedures, Bankman-Fried is alleged to have taken part in illegal activity.</p>
<p>Furthermore, SBF has also been accused of spending millions of dollars belonging to customers on lavish real estate in the Bahamas and making million-dollar <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/sam-bankman-fried-gave-a-lot-of-money-to-democrats-what-will-they-do-with-it/" data-wpel-link="internal">political donations to various</a> democrat candidates in both 2020 and 2022.</p>
<p>Sam Bankman-Fried will likely find no help from his former employees Caroline Ellison and Gary Wang, who served as the CEO of Alameda and the co-founder of FTX, respectively. Both Ellison and Wang have entered guilty pleas, with Ellison facing seven counts and Wang facing four.</p>
<p>In her testimony, Ellison stated the following:</p>
<blockquote><p>We prepared certain quarterly balance sheets that concealed the extent of Alameda&#8217;s borrowing and the billions of dollars in loans that Alameda had made to FTX executives and to related parties. I also understood that FTX had not disclosed to FTX&#8217;s equity investors that Alameda could borrow a potentially unlimited amount from FTX, thereby putting customer assets at risk.</p></blockquote>
<p>FTX is likely to go down in history as one of the biggest crypto embarrassments the space has ever seen. The exchange, barely three years old, rose to fruition in 2019 and quickly became one of the world’s top five digital exchanges. SBF was lauded as a genius, and prior to his company’s fall, his net worth was valued at several billion dollars.</p>
<h2>Two Months of Trouble So Far</h2>
<p>However, trouble began in mid-November of last year when Bankman-Fried complained of a liquidity crunch online and said he needed <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-i-the-fall-of-a-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">fast cash to</a> keep the company afloat. He approached his larger rival Binance to see if it’d be interested in buying his enterprise out, <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/ftx-drama-part-iii-the-rise-and-fall-of-sam-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="internal">though the firm backed</a> away, claiming the issues it was facing were too big.</p>
<p>From there, FTX had no <a href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/what-will-happen-now-that-ftx-is-bankrupt/" data-wpel-link="internal">choice but to file bankruptcy</a>, and SBF quickly resigned from his post.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-ftx-exec-sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-fraud/">Former FTX Exec Sam Bankman-Fried Enters Not Guilty Plea</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.livebitcoinnews.com">Live Bitcoin News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.livebitcoinnews.com/former-ftx-exec-sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-fraud/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
