<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 11:23:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Sees Juicy Capital Inflows &#8211; An Imminent Rebound in Sight?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-sees-juicy-capital-inflows/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 11:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=534005</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) has recently caught the attention of investors as its chart reflects a significant surge in capital inflows and buying pressure. These developments have left many speculators wondering if this positive momentum will be sufficient to initiate a much-anticipated price rebound.  With increased interest and activity surrounding Shiba Inu, all eyes are now focused on whether this surge in support will ultimately lead to a revitalization of the cryptocurrency&#8217;s fortunes. Related Reading: Ethereum Whale Resurfaces After 2-Year Hiatus, Stakes $7.4 Million In ETH Shiba Inu Price Consolidation And Increased Capital Inflows Shiba Inu, over the past few days, has witnessed relatively low volatility on higher timeframe price charts. From May 8 onwards, its price has oscillated within a range of $0.00000832 and $0.00000914, indicating a period of consolidation. At the time of writing, CoinGecko reflects Shiba Inu&#8217;s price at a mere $0.00000871. In the past 24 hours, the cryptocurrency experienced a slight slump of 1.4%. The meme coin was up a very modest 0.3% over the course of the last seven days. Source: Coingecko Despite the recent price consolidation, the daily chart&#8217;s CMF (Chaikin Money Flow) and RSI (Relative Strength Index) have shown notable upward movements in the past few days. The CMF suggests increased capital inflows, while the RSI indicates rising buying pressure. SHIB Potential Rally Based On Fib Retracement, Market Conditions To analyze the potential price movement of Shiba Inu, traders have utilized the Fibonacci retracement tool by placing it between the swing high of the first quarter (Q1) and the lows observed in December. This tool helps identify crucial levels based on the Fibonacci sequence. If the current trend in SHIB continues and the overall macro environment conditions continue to improve, there is a possibility of a rally. This rally could lead SHIB to reach the 23.6% Fibonacci retracement level, which stands at approximately $0.00000967. Fibonacci retracement levels are commonly used in technical analysis to identify potential support and resistance levels based on the historical price movement. The 23.6% level often represents an initial area of interest where a significant rebound or reversal could occur. SHIB market cap nearly unchanged at $5.22 billion. Chart: TradingView.com Related Reading: Bitcoin ‘Shrimp’ Catch Soars To All-Time High Of 1.31 Million Coins – Details Factors Influencing SHIB&#8217;s Potential Rally The realization of this potential rally in SHIB is contingent upon various factors, including the continuation of the current trend, market sentiment, and broader macroeconomic conditions. Positive developments and easing conditions could contribute to an upward movement in SHIB&#8217;s price. As traders and investors monitor these factors and the Fibonacci retracement levels, they will closely observe whether SHIB can indeed rally to the 23.6% Fib level, and if so, what implications it may have for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s future trajectory. -Featured image from Nairametrics]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB) has recently caught the attention of investors as its chart reflects a significant surge in capital inflows and buying pressure. These developments have left many speculators wondering if this positive momentum will be sufficient to initiate a much-anticipated price rebound. </p>
<p>With increased interest and activity surrounding Shiba Inu, all eyes are now focused on whether this surge in support will ultimately lead to a revitalization of the cryptocurrency&#8217;s fortunes.</p>

<h2><strong>Shiba Inu Price Consolidation And Increased Capital Inflows</strong></h2>
<p>Shiba Inu, over the past few days, has witnessed relatively low volatility on higher timeframe price charts. From May 8 onwards, its price has oscillated within a range of $0.00000832 and $0.00000914, indicating a period of consolidation.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/shiba-inu" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a> reflects Shiba Inu&#8217;s price at a mere $0.00000871. In the past 24 hours, the cryptocurrency experienced a slight slump of 1.4%. The meme coin was up a very modest 0.3% over the course of the last seven days.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-534007" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-116.png" alt="" width="1135" height="61" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-116.png 1135w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-116-460x25.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-116-860x46.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-116-768x41.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-116-750x40.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1135px) 100vw, 1135px"/></p>

<p>Despite the recent price consolidation, the daily chart&#8217;s CMF (Chaikin Money Flow) and RSI (Relative Strength Index) have shown notable upward movements in the past few days. The CMF suggests increased capital inflows, while the RSI indicates rising buying pressure.</p>
<h2><strong>SHIB Potential Rally Based On Fib Retracement, Market Conditions</strong></h2>
<p>To analyze the potential price movement of Shiba Inu, traders have utilized the Fibonacci retracement tool by placing it between the swing high of the first quarter (Q1) and the lows observed in December. This tool helps identify crucial levels based on the Fibonacci sequence.</p>
<p>If the current trend in SHIB continues and the overall macro environment conditions continue to improve, there is a <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/shiba-inu-stuck-below-23-6-fib-level-what-to-expect-next/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">possibility of a rally.</a> This rally could lead SHIB to reach the 23.6% Fibonacci retracement level, which stands at approximately $0.00000967.</p>
<p>Fibonacci retracement levels are commonly used in technical analysis to identify potential support and resistance levels based on the historical price movement. The 23.6% level often represents an initial area of interest where a significant rebound or reversal could occur.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/BnKeG3C9/" width="2047" height="979"/></p>


<strong>Factors Influencing SHIB&#8217;s Potential Rally</strong>
<p>The realization of this potential rally in SHIB is contingent upon various factors, including the continuation of the current trend, market sentiment, and broader macroeconomic conditions. Positive developments and easing conditions could contribute to an upward movement in SHIB&#8217;s price.</p>
<p>As traders and investors monitor these factors and the Fibonacci retracement levels, they will closely observe whether SHIB can indeed rally to the 23.6% Fib level, and if so, what implications it may have for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s future trajectory.</p>
<p><em>-Featured image from Nairametrics</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-117-460x228.png" width="460" height="228" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Dominance: Binance Receives Deluge Of Millions Of DOGE &#8211; Details</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin-binance-receives-millions-of-doge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 10:49:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doge price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533991</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE) has been embarking on a relentless quest for a price surge in recent weeks. As the market witnessed a flurry of activity, an unexpected twist unfolded when an anonymous whale made a significant decision—to sell a portion of their coveted meme coins.  In a move that raised eyebrows, one of these hefty Dogecoin holdings found its way to crypto exchange Binance, setting the stage for intrigue and speculation.  This interesting development came at a time when Dogecoin was fiercely determined to regain its footing and recoup some of the losses it had endured in recent weeks. Related Reading: Ethereum Whale Resurfaces After 2-Year Hiatus, Stakes $7.4 Million In ETH Dogecoin Whales Make Waves: Massive DOGE Transfers Raise Eyebrows In a series of transactions, the Dogecoin community has been abuzz with news of substantial transfers involving the popular meme-inspired cryptocurrency. Crypto platform @DogeWhaleAlert, known for tracking large DOGE transfers on Twitter, has recently reported multiple colossal movements of DOGE across wallets, with a cumulative total exceeding 100 million DOGE. 🐕🪙🐋🚨 14,835,380 $DOGE ($1,103,737 USD) was transferred from multiple wallets to a #Binance wallet. Fee: 1.00 ($0.07 USD) Tx: https://t.co/4lBCExiwYT#DogecoinWhaleAlert #WhaleAlert #Dogecoin #CryptoNews — Ðogecoin Whale Alert (@DogeWhaleAlert) May 17, 2023 Among the notable transactions, one of the largest transfers involved a staggering 14,835,380 DOGE, making its way to Binance. On the other end of the spectrum, the smallest transaction consisted of a still impressive 10,000,000 DOGE. Over a span of 24 hours, a total of five major transfers of the meme coin DOGE took place, as substantial chunks of cryptocurrency ranging from 10 million to 30 million DOGE were swiftly shifted between wallets.  The flurry of activity has piqued the interest of the Dogecoin community and the wider crypto sphere, as they eagerly analyze the implications of these substantial movements. DOGE Whale Behavior Sends Ripples Through The Market: Impact On Price The recent surge of large-scale DOGE transfers by anonymous whales has not gone unnoticed, and their behavior has sent ripples through the cryptocurrency market. Unsurprisingly, the market has reacted to the recent whale transfers, resulting in notable price volatility for Dogecoin. The price of DOGE, as reported by CoinGecko, experienced a slight 0.7% slump in the past 24 hours. This downturn is likely attributed, at least in part, to the influx of substantial DOGE holdings hitting exchanges and potentially creating selling pressure. DOGE market cap currently at $10 billion. Chart: TradingView.com Related Reading: PEPE Outperforms Bitcoin In Social Media Buzz, Triggers Bullish Run For Frog Coin However, the broader trend for Dogecoin remains positive, with a 2.7% rally over the past seven days. This upward momentum, coupled with increased adoption and renewed interest in DOGE, may indicate that the impact of the whale transfers on the overall price has been mitigated by bullish market sentiment. Until then, observers will continue to dissect the actions of these anonymous whales, searching for insights and anticipating the next twist in the ever-evolving tale of Dogecoin. -Featured image from Cryptoglobe]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dogecoin (DOGE) has been embarking on a relentless quest for a price surge in recent weeks. As the market witnessed a flurry of activity, an unexpected twist unfolded when an anonymous whale made a significant decision—to sell a portion of their coveted meme coins. </p>
<p>In a move that raised eyebrows, one of these hefty Dogecoin holdings found its way to crypto exchange Binance, setting the stage for intrigue and speculation. </p>
<p>This interesting development came at a time when Dogecoin was fiercely determined to regain its footing and recoup some of the losses it had endured in recent weeks.</p>



<h2><strong>Dogecoin Whales Make Waves: Massive DOGE Transfers Raise Eyebrows</strong></h2>
<p>In a series of transactions, the Dogecoin community has been abuzz with news of substantial transfers involving the popular meme-inspired cryptocurrency. Crypto platform @DogeWhaleAlert, known for tracking large DOGE transfers on Twitter, has recently reported multiple colossal movements of DOGE across wallets, with a cumulative total exceeding 100 million DOGE.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f415.png" alt="🐕" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1fa99.png" alt="🪙" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f40b.png" alt="🐋" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>14,835,380 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24DOGE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$DOGE</a> ($1,103,737 USD) was transferred from multiple wallets to a <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Binance</a> wallet.</p>
<p>Fee: 1.00 ($0.07 USD)</p>
<p>Tx: <a href="https://t.co/4lBCExiwYT" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/4lBCExiwYT</a><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/DogecoinWhaleAlert?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#DogecoinWhaleAlert</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/WhaleAlert?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#WhaleAlert</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Dogecoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Dogecoin</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/CryptoNews?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#CryptoNews</a></p>
<p>— Ðogecoin Whale Alert (@DogeWhaleAlert) <a href="https://twitter.com/DogeWhaleAlert/status/1658880286644420608?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Among the notable transactions, <a href="https://twitter.com/DogeWhaleAlert/status/1658880286644420608" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">one of the largest transfers</a> involved a staggering 14,835,380 DOGE, making its way to Binance. On the other end of the spectrum, the smallest transaction consisted of a still impressive 10,000,000 DOGE.</p>
<p>Over a span of 24 hours, a total of five major transfers of the meme coin DOGE took place, as substantial chunks of cryptocurrency ranging from 10 million to 30 million DOGE were swiftly shifted between wallets. </p>
<p>The flurry of activity has piqued the interest of the Dogecoin community and the wider crypto sphere, as they eagerly analyze the implications of these substantial movements.</p>
<h2><strong>DOGE Whale Behavior Sends Ripples Through The Market: Impact On Price</strong></h2>
<p>The recent surge of large-scale DOGE transfers by anonymous whales has not gone unnoticed, and their behavior has sent ripples through the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p>Unsurprisingly, the market has reacted to the recent whale transfers, resulting in notable price volatility for Dogecoin. The price of DOGE, as reported by <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/dogecoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a>, experienced a slight 0.7% slump in the past 24 hours. This downturn is likely attributed, at least in part, to the influx of substantial DOGE holdings hitting exchanges and potentially creating selling pressure.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/mibX9dmJ/" width="2047" height="979"/></p>


<p>However, the broader trend for Dogecoin remains positive, with a 2.7% rally over the past seven days. This upward momentum, coupled with increased adoption and renewed interest in DOGE, may indicate that the impact of the whale transfers on the overall price has been mitigated by bullish market sentiment.</p>
<p>Until then, observers will continue to dissect the actions of these anonymous whales, searching for insights and anticipating the next twist in the ever-evolving tale of Dogecoin.</p>
<p><em>-Featured image from Cryptoglobe</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-115-460x273.png" width="460" height="273" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin &#8216;Shrimp&#8217; Catch Soars To All-Time High Of 1.31 Million Coins &#8211; Details</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-shrimp-accumulation-surge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 07:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shrimp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533946</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) shrimp investors, affectionately dubbed the &#8220;underdogs&#8221; of the cryptocurrency world, are making waves in the market as they steadily accumulate the digital asset at an unprecedented rate.  These smaller investors, often overlooked in favor of institutional giants, have recently reached a significant milestone, with the total supply of Bitcoin held by them surging to an all-time high of 1.31 million coins.  This surge not only highlights the growing influence of retail investors in the volatile world of cryptocurrencies but also underscores their determination to ride the Bitcoin wave alongside their more affluent counterparts. Related Reading: Conflux Network Partners With China Telecom For Blockchain, SIM Project – Details The Rise Of Bitcoin Shrimp Investors According to data analytics firm Glassnode, these shrimp investors have surged to an all-time high (ATH) of 1.31 million coins. The continuous rise in their holdings highlights their growing influence and raises intriguing questions about the evolving dynamics within the Bitcoin ecosystem. The #Bitcoin supply held by Shrimp Entities (&#60;1 BTC) continues to relentlessly rise, expanding to an ATH of 1.31M coins. The cohort is currently experiencing a significant expansion of +26K coins per month, with only 202 (3.9%) trading days recording a larger monthly growth. pic.twitter.com/Fa2QCHxZPO — glassnode (@glassnode) May 18, 2023 The data further reveals that shrimp investors are adding an average of approximately 26,000 Bitcoins to their cumulative holdings each month. This significant expansion is worth noting, considering that only 3.9% of trading days, equivalent to 202 days, have witnessed a larger monthly growth rate.  These statistics underline the sustained interest in Bitcoin among retail investors, who remain undeterred by its well-known price volatility. The Shrimp Investor Effect On BTC Price Dynamics Bitcoin&#8217;s price, as reported by CoinGecko, currently stands at $26,914, reflecting a slight 1.1% decline over the past 24 hours, while the cryptocurrency was up 1.4% over the last seven days. Source: Coingecko The surge in shrimp investors, indicated by their increasing accumulation of Bitcoin, can have multiple impacts on the current price of BTC. The sustained interest and continuous buying pressure from shrimp investors can contribute to upward price momentum. As more retail investors enter the market and acquire Bitcoin, the increased demand can drive the price higher.  This influx of buyers, particularly if they are accumulating the cryptocurrency at an unprecedented rate, as mentioned earlier, can create a bullish sentiment that attracts further investors and potentially leads to price appreciation. BTCUSD backpedals to the $26K level. Chart: TradingView.com Related Reading: Ethereum Whale Resurfaces After 2-Year Hiatus, Stakes $7.4 Million In ETH Conversely, the impact of shrimp investors on the price of BTC can be influenced by market dynamics and investor sentiment. While their accumulation may indicate growing interest, the overall sentiment in the market, including the actions of larger institutional investors or regulatory developments, can also influence the price.  If negative news or a general bearish sentiment prevails, it can offset the impact of shrimp investors and result in a more stagnant or declining price. -Featured image from DELAYNA EARLEY / THE ISLAND PACKET VIA AP]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC) shrimp investors, affectionately dubbed the &#8220;underdogs&#8221; of the cryptocurrency world, are making waves in the market as they steadily accumulate the digital asset at an unprecedented rate. </p>
<p>These smaller investors, often overlooked in favor of institutional giants, have recently reached a significant milestone, with the total supply of Bitcoin held by them surging to an all-time high of 1.31 million coins. </p>
<p>This surge not only highlights the growing influence of retail investors in the volatile world of cryptocurrencies but also underscores their determination to ride the Bitcoin wave alongside their more affluent counterparts.</p>

<h2><strong>The Rise Of Bitcoin Shrimp Investors</strong></h2>
<p>According to data analytics firm <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1659279592899637253" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Glassnode</a>, these shrimp investors have surged to an all-time high (ATH) of 1.31 million coins. The continuous rise in their holdings highlights their growing influence and raises intriguing questions about the evolving dynamics within the Bitcoin ecosystem.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">The <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Bitcoin</a> supply held by Shrimp Entities (&lt;1 BTC) continues to relentlessly rise, expanding to an ATH of 1.31M coins.</p>
<p>The cohort is currently experiencing a significant expansion of +26K coins per month, with only 202 (3.9%) trading days recording a larger monthly growth. <a href="https://t.co/Fa2QCHxZPO" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/Fa2QCHxZPO</a></p>
<p>— glassnode (@glassnode) <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1659279592899637253?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 18, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>The data further reveals that shrimp investors are adding an average of approximately 26,000 Bitcoins to their cumulative holdings each month. This significant expansion is worth noting, considering that only 3.9% of trading days, equivalent to 202 days, have witnessed a larger monthly growth rate. </p>
<p>These statistics underline the sustained interest in Bitcoin among retail investors, who remain undeterred by its well-known price volatility.</p>
<h2><strong>The Shrimp Investor Effect On BTC Price Dynamics</strong></h2>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price, as reported by <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/bitcoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a>, currently stands at $26,914, reflecting a slight 1.1% decline over the past 24 hours, while the cryptocurrency was up 1.4% over the last seven days.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-533950" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-113.png" alt="" width="1133" height="65" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-113.png 1133w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-113-460x26.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-113-860x49.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-113-768x44.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-113-750x43.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1133px) 100vw, 1133px"/></p>

<p>The surge in shrimp investors, indicated by their increasing accumulation of Bitcoin, can have multiple impacts on the current price of BTC.</p>
<p>The sustained interest and continuous buying pressure from shrimp investors can contribute to upward price momentum. As more retail investors enter the market and acquire Bitcoin, the increased demand can drive the price higher. </p>
<p>This influx of buyers, particularly if they are accumulating the cryptocurrency at an unprecedented rate, as mentioned earlier, can create a bullish sentiment that attracts further investors and potentially leads to price appreciation.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/8XAYP7oe/" width="2047" height="979"/></p>


<p>Conversely, the impact of shrimp investors on the price of BTC can be influenced by market dynamics and investor sentiment. While their accumulation may indicate growing interest, the overall sentiment in the market, including the actions of larger institutional investors or regulatory developments, can also influence the price. </p>
<p>If negative news or a general bearish sentiment prevails, it can offset the impact of shrimp investors and result in a more stagnant or declining price.</p>
<p><em>-Featured image from DELAYNA EARLEY / THE ISLAND PACKET VIA AP</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-114-460x304.png" width="460" height="304" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Web3 Reinvented: Polygon Labs, Sequence Join Forces To Transform Infrastructure</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/web3-reinvented-polygon-labs-sequence-join-forces-to-transform-infrastructure/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 05:55:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web 3]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533940</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Web3 industry offers a diverse range of services, creating a dynamic landscape for individuals. A notable development in this space is the recent partnership announcement by Horizon, the creators of Sequence, aimed at redefining Web3 infrastructure. This collaboration has had a significant impact, particularly on Polygon&#8217;s governance token MATIC, which experienced a notable increase of nearly 3% within the past 24 hours. This bolstering of the infrastructure signifies a positive step forward for the Web3 ecosystem. Source: Coingecko This development came a day after Polygon’s blog post detailing the release of the v0.9 Testnet for Polygon’s Supernets. Once the final release of Supernets is launched, this partnership will surely affect the dominance of Polygon in the Web3 space.  Web3: Scalability, Seamlessness For Developers On Polygon The seamless integration of Sequence’s smart wallet and infrastructure stack on Polygon Supernets will pull business enterprises into the ecosystem. Polygon Supernets are custom-built blockchains for specific apps. The most important of these customizations is a custom blockspace, ensuring that the user experience isn’t affected by bumps in activity on-chain.  Sequence’s all-in-one development stack is the main attraction for both developers and investors. It is a complete package, covering tokens and NFTs to SDKs, the stack will fuel on-chain development as the release of Polygon Supernets nears.  To further push growth, both Polygon and Sequence will offer credits to incentivize developers to build on the platform. In doing so, the strategic alliance will have a strong effect on how quickly the Web3 infrastructure will improve.  .@AntimetalCloud launched its AI-powered cloud cost optimization platform, with an incredible $4.3M seed funding round led by @hiFramework☁️ 👉🏾We&#8217;re thrilled to have invested in Antimetal’s vision, driving innovation &#38; empowering the tech ecosystem More: https://t.co/beRTvlkVRE pic.twitter.com/TxJdJN76qv — Polygon (Labs) (@0xPolygonLabs) May 17, 2023 This isn’t the only move by Polygon to improve Web3 infrastructure. Recently, Polygon invested in Antimetal, a cloud-based platform, in a seed funding round led by Framework Ventures. With Polygon’s entry into the world of cloud infrastructure, we might see more developments in the space led by Polygon itself in the near future.  MATIC total market cap at $8.09 billion. Chart: TradingView.com Related Reading: Ethereum Whale Resurfaces After 2-Year Hiatus, Stakes $7.4 Million In ETH Investors Should Watch This Level  At the moment, MATIC is supported on the $0.8339 level which is crucial for ensuring future gain. However, the current market structure is bearish, supporting the bears in the short to medium term. Thus, MATIC bulls should defend $0.8339 as much as possible.  With on and off-chain developments backing the token, MATIC might see a return to $1 in the coming days or weeks. Despite this, investors should be cautious in the short to medium term. Ethereum’s recent upward swing caused the altcoin market to follow as well.  If these price swings continue to move upward, MATIC’s rise to $1 is secured. With the market showing signs of strength, investors and traders should be able to enjoy gains in the long term.  -Featured image from DailyCoin]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Web3 industry offers a diverse range of services, creating a dynamic landscape for individuals. A notable development in this space is the recent partnership <a href="https://medium.com/0xsequence/sequence-x-polygon-labs-join-forces-to-revolutionize-web3-infrastructure-4b2cb17aaa0b" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announcement</a> by Horizon, the creators of Sequence, aimed at redefining Web3 infrastructure.</p>
<p>This collaboration has had a significant impact, particularly on Polygon&#8217;s governance token MATIC, which experienced a notable <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/polygon" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">increase</a> of nearly 3% within the past 24 hours. This bolstering of the infrastructure signifies a positive step forward for the Web3 ecosystem.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-533942" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-110.png" alt="" width="1135" height="61" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-110.png 1135w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-110-460x25.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-110-860x46.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-110-768x41.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-110-750x40.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1135px) 100vw, 1135px"/></p>

<p>This development came a day after Polygon’s <a href="https://polygon.technology/blog/whats-new-in-polygon-supernets-v0-9-release" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">blog post</a> detailing the release of the v0.9 Testnet for Polygon’s Supernets. Once the final release of Supernets is launched, this partnership will surely affect the dominance of Polygon in the Web3 space. </p>
<h2><strong>Web3: Scalability, Seamlessness For Developers On Polygon</strong></h2>
<p>The seamless integration of Sequence’s smart wallet and infrastructure stack on Polygon Supernets will pull business enterprises into the ecosystem. <a href="https://polygon.technology/polygon-supernets" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Polygon Supernets</a> are custom-built blockchains for specific apps. The most important of these customizations is a custom blockspace, ensuring that the user experience isn’t affected by bumps in activity on-chain. </p>
<p>Sequence’s all-in-one development stack is the main attraction for both developers and investors. It is a complete package, covering tokens and NFTs to SDKs, the stack will fuel on-chain development as the release of Polygon Supernets nears. </p>
<p>To further push growth, both Polygon and Sequence will offer credits to incentivize developers to build on the platform. In doing so, the strategic alliance will have a strong effect on how quickly the Web3 infrastructure will improve. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">.<a href="https://twitter.com/AntimetalCloud?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@AntimetalCloud</a> launched its AI-powered cloud cost optimization platform, with an incredible $4.3M seed funding round led by <a href="https://twitter.com/hiFramework?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@hiFramework</a><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2601.png" alt="☁" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f449-1f3fe.png" alt="👉🏾" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />We&#8217;re thrilled to have invested in Antimetal’s vision, driving innovation &amp; empowering the tech ecosystem</p>
<p>More: <a href="https://t.co/beRTvlkVRE" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/beRTvlkVRE</a> <a href="https://t.co/TxJdJN76qv" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/TxJdJN76qv</a></p>
<p>— Polygon (Labs) (@0xPolygonLabs) <a href="https://twitter.com/0xPolygonLabs/status/1658921601759420423?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>This isn’t the only move by Polygon to improve Web3 infrastructure. Recently, Polygon <a href="https://twitter.com/0xPolygonLabs/status/1658921601759420423?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">invested</a> in Antimetal, a cloud-based platform, in a seed funding round led by <a href="https://twitter.com/hiFramework" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Framework Ventures</a>. With Polygon’s entry into the world of cloud infrastructure, we might see more developments in the space led by Polygon itself in the near future. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/TsScQkgN/" width="2047" height="979"/></p>


<h2><strong>Investors Should Watch This Level </strong></h2>
<p>At the moment, MATIC is supported on the $0.8339 level which is crucial for ensuring future gain. However, the current market structure is bearish, supporting the bears in the short to medium term. Thus, MATIC bulls should defend $0.8339 as much as possible. </p>
<p>With on and off-chain developments backing the token, MATIC might see a return to $1 in the coming days or weeks. Despite this, investors should be cautious in the short to medium term. <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/ethereum" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Ethereum’s</a> recent upward swing caused the altcoin market to follow as well. </p>
<p>If these price swings continue to move upward, MATIC’s rise to $1 is secured. With the market showing signs of strength, investors and traders should be able to enjoy gains in the long term. </p>
<p><em>-Featured image from DailyCoin</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/a-111-460x239.png" width="460" height="239" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Faces Confluence Of Bearish Factors and At Risk of Another Decline</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-bearish-1825/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 03:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533931</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum price is struggling below the $1,840 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH could decline heavily if there is a clear move below the $1,780 support. Ethereum is currently facing many hurdles near the $1,840 resistance zone. The price is trading below $1,820 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,825 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could start a fresh increase if it clears the $1,825 and $1,840 resistance levels. Ethereum Price Faces Uphill Task Ethereum’s price remained in a bearish zone below the $1,840 zone. ETH started a fresh decline below the $1,800 level and showed a few bearish signs, similar to Bitcoin. The price even declined below the $1,780 level. A low is formed near $1,772 and the price is now correcting losses. There was a move above the $1,800 level. The price cleared the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $1,834 swing high to the   $1,772 low. Ether is now trading above $1,820 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,825 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. Immediate resistance is near the $1,820 level. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $1,834 swing high to the $1,772 low. The next resistance sits near $1,825 and the trend line, above which Ethereum could rise toward $1,820. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com If there is a move above the $1,840 resistance level, the price might start a decent increase toward the $1,920 level. Any more gains above the $1,920 resistance zone could start a decent increase toward the $2,000 resistance. Fresh Decline in ETH? If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,825 resistance, it could start another decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,785 level. The next major support is near the $1,770 zone. If there is a clear move below the $1,770 support, the price could decline sharply. In the stated case, the price might drop toward the $1,720 support zone. Any more losses may perhaps take the price toward the $1,700 level in the near term. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is gaining momentum in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is below the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,770 Major Resistance Level – $1,825]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum price is struggling below the $1,840 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH could decline heavily if there is a clear move below the $1,780 support.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum is currently facing many hurdles near the $1,840 resistance zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $1,820 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,825 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a fresh increase if it clears the $1,825 and $1,840 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Faces Uphill Task</h2>
<p>Ethereum’s price remained in a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-surge-above-1850/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">bearish zone</a> below the $1,840 zone. ETH started a fresh decline below the $1,800 level and showed a few bearish signs, similar to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-rally-28k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p>The price even declined below the $1,780 level. A low is formed near $1,772 and the price is now correcting losses. There was a move above the $1,800 level. The price cleared the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $1,834 swing high to the   $1,772 low.</p>
<p>Ether is now trading above $1,820 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,825 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD.</p>
<p>Immediate resistance is near the $1,820 level. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $1,834 swing high to the $1,772 low. The next resistance sits near $1,825 and the trend line, above which Ethereum could rise toward $1,820.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-12.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-533932" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-12.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1950" height="1109" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-12.png 1950w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-12-460x262.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-12-860x489.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-12-768x437.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-12-1536x874.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-12-750x427.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-12-1140x648.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1950px) 100vw, 1950px"/></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>If there is a move above the $1,840 resistance level, the price might start a decent increase toward the $1,920 level. Any more gains above the $1,920 resistance zone could start a decent increase toward the $2,000 resistance.</p>
<h2>Fresh Decline in ETH?</h2>
<p>If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,825 resistance, it could start another decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,785 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $1,770 zone. If there is a clear move below the $1,770 support, the price could decline sharply. In the stated case, the price might drop toward the $1,720 support zone. Any more losses may perhaps take the price toward the $1,700 level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,770</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,825</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1353098829-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Topside Bias Vulnerable Unless It Surges Past $27,500</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-vulnerable-27500/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 02:43:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533928</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is struggling below $27,500. BTC is now at risk of a downside break unless there is a close above the $27,500 resistance. Bitcoin started another decline and traded below the $26,800 level. The price is trading below $27,200 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $27,320 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could start a fresh rally if it clears the $27,320 and $27,500 resistance levels. Bitcoin Price Faces Resistance Bitcoin price started a fresh decline below the $27,200 level. BTC even traded below the $26,550 support zone to set a new weekly low. A low is formed near $26,345 and the price is now attempting a fresh increase. There was a move above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $27,492 swing high to the $26,345 low. It is now trading below $27,200 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $27,320 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Bitcoin price is now struggling to clear the $27,000 resistance. It is facing barriers near the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $27,492 swing high to the $26,345 low. The next major resistance is near the $27,320 level and the trend line. A close above the $27,320 resistance might reduce selling pressure. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The next key resistance is near $27,550, above which the price might gain bullish momentum and test the $28,000 resistance. Any more gains might send the price toward the $28,500 level. Fresh Decline in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $27,320 resistance, it could start a fresh decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $26,550 level. The next major support is near the $26,350 zone, below which the price might gain bearish momentum. In the stated case, it could test the $26,000 level. Any more losses might take Bitcoin toward the $25,500 level in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now below the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $26,550, followed by $26,350. Major Resistance Levels – $27,000, $27,320, and $27,500.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is struggling below $27,500. BTC is now at risk of a downside break unless there is a close above the $27,500 resistance.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin started another decline and traded below the $26,800 level.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $27,200 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $27,320 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a fresh rally if it clears the $27,320 and $27,500 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Faces Resistance</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price started a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-rally-28k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">fresh decline</a> below the $27,200 level. BTC even traded below the $26,550 support zone to set a new weekly low.</p>
<p>A low is formed near $26,345 and the price is now attempting a fresh increase. There was a move above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $27,492 swing high to the $26,345 low. It is now trading below $27,200 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-holds-support-28k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>.</p>
<p>There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $27,320 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Bitcoin price is now struggling to clear the $27,000 resistance.</p>
<p>It is facing barriers near the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $27,492 swing high to the $26,345 low. The next major resistance is near the $27,320 level and the trend line. A close above the $27,320 resistance might reduce selling pressure.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-14.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-533929" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-14.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1950" height="1109" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-14.png 1950w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-14-460x262.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-14-860x489.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-14-768x437.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-14-1536x874.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-14-750x427.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-14-1140x648.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1950px) 100vw, 1950px"/></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The next key resistance is near $27,550, above which the price might gain bullish momentum and test the $28,000 resistance. Any more gains might send the price toward the $28,500 level.</p>
<h2>Fresh Decline in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $27,320 resistance, it could start a fresh decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $26,550 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $26,350 zone, below which the price might gain bearish momentum. In the stated case, it could test the $26,000 level. Any more losses might take Bitcoin toward the $25,500 level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $26,550, followed by $26,350.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $27,000, $27,320, and $27,500.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/shutterstock_1610297188-460x256.jpg" width="460" height="256" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>MATIC Surges Past Key Resistance Level: Can This Breakout Sustain?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/matic/matic-surges-past-key-resistance-level-can-this-breakout-sustain/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 22:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATICUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[maticusdt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533917</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The MATIC price recently broke above a key resistance level, indicating a positive development. However, its price appreciation over the past week has been modest, with only a 2% increase. MATIC has remained close to a critical support line on its daily chart despite the breakout. The technical outlook suggests that recovery might take some time as the bears dominate the price. Both demand and accumulation have decreased in the daily timeframe. Related Reading: Bitcoin Binary CDD Stays Low, Here’s What This Means While MATIC currently sits above an important resistance, the absence of buyer support could lead to a significant loss in value before any recovery occurs on the daily chart. If the bears exert further pressure, MATIC will likely resume sideways trading, fluctuating between $0.81 and $0.84. The uncertainty in the Bitcoin price movement, as it fluctuates from $27,000 and retraces from that level, has impacted altcoins, weakening their respective price action. The MATIC market capitalization has fallen, indicating a higher level of selling activity than buying activity. MATIC Price Analysis: One-Day Chart At the time of writing, MATIC was trading at $0.86. It successfully surpassed the $0.84 resistance level in the short term, but buyer sentiment remained weak. The coin&#8217;s next significant resistance is $0.87, and breaching this level could initiate a recovery trend. However, if sellers persist, the altcoin could drop toward $0.81 and potentially below $0.80. The key for the bulls to regain control of the price lies in MATIC, staying above $0.86 in the upcoming trading sessions. The trading volume of MATIC in the last session was low, indicating a lack of buying strength. Technical Analysis MATIC faced challenges in generating strong buying support throughout April and May, resulting in reduced demand. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) indicated a decline, with the indicator remaining below 40, highlighting the dominant presence of sellers in the market. Furthermore, the price dropped below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, indicating that sellers were driving the price momentum. However, if MATIC surpasses the $0.87 level, it will trade above the 20-SMA line. In contrast, the altcoin exhibited buy signals on the daily chart, albeit with a diminishing size and strength. The presence of green histograms on the Awesome Oscillator indicated buy signals for the altcoin, reflecting price momentum and potential reversals. Related Reading: Chainlink Price Consolidation Persists: Will Bulls Front A Recovery Soon? Additionally, the Bollinger Bands, which measure price volatility and the likelihood of price fluctuations, remained narrow and wide. However, the bands had a slight convergence, suggesting that the price may not undergo significant volatility or fluctuation in the immediate trading sessions. Featured Image From Adobe Stock, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The MATIC price recently broke above a key resistance level, indicating a positive development. However, its price appreciation over the past week has been modest, with only a 2% increase. MATIC has remained close to a critical support line on its daily chart despite the breakout.</p>
<p>The technical outlook suggests that recovery might take some time as the bears dominate the price. Both demand and accumulation have decreased in the daily timeframe.</p>

<p>While MATIC currently sits above an important resistance, the absence of buyer support could lead to a significant loss in value before any recovery occurs on the daily chart.</p>
<p>If the bears exert further pressure, MATIC will likely resume sideways trading, fluctuating between $0.81 and $0.84. The uncertainty in the Bitcoin price movement, as it fluctuates from $27,000 and retraces from that level, has impacted altcoins, weakening their respective price action. The MATIC market capitalization has fallen, indicating a higher level of selling activity than buying activity.</p>
<h2>MATIC Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-533918 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSD_2023-05-19_01-16-04.png" alt="MATIC" width="1816" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSD_2023-05-19_01-16-04.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSD_2023-05-19_01-16-04-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSD_2023-05-19_01-16-04-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSD_2023-05-19_01-16-04-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSD_2023-05-19_01-16-04-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSD_2023-05-19_01-16-04-750x343.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSD_2023-05-19_01-16-04-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>
<p>At the time of writing, MATIC was trading at $0.86. It successfully surpassed the $0.84 resistance level in the short term, but buyer sentiment remained weak. The coin&#8217;s next significant resistance is $0.87, and breaching this level could initiate a recovery trend.</p>
<p>However, if sellers persist, the altcoin could drop toward $0.81 and potentially below $0.80. The key for the bulls to regain control of the price lies in MATIC, staying above $0.86 in the upcoming trading sessions. The trading volume of MATIC in the last session was low, indicating a lack of buying strength.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-533919 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSD_2023-05-19_01-16-48.png" alt="MATIC" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSD_2023-05-19_01-16-48.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSD_2023-05-19_01-16-48-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSD_2023-05-19_01-16-48-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSD_2023-05-19_01-16-48-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSD_2023-05-19_01-16-48-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSD_2023-05-19_01-16-48-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSD_2023-05-19_01-16-48-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>
<p>MATIC faced challenges in generating strong buying support throughout April and May, resulting in reduced demand. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) indicated a decline, with the indicator remaining below 40, highlighting the dominant presence of sellers in the market.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the price dropped below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, indicating that sellers were driving the price momentum. However, if MATIC surpasses the $0.87 level, it will trade above the 20-SMA line.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-533921 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSD_2023-05-19_01-17-30.png" alt="MATIC" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSD_2023-05-19_01-17-30.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSD_2023-05-19_01-17-30-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSD_2023-05-19_01-17-30-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSD_2023-05-19_01-17-30-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSD_2023-05-19_01-17-30-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSD_2023-05-19_01-17-30-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATICUSD_2023-05-19_01-17-30-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>
<p>In contrast, the altcoin exhibited buy signals on the daily chart, albeit with a diminishing size and strength. The presence of green histograms on the Awesome Oscillator indicated buy signals for the altcoin, reflecting price momentum and potential reversals.</p>

<p>Additionally, the Bollinger Bands, which measure price volatility and the likelihood of price fluctuations, remained narrow and wide. However, the bands had a slight convergence, suggesting that the price may not undergo significant volatility or fluctuation in the immediate trading sessions.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/360_F_490918183_627MXWxdL8JkEBayMsga8hOqYRxg0Wsr-460x230.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Whale Alert: 1,750 Bitcoin (BTC) Moved To Exchange, Massive Plunge Incoming?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/whale-alert-1750-bitcoin-btc-moved-to-exchange-massive-plunge-incoming/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 20:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533890</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[An intriguing development has caught the crypto community&#8217;s attention as a Bitcoin whale deposited a substantial amount of BTC on the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange, Binance. This significant move has sparked speculation about potential selling pressure and the subsequent impact on Bitcoin&#8217;s price. Notably, the massive deposit was recorded when Bitcoin showed signs of a rebound following its recent losses in the past week. Whale Moves BTC To Binance According to renowned on-chain analyst Lookonchain, a notable Bitcoin whale made a deposit of 1,750 BTC which is worth over $48 Million, on the Binance exchange a few hours ago. This occurrence has raised concerns among market observers, as large transactions can indicate imminent selling pressure. Related Reading: Bitcoin whale moves BTC to Binance exchange The on-chain data analyst further reveals this whale has a history of triggering sudden moves in the price action. On April 21, the same individual deposited a staggering 5,791 BTC (equivalent to $163 million), leading to a subsequent 3% drop in Bitcoin&#8217;s price within five hours. Notably, Lookonchain says this whale has a history of buying large amounts of Bitcoin. The analyst reports that the whale initially acquired 10,000 BTC, valued at $171 million, on December 1, 2022, when Bitcoin was priced at $17,101. And as of now, the whale has a current Bitcoin holding balance of 2,459 BTC and an approximate profit of $107 million. Bitcoin Reaction: Analyzing the Possibilities It is worth noting that the Bitcoin market reaction to this whale can be quite unpredictable as the large investor alone might have a different reason to move the coins besides selling them. However, given the historical evidence of price movements following whale deposits on exchanges, Bitcoin will likely experience a spike in volatility soon. Related Reading: Is Bitcoin Ready For A Breakout? Glassnode Co-Founder Weighs In Particularly, If the past is any indication, there is a possibility of a short-term dip in Bitcoin&#8217;s price if the whale sells its BTC deposit. The sudden influx of 1,750 BTC into the exchange may trigger a cascade of sell-offs from other market participants, leading to a temporary downturn. Regardless, Bitcoin&#8217;s price has experienced a quick spike in the past 24 hours, up by 1%. Bitcoin has shown possible signs of rebound along with the rest of the crypto market. BTC has surged from low trading below $27,000 yesterday to trading for $27,406 at the time of writing. Before the bullish signs, BTC has since been in a downward trend in the past weeks, down by more than 10% in the past month. Interestingly, BTC trading volume remains below $10 billion despite the whale movement. Featured image from, Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An intriguing development has caught the crypto community&#8217;s attention as a Bitcoin whale <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1659171246008053760?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">deposited</a> a substantial amount of BTC on the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange, Binance. </p>
<p>This significant move has sparked speculation about potential selling pressure and the subsequent impact on Bitcoin&#8217;s price. Notably, the massive deposit was recorded when Bitcoin showed<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/is-bitcoin-ready-for-a-breakout-glassnode-co-founder-weighs-in/" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> signs of a rebound</a> following its recent losses in the past week.</p>
<h2>Whale Moves BTC To Binance</h2>
<p>According to renowned on-chain analyst Lookonchain, a notable Bitcoin whale made a deposit of 1,750 BTC which is worth over $48 Million, on the Binance exchange a few hours ago. This occurrence has raised concerns among market observers, as large transactions can indicate imminent selling pressure.</p>

<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">The on-chain data analyst further reveals this whale has a history of triggering sudden moves in the price action. On April 21, the same individual deposited a staggering 5,791 BTC (equivalent to $163 million), leading to a subsequent 3% drop in Bitcoin&#8217;s price within five hours. </p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Notably, Lookonchain says this whale has a history of buying large amounts of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-bullish-signal-whales-accumulate-84897-btc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a>. The analyst <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1659171249141223424?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reports</a> that the whale initially acquired 10,000 BTC, valued at $171 million, on December 1, 2022, when Bitcoin was priced at $17,101. </p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">And as of now, the whale has a current Bitcoin holding balance of 2,459 BTC and an approximate profit of $107 million.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin Reaction: Analyzing the Possibilities</h2>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">It is worth noting that the Bitcoin market reaction to this whale can be quite unpredictable as the large investor alone might have a different reason to move the coins besides selling them. However, given the historical evidence of price movements following whale deposits on exchanges, Bitcoin will likely experience a spike in volatility soon.</p>

<p dir="ltr">Particularly, If the past is any indication, there is a possibility of a short-term dip in <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-rally-28k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin&#8217;s price</a> if the whale sells its BTC deposit. The sudden influx of 1,750 BTC into the exchange may trigger a cascade of sell-offs from other market participants, leading to a temporary downturn.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Regardless, Bitcoin&#8217;s price has experienced a quick spike in the past 24 hours, up by 1%. Bitcoin has shown possible <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/is-bitcoin-headed-for-another-crash-heres-what-the-data-says/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">signs of rebound</a> along with the rest of the crypto market. BTC has surged from low trading below $27,000 yesterday to trading for $27,406 at the time of writing.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/EKYkzzPs/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC)&#039;s price chart on TradingView" width="2768" height="1556"/>
<p dir="ltr">Before the bullish signs, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/tether-bets-on-bitcoin-allocates-up-to-15-of-profits-for-btc-purchases/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">BTC</a> has since been in a downward trend in the past weeks, down by more than 10% in the past month. Interestingly, BTC trading volume remains below $10 billion despite the whale movement.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Featured image from, Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/todd-cravens-QnBrjY-nFUs-unsplash-2-460x305.jpg" width="460" height="305" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>CeFi Users Want To Explore DeFi: Uniswap Survey Uncovers New Wave Of Adoption</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cefi-users-want-to-explore-defi-uniswap-survey-uncovers-new-wave-of-adoption/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 19:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uniswap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UNIUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533893</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Uniswap Labs, a leading decentralized finance (DeFi) platform, has recently conducted a survey to understand the motivations and barriers of US-based retail users towards DeFi. The survey received 1,860 responses, including non-crypto, centralized finance (CeFi), and DeFi users. The survey revealed that despite the bear market backdrop, nearly half of CeFi users expressed an interest in experimenting with DeFi protocols in the next 12 months. This finding is encouraging as it indicates a growing interest in DeFi among traditional finance users, who are willing to learn and explore the possibilities of on-chain activity. Related Reading: Internet Computer (ICP) Dips, Will Bearish Momentum Persist?  Uniswap Survey Points to A Shift from CeFi To DeFi However, the survey also highlighted that complexity, lack of understanding, and costs are the main barriers preventing CeFi users from using DeFi platforms for all their cryptocurrency trades. This finding underscores the importance of providing educational material, improved user experience, and support to overcome the learning curve associated with DeFi. But how is Uniswap Labs simplifying DeFi for CeFi users? Seamless User Interface: Uniswap Labs has a user-friendly interface that allows users to easily navigate the platform and execute trades with a few clicks. This contrasts traditional DeFi platforms, which can be overwhelming for new users. Automated Market Making (AMM): Uniswap Labs uses an AMM system that eliminates the need for order books and allows users to easily swap tokens at a fair market price, simplifying the trading process and eliminating the need for users to understand complex trading concepts. Self-Custody: Uniswap Labs strongly emphasizes self-custody, meaning users have complete control over their assets and do not rely on centralized custodians. While this may seem daunting initially, Uniswap Labs provides educational resources and support to help users understand the benefits of self-custody. With this, Uniswap Labs, which builds products to onboard people directly to DeFi, aims to bridge the gap between CeFi and DeFi by focusing on UX and considering the first steps as a gateway into the broader crypto ecosystem. By doing so, Uniswap Labs seeks to provide CeFi users with a more transparent, self-custodial, and publicly verifiable alternative to centralized finance platforms that often lack accountability and transparency. Transaction Fees And Costs Identified As Biggest Barriers Transaction fees and costs were also identified as notable barriers to entry. However, as Ethereum continues to scale and layer 2 solutions see greater adoption, DeFi will become more economically accessible for price-sensitive users, according to Uniswap’s blog post. The survey also revealed that better educational resources and increased user support would increase willingness among CeFi users to trade on DeFi platforms. Products targeting this CeFi segment have already invested in these educational resources. Uniswap Labs has assembled one of the few customer support teams in crypto, considered one of the best in the industry. For this, Uniswap Labs is exploring layer 2 scaling solutions that will significantly reduce transaction fees and increase the speed of transactions. This will make DeFi more economically accessible and user-friendly for price-sensitive users. Related Reading: Ripple CTO Addresses Controversy Surrounding BitBoy’s BEN Token Sell-Off Overall, Uniswap Labs&#8217; survey sheds light on the motivations and barriers of US-based retail users towards DeFi. The platform aims to simplify and abstract the complexities unique to crypto without compromising on the ideals of self-custody and transparency. As the industry continues to grow, it is important to prioritize user education and support to help users build their knowledge base and grow their confidence. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Uniswap Labs, a leading decentralized finance (DeFi) platform, has recently <a href="https://blog.uniswap.org/cefi-defi-uniswap-survey" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">conducted a survey</a> to understand the motivations and barriers of US-based retail users towards DeFi. The survey received 1,860 responses, including non-crypto, centralized finance (CeFi), and DeFi users.</p>
<p>The survey revealed that despite the bear market backdrop, nearly half of CeFi users expressed an interest in experimenting with DeFi protocols in the next 12 months. This finding is encouraging as it indicates a growing interest in DeFi among traditional finance users, who are willing to learn and explore the possibilities of on-chain activity.</p>

<h2><b> Uniswap Survey Points to A Shift from CeFi To DeFi</b></h2>
<p>However, the survey also highlighted that complexity, lack of understanding, and costs are the main barriers preventing CeFi users from using DeFi platforms for all their cryptocurrency trades. This finding underscores the importance of providing educational material, improved user experience, and support to overcome the learning curve associated with DeFi. But how is Uniswap Labs simplifying DeFi for CeFi users?</p>
<ul>
<li>Seamless User Interface: Uniswap Labs has a user-friendly interface that allows users to easily navigate the platform and execute trades with a few clicks. This contrasts traditional DeFi platforms, which can be overwhelming for new users.</li>
<li>Automated Market Making (AMM): Uniswap Labs uses an AMM system that eliminates the need for order books and allows users to easily swap tokens at a fair market price, simplifying the trading process and eliminating the need for users to understand complex trading concepts.</li>
<li>Self-Custody: Uniswap Labs strongly emphasizes self-custody, meaning users have complete control over their assets and do not rely on centralized custodians. While this may seem daunting initially, Uniswap Labs provides educational resources and support to help users understand the benefits of self-custody.</li>
</ul>
<p>With this, Uniswap Labs, which builds products to onboard people directly to DeFi, aims to bridge the gap between CeFi and DeFi by focusing on UX and considering the first steps as a gateway into the broader crypto ecosystem. By doing so, Uniswap Labs seeks to provide CeFi users with a more transparent, self-custodial, and publicly verifiable alternative to centralized finance platforms that often lack accountability and transparency.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-533895" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image1-860x343.png" alt="Uniswap " width="860" height="343" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image1-860x343.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image1-460x184.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image1-768x307.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image1-750x299.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image1-1140x455.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image1.png 1508w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<b>Transaction Fees And Costs Identified As Biggest Barriers</b>
<p>Transaction fees and costs were also identified as notable barriers to entry. However, as Ethereum continues to scale and layer 2 solutions see greater adoption, DeFi will become more economically accessible for price-sensitive users, according to Uniswap’s blog post.</p>
<p>The survey also revealed that better educational resources and increased user support would increase willingness among CeFi users to trade on DeFi platforms. Products targeting this CeFi segment have already invested in these educational resources. Uniswap Labs has assembled one of the few customer support teams in crypto, considered one of the best in the industry.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-533894" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image2-860x294.png" alt="Uniswap" width="860" height="294" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image2-860x294.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image2-460x157.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image2-768x262.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image2-1536x524.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image2-750x256.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image2-1140x389.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image2.png 1594w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>For this, Uniswap Labs is exploring layer 2 scaling solutions that will significantly reduce transaction fees and increase the speed of transactions. This will make DeFi more economically accessible and user-friendly for price-sensitive users.</p>

<p>Overall, Uniswap Labs&#8217; survey sheds light on the motivations and barriers of US-based retail users towards DeFi. The platform aims to simplify and abstract the complexities unique to crypto without compromising on the ideals of self-custody and transparency. As the industry continues to grow, it is important to prioritize user education and support to help users build their knowledge base and grow their confidence.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/8FcEzKMc/" alt="Uniswap" width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1371837475-460x248.jpg" width="460" height="248" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Binary CDD Stays Low, Here&#8217;s What This Means</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-binary-cdd-stays-low-heres-what-this-means/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 18:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Binary CDD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Coin Days Destroyed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533791</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Bitcoin Binary Coin Days Destroyed (CDD) has stayed low recently. Here&#8217;s what this says about the current market. Bitcoin Binary CDD Has Remained At Very Low Levels Recently According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Glassnode, this indicator attained high values during the 2021 bull run. To understand the CDD metric, the concept of &#8220;coin days&#8221; needs to be looked at first. Whenever 1 BTC stays stationary on the blockchain for 1 day, it accumulates 1 &#8220;coin day.&#8221; If a coin that has remained unmoved on the network for a while, meaning that it has accumulated a certain number of coin days, is now suddenly transferred, its coin days counter would naturally reset back to zero. The coin days it had previously been carrying are said to be &#8220;destroyed.&#8221; The CDD indicator measures the total number of coin days being reset throughout the network on any given day. When this indicator has a high value, it implies that a large number of coin days are being reset in the market currently. Generally, this kind of trend is a sign of movement from the &#8220;long-term holders&#8221; (LTHs). This group includes investors that have been holding their BTC since at least 155 days ago, so these holders tend to accumulate large numbers of coin days. Because of this reason, whenever they make transfers, the CDD registers a spike. In the context of the current discussion, the CDD itself isn&#8217;t of interest, but a modified version of it called the Binary CDD is. This indicator basically tells us how the CDD currently compares with the historical average value of the metric. As is already obvious from its name, this indicator can only attain two values: 0 and 1. It has a value of 0 if the CDD is below the historical average, while it&#8217;s 1 when the metric is above it. Related Reading: Dogecoin, Shiba Inu Whales Move Massive Amounts, Dumping Going On? Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the 7-day average Bitcoin Binary CDD over the last few years: The value of the metric seems to have been low in recent days &#124; Source: Glassnode on Twitter As shown in the above graph, the 7-day average Bitcoin Binary CDD has had a pretty low value for a while now. This suggests that there hasn&#8217;t been any significant destruction of coin days in the market recently. Naturally, this means that the LTHs haven&#8217;t been making any moves out of the ordinary, despite the price observing a notable increase during the last few months. Related Reading: Bitcoin Bullish Signal: Whales Accumulate 84,897 BTC The LTHs are generally the most resolute bunch in the market, so transfers from them can have significant implications for the sector since they are a sign that even these holders may have been forced to sell. The Bitcoin bull run during the first half of 2021 saw the 7-day average Binary CDD stay near 1, implying that the LTHs had been selling in full force. As this hasn&#8217;t been the case in the rally so far, it appears that the current profits aren&#8217;t enough to move these diamond hands, and they are likely expecting better opportunities later on. These investors continuing to hold such a bullish conviction can be constructive for the price in the long term. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $27,300, down 1% in the last week. The asset continues to consolidate &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Jievani Weerasinghe on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Glassnode.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows the Bitcoin Binary Coin Days Destroyed (CDD) has stayed low recently. Here&#8217;s what this says about the current market.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Binary CDD Has Remained At Very Low Levels Recently</h2>
<p>According to data from the on-chain analytics firm <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1658831491319644161" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Glassnode</a>, this indicator attained high values during the 2021 bull run. To understand the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-90-day-cdd-hits-all-time-low-says-market/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">CDD</a> metric, the concept of &#8220;coin days&#8221; needs to be looked at first.</p>
<p>Whenever 1 BTC stays stationary on the blockchain for 1 day, it accumulates 1 &#8220;coin day.&#8221; If a coin that has remained unmoved on the network for a while, meaning that it has accumulated a certain number of coin days, is now suddenly transferred, its coin days counter would naturally reset back to zero.</p>
<p>The coin days it had previously been carrying are said to be &#8220;destroyed.&#8221; The CDD indicator measures the total number of coin days being reset throughout the network on any given day.</p>
<p>When this indicator has a high value, it implies that a large number of coin days are being reset in the market currently. Generally, this kind of trend is a sign of movement from the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-long-term-holders-holding-price-decline/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">long-term holders</a>&#8221; (LTHs).</p>
<p>This group includes investors that have been holding their BTC since at least 155 days ago, so these holders tend to accumulate large numbers of coin days. Because of this reason, whenever they make transfers, the CDD registers a spike.</p>
<p>In the context of the current discussion, the CDD itself isn&#8217;t of interest, but a modified version of it called the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-binary-cdd-breakout-kicked-off-bull-rallies/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Binary CDD</a> is. This indicator basically tells us how the CDD currently compares with the historical average value of the metric.</p>
<p>As is already obvious from its name, this indicator can only attain two values: 0 and 1. It has a value of 0 if the CDD is below the historical average, while it&#8217;s 1 when the metric is above it.</p>

<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the 7-day average Bitcoin Binary CDD over the last few years:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FwVYle8WcAAwZCd?format=png&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Bitcoin Binary CDD" width="4081" height="2350"/></p>

<p>As shown in the above graph, the 7-day average Bitcoin Binary CDD has had a pretty low value for a while now. This suggests that there hasn&#8217;t been any significant destruction of coin days in the market recently.</p>
<p>Naturally, this means that the LTHs haven&#8217;t been making any moves out of the ordinary, despite the price observing a notable increase during the last few months.</p>

<p>The LTHs are generally the most resolute bunch in the market, so transfers from them can have significant implications for the sector since they are a sign that even these holders may have been forced to sell.</p>
<p>The Bitcoin bull run during the first half of 2021 saw the 7-day average Binary CDD stay near 1, implying that the LTHs had been selling in full force. As this hasn&#8217;t been the case in the rally so far, it appears that the current profits aren&#8217;t enough to move these diamond hands, and they are likely expecting better opportunities later on.</p>
<p>These investors continuing to hold such a bullish conviction can be constructive for the price in the long term.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $27,300, down 1% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/rblDiBOD/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1533" height="911"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/jievani-weerasinghe-NHRM1u4GD_A-unsplash-460x282.jpg" width="460" height="282" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
