<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"

	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 22:26:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">221170450</site>	<item>
		<title>Curve Impressively Adds 22% As Founder Sells CRV To Repay Aave Loan</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/defi/curve-crv-adds-22-founder-repay-aave-loan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 02:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[aave]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CRV]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Justin Sun]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Erogov]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545733</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CRV, the governance token of Curve, a decentralized exchange for stablecoins and a key player in the decentralized finance (DeFi) landscape, has impressively recovered, adding 22% after sinking to its August 2023 lows this week. When writing on August 3, CRV is trading at $0.59, rising double digits after dropping to $0.48 on August 1 following a damaging hack that saw liquidity providers in several pools lose funds.  Whales Stepping In To Buy CRV This recovery is attributed primarily to strategic actions by notable crypto whales who have stepped in to mitigate risks on DeFi should CRV prices continue to tank. Meanwhile, Michael Egorov, the founder of Curve and one of the largest CRV holders, has been actively unloading tokens in the secondary market. Egorov is selling to whales like Justin Sun, the founder of Tron, and other venture capitals and decentralized autonomous organizations (DAOs). The founder held around 292 million CRV and used a big percentage to back his loans. Related Reading: Shiba Inu’s DeFi Aspirations May Rattle DOGE’s Market As SHIB Turns To Digital IDs On-chain data indicates that on August 2, Egorov sold 3.75 million CRV tokens to Yearn Treasury and another 1.25 million CRV tokens to Stake DAO Governance via the over-the-counter (OTC) market. Egorov has, overall, sold 59.5 million CRV to various institutions and investors, yielding approximately $23.8 million. These OTC sales are at significant discounts, reflecting the founder&#8217;s efforts to stabilize CRV prices and prevent further contagion. The July 30 hack saw attackers steal funds from several liquidity pools after exploiting a re-entrancy flaw. JPEG’d, Alchemix, Pendle, and Metronome pools suffered losses initially estimated at around $70 million. However, other reports suggest that white hat hackers intervened, reducing the total impact to approximately $50 million.  Following this news, CRV prices dropped by over 12%. Considering Curve&#8217;s prominence in DeFi, the hack and price crash caused reverberation throughout Curve and DeFi, especially in decentralized money markets.  Curve Is A Big Player In DeFi, Egorov Paying Off Debt Curve manages over $2 billion as total value locked (TVL), according to DeFiLlama. While there are no confirmed repercussions on other protocols, attention swung to Egorov&#8217;s $60 million Aave v2 loan, which was primarily backed by CRV. Should this loan be liquidated, it would likely mean more selling pressure on CRV, leading to another possible contagion, especially for other CRV holders with loans across different protocols. Related Reading: Solana Price Could Surge To $30 Upon Overcoming This Resistance Looking at on-chain data, Egorov is taking active steps to reduce the risks brought about by his huge Aave loan that&#8217;s overly collateralized by CRV. Egorov aims to minimize the potential consequences of forced liquidation through off-market transactions, where he is selling his CRV at a discount and simultaneously repaying his loan. This, in turn, appears to be supporting prices. Feature image from Canva, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CRV, the governance token of Curve, a decentralized exchange for stablecoins and a key player in the decentralized finance (DeFi) landscape, has impressively recovered, adding 22% after sinking to its August 2023 lows this week.</p>
<p> When writing on August 3, CRV is trading at $0.59, rising double digits after dropping to $0.48 on August 1 following a damaging <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/CurveFinance/status/1685925429041917952" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">hack</a> that saw liquidity providers in several pools lose funds. </p>
<h2>Whales Stepping In To Buy CRV</h2>
<p>This recovery is attributed primarily to strategic actions by notable crypto whales who have stepped in to mitigate risks on DeFi should CRV prices continue to tank. Meanwhile, Michael Egorov, the founder of Curve and one of the largest CRV holders, has been actively unloading tokens in the secondary market.</p>
<p>Egorov is selling to <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1686291199517437953" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">whales</a> like Justin Sun, the founder of Tron, and other venture capitals and decentralized autonomous organizations (DAOs). The founder held around 292 million CRV and used a big percentage to back his loans.</p>

<p>On-chain data <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1686760423868272640" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">indicates</a> that on August 2, Egorov sold 3.75 million CRV tokens to Yearn Treasury and another 1.25 million CRV tokens to Stake DAO Governance via the over-the-counter (OTC) market. </p>
<p>Egorov has, overall, sold 59.5 million CRV to various institutions and investors, yielding approximately $23.8 million. These OTC sales are at significant discounts, reflecting the founder&#8217;s efforts to stabilize CRV prices and prevent further contagion.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/UjFZtMtk/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/UjFZtMtk/" alt="CRV price on August 3| Source: CRVUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595" loading="lazy"/></a>
<p>The July 30 hack saw attackers steal funds from several liquidity pools after exploiting a re-entrancy flaw. JPEG’d, Alchemix, Pendle, and Metronome pools suffered losses initially estimated at around $70 million. However, other reports suggest that white hat hackers intervened, reducing the total impact to approximately $50 million. </p>
<p>Following this news, CRV prices dropped by over 12%. Considering Curve&#8217;s prominence in DeFi, the hack and price crash caused reverberation throughout Curve and DeFi, especially in decentralized money markets. </p>
<h2>Curve Is A Big Player In DeFi, Egorov Paying Off Debt</h2>
<p>Curve manages over $2 billion as total value locked (TVL), according to <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://defillama.com/protocol/curve-dex" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">DeFiLlama</a>. While there are no confirmed repercussions on other protocols, attention swung to Egorov&#8217;s $60 million Aave v2 loan, which was primarily backed by CRV. Should this loan be liquidated, it would likely mean more selling pressure on CRV, leading to another possible contagion, especially for other CRV holders with loans across different protocols.</p>

<p>Looking at on-chain data, Egorov is taking active steps to reduce the risks brought about by his huge Aave loan that&#8217;s overly collateralized by CRV. Egorov aims to minimize the potential consequences of forced liquidation through off-market transactions, where he is selling his CRV at a discount and simultaneously <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1686773784760684544" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">repaying</a> his loan. This, in turn, appears to be supporting prices.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Curve-CRV-.jpg?fit=460%2C260" width="460" height="260" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545733</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Curve Finance Fights Back With Warning And Unrefusable Offer To Hacker</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/curve-finance-fights-back-with-warning-and-unrefusable-offer-to-hacker/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 01:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CRV]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CRVUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curve Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545724</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Curve Finance (CRV) has issued a statement on Etherscan, addressing the hackers responsible for the recent exploit that resulted in the loss of over $60 million from the protocol.  In the statement, Curve, Metronome &#38; Alchemix have invited the hackers to discuss a potential bounty, offering a 10% reward for any stolen funds, which they can keep if they return the remaining 90%. Curve Finance Gives Hackers Ultimatum The group has emphasized that there will be no risk of them pursuing legal action or involving law enforcement if the hackers participate in this voluntary return process.  However, suppose the hackers do not participate and complete the process by August 6. In that case, Curve Finance will expand the bounty to the public and offer the full 10% reward to anyone who can identify them in a way that leads to their conviction in court. The encrypted message on Etherscan further noted: If you choose not to participate in the voluntary return and complete the process by August 6, we will expand the bounty to the public, and offer the full 10% to the person who can identify you in a way that leads to your conviction in the courts. We will pursue you from all angles with the full extent of the law. To verify their ownership of the email address, anyone emailing Curve Finance will have to complete a verification process on-cain before any discussions occur. Related Reading: Quant Explains How These Indicators Affect Ethereum Price The statement highlights Curve Finance&#8217;s commitment to recovering the stolen funds and bringing those responsible to justice.  By offering a bounty and encouraging the hackers to return the funds voluntarily, Curve Finance is proactively resolving the situation. However, the group has also clarified that they will pursue all legal avenues to recover the funds if the hackers choose not to cooperate. It remains to be seen whether the hackers will take Curve Finance up on their offer or whether the group will need to expand the bounty to the public. Nevertheless, this statement demonstrates Curve Finance&#8217;s determination to protect the protocol and its users and sends a strong message to would-be attackers that such actions will not be tolerated. Aave DAO Member Suggests Tactical Move To Acquire CRV An Aave Decentralized Autonomous Organization (DAO) member has proposed a strategic move to acquire CRV tokens using USDT from the Aave DAO treasury.  Recent events surrounding Aave V2 have provided an opportunity to incentivize GHO liquidity through Curve voting power.  The proposed acquisition of CRV tokens will benefit the Decentralized Finance (DeFi) ecosystem by providing additional liquidity to the Curve protocol. Additionally, the move will position Aave DAO to benefit from the ongoing &#8220;Curve wars&#8221; and gain extra voting power on the platform. The Aave DAO member who proposed the move emphasized the importance of taking a strategic approach to treasury management. By acquiring CRV tokens with USDT, Aave DAO can maintain a conservative approach to treasury holdings while still supporting the growth of the DeFi ecosystem. Related Reading: Binance CEO Shares Details Of $20 Million Scam Attempt The proposal has received positive feedback from the community, with many members expressing support for the move. If the proposal is approved, it will be a significant step forward for Aave DAO and the broader DeFi ecosystem. Overall, this proposal demonstrates the importance of strategic treasury management in the fast-paced world of DeFi. By taking a conservative approach to treasury holdings while still supporting the ecosystem&#8217;s growth, Aave DAO is setting an example for other DeFi projects to follow. Despite the ongoing issues experienced by the Curve protocol, CRV has reported significant gains of over 4% in the last 24 hours, with the current trading price at $0.602.  Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Curve Finance (CRV) has issued a <a href="https://twitter.com/CurveFinance/status/1687180381714358272?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">statement </a>on Etherscan, addressing the hackers responsible for the recent exploit that resulted in the loss of over $60 million from the protocol. </p>
<p>In the statement, Curve, Metronome &amp; Alchemix have invited the hackers to discuss a potential bounty, offering a 10% reward for any stolen funds, which they can keep if they return the remaining 90%.</p>
<h2>Curve Finance Gives Hackers Ultimatum</h2>
<p>The group has emphasized that there will be no risk of them pursuing legal action or involving law enforcement if the hackers participate in this voluntary return process. </p>
<p>However, suppose the hackers do not participate and complete the process by August 6. In that case, Curve Finance will expand the bounty to the public and offer the full 10% reward to anyone who can identify them in a way that leads to their conviction in court. The encrypted message on Etherscan further noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>If you choose not to participate in the voluntary return and complete the process by August 6, we will expand the bounty to the public, and offer the full 10% to the person who can identify you in a way that leads to your conviction in the courts. We will pursue you from all angles with the full extent of the law.</p></blockquote>
<p>To verify their ownership of the email address, anyone emailing Curve Finance will have to complete a verification process on-cain before any discussions occur.</p>

<p>The statement highlights Curve Finance&#8217;s commitment to recovering the stolen funds and bringing those responsible to justice. </p>
<p>By offering a bounty and encouraging the hackers to return the funds voluntarily, Curve Finance is proactively resolving the situation. However, the group has also clarified that they will pursue all legal avenues to recover the funds if the hackers choose not to cooperate.</p>
<p>It remains to be seen whether the hackers will take Curve Finance up on their offer or whether the group will need to expand the bounty to the public. Nevertheless, this statement demonstrates Curve Finance&#8217;s determination to protect the protocol and its users and sends a strong message to would-be attackers that such actions will not be tolerated.</p>
Aave DAO Member Suggests Tactical Move To Acquire CRV
<p>An Aave Decentralized Autonomous Organization (DAO) member has <a href="https://messari.io/governor/proposal/580e6b73-73ec-4378-9d24-110fa6a07c99" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">proposed </a>a strategic move to acquire CRV tokens using USDT from the Aave DAO treasury. </p>
<p>Recent events surrounding Aave V2 have provided an opportunity to incentivize GHO liquidity through Curve voting power. </p>
<p>The proposed acquisition of CRV tokens will benefit the Decentralized Finance (DeFi) ecosystem by providing additional liquidity to the Curve protocol. Additionally, the move will position Aave DAO to benefit from the ongoing &#8220;Curve wars&#8221; and gain extra voting power on the platform.</p>
<p>The Aave DAO member who proposed the move emphasized the importance of taking a strategic approach to treasury management. By acquiring CRV tokens with USDT, Aave DAO can maintain a conservative approach to treasury holdings while still supporting the growth of the DeFi ecosystem.</p>

<p>The proposal has received positive feedback from the community, with many members expressing support for the move. If the proposal is approved, it will be a significant step forward for Aave DAO and the broader DeFi ecosystem.</p>
<p>Overall, this proposal demonstrates the importance of strategic treasury management in the fast-paced world of DeFi. By taking a conservative approach to treasury holdings while still supporting the ecosystem&#8217;s growth, Aave DAO is setting an example for other DeFi projects to follow.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Lf9HCzDM/" alt="Curve Finance" width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>Despite the ongoing issues experienced by the Curve protocol, CRV has reported significant gains of over 4% in the last 24 hours, with the current trading price at $0.602. </p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/muhammad-daudy-4eeG4Mn0HVY-unsplash.jpg?fit=307%2C460" width="307" height="460" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545724</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Could Break Above $2,000 If This Happens</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-could-break-above-2000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum futures ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545704</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum price is currently still below $2,000 but this could quickly change if some things were to come to pass. Some of the most notable things that have been going on for the cryptocurrency include the multiple exchange-traded funds (ETFs) filings that have been made to the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). When Will An Ethereum ETF Be Approved? The topic of Ethereum futures ETFs has become hotter especially after Bitcoin futures ETFs received multiple approvals from the SEC since 2021. However, even two years after the first Bitcoin futures ETF was approved, the regulator is still yet to approve an Ethereum futures ETF. Related Reading: Litecoin Sharks Buy More Than 200,000 LTC Ahead Of Wednesday’s Halving Despite this, investment firms have remained undeterred as they have continued to file for Ethereum futures ETFs. As reported by NewsBTC, there are now a total of six ETH futures ETF filings with the SEC after Grayscale refiled its application with the regulator. In addition to Grayscale, VanEck, ProShares, Volatility Shares, Bitwise, and Roundhill all have pending applications with the commission. With so many interested applications, there is now mounting pressure on the SEC to approve the first Ethereum futures ETF to trade in the country. And according to people familiar with the matter, it may not be much longer until the first ETF is approved for trading. The reason behind this is the fact that the regulator had previously asked interested parties to halt activities regarding applying for ETH ETFs. However, with the re-filings and new filings, it signals that the SEC may finally be ready to review the applications and consider them. ETH price still holding above $1,800 &#124; Source: ETHUSD on Tradingview.com What Happens When An ETF Gets Approved? The anticipation around a possible approval for an Ethereum futures ETF is mostly the implications of such an occurrence. Like in 2021 when the first Bitcoin futures ETF was approved in October, the price of BTC surged drastically, reaching a new all-time high price just a month later. Related Reading: Bitcoin Investor Sentiment Flips Toward Greed Despite Fall Below $29,000 ETFs are an instrument that helps to bring more volume to an asset and if an ETH ETF gets approved, the price of ETH is expected to rally. This would be the result of a combination of the new volume and interest, as well as the euphoria that comes with it. An ETF approval would likely push the price of ETH above $2,000 and could trigger another bull rally for the coin. Currently, all eyes are on October 16, 2023, when one new filing and four re-filings for Ethereum futures ETFs become active. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Ethereum price is currently still below $2,000 but this could quickly change if some things were to come to pass. Some of the most notable things that have been going on for the cryptocurrency include the multiple exchange-traded funds (ETFs) filings that have been made to the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<h2 class="p2">When Will An Ethereum ETF Be Approved?</h2>
<p class="p2">The topic of Ethereum futures ETFs has become hotter especially after Bitcoin futures ETFs received multiple approvals from the SEC since 2021. However, even two years after the first Bitcoin futures ETF was approved, the regulator is still yet to approve an Ethereum futures ETF.</p>

<p class="p2">Despite this, investment firms have remained undeterred as they have continued to file for Ethereum futures ETFs. As <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-etfs-heat-up/">reported by NewsBTC</a>, there are now a total of six ETH futures ETF filings with the SEC after Grayscale refiled its application with the regulator. In addition to Grayscale, VanEck, ProShares, Volatility Shares, Bitwise, and Roundhill all have pending applications with the commission.</p>
<p class="p2">With so many interested applications, there is now <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-etfs-could-soon-get-sec-nod/" rel="nofollow">mounting pressure on the SEC to approve the first Ethereum futures ETF</a> to trade in the country. And according to people familiar with the matter, it may not be much longer until the first ETF is approved for trading.</p>
<p class="p2">The reason behind this is the fact that the regulator had previously asked interested parties to halt activities regarding applying for ETH ETFs. However, with the re-filings and new filings, it signals that the SEC may finally be ready to review the applications and consider them.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/iR5EjlE2/" alt="Ethereum (ETH) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2 class="p2">What Happens When An ETF Gets Approved?</h2>
<p class="p2">The anticipation around a possible approval for an Ethereum futures ETF is mostly the implications of such an occurrence. Like in 2021 when the first Bitcoin futures ETF was approved in October, the price of BTC surged drastically, reaching a new all-time high price just a month later.</p>

<p class="p2">ETFs are an instrument that helps to bring more volume to an asset and if an ETH ETF gets approved, the price of ETH is expected to rally. This would be the result of a combination of the new volume and interest, as well as the euphoria that comes with it. An ETF approval would likely push the price of ETH above $2,000 and could trigger another bull rally for the coin.</p>
<p class="p2">Currently, <a href="https://twitter.com/ETFhearsay/status/1686495327333863424?s=20" rel="nofollow">all eyes are on October 16, 2023</a>, when one new filing and four re-filings for Ethereum futures ETFs become active.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-904735154.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545704</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana Price Could Surge To $30 Upon Overcoming This Resistance</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/solana/solana-price-could-surge-to-30-upon-overcoming-this-resistance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 22:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545698</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Solana price experienced notable gains in mid-June, but a recent correction phase has pulled it down to $22, which has found strong support. The technical outlook currently leans towards the bears, suggesting a potential slight dip before a possible turnaround. Related Reading: All Hype? BALD Meme Coin’s Volume Shaved By 96% The altcoin attempted to rise from the support level in the past week, but the bullish momentum waned. Despite the chance of a rally due to a demand zone below $22, a new resistance at the $25 level may pose a challenge. As Bitcoin slipped into the $29,000 range, other altcoins also faced downward pressure on their charts. For SOL to reverse its trend, overall market strength is vital. The falling market capitalization of SOL indicates continued control by sellers over the price. Solana Price Analysis: One-Day Chart At the time of writing, SOL was trading at $22.80, demonstrating stability around a significant support zone. Although a drop from this level might attract buyers, there is a possibility that the altcoin could slip below the $20 mark. If buyers step in, the next resistance levels would be $23 and $25. Once the $25 price mark is breached, Solana could aim for $30, signifying a potential 36% rally. However, SOL must avoid falling below $20, as that would nullify any bullish revival. In the last session, the volume of SOL traded declined, suggesting a decrease in buying strength. Technical Analysis SOL showed increased selling pressure, indicating buyers had not yet entered the positive zone. The Relative Strength Index remained below the half-line, stressing the lack of bullish momentum as sellers outnumbered buyers at the time of observation. Moreover, SOL was positioned below the 20-Simple Moving Average line, signifying a lack of demand at this level and further suggesting that sellers had control over the price momentum in the market. The upcoming trading sessions hold significance for the coin as buyers will determine the altcoin&#8217;s future direction. The altcoin&#8217;s low demand has led to the formation of sell signals. This indicated the continued dominance of bears in the market. However, it&#8217;s worth noting that the size of these sell signals is gradually decreasing. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicator, which measures price momentum and trend changes, showed red histograms. This reading was linked to sell signals. Despite this, the sell signals were relatively short, suggesting that the altcoin might see some buying strength in the upcoming trading sessions. On the other hand, the Directional Movement Index (DMI), which indicates price direction, remained negative. The -DI line (orange) was positioned above the +DI line (blue). Related Reading: Can Dogecoin Reach $0.85? Bullish Setup Hints At Potential For Advance Conversely, the Average Moving Index was above the 40 mark, indicating that a change in price direction could be expected in the next trading sessions. Featured image from UnSplash, charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Solana price experienced notable gains in mid-June, but a recent correction phase has pulled it down to $22, which has found strong support. The technical outlook currently leans towards the bears, suggesting a potential slight dip before a possible turnaround.</p>

<p>The altcoin attempted to rise from the support level in the past week, but the bullish momentum waned. Despite the chance of a rally due to a demand zone below $22, a new resistance at the $25 level may pose a challenge.</p>
<p>As Bitcoin slipped into the $29,000 range, other altcoins also faced downward pressure on their charts. For SOL to reverse its trend, overall market strength is vital. The falling market capitalization of SOL indicates continued control by sellers over the price.</p>
<h2>Solana Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-545706 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSDT_2023-08-03_19-52-55.png?resize=1817%2C820" alt="Solana" width="1817" height="820" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSDT_2023-08-03_19-52-55.png?resize=1817%2C820?w=1817 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSDT_2023-08-03_19-52-55.png?resize=1817%2C820?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSDT_2023-08-03_19-52-55.png?resize=1817%2C820?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSDT_2023-08-03_19-52-55.png?resize=1817%2C820?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSDT_2023-08-03_19-52-55.png?resize=1817%2C820?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSDT_2023-08-03_19-52-55.png?resize=1817%2C820?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSDT_2023-08-03_19-52-55.png?resize=1817%2C820?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>At the time of writing, SOL was trading at $22.80, demonstrating stability around a significant support zone. Although a drop from this level might attract buyers, there is a possibility that the altcoin could slip below the $20 mark. If buyers step in, the next resistance levels would be $23 and $25.</p>
<p>Once the $25 price mark is breached, Solana could aim for $30, signifying a potential 36% rally. However, SOL must avoid falling below $20, as that would nullify any bullish revival. In the last session, the volume of SOL traded declined, suggesting a decrease in buying strength.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-545710 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSDT_2023-08-03_20-02-21.png?resize=1817%2C820" alt="Solana" width="1817" height="820" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSDT_2023-08-03_20-02-21.png?resize=1817%2C820?w=1817 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSDT_2023-08-03_20-02-21.png?resize=1817%2C820?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSDT_2023-08-03_20-02-21.png?resize=1817%2C820?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSDT_2023-08-03_20-02-21.png?resize=1817%2C820?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSDT_2023-08-03_20-02-21.png?resize=1817%2C820?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSDT_2023-08-03_20-02-21.png?resize=1817%2C820?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSDT_2023-08-03_20-02-21.png?resize=1817%2C820?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>SOL showed increased selling pressure, indicating buyers had not yet entered the positive zone. The Relative Strength Index remained below the half-line, stressing the lack of bullish momentum as sellers outnumbered buyers at the time of observation.</p>
<p>Moreover, SOL was positioned below the 20-Simple Moving Average line, signifying a lack of demand at this level and further suggesting that sellers had control over the price momentum in the market. The upcoming trading sessions hold significance for the coin as buyers will determine the altcoin&#8217;s future direction.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-545711 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSDT_2023-08-03_20-03-27.png?resize=1818%2C820" alt="Solana" width="1818" height="820" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSDT_2023-08-03_20-03-27.png?resize=1818%2C820?w=1818 1818w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSDT_2023-08-03_20-03-27.png?resize=1818%2C820?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSDT_2023-08-03_20-03-27.png?resize=1818%2C820?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSDT_2023-08-03_20-03-27.png?resize=1818%2C820?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSDT_2023-08-03_20-03-27.png?resize=1818%2C820?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSDT_2023-08-03_20-03-27.png?resize=1818%2C820?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SOLUSDT_2023-08-03_20-03-27.png?resize=1818%2C820?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>The altcoin&#8217;s low demand has led to the formation of sell signals. This indicated the continued dominance of bears in the market. However, it&#8217;s worth noting that the size of these sell signals is gradually decreasing.</p>
<p>The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicator, which measures price momentum and trend changes, showed red histograms. This reading was linked to sell signals. Despite this, the sell signals were relatively short, suggesting that the altcoin might see some buying strength in the upcoming trading sessions.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the Directional Movement Index (DMI), which indicates price direction, remained negative. The -DI line (orange) was positioned above the +DI line (blue).</p>

<p>Conversely, the Average Moving Index was above the 40 mark, indicating that a change in price direction could be expected in the next trading sessions.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shubham-s-web3-uNP6X3Ec9jk-unsplash-4.jpg?fit=460%2C259" width="460" height="259" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545698</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>CRV Price Recovers From 6-Month Lows, What’s Driving The Price?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/crv/crv-price-recovers-from-6-month-lows/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 21:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[CRV]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CRV Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CRVUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CRVUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curve]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545709</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Curve Finance’s native token CRV has recovered from a 6-month low, and many believe that the news of Huobi co-founder Jun Du buying CRV tokens has contributed to it.  Jun Du bought 10 million tokens valued at $4 million from Micheal Egorov, founder of Curve. Egorov had offered his tokens for sale to bolster his at-risk loan positions, primarily for borrowing stablecoins using CRV tokens as collateral.  Some Positives For Curve Finance Despite Hack Curve Finance, one of the biggest DeFi protocols on the Ethereum blockchain, recently saw its in-house CRV price recover about 25% at the start of the month. It had previously dropped by 35% between July 30-31 following the panic selloff spearheaded by Curve Finance’s $47 million exploit.  Related Reading: Buying Pressure Incoming? MicroStrategy Files Notice With SEC To Sell $750 Million In Stocks The July reentrancy attack was not the only exploit recorded on Curve Finance as the DeFi protocol had previously lost over $570,000 in August 2022 after hackers compromised the front end of its liquidity pool.  However, the recent acquisition of 10 million tokens by Jun Du projects a positive outlook for CRV tokens, especially the recent attack on its ecosystem. Confirming the transaction, Du noted that he has locked up his investment for a period of one year as veCRV.  Apart from Du, the Aave Chan Initiative, a delegate platform from Aave’s governance forum, recently put forward a proposal for the purchase of about $2 million worth of CRV. After the planned purchase, which is to be made by the Aave Treasury, the CRV tokens would also be locked up as veCRV for about four years.  Token price recovers from weekly lows &#124; Source: CRVUSD on Tradingview.com CRV Remains Popular Among Investors Egorov has so far sold 72 million CRV tokens to various investors and the continued purchase and acceptance of the CRV token demonstrates its popularity and utility.  One such investor who remains bullish on CRV is Justin Sun, founder of the Tron network. He recently acquired 5 million CRV from Egorov by paying using Tether’s USDT in a direct Over-the-counter (OTC) trade. Justin confirmed the purchase in a tweet noting that both platforms “As steadfast partners” will keep being “&#8230;committed to providing support whenever needed.” According to a Twitter post by Sandra from Nansen, other popular purchasers of Curve tokens include Cream Finance, Machi Big Brother, DWF Labs, DCFGod, and Andrew Kang, co-founder of Mechanism Capital.  Related Reading: Ethereum ETFs Heat Up As Filings With SEC Climbs To Six A vast majority of these transactions were conducted through OTC, with Egorov realizing over $20 million, which he applied to balancing his borrowings and removing himself from liquidation. Egorov also sent another huge supply of CRV (17.5 million) to an address starting with 0xf51.  Once the largest DeFi protocol on the Ethereum blockchain, the vast majority of Curve trading volumes still come from Ethereum.  Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Curve Finance’s native token CRV has recovered from a 6-month low, and many believe that the news of Huobi co-founder Jun Du buying CRV tokens has contributed to it. </p>
<p>Jun Du bought 10 million tokens valued at $4 million from Micheal Egorov, founder of Curve. Egorov had offered his tokens for sale to bolster his at-risk loan positions, primarily for borrowing stablecoins using CRV tokens as collateral. </p>
<h2>Some Positives For Curve Finance Despite Hack</h2>
<p>Curve Finance, one of the biggest DeFi protocols on the Ethereum blockchain, recently saw its in-house CRV price recover about 25% at the start of the month. It had previously dropped by 35% between July 30-31 following the panic selloff spearheaded by Curve Finance’s $47 million <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/curve-dao-tokens-suffer-millions-in-hack/" rel="nofollow">exploit</a>. </p>

<p>The July <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/upbit-suspends-curve-crv-deposits-and-withdrawals/" rel="nofollow">reentrancy</a> attack was not the only exploit recorded on Curve Finance as the DeFi protocol had previously lost over $570,000 in August 2022 after hackers compromised the front end of its liquidity pool. </p>
<p>However, the recent acquisition of 10 million tokens by Jun Du projects a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/defi/is-it-a-good-idea-to-buy-curve-now/">positive outlook for CRV tokens</a>, especially the recent attack on its ecosystem. Confirming the transaction, Du noted that he has locked up his investment for a period of one year as veCRV. </p>
<p>Apart from Du, the Aave Chan Initiative, a delegate platform from Aave’s governance forum, recently put forward a proposal for the purchase of about $2 million worth of CRV. After the planned purchase, which is to be made by the Aave Treasury, the CRV tokens would also be locked up as veCRV for about four years. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/g76Vadkf/" alt="Curve (CRV) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2>CRV Remains Popular Among Investors</h2>
<p>Egorov has so far sold 72 million CRV tokens to various investors and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/all/curve-dao-crv-price-recovery-post-exploit-what-would-be-a-realistic-scenario/">continued purchase and acceptance of the CRV token</a> demonstrates its popularity and utility. </p>
<p>One such investor who remains bullish on CRV is Justin Sun, founder of the Tron network. He<a href="https://bitcoinist.com/justin-sun-buys-5-million-crv/" rel="nofollow"> recently acquired 5 million CRV from Egorov</a> by paying using Tether’s USDT in a direct Over-the-counter (OTC) trade. Justin confirmed the purchase in a <a href="https://twitter.com/justinsuntron/status/1686308662363697152?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1686308662363697152%7Ctwgr%5E98878e86dd216b015459ccfb3b0218b6ed070606%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cryptotimes.io%2Fjustin-sun-and-dcf-god-acquires-curve-founders-crv-tokens%2F" rel="nofollow">tweet</a> noting that both platforms “As steadfast partners” will keep being “&#8230;committed to providing support whenever needed.”</p>
<p>According to a Twitter <a href="https://twitter.com/sandraaleow/status/1686331246593359872" rel="nofollow">post</a> by Sandra from Nansen, other popular purchasers of Curve tokens include Cream Finance, Machi Big Brother, DWF Labs, DCFGod, and Andrew Kang, co-founder of Mechanism Capital. </p>

<p>A vast majority of these transactions were conducted through OTC, with Egorov realizing over $20 million, which he applied to balancing his borrowings and removing himself from liquidation. Egorov also sent another huge supply of CRV (17.5 million) to an address starting with 0xf51. </p>
<p>Once the largest DeFi protocol on the Ethereum blockchain, the vast majority of Curve trading volumes still come from Ethereum. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-157559643.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545709</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu’s DeFi Aspirations May Rattle DOGE’s Market As SHIB Turns To Digital IDs</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-defi-aspirations-may-rattle-doges-market-as-shib-turns-to-digital-ids/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 20:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[memecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545685</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Initially tagged as a meme coin, Shiba Inu has been reinventing itself, aiming to break away from its meme coin status and step into the league of serious Decentralized Finance (DeFi) contenders, according to a new report. A key step towards this transformation involves an innovation that is about to reshape the Shiba Inu ecosystem: Digital Identity Verification. Embracing Digital Identity In The Shiba Inu Ecosystem In a push to improve the platform&#8217;s credibility among users and governmental entities, the Shiba Inu project is said to integrate Digital Identity Verification into all its future developments. This includes the forthcoming Shibarium Layer 2 blockchain, an update eagerly anticipated by the community. Related Reading: Whale Activity Spikes As Shiba Inu Preps For Shibarium Launch Digital identities or Self-Sovereign Identities (SSI) are, in essence, the digital counterparts of traditional identification documents such as passports and driver’s licenses. In the digital realm, SSIs confer users greater control over their personal data and its distribution online. Currently, Shiba Inu developers are reportedly collaborating with community projects that use SHIB or plan to build on the Shibarium blockchain to prioritize SSI deployment. Shiba Inu&#8217;s lead developer, &#8220;Shytoshi Kusama,&#8221; was the one who revealed the project&#8217;s ambitious goals. He stated that they are currently &#8220;laying the groundwork for a new global standard in decentralized digital trust and international identity verification. In this way, Shibarium is the herald of a new digital age where faith in systems is restored and enhanced.” Implications For Dogecoin (DOGE) A shift in the crypto market dynamics may be on the horizon as Shiba Inu&#8217;s foray into DeFi may have ripple effects, most specifically on Dogecoin (DOGE). Both SHIB and DOGE started as meme coins, but Shiba Inu&#8217;s recent maneuvers may force a reconsideration of its stature. With the rise of digital identities and data protection as hot-button topics in areas like Canada and the European Union, Shiba Inu’s move to integrate digital identities into its ecosystem could elevate its reputation. This could lead to an increase in demand for SHIB tokens, which may exert upward pressure on the coin&#8217;s price. In contrast, Dogecoin, which remains firmly in its meme coin status, may find itself in an increasingly precarious position. Although, DOGE still has its biggest fan and supporter, Elon Musk behind it, should Shiba Inu succeed in its DeFi transformation, it may establish a new benchmark for meme coins and, in turn, create additional pressure on DOGE to redefine its strategic direction. Furthermore, currently, DOGE is recording more losses than Shiba Inu in the past 24 hours. Particularly, Dogecoin has dropped by nearly 4% in this period while SHIB has only seen a modest downtrend of just 0.4% Related Reading: Can Dogecoin Reach $0.85? Bullish Setup Hints At Potential For Advance Meanwhile, as DOGE records losses of 7.4% in the past week, SHIB has gone in the opposite direction with an upward trend of 4.5%. At the time of writing, DOGE currently trades at a price of $0.073 while SHIB trades at $0.00000822. It is worth noting that despite the noteworthy difference in both DOGE and SHIB price action, the former still remains at the top among the largest crypto by market cap with over $10 billion in market cap while the latter records $4.8 billion in market cap. Featured image from CoinDesk, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Initially tagged as a meme coin, Shiba Inu has been reinventing itself, aiming to break away from its meme coin status and step into the league of serious Decentralized Finance (DeFi) contenders, according to a new <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/08/03/shiba-inu-take-steps-to-become-defi-contender-will-add-digital-ids-to-ecosystem-projects/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a>.</p>
<p>A key step towards this transformation involves an innovation that is about to reshape the Shiba Inu ecosystem: Digital Identity Verification.</p>
<h2>Embracing Digital Identity In The Shiba Inu Ecosystem</h2>
<p>In a push to improve the platform&#8217;s credibility among users and governmental entities, the Shiba Inu project is said to integrate Digital Identity Verification into all its future developments. This includes the forthcoming <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/whale-activity-spikes-as-shiba-inu-preps-for-shibarium-launch/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Shibarium Layer 2 blockchain</a>, an update eagerly anticipated by the community.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/whale-activity-spikes-as-shiba-inu-preps-for-shibarium-launch/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Whale Activity Spikes As Shiba Inu Preps For Shibarium Launch</a></p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Digital identities or Self-Sovereign Identities (SSI) are, in essence, the digital counterparts of traditional identification documents such as passports and driver’s licenses. In the digital realm, SSIs confer users greater control over their personal data and its distribution online. </p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Currently, Shiba Inu developers are reportedly collaborating with community projects that use SHIB or plan to build on the Shibarium blockchain to prioritize SSI deployment.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Inu&#8217;s lead developer, &#8220;Shytoshi Kusama,&#8221; was the one who revealed the project&#8217;s ambitious goals. He stated that they are currently &#8220;laying the groundwork for a new global standard in decentralized digital trust and international identity verification. In this way, Shibarium is the herald of a new digital age where faith in systems is restored and enhanced.”</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Implications For Dogecoin (DOGE)</h2>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">A shift in the crypto market dynamics may be on the horizon as Shiba Inu&#8217;s foray into DeFi may have ripple effects, most specifically on Dogecoin (DOGE). Both <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-whales-snag-1-trillion-tokens/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">SHIB</a> and DOGE started as meme coins, but Shiba Inu&#8217;s recent maneuvers may force a reconsideration of its stature.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the rise of digital identities and data protection as hot-button topics in areas like Canada and the European Union, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-price-prediction-shibarium-trend-reversal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Shiba Inu’s move</a> to integrate digital identities into its ecosystem could elevate its reputation. </p>
<p dir="ltr">This could lead to an increase in demand for SHIB tokens, which may exert upward pressure on the coin&#8217;s price. In contrast, Dogecoin, which remains firmly in its meme coin status, may find itself in an increasingly precarious position. </p>
<p dir="ltr">Although, DOGE still has its <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin-up-13-after-musk-tweet/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">biggest fan and supporter, Elon Musk</a> behind it, should Shiba Inu succeed in its DeFi transformation, it may establish a new benchmark for meme coins and, in turn, create additional pressure on DOGE to redefine its strategic direction.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Furthermore, currently, DOGE is recording more losses than Shiba Inu in the past 24 hours. Particularly, Dogecoin has dropped by nearly 4% in this period while SHIB has only seen a modest downtrend of just 0.4%</p>

<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, as DOGE records losses of 7.4% in the past week, SHIB has gone in the opposite direction with an upward trend of 4.5%. At the time of writing, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/all/can-dogecoin-reach-0-85-bullish-setup-hints-at-potential-for-advance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">DOGE currently trades at a price of $0.073</a> while SHIB trades at $0.00000822.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is worth noting that despite the noteworthy difference in both DOGE and SHIB price action, the former still remains at the top among the largest crypto by market cap with over $10 billion in market cap while the latter records $4.8 billion in market cap.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/EGGnxP0s/" alt="Shiba Inu (SHIB)’s price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1408"/>
<p dir="ltr">Featured image from CoinDesk, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Shiba-Inu.jpeg?fit=460%2C329" width="460" height="329" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545685</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance CEO Shares Details Of $20 Million Scam Attempt</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/binance/binance-ceo-shares-details-of-20-million-scam-attempt/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 19:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance CEO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[changpeng zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto scam]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zero-transfer phishing attack]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545675</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Binance CEO, Changpeng ‘CZ’ Zhao has recently provided details on a failed $20 million scam attempt in a bid to keep the crypto community on alert for future occurrences. Crypto Scammers Are &#8220;So Good Now,&#8221; Binance CEO Says In a tweet on August 2, Changpeng Zhao described a recent scam attempt as &#8220;clever,&#8221; stating that it was &#8220;luckily&#8221; prevented as the bad actors in the crypto space seem to have gotten better.  Related Reading: Curve DAO (CRV) Price Recovery Post-Exploit: What Would Be A Realistic Scenario? Specifically, the Binance CEO drew attention to how these scammers now generate addresses with identical starting and ending letters as other wallet addresses. Using these new addresses, they then proceed to impersonate other network participants and swindle unsuspecting crypto users. Technically, these kinds of scams are referred to as  “zero-transfer phishing attacks.” I want to share this (luckily) unsuccessful, but very clever and close scam incident from yesterday 👇. Saved $20m. Hope it may also save you one day. The scammers are so good now they generate addresses with the same starting and ending letters, which is what most people check… https://t.co/DFpdX8aNay — CZ 🔶 Binance (@cz_binance) August 2, 2023 Changpeng Zhao noted that these scams are particularly effective as most crypto users only confirm the first and last characters of an address when conducting transactions. In fact, he stated that most wallet designs exclude the middle parts of addresses in an attempt to offer a better user interface to users Asides from creating similar wallet addresses, the Binance CEO mentioned that these scammers would send “dust transactions” so they could be registered in their targets’ transaction history. To explain, dust refers to a minute amount of cryptocurrency, usually valued at less than a cent, and cannot be traded on any exchange.  With the scammer’s address now present in their target’s transaction history, one can unknowingly transfer assets to these bad actors, especially if the impersonated address is one they constantly transact with. &#160; Total crypto market cap valued at $1.13 trillion on the 4-hour chart &#124; Source: TOTAL chart on Tradingview.com Fast Response Helped Thwart Zero-Transfer Phishing Attack Changpeng Zhao stated that a zero phishing attack happened to a veteran crypto operator on Aug 1 in which they transferred $20 million worth of USDT to the wrong address. For context, the original wallet address was 0xa7Bf48749D2E4aA29e3209879956b9bAa9E90570, while the phishing address was 0xa7B4BAC8f0f9692e56750aEFB5f6cB5516E90570. Luckily, the operator detected the scam quickly, and Binance was able to officially request for Tether to freeze the stolen USDT. The stablecoin operator responded promptly by blacklisting the wallet to prevent any further deposit or withdrawal.  Related Reading: Ethereum DeFi Coins Plunge As Curve Concerns Threaten Major Market Crash The Binance CEO rounded off his tweet by stating that a fast reaction was vital to reclaiming users&#8217; funds in these kinds of attacks. However, he did state that the assets recovery may take some time as the sender would have to complete a number of processes, including submitting a police report.  It is no news that the crypto space is riddled with heists, scams, and attacks which result in the loss of millions of dollars yearly. And these crypto scams are considered one of the major plagues in the crypto space. According to data from Certik Security, crypto scams and hacks claimed over $313 million in just Q2 2023 alone. Another report from TRM Labs in June 2023 said that over $9 billion was lost to various scams and frauds in 2022. A huge portion (around $7.8 billion) of this figure was lost to Ponzi schemes alone, TRM added.  Featured image from Binance, chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance CEO, Changpeng ‘CZ’ Zhao has recently provided details on a failed $20 million scam attempt in a bid to keep the crypto community on alert for future occurrences.</p>
<h2>Crypto Scammers Are &#8220;So Good Now,&#8221; Binance CEO Says
</h2>
<p>In a <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1686764372616515585?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">tweet on August 2</a>, Changpeng Zhao described a recent scam attempt as &#8220;clever,&#8221; stating that it was &#8220;luckily&#8221; prevented as the bad actors in the crypto space seem to have gotten better. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/all/curve-dao-crv-price-recovery-post-exploit-what-would-be-a-realistic-scenario/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Curve DAO (CRV) Price Recovery Post-Exploit: What Would Be A Realistic Scenario?</a></p>
<p>Specifically, the Binance CEO drew attention to how these scammers now generate addresses with identical starting and ending letters as other wallet addresses.
</p>
<p>Using these new addresses, they then proceed to impersonate other network participants and swindle unsuspecting crypto users. Technically, these kinds of scams are referred to as  “zero-transfer phishing attacks.”</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">I want to share this (luckily) unsuccessful, but very clever and close scam incident from yesterday <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f447.png" alt="👇" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />. Saved $20m. Hope it may also save you one day.</p>
<p>The scammers are so good now they generate addresses with the same starting and ending letters, which is what most people check… <a href="https://t.co/DFpdX8aNay" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/DFpdX8aNay</a></p>
<p>— CZ <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f536.png" alt="🔶" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Binance (@cz_binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1686764372616515585?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 2, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Changpeng Zhao noted that these scams are particularly effective as most crypto users only confirm the first and last characters of an address when conducting transactions.</p>
<p>In fact, he stated that most wallet designs exclude the middle parts of addresses in an attempt to offer a better user interface to users</p>
<p>Asides from creating similar wallet addresses, the Binance CEO mentioned that these scammers would send “dust transactions” so they could be registered in their targets’ transaction history.</p>
<p>To explain, dust refers to a minute amount of cryptocurrency, usually valued at less than a cent, and cannot be traded on any exchange. </p>
<p>With the scammer’s address now present in their target’s transaction history, one can unknowingly transfer assets to these bad actors, especially if the impersonated address is one they constantly transact with.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Fq6adiJ4/" alt="Binance CEO" width="1480" height="906"/></p>

<h2>Fast Response Helped Thwart Zero-Transfer Phishing Attack</h2>
<p>Changpeng Zhao stated that <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-scam-7-8b-in-losses-in-2022/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">a zero phishing attack happened</a> to a veteran crypto operator on Aug 1 in which they transferred $20 million worth of USDT to the wrong address. </p>
<p>For context, the original wallet address was 0xa7Bf48749D2E4aA29e3209879956b9bAa9E90570, while the phishing address was 0xa7B4BAC8f0f9692e56750aEFB5f6cB5516E90570.</p>
<p>Luckily, the operator detected the scam quickly, and Binance was able to officially request for Tether to freeze the stolen USDT. The stablecoin operator responded promptly by blacklisting the wallet to prevent any further deposit or withdrawal. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum-defi-coins-plunge-curve-concerns-crash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum DeFi Coins Plunge As Curve Concerns Threaten Major Market Crash</a></p>
<p>The Binance CEO rounded off his tweet by stating that a fast reaction was vital to reclaiming users&#8217; funds in these kinds of attacks. However, he did state that the assets recovery may take some time as the sender would have to complete a number of processes, including submitting a police report. </p>
<p>It is no news that the crypto space is riddled with heists, scams, and attacks which result in the loss of millions of dollars yearly. And these crypto scams are considered one of the major plagues in the crypto space. </p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.certik.com/resources/blog/6KJQKBrVJEwHR6Tc4PAvJo-hack3d-the-web3-security-quarterly-report-q2-2023" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from Certik Security</a>, crypto scams and hacks claimed over $313 million in just Q2 2023 alone. Another <a href="https://www.trmlabs.com/report#Fraud-and-Scams" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report from TRM Labs in June 2023</a> said that over $9 billion was lost to various scams and frauds in 2022. A huge portion (around $7.8 billion) of this figure was lost to Ponzi schemes alone, TRM added. </p>
<p>Featured image from Binance, chart from Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/974499ec-8af9-4eb3-967e-2885471a5c54.png?fit=460%2C259" width="460" height="259" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545675</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Quant Explains How These Indicators Affect Ethereum Price</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/quant-explains-how-these-indicators-affect-ethereum-price/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 18:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Coinbase Premium]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Korean Premium]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Taker Buy/Sell Ratio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545635</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A quant has explained how the indicators like taker buy/sell ratio and Coinbase premium index can influence the price of Ethereum. Ethereum&#8217;s Relationship With Taker Buy/Sell Ratio &#38; Coinbase Premium Index In a new CryptoQuant quicktake post, an analyst has discussed some metrics that could hold relevance for the ETH price. The first indicator of interest here is the &#8220;taker buy/sell ratio,&#8221; which tells us about the ratio between the Ethereum buy and sell orders in the market right now. When this metric has a value greater than 1, it means that the taker buy volume is higher than the taker sell volume. Such a trend implies that the majority of the investors are bullish on the asset currently. On the other hand, values below the threshold naturally imply the dominance of bearish sentiment, as there are currently more sell orders present on exchanges. Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the 50-day moving average (MA) Ethereum taker buy/sell ratio over the past few years: The potential relationship between these indicators and the value of the cryptocurrency &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As you can see in the above graph, the quant has highlighted the pattern that the Ethereum price and the 50-day MA taker buy/sell ratio have possibly followed during the past couple of years. It would appear that whenever the value of the asset has rallied, the taker buy/sell ratio has gone down. This would suggest that the sell orders on the market pile up as the ETH price trends up. Related Reading: Bitcoin Funding Rates Most Positive Since Feb, Long Squeeze Soon? The analyst notes that this is naturally because the investors become more cautious as the price continues to rise since they think a correction may be coming soon. The sell orders continue until the cryptocurrency has topped out, and once the decline hits the asset, the buy orders start going up instead. From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that significant accumulation periods have generally paved the way for the price to bottom out and begin another rally. The quant has also attached data for another metric: the Coinbase Premium Index. This indicator keeps track of the difference in the Ethereum prices listed on Coinbase and Binance. Whenever this metric has a positive value, it means that the Coinbase platform has BTC listed at a higher price than Binance currently. This implies that buying pressure has been stronger from US-based investors, who usually use the former exchange. Similarly, negative values imply just the opposite. According to the analyst, major fluctuations in the Ethereum price have generally come with strong changes in the Coinbase premium index, a possible sign that activity on the exchange is the driver for these price moves. Currently, the 50-day MA taker buy/sell ratio is at relatively low values and is looking to turn around, although this trend shift towards buy order dominance isn&#8217;t confirmed just yet. Related Reading: Litecoin Completes Halving, But Price Plunges 6% The Coinbase Premium Index is at neutral values, implying that there hasn&#8217;t been any trading activity happening on the platform that&#8217;s different from Binance. Given these trends, it&#8217;s possible that Ethereum may not see any big moves in the near future. ETH Price At the time of writing, Ethereum is trading around $1,830, up 2% in the last week. ETH has erased its gains from yesterday &#124; Source: ETHUSD on TradingView Featured image from DrawKit Illustrations on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A quant has explained how the indicators like taker buy/sell ratio and Coinbase premium index can influence the price of Ethereum.</p>
<h2>Ethereum&#8217;s Relationship With Taker Buy/Sell Ratio &amp; Coinbase Premium Index</h2>
<p>In a new CryptoQuant quicktake <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/64cab1b83315ff59e279b12f-The-Impact-of-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-and-Coinbase-Premium-Index-on-the-Price-of-Et" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, an analyst has discussed some metrics that could hold relevance for the ETH price. The first indicator of interest here is the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-taker-buy-sell-ratio-highest-636-days/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">taker buy/sell ratio</a>,&#8221; which tells us about the ratio between the Ethereum buy and sell orders in the market right now.</p>
<p>When this metric has a value greater than 1, it means that the taker buy volume is higher than the taker sell volume. Such a trend implies that the majority of the investors are bullish on the asset currently.</p>
<p>On the other hand, values below the threshold naturally imply the dominance of bearish sentiment, as there are currently more sell orders present on exchanges.</p>
<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the 50-day moving average (MA) Ethereum taker buy/sell ratio over the past few years:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://i0.wp.com/img.cryptoquant.com/201529/quicktake/Bz0vpH_ab0daefa6855e4e60de043f9952fe38403c97d48cbdd644b078f6b4042cab78e.png?resize=1280%2C496&#038;ssl=1" alt="Ethereum Taker Buy/Sell Ratio" width="1280" height="496"  data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>As you can see in the above graph, the quant has highlighted the pattern that the Ethereum price and the 50-day MA taker buy/sell ratio have possibly followed during the past couple of years.</p>
<p>It would appear that whenever the value of the asset has rallied, the taker buy/sell ratio has gone down. This would suggest that the sell orders on the market pile up as the ETH price trends up.</p>

<p>The analyst notes that this is naturally because the investors become more cautious as the price continues to rise since they think a correction may be coming soon.</p>
<p>The sell orders continue until the cryptocurrency has topped out, and once the decline hits the asset, the buy orders start going up instead.</p>
<p>From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that significant accumulation periods have generally paved the way for the price to bottom out and begin another rally.</p>
<p>The quant has also attached data for another metric: the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-coinbase-premium-buying-ending/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Coinbase Premium Index</a>. This indicator keeps track of the difference in the Ethereum prices listed on Coinbase and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/doj-action-binance-hidden-blessing-bitcoin-crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Binance</a>.</p>
<p>Whenever this metric has a positive value, it means that the Coinbase platform has BTC listed at a higher price than Binance currently. This implies that buying pressure has been stronger from US-based investors, who usually use the former exchange. Similarly, negative values imply just the opposite.</p>
<p>According to the analyst, major fluctuations in the Ethereum price have generally come with strong changes in the Coinbase premium index, a possible sign that activity on the exchange is the driver for these price moves.</p>
<p>Currently, the 50-day MA taker buy/sell ratio is at relatively low values and is looking to turn around, although this trend shift towards buy order dominance isn&#8217;t confirmed just yet.</p>

<p>The Coinbase Premium Index is at neutral values, implying that there hasn&#8217;t been any trading activity happening on the platform that&#8217;s different from Binance. Given these trends, it&#8217;s possible that Ethereum may not see any big moves in the near future.</p>
<h2>ETH Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Ethereum is trading around $1,830, up 2% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/SBCDbhaX/" alt="Ethereum Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/drawkit-illustrations-8iIUDnRq87o-unsplash.jpg?fit=460%2C259" width="460" height="259" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545635</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breaking: Elon Musk&#8217;s X To Launch Trading App, Dogecoin To Play A Part?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/breaking-elon-musks-x-to-launch-trading-app-dogecoin-to-play-a-part/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 17:49:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Breaking News Ticker]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusdt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545719</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[According to a recent report by Semafor, the company formerly known as Twitter (X) is making waves yet again, as it seeks to transform itself into a financial data giant by building a trading hub within its app. Will Dogecoin take the center of the stage? Elon Musk&#8217;s X Set To Disrupt Traditional Trading Platforms? In a request for plans viewed by Semafor and individuals familiar with the matter, the company outlined its vision for integrating financial content, real-time stock data, and other features into its platform.  The request emphasizes the power of real-time information in investing. It highlights the enormous user base of &#8220;hundreds of millions of highly-qualified users&#8221; that the company can offer to potential partners. Related Reading: Why The Uniswap (UNI) Token Is Almost Worthless: Researcher One striking aspect of the request is the absence of any mention of compensation. Instead, interested bidders are asked to state how much money they will commit to the project.  This unconventional approach reflects the company&#8217;s determination to forge a new path and disrupt the industry without relying on traditional financial partnerships or revenue models. The comparison to WeChat in China, Gojek in Indonesia, Grab in Singapore, and Gozem in Africa further illustrates the company&#8217;s ambition.  These “super-apps” have transformed how people in their respective regions interact with technology, offering a wide range of services within a single platform. By positioning itself as the first Western super-app, the company aims to disrupt the traditional trading platforms. Dogecoin Integration On X&#8217;s Trading App? Twitter&#8217;s latest move to introduce a feature allowing users to access live stock charts by simply searching for a &#8220;cashtag&#8221; has sparked intrigue and speculation in the online community.  With cashtag clicks experiencing a remarkable 51% growth over the past two months, it&#8217;s clear that Twitter is onto something potentially lucrative. This feature could attract users and generate revenue for the company through partnerships with data startups like TradingView. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Notches New Adoption Record In Anticipation Of Shibarium Launch On the other hand, Musk&#8217;s support for Dogecoin has been well-documented, and now, with the introduction of his new trading app, speculation is growing about the potential impact on the meme coin&#8217;s price. When writing, Dogecoin is trading at $0.07461, maintaining its price level for the past 24 hours. Nevertheless, the introduction of Musk&#8217;s trading app has the potential to ignite a new wave of enthusiasm for Dogecoin, increasing its value. However, it&#8217;s worth noting that Twitter&#8217;s plans to incorporate a one-click option to buy and sell stocks on eToro, a competitor to Robinhood, have been delayed.  Initially slated for an April launch, this feature has yet to materialize. The potential to refer users to a brokerage platform like eToro could be a significant revenue stream for Twitter, as it seeks to regain the advertisers it lost after Elon Musk&#8217;s takeover. While Twitter&#8217;s foray into financial services and e-commerce may seem bold and innovative, it is not without its challenges. Other social media giants in the United States, such as Snapchat and Meta (formerly Facebook), have attempted similar ventures with little success. UPDATE: Elon Musk denied the report and claims that X (Twitter) is not looking to launch trading services. No we aren’t — Elon Musk (@elonmusk) August 3, 2023  Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to a recent <a href="https://www.semafor.com/article/08/03/2023/elon-musks-plan-to-own-the-meme-stocks" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a> by Semafor, the company formerly known as Twitter (X) is making waves yet again, as it seeks to transform itself into a financial data giant by building a trading hub within its app. Will Dogecoin take the center of the stage?</p>
<h2>Elon Musk&#8217;s X Set To Disrupt Traditional Trading Platforms?</h2>
<p>In a request for plans viewed by Semafor and individuals familiar with the matter, the company outlined its vision for integrating financial content, real-time stock data, and other features into its platform. </p>
<p>The request emphasizes the power of real-time information in investing. It highlights the enormous user base of &#8220;hundreds of millions of highly-qualified users&#8221; that the company can offer to potential partners.</p>

<p>One striking aspect of the request is the absence of any mention of compensation. Instead, interested bidders are asked to state how much money they will commit to the project. </p>
<p>This unconventional approach reflects the company&#8217;s determination to forge a new path and disrupt the industry without relying on traditional financial partnerships or revenue models.</p>
<p>The comparison to WeChat in China, Gojek in Indonesia, Grab in Singapore, and Gozem in Africa further illustrates the company&#8217;s ambition. </p>
<p>These “super-apps” have transformed how people in their respective regions interact with technology, offering a wide range of services within a single platform. By positioning itself as the first Western super-app, the company aims to disrupt the traditional trading platforms.</p>
Dogecoin Integration On X&#8217;s Trading App?
<p>Twitter&#8217;s latest move to introduce a feature allowing users to access live stock charts by simply searching for a &#8220;cashtag&#8221; has sparked intrigue and speculation in the online community. </p>
<p>With cashtag clicks experiencing a remarkable 51% growth over the past two months, it&#8217;s clear that Twitter is onto something potentially lucrative. This feature could attract users and generate revenue for the company through partnerships with data startups like TradingView.</p>

<p>On the other hand, Musk&#8217;s support for Dogecoin has been well-documented, and now, with the introduction of his new trading app, speculation is growing about the potential impact on the meme coin&#8217;s price.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/iZF2rpcf/" alt="Dogecoin " width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>When writing, Dogecoin is trading at $0.07461, maintaining its price level for the past 24 hours. Nevertheless, the introduction of Musk&#8217;s trading app has the potential to ignite a new wave of enthusiasm for Dogecoin, increasing its value.</p>
<p>However, it&#8217;s worth noting that Twitter&#8217;s plans to incorporate a one-click option to buy and sell stocks on eToro, a competitor to Robinhood, have been delayed. </p>
<p>Initially slated for an April launch, this feature has yet to materialize. The potential to refer users to a brokerage platform like eToro could be a significant revenue stream for Twitter, as it seeks to regain the advertisers it lost after Elon Musk&#8217;s takeover.</p>
<p>While Twitter&#8217;s foray into financial services and e-commerce may seem bold and innovative, it is not without its challenges. Other social media giants in the United States, such as Snapchat and Meta (formerly Facebook), have attempted similar ventures with little success.</p>
<p>UPDATE: Elon Musk denied the report and claims that X (Twitter) is not looking to launch trading services.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">No we aren’t</p>
<p>— Elon Musk (@elonmusk) <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1687179163856424961?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">August 3, 2023</a> </p></blockquote>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1311148884.jpg?fit=460%2C316" width="460" height="316" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545719</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Notches New Adoption Record In Anticipation Of Shibarium Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-notches-new-adoption-record-in-anticipation-of-shibarium-launch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 17:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shibarium]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545674</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) has been garnering attention in recent weeks, with its price showing a good recovery after reaching a yearly low in June. This coincides with the excitement around the upcoming launch of Shibarium, a layer-2 blockchain network for the second-largest meme token. It appears that the forthcoming Shibarium launch has propelled SHIB to a significant milestone, as the number of addresses holding the token has hit a new all-time record.  Shiba Inu Sets New All-Time High In Addresses Data from IntoTheBlock reveals that the number of SHIB addresses at a given time has reached a new peak of 3.51 million. The previous all-time high was set in May 2022, when the number of addresses stood at 3.23 million. The number of addresses holding the SHIB token has been steadily rising in the past few months, but this rate of adoption notably surged in July. This is reflected in last week’s figure, as the number of addresses holding the token spiked by more than 22%. Related Reading: Over $28 Million In SHIB Withdrawn From Exchanges Ahead Of Shibarium Launch A steady increase in the number of SHIB addresses suggests a growing interest in the meme token. This can be attributed to a combination of various factors, including the upcoming Shibarium launch, the token’s price performance, and the recent resurgence of DOGE &#8211; the poster boy for meme coins. The recent market activity of Shiba Inu whales further amplifies the optimism surrounding the SHIB token. On Wednesday, August 2, NewsBTC reported that the cryptocurrency’s large volume transactions reached approximately 1.13 trillion SHIB. SHIB Price Hovers Around Critical Level &#8211; Price Overview The price of the Shiba Inu appears to be slowing down after displaying bullish strength before the end of July. The token rallied nearly 12% between July 28 and July 30 to break above the $0.000008 level. However, this recent momentum appears to be waning, as the token’s price has not made any notable action in the past few days. With a 0.9% price dip in the last 24 hours, the SHIB token continues to trade within the $0.00000831 zone. SHIBUSDT trading within the $0.0000083 zone on daily timeframe &#124; Source: SHIBUSDT chart from TradingView Investors should keep an eye on the meme coin in the coming week, as a break out of this zone could see it visit the $0.0000087 mark again. Moreover, with the Shibarium mainnet launch roughly 10 days away, a bullish scenario may be on the cards. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Price Prediction: Is Shibarium The Key To A Trend Reversal? According to CoinGecko data, the SHIB token is currently valued at $0.0000082, representing a 4.5% price increase in the past week. With a market cap of roughly $4.86 billion, Shiba Inu ranks as the 15th-largest cryptocurrency in the market. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB) has been garnering attention in recent weeks, with its price showing a good recovery after reaching a yearly low in June. This coincides with the excitement around the upcoming launch of Shibarium, a layer-2 blockchain network for the second-largest meme token.</p>
<p>It appears that the forthcoming Shibarium launch has propelled SHIB to a significant milestone, as the number of addresses holding the token has hit a new all-time record. </p>
<h2>Shiba Inu Sets New All-Time High In Addresses</h2>
<p>Data from <a href="https://app.intotheblock.com/coin/SHIB/deep-dive?group=all&amp;chart=all" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">IntoTheBlock</a> reveals that the number of SHIB addresses at a given time has reached a new peak of 3.51 million. The previous all-time high was set in May 2022, when the number of addresses stood at 3.23 million.</p>
<p>The number of addresses holding the SHIB token has been steadily rising in the past few months, but this rate of adoption notably surged in July. This is reflected in last week’s figure, as the number of addresses holding the token spiked by more than 22%.</p>



<p>A steady increase in the number of SHIB addresses suggests a growing interest in the meme token. This can be attributed to a combination of various factors, including the upcoming Shibarium launch, the token’s price performance, and the recent resurgence of DOGE &#8211; the poster boy for meme coins.</p>
<p>The recent market activity of Shiba Inu whales further amplifies the optimism surrounding the SHIB token. On Wednesday, August 2, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/whale-activity-spikes-as-shiba-inu-preps-for-shibarium-launch/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">NewsBTC reported</a> that the cryptocurrency’s large volume transactions reached approximately 1.13 trillion SHIB.</p>
<h2>SHIB Price Hovers Around Critical Level &#8211; Price Overview</h2>
<p>The price of the Shiba Inu appears to be slowing down after displaying bullish strength before the end of July. The token rallied nearly 12% between July 28 and July 30 to break above the $0.000008 level.</p>
<p>However, this recent momentum appears to be waning, as the token’s price has not made any notable action in the past few days. With a 0.9% price dip in the last 24 hours, the SHIB token continues to trade within the $0.00000831 zone.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/SI1zK2OH/" alt="Shiba Inu" width="997" height="580"/></p>

<p>Investors should keep an eye on the meme coin in the coming week, as a break out of this zone could see it visit the $0.0000087 mark again. Moreover, with the Shibarium mainnet launch roughly 10 days away, a bullish scenario may be on the cards.</p>
<p>Related Reading:<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-price-prediction-shibarium-trend-reversal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> Shiba Inu Price Prediction: Is Shibarium The Key To A Trend Reversal?</a></p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/shiba-inu" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko data</a>, the SHIB token is currently valued at $0.0000082, representing a 4.5% price increase in the past week. With a market cap of roughly $4.86 billion, Shiba Inu ranks as the 15th-largest cryptocurrency in the market.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/mike-hindle-xl_MQrtiuvg-unsplash-1-1536x1024-1.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545674</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
