<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 02:32:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Saw Increase In Volatility, Here’s Why The Bulls Are Safe</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-volatility-30k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 02:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528800</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price saw a couple of wild moves above the $28,500 pivot level. BTC is now rising and showing positive signs above the $28,800 level. Bitcoin climbed sharply and then nosedived to revisit the $27,250 support. The price is trading above $28,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $27,800 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could continue to rise if it clears the $29,400 and $29,500 resistance levels. Bitcoin Price Regains Traction Bitcoin price started a major increase from the $27,000 support zone. BTC climbed over $2,000 and broke the $29,250 resistance zone. It even tested the $30,000 resistance before the bears appeared. There was a sharp decline from the $30,037 high. Bitcoin dived over $2,000 and retested the $27,250 support where the bulls emerged. The price is now rising and trading above $28,000. It is also above $28,200 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. Besides, there is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $27,800 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. The bulls pushed the price above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $30,037 swing high to the $27,258 low. Immediate resistance is near the $29,400 level. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $30,037 swing high to the $27,258 low is also near the $29,400 zone. The next major resistance sits near the $29,500 zone. A close above the $29,500 resistance could send Bitcoin toward $30,000. Any more gains could open the doors for a test of the key barrier at $31,000. Fresh Decline in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $29,400 resistance, it could again start a fresh decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $28,650 level. The next major support is near the $28,000 zone or the trend line. A downside break and close below the $28,000 support might push the price toward the $27,500 support. Any more losses might take Bitcoin toward $27,250. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $28,650, followed by $28,000. Major Resistance Levels – $29,400, $29,500, and $30,000.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price saw a couple of wild moves above the $28,500 pivot level. BTC is now rising and showing positive signs above the $28,800 level.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin climbed sharply and then nosedived to revisit the $27,250 support.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $28,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $27,800 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to rise if it clears the $29,400 and $29,500 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Regains Traction</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price started a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-signals-increase-29k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">major increase from the $27,000 support zone</a>. BTC climbed over $2,000 and broke the $29,250 resistance zone. It even tested the $30,000 resistance before the bears appeared.</p>
<p>There was a sharp decline from the $30,037 high. Bitcoin dived over $2,000 and retested the $27,250 support where the bulls emerged. The price is now rising and trading above $28,000. It is also above $28,200 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-vulnerable-28k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>. Besides, there is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $27,800 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>The bulls pushed the price above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $30,037 swing high to the $27,258 low. Immediate resistance is near the $29,400 level.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-17.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-528801" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-17.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-17.png 1834w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-17-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-17-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-17-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-17-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-17-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-17-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $30,037 swing high to the $27,258 low is also near the $29,400 zone. The next major resistance sits near the $29,500 zone. A close above the $29,500 resistance could send Bitcoin toward $30,000. Any more gains could open the doors for a test of the key barrier at $31,000.</p>
<h2>Fresh Decline in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $29,400 resistance, it could again start a fresh decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $28,650 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $28,000 zone or the trend line. A downside break and close below the $28,000 support might push the price toward the $27,500 support. Any more losses might take Bitcoin toward $27,250.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $28,650, followed by $28,000.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $29,400, $29,500, and $30,000.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/shutterstock_587323760-460x343.jpg" width="460" height="343" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Flash Crashes 6% In Under 60 Minutes, What Happened?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-flash-crashes-6-in-under-60-minutes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 21:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528795</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price was trading in the green today, up about $1,500 at the high. The top cryptocurrency by market cap also made another attempt at $30,000 around mid-day.  Shortly thereafter, in the span of less than 60 minutes, BTCUSD flash crashed by more than 6%, leaving the marker bewildered. Here is a closer look at the sharp selloff and some potential reasons for the reset.  Bitcoin Price Bleeds 6% In 60 Minutes Crypto market volatility is picking up and it’s doing so in a major way. Today alone, Bitcoin price was up by more than 6%, then saw the entire rally and then some wiped out in a nearly 7%, one hour long selloff.  Bulls who were gloating to start the day are now licking wounds and scratching their heads. Even bears aren’t sure what to think about today’s price action, it happened so quickly.  Related Reading: Not So Fast: Bitcoin Strength Fails To Breach This Key Bullish Level If recent lows at $27,000 don’t hold, today’s selloff could be the start of a second corrective wave down in BTCUSD. If the level does indeed hold, the move is more than likely the results of long positions in profit closing in succession, followed by stop losses being triggered who entered on the way up, wiping out open interest and resetting technical indicators.  6%+ in under 60 minutes &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com What To Watch For: Shakeout Or Rejection? The daily candle currently has a massive wick at the top and a decent-sized lower shadow, demonstrating the struggle between bulls and bears in today’s trading session.  Related Reading: Why Bitcoin May Have Completed The “Perfect” Pullback Bitcoin price continues to find resistance at $30,000, and needs to press higher to convince the market that crypto winter is over. Rejection here could be disastrous for the top cryptocurrency by market cap. However, it is possible the move was merely a shakeout before continuation. One thing is certain: this type of volatility should continue for the near term.  Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for exclusive daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-price-reclaims-29800-driven-by-these-factors/">Bitcoin price</a> was trading in the green today, up about $1,500 at the high. The top cryptocurrency by market cap also made another attempt at $30,000 around mid-day. </p>
<p>Shortly thereafter, in the span of less than 60 minutes, BTCUSD flash crashed by more than 6%, leaving the marker bewildered. Here is a closer look at the sharp selloff and some potential reasons for the reset. </p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Bleeds 6% In 60 Minutes</h2>
<p>Crypto market volatility is picking up and it’s doing so in a major way. Today alone, Bitcoin price was up by more than 6%, then saw the entire rally and then some wiped out in a nearly 7%, one hour long selloff. </p>
<p>Bulls who were gloating to start the day are now licking wounds and scratching their heads. Even bears aren’t sure what to think about today’s price action, it happened so quickly. </p>

<p>If recent lows at $27,000 don’t hold, today’s selloff could be the start of a second corrective wave down in BTCUSD. If the level does indeed hold, the move is more than likely the results of long positions in profit closing in succession, followed by stop losses being triggered who entered on the way up, wiping out open interest and resetting technical indicators. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-528796 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-26_17-15-50-860x412.png" alt="BTCUSD_2023-04-26_17-15-50" width="860" height="412" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-26_17-15-50-860x412.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-26_17-15-50-460x220.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-26_17-15-50-768x368.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-26_17-15-50-1536x736.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-26_17-15-50-2048x981.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-26_17-15-50-750x359.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-26_17-15-50-1140x546.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>

<h2>What To Watch For: Shakeout Or Rejection?</h2>
<p>The daily candle currently has a massive wick at the top and a decent-sized lower shadow, demonstrating the struggle between bulls and bears in today’s trading session. </p>

<p>Bitcoin price continues to find resistance at $30,000, and needs to press higher to convince the market that crypto winter is over. Rejection here could be disastrous for the top cryptocurrency by market cap. However, it is possible the move was merely a shakeout before continuation.</p>
<p>One thing is certain: this type of volatility should continue for the near term. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/iStock-626245206-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Highly Profitable Bitcoin Cross Has Just Formed Again</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/highly-profitable-bitcoin-cross-formed-again/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 19:25:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bullish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bullish Cross]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Realized Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528764</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that a Bitcoin cross that has proved quite profitable has once again formed for the cryptocurrency. Bitcoin Realized Price Of Short-Term Holders Overtakes Long-Term Holders As an analyst in a CryptoQuant post explained, the realized price of the 1 to 3 months holders has just exceeded that of the 6 to 12 months investors. The &#8220;realized price&#8221; here refers to a metric derived from the &#8220;realized cap,&#8221; which is a capitalization model for Bitcoin that assumes a coin&#8217;s true value is the price at which it was last transacted on the blockchain rather than the current BTC price as the usual market cap says. The realized price is obtained when the realized cap is divided by the total number of coins in circulation. Since the realized cap accounted for the prices at which the investors acquired their coins (their &#8220;cost basis&#8221;), the realized price represents the average acquisition price in the market. This means that whenever the Bitcoin price dips below this metric, the average cryptocurrency investor holds assets at a loss. Similarly, a break above implies a transition towards profits for the average investor. In the context of the current discussion, the realized price of three specific segments of the market is relevant; the holders who bought between 1 month and 3 months ago, 3 months and 6 months ago, and 6 months and 12 months ago. Related Reading: Bitcoin Bearish Signal: NVT Golden Cross Enters Overbought Zone The first two of these are parts of the &#8220;short-term holder&#8221; (STH) cohort, while the third one is part of the &#8220;long-term holder&#8221; (LTH) group. Here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin realized price specifically for these segments of the market: Looks like two of these metrics have come together in recent days &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As shown in the above graph, an interesting pattern formed during the leadup to the 2021 bull run. First, the realized price of the 1-month to 3 months cohort exceeded that of the 6- 12 months group. Following this crossover, BTC saw some sharp uptrend, but it didn&#8217;t last long. Related Reading: Bitcoin Market At Decision Point: aSOPR Retests Crucial Level Then, as this price increase winded down, the 3- 6 months segment also crossed above this LTH cohort. These crossovers implied that fresh purchases were happening in the market as the rally built up. Since the prices were rising during this leadup, the STHs had to buy at higher and higher prices, which is why their realized price went up and eventually became higher than the LTHs&#8217;. After these crossovers were completed, the BTC bull run ramped up. Recently, the first of these crossovers seem to be forming again, as the realized price of the 1-month 3 months group is now equal to that of the 6 months to 12 months band. While it&#8217;s uncertain if the second crossover will also go and take shape now, Bitcoin could observe at least some bullish momentum from this initial cross alone (assuming that it&#8217;s not just a fake-out), just like it did back in 2020. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,800, up 1% in the last week. BTC has seen rapid increase in the past day &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Dylan Leagh on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows that a Bitcoin cross that has proved quite profitable has once again formed for the cryptocurrency.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Realized Price Of Short-Term Holders Overtakes Long-Term Holders</h2>
<p>As an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/6448f93dbbe24f02e5e1a794-BTC-Another-price-growth" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a> explained, the realized price of the 1 to 3 months holders has just exceeded that of the 6 to 12 months investors.</p>
<p>The &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-under-realized-price-163-days/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">realized price</a>&#8221; here refers to a metric derived from the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-long-term-holders-own-80-realized-cap/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">realized cap</a>,&#8221; which is a capitalization model for Bitcoin that assumes a coin&#8217;s true value is the price at which it was last transacted on the blockchain rather than the current BTC price as the usual market cap says.</p>
<p>The realized price is obtained when the realized cap is divided by the total number of coins in circulation. Since the realized cap accounted for the prices at which the investors acquired their coins (their &#8220;cost basis&#8221;), the realized price represents the average acquisition price in the market.</p>
<p>This means that whenever the Bitcoin price dips below this metric, the average cryptocurrency investor holds assets at a loss. Similarly, a break above implies a transition towards profits for the average investor.</p>
<p>In the context of the current discussion, the realized price of three specific segments of the market is relevant; the holders who bought between 1 month and 3 months ago, 3 months and 6 months ago, and 6 months and 12 months ago.</p>

<p>The first two of these are parts of the &#8220;short-term holder&#8221; (STH) cohort, while the third one is part of the &#8220;long-term holder&#8221; (LTH) group. Here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin realized price specifically for these segments of the market:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/408039/quicktake/9d6L4HH_9938fb69e6ba213af28402eabe67aa8172d0e5599c7368d32d781db8be86c564.png" alt="Bitcoin Realized Price" width="1280" height="806" /></p>

<p>As shown in the above graph, an interesting pattern formed during the leadup to the 2021 bull run. First, the realized price of the 1-month to 3 months cohort exceeded that of the 6- 12 months group. Following this crossover, BTC saw some sharp uptrend, but it didn&#8217;t last long.</p>

<p>Then, as this price increase winded down, the 3- 6 months segment also crossed above this LTH cohort. These crossovers implied that fresh purchases were happening in the market as the rally built up. Since the prices were rising during this leadup, the STHs had to buy at higher and higher prices, which is why their realized price went up and eventually became higher than the LTHs&#8217;.</p>
<p>After these crossovers were completed, the BTC <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-supply-structure-very-similar-to-early-2019-bull-run-ahead/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bull run</a> ramped up. Recently, the first of these crossovers seem to be forming again, as the realized price of the 1-month 3 months group is now equal to that of the 6 months to 12 months band.</p>
<p>While it&#8217;s uncertain if the second crossover will also go and take shape now, Bitcoin could observe at least some bullish momentum from this initial cross alone (assuming that it&#8217;s not just a fake-out), just like it did back in 2020.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,800, up 1% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/jTpZf1TU/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1533" height="911" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/dylan-leagh-qnVXHhUP0xU-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Bulls On Edge As Pivotal Level Sets Stage For Potential Price Surge Or Slump</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-bulls-on-edge-as-pivotal-level-sets-stage-for-potential-price-surge-or-slump/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 18:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528765</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC), the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization, has experienced a volatile market over the past few days, with its price fluctuating between highs and lows. However, BTC has recently bounced back from a major trend line at $27,000 and is currently trading at $29,600, representing a profit of over 8% in the last 24 hours. This latest surge in BTC&#8217;s price comes after the collapse of a major US bank, First Republic Bank. The news of this collapse may have contributed to the uptick in BTC&#8217;s price, as investors seek alternative investment options after the bank&#8217;s failure. Related Reading: XRP Trades Near Crucial Support Of $0.46, Will This Level Hold? Another Bank Failure Tied To BTC’s Price Surge Theto the trader and analyst, who goes by the pseudonym &#8220;CJ,&#8221; has identified what they believe to be the current parameters for the market. According to CJ, if Bitcoin&#8217;s price closes above 30k and the US dollar index (DXY) breaks to a range of 97-100, the market will likely reach the 33k liquidity level. However, if Bitcoin&#8217;s price rejects this level and closes below 29250, it could be a bearish re-test. It is worth noting that Bitcoin has recently bounced from a key pivotal support level of $27,000, which is good news for bulls in the short term. However, the market is still uncertain whether Bitcoin will break above the $30,000 resistance again or experience another slump.  On the other hand, the recent bank failure, as described by Nick Gerli, CEO and Founder of Reventure Consulting, has highlighted the potential risks associated with traditional banking and finance. This has led investors to question the stability of the traditional financial system and seek alternative options. On the contrary to this situation, Bitcoin has been on the rise since the beginning of 2023, and some analysts believe that the current economic climate could be a contributing factor. The recent contraction in the money supply in the US has led to a decrease in available capital, which could lead investors to seek alternative investment options.  With its decentralized nature and limited supply, Bitcoin has become an attractive option for investors looking to diversify their portfolios. Furthermore, Bitcoin&#8217;s recent price uptick can be attributed to several factors, including increased institutional adoption and growing mainstream acceptance. However, the current economic climate has undoubtedly played a role in Bitcoin&#8217;s recent surge in value. As the economic outlook remains uncertain, many investors turn to Bitcoin as a safe haven asset. The cryptocurrency has been touted as a hedge against inflation and economic instability, and its recent price uptick could reflect these beliefs. Bitcoin Highs Already Made For The Year? The Puell Multiple, a metric used by cryptocurrency traders and analysts to gauge the value of Bitcoin, has recently made a perfect retest of its uptrend, according to CryptoCon, a trader and analyst of the crypto market. This retest suggests that the upward trend of Bitcoin remains intact and could potentially lead to much higher valuations in the future. The Puell Multiple is calculated by dividing the daily issuance value of Bitcoin by the 365-day moving average of the daily issuance value. It is a useful metric for understanding the current state of Bitcoin&#8217;s mining ecosystem and can provide insights into the potential future direction of Bitcoin&#8217;s price. With the Puell Multiple&#8217;s recent retests of its uptrend, CryptoCon suggests that the upward momentum of Bitcoin remains strong and could lead to even higher valuations in the future. This is welcome news for bulls eagerly anticipating a continued rise in Bitcoin&#8217;s price. Related Reading: Cardano ADA Trades Below The $0.41 Mark, Will It Break The Barriers? Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC), the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization, has experienced a volatile market over the past few days, with its price fluctuating between highs and lows. However, BTC has recently bounced back from a major trend line at $27,000 and is currently trading at $29,600, representing a profit of over 8% in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>This latest surge in BTC&#8217;s price comes after the collapse of a major US bank, First Republic Bank. The news of this collapse may have contributed to the uptick in BTC&#8217;s price, as investors seek alternative investment options after the bank&#8217;s failure.</p>

<h2><b>Another Bank Failure Tied To BTC’s Price Surge</b></h2>
<p>Theto the trader and analyst, who goes by the pseudonym &#8220;CJ,&#8221; has identified what they believe to be the current parameters for the market. According to CJ, if Bitcoin&#8217;s price closes above 30k and the US dollar index (DXY) breaks to a range of 97-100, the market will likely reach the 33k liquidity level. However, if Bitcoin&#8217;s price rejects this level and closes below 29250, it could be a bearish re-test.</p>
<p>It is worth noting that Bitcoin has recently bounced from a key pivotal support level of $27,000, which is good news for bulls in the short term. However, the market is still uncertain whether Bitcoin will break above the $30,000 resistance again or experience another slump. </p>
<p>On the other hand, the recent bank failure, as <a href="https://twitter.com/nickgerli1/status/1650927931126849548?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">described </a>by Nick Gerli, CEO and Founder of Reventure Consulting, has highlighted the potential risks associated with traditional banking and finance. This has led investors to question the stability of the traditional financial system and seek alternative options.</p>
<p>On the contrary to this situation, Bitcoin has been on the rise since the beginning of 2023, and some analysts believe that the current economic climate could be a contributing factor. The recent contraction in the money supply in the US has led to a decrease in available capital, which could lead investors to seek alternative investment options. </p>
<p>With its decentralized nature and limited supply, Bitcoin has become an attractive option for investors looking to diversify their portfolios. Furthermore, Bitcoin&#8217;s recent price uptick can be attributed to several factors, including increased institutional adoption and growing mainstream acceptance. However, the current economic climate has undoubtedly played a role in Bitcoin&#8217;s recent surge in value.</p>
<p>As the economic outlook remains uncertain, many investors turn to Bitcoin as a safe haven asset. The cryptocurrency has been touted as a hedge against inflation and economic instability, and its recent price uptick could reflect these beliefs.</p>
<b>Bitcoin Highs Already Made For The Year?</b>
<p>The Puell Multiple, a metric used by cryptocurrency traders and analysts to gauge the value of Bitcoin, has recently made a perfect retest of its uptrend, <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoCon_/status/1651245042076381188?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">according </a>to CryptoCon, a trader and analyst of the crypto market. This retest suggests that the upward trend of Bitcoin remains intact and could potentially lead to much higher valuations in the future.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-528768" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuplDGDWAAAQgDV-860x564.png" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="564" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuplDGDWAAAQgDV-860x564.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuplDGDWAAAQgDV-460x302.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuplDGDWAAAQgDV-768x504.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuplDGDWAAAQgDV-750x492.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuplDGDWAAAQgDV-1140x748.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FuplDGDWAAAQgDV.png 1396w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>The Puell Multiple is calculated by dividing the daily issuance value of Bitcoin by the 365-day moving average of the daily issuance value. It is a useful metric for understanding the current state of Bitcoin&#8217;s mining ecosystem and can provide insights into the potential future direction of Bitcoin&#8217;s price.</p>
<p>With the Puell Multiple&#8217;s recent retests of its uptrend, CryptoCon suggests that the upward momentum of Bitcoin remains strong and could lead to even higher valuations in the future. This is welcome news for bulls eagerly anticipating a continued rise in Bitcoin&#8217;s price.</p>

<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-528767" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSDT_2023-04-26_10-44-56_735c5-860x407.png" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="407" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSDT_2023-04-26_10-44-56_735c5-860x407.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSDT_2023-04-26_10-44-56_735c5-460x218.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSDT_2023-04-26_10-44-56_735c5-768x363.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSDT_2023-04-26_10-44-56_735c5-1536x727.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSDT_2023-04-26_10-44-56_735c5-750x355.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSDT_2023-04-26_10-44-56_735c5-1140x540.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSDT_2023-04-26_10-44-56_735c5.png 1813w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/daniel-lloyd-blunk-fernandez-vrSKrUEZsDY-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin (BTC) Could Be Warming Up For Another Rally, Here’s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-btc-could-be-warming-up-for-another-rally-heres-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 17:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528746</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[While Bitcoin&#8217;s (BTC) price action since the beginning of the year has been impressive, surging by over 80% since January due to several factors, the asset has plummeted in recent weeks for other reason that include the continuous regulatory scrutiny in the industry.  However, according to recent reports, the asset may just be gearing for another rally. In the last 24 hours, another major United States bank was reported to be facing a financial run signaling insolvency issue or bankruptcy. Another Major Bank Collapse Could Impact Bitcoin Rally According to the latest update, First Republic Bank (FRC) is currently experiencing a financial run as the bank disclosed it lost nearly $100 billion in deposits amid last month’s banking crisis. The bank said it is currently unloading between $50 billion and $100 billion in debt instruments as part of its “strategic options” to resolve the massive capital outflow. However, the White House has expressed concern about a way to assist the bank out of insolvency, as reported by the Financial Times, which revealed that officials from the Biden Administration, the Federal Reserve, and the Treasury Department have consulted the bank’s top executives in the past few days. Related Reading: Notorious B.I.D. 2.0: Biggie-Sized Bidder Will Fuel Bitcoin Rally Again? Despite this, investors and traditional bankers seem to have begun panicking, searching for a safer haven or alternative for the store of value. Following the news, the First Republic shares plunged by more than 40% reaching an all-time low in Tuesday’s trading session.  Particularly, FRC shares hit an all-time low of $8.10 as the markets closed on Tuesday. Interestingly, while that happened, Bitcoin prices began to experience a bullish movement. This bullish movement can be attributed to the panic of traditional bankers seeing BTC as a bold alternative as major banks continue to collapse. BTC Could Be Warming Up For Another Rally The last time a similar banking crisis occurred in the US in March this year, Bitcoin reacted positively to the news and tapped $30,000 for the first time in nine months. And according to Bitcoin’s latest price action, the asset seems to be affirming expected price action based on past price action exposure to the banking crisis news.  In the last 24 hours, Bitcoin has recorded gains in its value, surging 7.5% with a market price of $29,817. Over $30 billion has been added to its market capitalization in the same period. Its trading volume has also surged indicating a buying pressure.  According to on-chain data provider Santiment, Bitcoin’s social dominance has increased compared to other altcoins in the market. Santiment noted this “happens during market euphoria or (in this case) fear.” The data provider further noted, “Prices can rebound quickly.” Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Reclaims $29,800, Driven By These Factors Santiment is not the only one that anticipated Bitcoin’s rebound from its previous bearish price action. Popular crypto analyst Michael Van de Poppe stated: Bitcoin isn’t looking bad on the higher timeframes. Healthy correction, and as long as Bitcoin sustains above $25,300 it’s likely we’ll continue this rally towards $42,000. &#160; According to the analyst, as long as Bitcoin remains above $25,300, which it currently is as the asset trades above $29,000, Bitcoin will enjoy another rally to trade above $40,000. Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/dormant-bitcoin-whales-waking-up-a-concern-for-btc-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin&#8217;s (BTC)</a> price action since the beginning of the year has been impressive, surging by over 80% since January due to several factors, the asset has plummeted in recent weeks for other reason that include the continuous regulatory scrutiny in the industry. </p>
<p>However, according to recent reports, the asset may just be <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/notorious-b-i-d-2-0-biggie-sized-bidder-will-fuel-bitcoin-rally-again/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">gearing for another rally</a>. In the last 24 hours, another major United States bank was reported to be facing a financial run signaling insolvency issue or bankruptcy.</p>
<h2>Another Major Bank Collapse Could Impact Bitcoin Rally</h2>
<p>According to the latest update, First Republic Bank (FRC) is currently experiencing a financial run as the bank <a href="https://news.sky.com/story/sense-of-crisis-regrips-first-republic-bank-as-it-admits-100bn-deposit-flight-12866172" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">disclosed</a> it lost nearly $100 billion in deposits amid last month’s banking crisis. The bank said it is currently unloading between $50 billion and $100 billion in debt instruments as part of its “strategic options” to resolve the massive capital outflow.</p>
<p>However, the White House has expressed concern about a way to assist the bank out of insolvency, as reported by the Financial Times, which revealed that officials from the Biden Administration, the Federal Reserve, and the Treasury Department have consulted the bank’s top executives in the past few days.</p>

<p>Despite this, investors and traditional bankers seem to have begun panicking, searching for a safer haven or alternative for the store of value. Following the news, the First Republic shares plunged by more than 40% reaching an all-time low in Tuesday’s trading session. </p>
<p>Particularly, FRC shares hit an all-time low of $8.10 as the markets closed on Tuesday. Interestingly, while that happened, Bitcoin prices began to experience a bullish movement. This bullish movement can be attributed to the panic of traditional bankers seeing BTC as a bold alternative as major banks continue to collapse.</p>
<h2>BTC Could Be Warming Up For Another Rally</h2>
<p>The last time a similar banking crisis occurred in the US in March this year, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/all/banking-crisis-redux-bitcoin-first-republic-bank-shares/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin reacted positively to the news</a> and tapped $30,000 for the first time in nine months. And according to Bitcoin’s latest price action, the asset seems to be affirming expected price action based on past price action exposure to the banking crisis news. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/HQ5sq5P0/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart on TradingView" width="2768" height="1372" />
<p>In the last 24 hours, Bitcoin has recorded gains in its value, surging 7.5% with a market price of $29,817. Over $30 billion has been added to its market capitalization in the same period. Its trading volume has also surged indicating a buying pressure. </p>
<p>According to on-chain data provider Santiment, Bitcoin’s social dominance has increased compared to other altcoins in the market. Santiment <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1650955088268242944" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">noted</a> this “happens during market euphoria or (in this case) fear.” The data provider further noted, “Prices can rebound quickly.”</p>

<p>Santiment is not the only one that anticipated Bitcoin’s rebound from its previous bearish price action. Popular crypto analyst Michael Van de Poppe <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1650839508231892994" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">stated:</a></p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin isn’t looking bad on the higher timeframes. Healthy correction, and as long as Bitcoin sustains above $25,300 it’s likely we’ll continue this rally towards $42,000.</p></blockquote>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-528747" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-BTC-analysis-460x230.png" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) analysis." width="460" height="230" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-BTC-analysis-460x230.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-BTC-analysis-860x430.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-BTC-analysis-768x384.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-BTC-analysis-1536x767.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-BTC-analysis-2048x1023.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-BTC-analysis-360x180.png 360w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-BTC-analysis-750x375.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-BTC-analysis-1140x570.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" />
<p>According to the analyst, as long as Bitcoin remains above $25,300, which it currently is as the asset <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-signals-increase-29k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">trades above $29,000</a>, Bitcoin will enjoy another rally to trade above $40,000.</p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/HUOBI-460x230.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>EOS Foundation Launches Upgrade As Crypto Market Rallies</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/eos/eos-foundation-launches-upgrade-as-crypto-market-rallies/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mudiaga Iritare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[EOS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eos blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EOS Token]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Eos Upgrade]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528650</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In an exciting update, the EOS Foundation recently launched a major upgrade with innovative developments and solutions to its network ecosystem. The upgrade coincided with a market recovery today that saw the price rally of Bitcoin and some altcoins alongside it. The theme of the upgrade had a positive ring to it, intending to deliver speed, scalability, and reliability to the EOS blockchain network. EOS Network Launches Antelope Leap V4.0.0 Upgrade The Antelope Leap v4.0.0 upgrade is an open-source software that enables anyone to operate a node on the EOS blockchain network seamlessly. For clarity, a node is a computer system that runs a blockchain consensus model by validating incoming user transactions and storing the data in a distributed network ledger. Node operators use these computer systems to validate network transactions while securing a blockchain network. They earn token rewards for their contributions to the validity and integrity of blockchain ecosystems. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Signals Fresh Increase But $29K Is The Key To More Gains That said, the EOS Antelope Leap v4.0.0 upgrade was launched to optimize node performance, making it easy for anyone to carry out node operations without hassle. Solutions the upgrade brings forward to node operators include multi-threading features to boost node performance, reduced node latency, faster block propagation, and more visibility and control. The Leap v4.0.0 upgrade is an important milestone and achievement for the EOS blockchain ecosystem. Node operators have been advised to upgrade their nodes to the newest Leap version for ease of use and compatibility with other network infrastructure. Will Price Respond The price of the EOS token has responded sluggishly despite the Leap v4.0.0 upgrade launch and recent market rally, which saw Bitcoin reclaim the $29,000 price region. At the time of writing, the third-generation blockchain token is seen trading at $1.07, according to Coinmarketcap data. This is only a slight increase from its 24-hour low of $1.02. While BTC gained over $1600 from its 24-hour price change, EOS is still yet to notably move compared to some altcoins, largely profiting from the BTC rally. Related Reading: Bitcoin Market At Decision Point: aSOPR Retests Crucial Level Bitcoin is on the move to test its $29,200 resistance. If it fails to break, a retracement could occur, negatively impacting the price of EOS and other cryptocurrencies traded in the markets. However, on the EOS monthly chart timeframe, the token is seen to be trading at base levels and halfway close to its all-time lows, which may indicate close to bottom levels for a reversal. There is room for upside movements of the token to profit from as current market sentiments are becoming positive due to BTC&#8217;s recent price move. &#160; EOS token shows signs of price recovery after major upgrade &#124; Source: EOSUSD on TradingView.com Featured image from Istock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In an exciting update, the EOS Foundation recently launched a major upgrade with innovative developments and solutions to its network ecosystem.
</p>
<p>The upgrade coincided with a market recovery today that saw the price rally of <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-signals-increase-29k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> and some altcoins alongside it. The theme of the upgrade had a positive ring to it, intending to deliver speed, scalability, and reliability to the EOS blockchain network.</p>
<h2>EOS Network Launches Antelope Leap V4.0.0 Upgrade</h2>
<p>The Antelope Leap v4.0.0 <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://eosnetwork.com/blog/antelope-leap-4-released/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">upgrade</a> is an open-source software that enables anyone to operate a node on the EOS blockchain network seamlessly.</p>
<p>For clarity, a node is a computer system that runs a blockchain consensus model by validating incoming user transactions and storing the data in a distributed network ledger.</p>
<p>Node operators use these computer systems to validate network transactions while securing a blockchain network. They earn token rewards for their contributions to the validity and integrity of blockchain ecosystems.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-signals-increase-29k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin Price Signals Fresh Increase But $29K Is The Key To More Gains</a></p>
<p>That said, the EOS Antelope Leap v4.0.0 upgrade was launched to optimize node performance, making it easy for anyone to carry out node operations without hassle.</p>
<p>Solutions the upgrade brings forward to node operators include multi-threading features to boost node performance, reduced node latency, faster block propagation, and more visibility and control.
</p>
<p>The Leap v4.0.0 upgrade is an important milestone and achievement for the EOS blockchain ecosystem.
</p>
<p>Node operators have been advised to upgrade their <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://github.com/AntelopeIO/leap" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">nodes</a> to the newest Leap version for ease of use and compatibility with other network infrastructure.</p>
<h2>Will Price Respond</h2>
<p>The price of the EOS token has responded sluggishly despite the Leap v4.0.0 upgrade launch and recent market rally, which saw Bitcoin reclaim the $29,000 price region.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, the third-generation blockchain token is seen trading at $1.07, according to Coinmarketcap data. This is only a slight increase from its 24-hour low of $1.02.</p>
<p>While BTC gained over $1600 from its 24-hour price change, EOS is still yet to notably move compared to some <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/link/chainlink-trends-in-the-green-zone-will-a-rally-follow/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">altcoins</a>, largely profiting from the BTC rally.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-decision-point-asopr-retests-crucial-level/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin Market At Decision Point: aSOPR Retests Crucial Level</a></p>
<p>Bitcoin is on the move to test its $29,200 resistance. If it fails to break, a retracement could occur, negatively impacting the price of EOS and other cryptocurrencies traded in the markets.</p>
<p>However, on the EOS monthly chart timeframe, the token is seen to be trading at base levels and halfway close to its all-time lows, which may indicate close to bottom levels for a reversal.</p>
<p>There is room for upside movements of the token to profit from as current market sentiments are becoming positive due to BTC&#8217;s recent <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-signals-increase-29k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">price</a> move.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/TcB1xoBE/" alt="EOS" width="1280" height="595" /></p>



]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/iStock-1357255026-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Bearish Signal: NVT Golden Cross Enters Overbought Zone</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-bearish-nvt-golden-cross-overbought/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 15:10:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bearish Signal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin NVT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin NVT Golden Cross]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Overbought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528649</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Bitcoin NVT Golden Cross has entered into the overbought region, something that could be bearish for the price. Bitcoin NVT Golden Cross Has Been Going Up Recently As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, the most recent touch of this zone led to a drop in the price of the cryptocurrency. The &#8220;Network Value to Transactions&#8221; (NVT) is an indicator that measures the ratio between the market cap of Bitcoin and its transaction volume (both in USD). What this metric tells is whether the asset is overpriced or underpriced right now, based on how the value of the network (the market cap) compares with its ability to transact coins (the transaction volume). High values of the indicator suggest the cryptocurrency&#8217;s cap is inflated compared to its volume, and hence, the coin&#8217;s price may be overvalued currently. Similarly, low values can imply the asset may be undervalued at the moment. Now, a metric derived from the NVT is the &#8220;NVT Golden Cross,&#8221; which compares the 30-day moving average (MA) of the NVT with its 10-day MA. By taking the ratio of the long-term and short-term trends like this, the indicator can help point out the tops and bottoms in the NVT. Here is a chart that displays how the value of the Bitcoin NVT Golden Cross has changed over the past year: The value of the metric seems to have been climbing in recent days &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As shown in the above graph, the quant has marked the historical regions where the Bitcoin NVT Golden Cross has signaled underbought and overbought conditions for the asset. It looks like the values of the metric above 2.2 have been a sign that the cryptocurrency is undersold, while those below the -1.6 level have implied an oversold condition. Related Reading: Bitcoin Market At Decision Point: aSOPR Retests Crucial Level From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that the indicator touched the underpriced region last month, and the price reacted by observing some bullish momentum. Since then, the metric has seen an overall uptrend. A week or so ago, when Bitcoin was floating around the $30,000 level, the NVT Golden Cross entered inside the overpriced region. Following this formation, the price faced some severe drawdown as it plunged to the low $27,000 level. The metric cooled down for a while following this selloff, but in the past couple of days, it has once again risen to touch the red zone. This would mean that the asset may be becoming overbought again. Over the past day, however, Bitcoin has actually only observed some strong upwards momentum, as the coin&#8217;s value has now recovered to levels above $29,000 again. Related Reading: Polygon Exchange Supply Spikes, More Downtrend Incoming? In the past, tops haven&#8217;t always been immediately formed whenever the NVT Golden Cross has surged to this area, so this wouldn&#8217;t exactly be unprecedented. However, considering that the surge may have only made the coin more overpriced, a local top may be hit soon for the asset, if this metric&#8217;s pattern is anything to go by. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,400, up 1% in the last week. Looks like BTC has sharply surged over the last 24 hours &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from mana5280 on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows the Bitcoin NVT Golden Cross has entered into the overbought region, something that could be bearish for the price.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin NVT Golden Cross Has Been Going Up Recently</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/6448122710b8f142c0b09940-NVT-Golden-Cross-entered-BTC-selling-zone-again" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, the most recent touch of this zone led to a drop in the price of the cryptocurrency. The &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-overvalued-according-nvt-ratio/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Network Value to Transactions</a>&#8221; (NVT) is an indicator that measures the ratio between the market cap of Bitcoin and its transaction volume (both in USD).</p>
<p>What this metric tells is whether the asset is overpriced or underpriced right now, based on how the value of the network (the market cap) compares with its ability to transact coins (the transaction volume).</p>
<p>High values of the indicator suggest the cryptocurrency&#8217;s cap is inflated compared to its volume, and hence, the coin&#8217;s price may be overvalued currently. Similarly, low values can imply the asset may be undervalued at the moment.</p>
<p>Now, a metric derived from the NVT is the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-nvt-golden-cross-overbought-volatility/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NVT Golden Cross</a>,&#8221; which compares the 30-day moving average (MA) of the NVT with its 10-day MA. By taking the ratio of the long-term and short-term trends like this, the indicator can help point out the tops and bottoms in the NVT.</p>
<p>Here is a chart that displays how the value of the Bitcoin NVT Golden Cross has changed over the past year:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/322923/quicktake/Lvs93B_4ade16ab9a5ca400aa560adf3c6692e22209f53fe4253aa66145fc2399c8b36f.png" alt="Bitcoin NVT Golden Cross" width="821" height="503" /></p>

<p>As shown in the above graph, the quant has marked the historical regions where the Bitcoin NVT Golden Cross has signaled underbought and overbought conditions for the asset.</p>
<p>It looks like the values of the metric above 2.2 have been a sign that the cryptocurrency is undersold, while those below the -1.6 level have implied an oversold condition.</p>

<p>From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that the indicator touched the underpriced region last month, and the price reacted by observing some bullish momentum. Since then, the metric has seen an overall uptrend.</p>
<p>A week or so ago, when Bitcoin was floating around the $30,000 level, the NVT Golden Cross entered inside the overpriced region. Following this formation, the price faced some severe drawdown as it plunged to the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-market-update-27000-local-bottom/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">low $27,000 level</a>.</p>
<p>The metric cooled down for a while following this selloff, but in the past couple of days, it has once again risen to touch the red zone. This would mean that the asset may be becoming overbought again.</p>
<p>Over the past day, however, Bitcoin has actually only observed some strong upwards momentum, as the coin&#8217;s value has now recovered to levels above $29,000 again.</p>

<p>In the past, tops haven&#8217;t always been immediately formed whenever the NVT Golden Cross has surged to this area, so this wouldn&#8217;t exactly be unprecedented. However, considering that the surge may have only made the coin more overpriced, a local top may be hit soon for the asset, if this metric&#8217;s pattern is anything to go by.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,400, up 1% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/pLonCpHL/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1533" height="911" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/mana5280-rGPDLlMNFF4-unsplash-1-460x341.jpg" width="460" height="341" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano ADA Trades Below The $0.41 Mark, Will It Break The Barriers?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/ada/cardano-ada-trades-below-the-0-41-mark-will-it-break-the-barriers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli Dambel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 14:40:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528702</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) coin has captured the interest of investors and holders with its recent price drop below the $0.40 mark on April 25. This notable price dip left everyone wondering if Cardano (ADA) will break this barrier, which has proven significant in recent trading sessions. However, today April 26, the general market is recovering as the global market cap gained over a 4.5% increase in 24 hours. The marker-wide rally has pushed ADA back to the $0.40 mark with a massive gain of 6.93% in 24 hours. Related Reading: Solana (SOL) Plunges Over 13% – Will It Bounce Back? The ADA price has been trending downward for the past 7 days, and the coin is finally gaining momentum. Only time will tell if Cardano ADA can surpass the $0.41 resistance level and trade above it in the coming days.  ADA Price Trend The recent price fluctuation in the crypto market harmed Cardano (ADA)’s price, causing a significant loss in its market capitalization. The Cardano market cap is currently at $13.9 billion with a $267 million 24-hour trading volume. According to CoinMarketCap data, Cardano (ADA) is now the seventh biggest cryptocurrency. Cardano’s price drop yesterday, April 25, may have been caused by several variables, such as market sentiment generally and shifts in investor perceptions. Also, the fluctuations in trading volume, regulatory announcements, or market news that impacted the cryptocurrency market may have played a huge role too. The chart below shows the potential support and resistance levels for Cardano (ADA) in 2023. While buyers are trying to build a bullish momentum, ADA is still found at the $0.40 zone and might break the support zone of $0.38 if the sellers increase the selling pressure. Related Reading: Solana (SOL) Rebounding After A Major Drop, Will It Recover Previous Losses? The $0.38 level of support has maintained steady during the retest earlier this week and can act as a driving force for a higher valuation. Cardano&#8217;s price may surpass its resistance level of $0.42 if the bulls completely control the market. On the other hand, if bears take control of the trend, ADA&#8217;s price could fall below $0.30 and might hit $0.2777 Cardano (ADA) Price Prediction The Simple Moving Average (SMA) indicates a potential trend reversal as the 50-day SMA changes directions. The 50-day SMA is trying to cross below the 200, forming a death cross. This action may generate a bearish signal and indicate a potential selling opportunity. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) is above the neutral level and is heading toward the overbought zone, which might ignite a potential price correction.  The MACD line is above the signal line, indicating a potential buy opportunity. The histogram is slightly above the zero line and is also increasing in size; this means bullish momentum. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cardano (ADA) coin has captured the interest of investors and holders with its recent price drop below the $0.40 mark on April 25. This notable price dip left everyone wondering if Cardano (ADA) will break this barrier, which has proven significant in recent trading sessions.</p>
<p>However, today April 26, the general market is recovering as the global market cap gained over a 4.5% increase in 24 hours. The marker-wide rally has pushed ADA back to the $0.40 mark with a massive gain of 6.93% in 24 hours.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/solana/solana-sol-plunges-over-13-will-it-bounce-back/">Solana (SOL) Plunges Over 13% – Will It Bounce Back?</a></p>
<p>The ADA price has been trending downward for the past 7 days, and the coin is finally gaining momentum. Only time will tell if Cardano ADA can surpass the $0.41 resistance level and trade above it in the coming days. </p>
<h2>ADA Price Trend</h2>
<p>The recent price fluctuation in the crypto market harmed Cardano (ADA)’s price, causing a significant loss in its market capitalization.</p>
<p>The Cardano market cap is currently at $13.9 billion with a $267 million 24-hour trading volume. According to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/cardano/historical-data/" rel="nofollow">CoinMarketCap</a> data, Cardano (ADA) is now the seventh biggest cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>Cardano’s price drop yesterday, April 25, may have been caused by several variables, such as market sentiment generally and shifts in investor perceptions. </p>
<p>Also, the fluctuations in trading volume, <a href="https://www.europarl.europa.eu/news/en/press-room/20230414IPR80133/crypto-assets-green-light-to-new-rules-for-tracing-transfers-in-the-eu" rel="nofollow">regulatory announcements</a>, or <a href="https://www.forbes.com/advisor/au/investing/cryptocurrency/crypto-news-australia/" rel="nofollow">market news</a> that impacted the cryptocurrency market may have played a huge role too. The chart below shows the potential support and resistance levels for Cardano (ADA) in 2023.</p>
<p>While buyers are trying to build a bullish momentum, ADA is still found at the $0.40 zone and might break the support zone of $0.38 if the sellers increase the selling pressure.</p>

<p>The $0.38 level of support has maintained steady during the retest earlier this week and can act as a driving force for a higher valuation. Cardano&#8217;s price may surpass its resistance level of $0.42 if the bulls completely control the market.</p>
<p>On the other hand, if bears take control of the trend, ADA&#8217;s price could fall below $0.30 and might hit $0.2777</p>
<h2>Cardano (ADA) Price Prediction</h2>
<p>The Simple Moving Average (SMA) indicates a potential trend reversal as the 50-day SMA changes directions. The 50-day SMA is trying to cross below the 200, forming a death cross. This action may generate a bearish signal and indicate a potential selling opportunity.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-528715 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSDT_2023-04-26_17-24-06-860x501.png" alt="Cardano ADA Trades Below The $0.41 Mark, Will It Break The Barriers?" width="860" height="501" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSDT_2023-04-26_17-24-06-860x501.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSDT_2023-04-26_17-24-06-460x268.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSDT_2023-04-26_17-24-06-768x447.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSDT_2023-04-26_17-24-06-750x437.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSDT_2023-04-26_17-24-06-1140x664.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSDT_2023-04-26_17-24-06.png 1437w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>The Relative Strength Index (RSI) is above the neutral level and is heading toward the overbought zone, which might ignite a potential price correction. </p>
<p>The MACD line is above the signal line, indicating a potential buy opportunity. The histogram is slightly above the zero line and is also increasing in size; this means bullish momentum.</p>
<p>Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/cardano-g57d2ba5c1_1280-460x230.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Trades Near Crucial Support Of $0.46, Will This Level Hold?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-trades-near-crucial-support-of-0-46-will-this-level-hold/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 14:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528657</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[During the past week, the price of XRP has suffered significant losses due to a powerful selling wave. While the one-day chart reflects a 3% increase, the weekly chart shows a decline of over 12%. Buyers have faced resistance in the $0.45-$0.46 range and the technical outlook for XRP indicates a selling trend. The demand for this altcoin has also dropped, leading to a decrease in accumulation. Unless buyers return to the market and stabilize the price, XRP is likely to continue losing value. Meanwhile, Bitcoin&#8217;s price has remained uncertain over the past week, and its recent climb above $28,000 may inspire other altcoins to follow suit. Related Reading: 37 Billion Dogecoin Holdings In Jeopardy: Price Level Investors Should Watch For XRP to see upward momentum, Bitcoin must maintain a price above $27,000. Furthermore, XRP must surpass the immediate resistance level to preserve its current support level. The decline in XRP&#8217;s market capitalization suggests that sellers are currently in control of the market. XRP Price Analysis: One-Day Chart At the time of writing, the altcoin&#8217;s trading price is $0.47, and it currently stands above its critical support level of $0.46. Despite attempting to recover significantly over the past few weeks, XRP experienced considerable selling pressure in the past week. The coin faces overhead resistance at $0.48, and breaching that level could drive the price up to $0.50. Conversely, if XRP fails to remain above $0.46, the coin may decline to around $0.42 and possibly $0.40. The amount of XRP traded in the last session was negative, indicating a decrease in demand. Technical Analysis Despite the daily chart indicating a recovery, buyers seemed hesitant to make a move. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) was below 50, implying that sellers currently outnumber buyers. Although there was an uptick in the RSI, buying strength remained fragile unless XRP surpasses the immediate resistance level. Furthermore, the altcoin was below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, indicating that sellers were driving the price momentum in the market. Aligned with other technical indicators, the altcoin began to exhibit sell signals on the one-day chart. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) displays price momentum and trend reversals. Red histograms formed under the half-line, indicating a sell signal for the altcoin and a bearish price. The Bollinger Bands measure price volatility and potential price fluctuations of the asset. The bands diverged in anticipation of incoming price volatility, with the upper band serving as a vital resistance level for the altcoin. Related Reading: MATIC Price Prediction: Polygon Recovery Faces Many Hurdles A move above the immediate price ceiling would aid XRP&#8217;s recovery and reduce the likelihood of heavy price fluctuation. Broader market strength will also be important for XRP to start its recovery. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>During the past week, the price of XRP has suffered significant losses due to a powerful selling wave. While the one-day chart reflects a 3% increase, the weekly chart shows a decline of over 12%. Buyers have faced resistance in the $0.45-$0.46 range and the technical outlook for XRP indicates a selling trend.</p>
<p>The demand for this altcoin has also dropped, leading to a decrease in accumulation. Unless buyers return to the market and stabilize the price, XRP is likely to continue losing value. Meanwhile, Bitcoin&#8217;s price has remained uncertain over the past week, and its recent climb above $28,000 may inspire other altcoins to follow suit.</p>

<p>For XRP to see upward momentum, Bitcoin must maintain a price above $27,000. Furthermore, XRP must surpass the immediate resistance level to preserve its current support level. The decline in XRP&#8217;s market capitalization suggests that sellers are currently in control of the market.</p>
<h2>XRP Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-528679 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-26_16-40-20.png" alt="XRP" width="1816" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-26_16-40-20.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-26_16-40-20-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-26_16-40-20-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-26_16-40-20-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-26_16-40-20-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-26_16-40-20-750x343.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-26_16-40-20-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>At the time of writing, the altcoin&#8217;s trading price is $0.47, and it currently stands above its critical support level of $0.46. Despite attempting to recover significantly over the past few weeks, XRP experienced considerable selling pressure in the past week.</p>
<p>The coin faces overhead resistance at $0.48, and breaching that level could drive the price up to $0.50. Conversely, if XRP fails to remain above $0.46, the coin may decline to around $0.42 and possibly $0.40. The amount of XRP traded in the last session was negative, indicating a decrease in demand.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-528687 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-26_16-52-58.png" alt="XRP" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-26_16-52-58.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-26_16-52-58-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-26_16-52-58-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-26_16-52-58-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-26_16-52-58-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-26_16-52-58-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-26_16-52-58-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>Despite the daily chart indicating a recovery, buyers seemed hesitant to make a move. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) was below 50, implying that sellers currently outnumber buyers.</p>
<p>Although there was an uptick in the RSI, buying strength remained fragile unless XRP surpasses the immediate resistance level. Furthermore, the altcoin was below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, indicating that sellers were driving the price momentum in the market.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-528692 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-26_16-53-37.png" alt="XRP" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-26_16-53-37.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-26_16-53-37-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-26_16-53-37-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-26_16-53-37-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-26_16-53-37-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-26_16-53-37-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRPUSD_2023-04-26_16-53-37-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px" />
<p>Aligned with other technical indicators, the altcoin began to exhibit sell signals on the one-day chart. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) displays price momentum and trend reversals. Red histograms formed under the half-line, indicating a sell signal for the altcoin and a bearish price.</p>
<p>The Bollinger Bands measure price volatility and potential price fluctuations of the asset. The bands diverged in anticipation of incoming price volatility, with the upper band serving as a vital resistance level for the altcoin.</p>

<p>A move above the immediate price ceiling would aid XRP&#8217;s recovery and reduce the likelihood of heavy price fluctuation. Broader market strength will also be important for XRP to start its recovery.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/kanchanara-0kRsP5iRZI4-unsplash-5-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Reclaims $29,800, Driven By These Factors</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-price-reclaims-29800-driven-by-these-factors/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 12:50:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528689</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin price regained the $29,000 mark today for the first time since last Thursday. The decisive impulse was provided yesterday by the news that with First Republic Bank the next big bank in the US is about to be seized by the US Federal Reserve and FDIC. As was the case after the collapse of Silicon Valley Bank, the news triggered a rally for Bitcoin that initially catapulted the price above the crucial $27,800 resistance level before a brief consolidation and then continuation of the price surge took place. With the reaction, Bitcoin is strengthening its digital gold narrative. As analyst James V. Straten predicts, the correlation between Bitcoin and gold will continue to increase as interest rates remain high and weak banks are purged. Even on a 30-day rolling average, the correlation stands at 57%, its highest level in almost 2 years. Bitcoin 30-day rolling correlation with gold has surged since March and now stands at 57% &#8211; its highest level in almost 2 years.#BTC #Gold #correlation pic.twitter.com/l7N5eYAgEl &#8212; Kaiko (@KaikoData) April 26, 2023 More Reasons For The Bitcoin Rally Another reason was presented by analyst James Choi, who believes that the market is front-running the US Federal Reserve (Fed). According to Choi, the second wave of bank failures, led by First Republic Bank, will cause the Fed to pump more liquidity into the financial system. The &#8220;market is a liquidity junkie and already pricing this in.&#8221; As Bitcoinist reported today, the M2 money supply has fallen to a historic 90-year low. Every time money has been slashed to this extent in the history of the United States, there has been a recession and banking crisis. Related Reading: Banking Crisis Redux: Bitcoin Priced In First Republic Bank Shares Rockets Higher Popular analyst Ted (@tedtalksmacro) agrees. According to him, liquidity has been the indicator that has led the Bitcoin price in recent weeks, while most data has lagged. 1/ While most data is lagging, what tends to lead price is monetary + fiscal liquidity&#8230; Let&#39;s quickly investigate whether liquidity has peaked or if new highs are to come👇 pic.twitter.com/PXgFv47xU6 &#8212; tedtalksmacro (@tedtalksmacro) April 25, 2023 According to him, the BTC price rise since mid-March is due to increased global liquidity, specifically: the US debt ceiling, with which the Treasury is drawing on its cash reserves; the banking crisis, which led to the expansion of the Fed&#8217;s balance sheet; and the stimulation of the Chinese economy through loose monetary policy after the end of Zero-Covid. Related Reading: Dormant Bitcoin Whales Waking Up, A Concern For BTC Price? From a technical perspective, liquidation of shorts in the futures market and funding rates once again played a role in the price move. Bitcoin perps had started to go negative while open interest was rising slightly. As a result, there was a short squeeze, as Straten notes. #Bitcoin perps have started to go negative, while open interest increases slightly, time for a short squeeze. pic.twitter.com/6O00Kt3BB2 &#8212; James V. Straten (@jimmyvs24) April 26, 2023 Renowned trader @52skew, meanwhile, noted, &#8220;$BTC Binance Market CVDs &#38; Delta: Most of this bounce was unwinding in shorts, however large binance spot buyers came in before price could roll over leading to another squeeze.&#8221; Even after the move above $29,000, shorts which were liquidated are piling up. $BTC Binance Open InterestThose revenge shorts are starting to get squeezed here Funding even more negative than earlier lol https://t.co/5Ool5mWmNP pic.twitter.com/KPpFecZXae &#8212; Skew Δ (@52kskew) April 26, 2023 At press time, the Bitcoin price traded at $28,865, eyeing the next resistance level at $30,000. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin price regained the $29,000 mark today for the first time since last Thursday. The decisive impulse was provided yesterday by the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/all/banking-crisis-redux-bitcoin-first-republic-bank-shares/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">news</a> that with First Republic Bank the next big bank in the US is about to be seized by the US Federal Reserve and FDIC.</p>
<p>As was the case after the collapse of Silicon Valley Bank, the news triggered a rally for Bitcoin that initially catapulted the price above the crucial $27,800 resistance level before a brief consolidation and then continuation of the price surge took place.</p>
<p>With the reaction, Bitcoin is strengthening its digital gold narrative. As analyst James V. Straten predicts, the correlation between Bitcoin and gold will continue to increase as interest rates remain high and weak banks are purged. Even on a 30-day rolling average, the correlation stands at 57%, its highest level in almost 2 years.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Bitcoin 30-day rolling correlation with gold has surged since March and now stands at 57% &#8211; its highest level in almost 2 years.<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BTC?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#BTC</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Gold?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Gold</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/correlation?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#correlation</a> <a href="https://t.co/l7N5eYAgEl" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/l7N5eYAgEl</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Kaiko (@KaikoData) <a href="https://twitter.com/KaikoData/status/1651173606796263424?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">April 26, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<h2>More Reasons For The Bitcoin Rally</h2>
<p>Another reason was <a href="https://twitter.com/JC_Investment/status/1651117627123851269" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">presented</a> by analyst James Choi, who believes that the market is front-running the US Federal Reserve (Fed). According to Choi, the second wave of bank failures, led by First Republic Bank, will cause the Fed to pump more liquidity into the financial system. The &#8220;market is a liquidity junkie and already pricing this in.&#8221;</p>
<p>As Bitcoinist <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-rally-m2-money-supply-90-year-low/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reported</a> today, the M2 money supply has fallen to a historic 90-year low. Every time money has been slashed to this extent in the history of the United States, there has been a recession and banking crisis.</p>

<p>Popular analyst Ted (@tedtalksmacro) agrees. According to him, liquidity has been the indicator that has led the Bitcoin price in recent weeks, while most data has lagged.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">1/ While most data is lagging, what tends to lead price is monetary + fiscal liquidity&#8230;</p>
<p>Let&#39;s quickly investigate whether liquidity has peaked or if new highs are to come<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f447.png" alt="👇" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/PXgFv47xU6" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/PXgFv47xU6</a></p>
<p>&mdash; tedtalksmacro (@tedtalksmacro) <a href="https://twitter.com/tedtalksmacro/status/1650832984306749441?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">April 25, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>According to him, the BTC price rise since mid-March is due to increased global liquidity, specifically: the US debt ceiling, with which the Treasury is drawing on its cash reserves; the banking crisis, which led to the expansion of the Fed&#8217;s balance sheet; and the stimulation of the Chinese economy through loose monetary policy after the end of Zero-Covid.</p>

<p>From a technical perspective, liquidation of shorts in the futures market and funding rates once again played a role in the price move. Bitcoin perps had started to go negative while open interest was rising slightly. As a result, there was a short squeeze, as Straten notes.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Bitcoin</a> perps have started to go negative, while open interest increases slightly, time for a short squeeze. <a href="https://t.co/6O00Kt3BB2" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/6O00Kt3BB2</a></p>
<p>&mdash; James V. Straten (@jimmyvs24) <a href="https://twitter.com/jimmyvs24/status/1651148639593541632?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">April 26, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>Renowned trader @52skew, meanwhile, <a href="https://twitter.com/52kskew/status/1651087846235832320" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">noted</a>, &#8220;$BTC Binance Market CVDs &amp; Delta: Most of this bounce was unwinding in shorts, however large binance spot buyers came in before price could roll over leading to another squeeze.&#8221; Even after the move above $29,000, shorts which were liquidated are piling up.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$BTC</a> Binance Open InterestThose revenge shorts are starting to get squeezed here</p>
<p>Funding even more negative than earlier lol <a href="https://t.co/5Ool5mWmNP" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/5Ool5mWmNP</a> <a href="https://t.co/KPpFecZXae" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/KPpFecZXae</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Skew Δ (@52kskew) <a href="https://twitter.com/52kskew/status/1651199805992103936?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">April 26, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>At press time, the Bitcoin price traded at $28,865, eyeing the next resistance level at $30,000.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-528721 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-26_14-32-59.png" alt="Bitcoin price BTC USD" width="3625" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-26_14-32-59.png 3625w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-26_14-32-59-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-26_14-32-59-860x397.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-26_14-32-59-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-26_14-32-59-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-26_14-32-59-2048x945.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-26_14-32-59-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-26_14-32-59-1140x526.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3625px) 100vw, 3625px" />

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/iStock-637063476-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
