<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 02:54:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Recovers Above Critical Level, Why Bulls Could Be Ready To Charge</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-recovers-above-critical-level-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 19:22:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusdc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538352</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin CME Futures BTC1 front month continuous contract price action closes over the weekend, making Friday evening the closing bell for the week. This Friday&#8217;s close saw price recover above a crucial level that in the past led to a bullish impulse in crypto. Here is a closer look at why bulls could be ready to charge in the coming weeks. Using BTC CME Futures As A Crypto Crystal Ball Large institutional traders don&#8217;t just trade spot BTCUSD, nor do they trade on Binance, ByBit, or another crypto platform. When they want to speculate and trade using derivatives contracts, they look to the Chicago Mercantile Exchange, better known as CME Group. Unlike the 24/7, always-on crypto market, CME Group charts close down for the weekend and holidays much like stocks. Due to this behavior, the chart often features gaps that don&#8217;t appear on standard BTCUSD price charts. Discrepancies between BTC CME Futures charts and BTCUSD charts can lead to fakeouts and shakeouts. Related Reading: One Coin, Two Trades: Why Bitcoin Futures And Spot Signals Don’t Match Up Because Bitcoin CME Futures does stop on Friday for the weekend, it also can provide early clues as to how spot price charts might close on Sunday night. In this case, BTC Futures has reclaimed the Bollinger Band basis line, often referred to as the &#8220;mid-BB&#8221;. Is the third time the charm? &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com Bitcoin Price Recovers Above The Bollinger Band Basis Line The basis line on the Bollinger Bands is a 20-period simple moving average. The tool&#8217;s creator, John Bollinger, then adds an upper and lower band set at two standard deviations of the SMA. This causes the bands to expand and contract with market volatility. Like any moving average, it can act as dynamic support and resistance, holding up price action or preventing it from pushing along further. Following this Friday&#8217;s BTC Futures weekly close, Bitcoin has made it back above the mid-BB, possibly confirming it as support. Related Reading: Bitcoin “Throwback” Could Trigger Flawless Technical Bottom Formation In the upper portion of the chart above, Bitcoin goes on an impulsive uptrend after holding above the basis line in 2019 and 2020. The lower portion depicts a closer look at this latest weekly close. Unless there is a massive collapse before Sunday night, BTCUSD technicals should follow suit. And if history repeats, a bull run could follow. Is Bitcoin ready for a strong rally higher after reclaiming the key level as support? This chart was featured in issue #8 of CoinChartist (VIP) alongside a dozen other exclusive crypto charts. Click here to learn more. Tony is the author of the CoinChartist (VIP) newsletter. Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter. Or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin CME Futures BTC1 front month continuous contract price action closes over the weekend, making Friday evening the closing bell for the week. This Friday&#8217;s close saw price recover above a crucial level that in the past led to a bullish impulse in crypto. Here is a closer look at why bulls could be ready to charge in the coming weeks.</p>
<h2>Using BTC CME Futures As A Crypto Crystal Ball</h2>
<p>Large institutional traders don&#8217;t just trade spot BTCUSD, nor do they trade on Binance, ByBit, or another crypto platform. When they want to speculate and trade using derivatives contracts, they look to the Chicago Mercantile Exchange, better known as <a href="https://www.cmegroup.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CME Group</a>.</p>
<p>Unlike the 24/7, always-on crypto market, CME Group charts close down for the weekend and holidays much like stocks. Due to this behavior, the chart often features gaps that don&#8217;t appear on standard BTCUSD price charts. Discrepancies between BTC CME Futures charts and BTCUSD charts can lead to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-futures-and-spot-signals-dont-match-up/">fakeouts and shakeouts</a>.</p>

<p>Because Bitcoin CME Futures does stop on Friday for the weekend, it also can provide <em>early</em> <em>clues</em> as to how spot price charts might close on Sunday night. In this case, BTC Futures has reclaimed the Bollinger Band basis line, often referred to as the &#8220;mid-BB&#8221;.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-large wp-image-538353 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-17_09-27-32-860x470.png" alt="BTC1!_2023-06-17_09-27-32" width="860" height="470" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-17_09-27-32-860x470.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-17_09-27-32-460x252.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-17_09-27-32-768x420.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-17_09-27-32-1536x840.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-17_09-27-32-2048x1120.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-17_09-27-32-750x410.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC1_2023-06-17_09-27-32-1140x623.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<h2>Bitcoin Price Recovers Above The Bollinger Band Basis Line</h2>
<p>The basis line on the <a href="https://coinchartist.io/bollinger-bands/education/technical-indicators-oscillators/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Bollinger Bands</a> is a 20-period simple moving average. The tool&#8217;s creator, John Bollinger, then adds an upper and lower band set at two standard deviations of the SMA. This causes the bands to expand and contract with market volatility.</p>
<p>Like any moving average, it can act as dynamic support and resistance, holding up price action or preventing it from pushing along further. Following this Friday&#8217;s BTC Futures weekly close, Bitcoin has made it back above the mid-BB, possibly confirming it as support.</p>

<p>In the upper portion of the chart above, Bitcoin goes on an impulsive uptrend after holding above the basis line in 2019 and 2020. The lower portion depicts a closer look at this latest weekly close. Unless there is a massive collapse before Sunday night, BTCUSD technicals should follow suit. And if history repeats, a bull run could follow.</p>
<p>Is Bitcoin ready for a strong rally higher after reclaiming the key level as support? This chart was featured in <a href="https://coinchartist.substack.com/p/issue-8-btc-2023-2020-2019" rel="nofollow">issue #8 of CoinChartist (VIP)</a> alongside a dozen other exclusive crypto charts. Click <a href="https://coinchartist.substack.com/p/issue-8-btc-2023-2020-2019" rel="nofollow">here</a> to learn more.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-933665824-460x339.jpg" width="460" height="339" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polygon (MATIC) Witnesses High Volatility Amid Positive Developments</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/matic-analysis/polygon-matic-witnesses-high-volatility-amid-positive-developments/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olowoporoku Adeniyi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 13:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Matic Network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538338</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Polygon (MATIC), one of the prominent Web3 networks, has recently experienced a period of volatility in its price. Currently trading at $0.625112 USD, with a 24-hour trading volume of $547,815,952 USD, MATIC has shown a 9.63% increase in the last 24 hours. Polygon has rebounded from the bearish sentiments earlier in the week. This comes on the back of recent developments within the Polygon ecosystem towards increasing utility and partnerships with key financial institutions.  Polygon Launches &#8216;The Value Prop&#8217; Polygon has made an important announcement, launching &#8220;The Value Prop,&#8221; an open database of blockchain use cases. This comprehensive catalog contains over 300 applications and diverse use cases across multiple business sectors, blockchain networks, and geographical locations. The initiative aims to showcase positive applications for blockchain technology, presenting it as a versatile tool beyond asset trading. Related Reading: Percentage Of ETH Addresses In Profit Reaches 5-Month Low Amid the negative sentiment surrounding blockchain technology due to regulatory pressures on major market participants like Binance and Coinbase, Polygon&#8217;s move to highlight real-world applications is significant. It aligns with the belief among Web3 experts and industry players that blockchain should be viewed as a general-purpose technology addressing real-world challenges. Web3 Development And Positive Trends Polygon&#8217;s efforts to boost Web3 development and unlock new use cases align with the industry&#8217;s overall trajectory. Ripple (XRP) recently partnered with Banco de la República, Colombia&#8217;s central bank, to explore blockchain use cases. This indicates a growing recognition of the potential of blockchain technology beyond cryptocurrencies. Polygon&#8217;s co-founder, Sandeep Nailwal, also launched the Nailwal Fellowship, a grant program providing financial support and resources to early-stage Web3 developers. This initiative offers funding, mentorship, and access to top founders and investors, nurturing the growth of the Web3 ecosystem. Related Reading: Shiba Inu (SHIB) Positive Social Sentiment Sparks Bullish Speculation Despite the U.S. banking crisis contagion, Web3 development has shown resilience. According to Alchemy, a blockchain developer platform, Q1 2023 witnessed rapid growth in Web3 development. The number of developer teams working on the Alchemy platform reached a record high, with increased activity compared to the previous year. Future Prospect For Polygon MATIC, the native token of Polygon, is trading in the positive zone and is up 9% in the last 24 hours. At the time of writing, the price is $0.6228, according to TradingView chart. However, amid the price volatility, the launch of &#8220;The Value Prop&#8221; and the focus on Web3 development suggest potential positive catalysts for Polygon&#8217;s future performance. As the blockchain industry continues to evolve, market participants will closely monitor the progress of Web3 development, the expansion of real-world use cases, and the regulatory landscape. These factors will significantly impact the prospects of Polygon and its native token, MATIC. Featured image from iStock, charts from Tradingview and Coingecko]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Polygon (MATIC), one of the prominent Web3 networks, has recently experienced a period of volatility in its price. Currently trading at $0.625112 USD, with a 24-hour trading volume of $547,815,952 USD, MATIC has shown a 9.63% increase in the last 24 hours. Polygon has rebounded from the bearish sentiments earlier in the week. This comes on the back of recent developments within the Polygon ecosystem towards increasing utility and partnerships with key financial institutions. </p>
<h2><strong>Polygon Launches &#8216;The Value Prop&#8217;</strong></h2>
<p>Polygon has made an important announcement, launching &#8220;The Value Prop,&#8221; an open database of blockchain use cases. This comprehensive catalog contains over 300 applications and diverse use cases across multiple business sectors, blockchain networks, and geographical locations. The initiative aims to showcase positive applications for blockchain technology, presenting it as a versatile tool beyond asset trading.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-538345 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_169.png" alt="Matic Is up 5.9% in the past 7-days: source @coingecko" width="814" height="77" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_169.png 814w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_169-460x44.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_169-768x73.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_169-750x71.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 814px) 100vw, 814px"/>
<p><strong>Related Reading</strong>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/percentage-of-eth-addresses-in-profit-reaches-5-month-low/">Percentage Of ETH Addresses In Profit Reaches 5-Month Low</a></p>
<p>Amid the negative sentiment surrounding blockchain technology due to regulatory pressures on major market participants like Binance and Coinbase, Polygon&#8217;s move to highlight real-world applications is significant. It aligns with the belief among Web3 experts and industry players that blockchain should be viewed as a general-purpose technology addressing real-world challenges.</p>
<h2><strong>Web3 Development And Positive Trends</strong></h2>
<p>Polygon&#8217;s efforts to boost Web3 development and unlock new use cases align with the industry&#8217;s overall trajectory. Ripple (XRP) recently partnered with <a href="https://www.banrep.gov.co/es" rel="nofollow">Banco de la República</a>, Colombia&#8217;s central bank, to explore blockchain use cases. This indicates a growing recognition of the potential of blockchain technology beyond cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Polygon&#8217;s co-founder, Sandeep Nailwal, also launched the Nailwal Fellowship, a grant program providing financial support and resources to early-stage Web3 developers. This initiative offers funding, mentorship, and access to top founders and investors, nurturing the growth of the Web3 ecosystem.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading</strong>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-shib-positive-social-sentiment-sparks-bullish-speculation/?swcfpc=1">Shiba Inu (SHIB) Positive Social Sentiment Sparks Bullish Speculation</a></p>
<p>Despite the U.S. banking crisis contagion, Web3 development has shown resilience. According to Alchemy, a blockchain developer platform, Q1 2023 witnessed rapid growth in Web3 development. The number of developer teams working on the Alchemy platform reached a record high, with increased activity compared to the previous year.</p>
<strong>Future Prospect For Polygon</strong>
<p>MATIC, the native token of Polygon, is trading in the positive zone and is up 9% in the last 24 hours. At the time of writing, the price is $0.6228, according to TradingView chart. However, amid the price volatility, the launch of &#8220;The Value Prop&#8221; and the focus on Web3 development suggest potential positive catalysts for Polygon&#8217;s future performance.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-538344 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-17_13-18-43-860x445.png" alt="Matic has experienced a bullish rally in the past 24 hours: source @tradingview" width="860" height="445" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-17_13-18-43-860x445.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-17_13-18-43-460x238.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-17_13-18-43-768x397.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-17_13-18-43-1536x794.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-17_13-18-43-750x388.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-17_13-18-43-1140x589.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-17_13-18-43.png 1567w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>As the blockchain industry continues to evolve, market participants will closely monitor the progress of Web3 development, the expansion of real-world use cases, and the regulatory landscape. These factors will significantly impact the prospects of Polygon and its native token, MATIC.</p>
<p><em>Featured image from iStock, charts from Tradingview and Coingecko</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1291935777-460x263.jpg" width="460" height="263" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>ZachXBT Slapped With Defamation Lawsuit For MachiBigBrother Exposé</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/zachxbt-slapped-with-defamation-lawsuit-for-machibigbrother-expose/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 13:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto investigation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto lawsuit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MachiBigBrother]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ZachXBT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538337</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A throwback article just came back to haunt one of the crypto industry&#8217;s favorite crypto investigators. ZachXBT, a popular crypto on-chain sleuth recently got slapped with a defamatory lawsuit over an article he published last year.  The Controversial Article That Started It All Around a year ago, ZachXBT published an article accusing Jeffrey Huang aka MachiBigBrother, of embezzling crypto assets using various methods ranging from failed pump and dump tokens to NFT projects. The article quickly gained widespread attention at the time, but it has been largely forgotten up until this point.  Related Reading: Shiba Inu (SHIB) Positive Social Sentiment Sparks Bullish Speculation Jeffrey Huang, known online as Machi Big Brother, is a former Taiwanese-American musician and tech entrepreneur.  Huang has now filed a defamation lawsuit against ZachXBT, claiming the year-old article has damaged his reputation. Huang has insisted, at least according to a post that he published on Twitter, that ZachXBT&#8217;s charges are false and defamatory. As a result, he has decided to sue for defamation of character. A cursory reading of the article, on the other hand, reveals that it is an investigational piece that goes into considerable detail. In the article, ZachXBT provided on-chain data to back up his claims. The crypto sleuth initially accused Machi Big Brother of embezzling 22,000 ETH from Formosa Financial, a treasury management platform built for blockchain companies in 2018. Furthermore, ZachXBT then provided a list of other projects like Machi X and Wifey Finance. Total market cap still sitting above $1 trillion &#124; Source: Crypto Total Market Cap on TradingView.com How ZachXBT Is Fighting Back Against The Lawsuit ZachXBT is not taking this lawsuit lying down as he’s come out swinging against what he calls a baseless lawsuit with &#8220;an attempt to chill free speech.&#8221; ZachXBT has asked his followers and subscribers to support him against censorship and cancel culture, ensuring the truth survives.  He termed the whole situation as a &#8220;classic David &#38; Goliath story,” and many have spoken out on social media defending his right to express his opinions. Brown Rudnick, a law firm with its headquarters in Boston famous for defending Johnny Depp in his case against his ex-wife Amber Heard, has agreed to represent ZachXBT in the lawsuit. Related Reading: PEPE Jumps Nearly 10% In 24 Hours, Sparking Speculation Of A New Rally While lawsuits can be expensive to defend, ZachXBT says he will rely on donations from his followers to mount a proper defense. In this case, he says legal costs associated with the defense of this matter could easily exceed $1 million while providing a donation address. Donations have started to troop in. At the time of this writing, the address now contains more than $290,000.  The outcome of this case could have significant implications for crypto media and regulations around defamation and libel for public figures in the crypto industry.  Featured image from Legacy Design Strategies, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A throwback article just came back to haunt one of the crypto industry&#8217;s favorite crypto investigators. ZachXBT, a popular crypto on-chain sleuth recently got slapped with a defamatory lawsuit over an article he published last year. </p>
<h2>The Controversial Article That Started It All</h2>
<p>Around a year ago, ZachXBT published an <a href="https://medium.com/@investigationsbyzachxbt/22-000-eth-embezzled-and-over-ten-projects-failed-the-story-of-machi-big-brother-jeff-huang-a1ad073fcfa8" rel="nofollow">article </a>accusing Jeffrey Huang aka MachiBigBrother, of embezzling crypto assets using various methods ranging from failed pump and dump tokens to NFT projects. The article quickly gained widespread attention at the time, but it has been largely forgotten up until this point. </p>

<p>Jeffrey Huang, known online as Machi Big Brother, is a former Taiwanese-American musician and tech entrepreneur. </p>
<p>Huang has now filed a defamation lawsuit against ZachXBT, claiming the year-old article has damaged his reputation. Huang has insisted, at least according to a <a href="https://twitter.com/machibigbrother/status/1669780922449956864?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1669780922449956864%7Ctwgr%5E66e989d4ba25dc44d5ef67f4c0184b3d3311aaa4%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fcointelegraph.com%2Fnews%2Fzach-xbt-sued-libel-claimed-plaintiff-drained-funds-from-project" rel="nofollow">post </a>that he published on Twitter, that ZachXBT&#8217;s charges are false and defamatory. As a result, he has decided to sue for defamation of character.</p>
<p>A cursory reading of the article, on the other hand, reveals that it is an investigational piece that goes into considerable detail. In the article, ZachXBT provided on-chain data to back up his claims. The crypto sleuth initially accused Machi Big Brother of embezzling 22,000 ETH from Formosa Financial, a treasury management platform built for blockchain companies in 2018. Furthermore, ZachXBT then provided a list of other projects like Machi X and Wifey Finance.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Jjbwg7rR/" alt="Crypto total market cap chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1724"/></p>

<h2>How ZachXBT Is Fighting Back Against The Lawsuit</h2>
<p>ZachXBT is not taking this lawsuit lying down as he’s come out swinging against what he calls a baseless lawsuit with &#8220;an attempt to chill free speech.&#8221; ZachXBT has asked his followers and subscribers to support him against censorship and cancel culture, ensuring the truth survives. </p>
<p>He termed the whole situation as a &#8220;classic David &amp; Goliath story,” and many have spoken out on social media defending his right to express his opinions. Brown Rudnick, a law firm with its headquarters in Boston famous for defending Johnny Depp in his case against his ex-wife Amber Heard, has agreed to represent ZachXBT in the lawsuit.</p>

<p>While lawsuits can be expensive to defend, ZachXBT says he will rely on donations from his followers to mount a proper defense. In this case, he says legal costs associated with the defense of this matter could easily exceed $1 million while providing a donation address. Donations have started to troop in. At the time of this writing, the address now contains more than $290,000. </p>
<p>The outcome of this case could have significant implications for crypto media and regulations around defamation and libel for public figures in the crypto industry. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ZachXBT-crypto-lawsuit-460x299.jpeg" width="460" height="299" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Coin (BNB) Faces Sideways Movement, Bears Threaten Further Sell-Off</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/binance-coin/binance-coin-bnb-faces-sideways-movement-bears-threaten-further-sell-off/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olowoporoku Adeniyi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 12:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538333</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Binance Coin (BNB), the native token of the Binance exchange, has recently experienced a period of sideways movement. Despite reaching a weekly high of $307 on June 4th, BNB&#8217;s price has encountered resistance and is currently trading at $246.2. This article provides an analysis of the recent price action, discusses the potential reasons behind BNB&#8217;s performance, and explores the future prospects for the coin. The recent decline in BNB&#8217;s price can be attributed to several factors. Firstly, the overall market sentiment has been influenced by a broader correction in the cryptocurrency market. Many altcoins, including BNB, have witnessed a decrease in value as investors take profits and adjust their portfolios. Additionally, concerns over regulatory developments and market uncertainties have added to the selling pressure on BNB. Bearish Threat And Technical Indicators Despite attempts by bulls to regain control, bears pose a significant threat to BNB&#8217;s price stability. The crucial resistance level of $308 has become a battleground for market participants. If the bears manage to break down this level, it could trigger a further sell-off, potentially pushing the price lower.  Technical indicators paint a cautious picture for BNB. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicator has exhibited a bearish crossover, signaling a continuation of selling pressure in the near term. Furthermore, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) currently stands at 35.63 levels, suggesting that there could be a further downside if buying pressure does not increase. Related Reading: PEPE Jumps Nearly 10% In 24 Hours, Sparking Speculation Of A New Rally Moreover, the 50-Weekly Moving Average positioned below the 200-Weekly MA indicates a bearish trend for BNB. This configuration suggests that the price could continue downward in the coming days unless significant positive developments or market catalysts emerge. What’s Next For BNB? Market participants will closely monitor the price action around the critical resistance level of $308. A successful breach above this level could ignite renewed bullish momentum, potentially leading to a recovery in BNB&#8217;s price. Traders and investors will also pay attention to any regulatory developments and market trends that could influence BNB&#8217;s performance. Despite the current challenges, Binance Coin holds promise as a key player in the cryptocurrency ecosystem. As Binance continues to expand its services and offerings, including its decentralized exchange (DEX) and various partnerships, there is potential for increased adoption of BNB, which could positively impact its price in the long run. Related Reading: Percentage Of ETH Addresses In Profit Reaches 5-Month Low It is important to note that the cryptocurrency market is highly volatile, and prices can change rapidly. Investors are advised to conduct thorough research, stay informed about market developments, and exercise caution when making investment decisions. At press time, Binance Coin (BNB) was trading at $246.2 with a daily price increase of 2.93%. Featured image from iStock.com, charts from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance Coin (BNB), the native token of the Binance exchange, has recently experienced a period of sideways movement. Despite reaching a weekly high of $307 on June 4th, BNB&#8217;s price has encountered resistance and is currently trading at $246.2. This article provides an analysis of the recent price action, discusses the potential reasons behind BNB&#8217;s performance, and explores the future prospects for the coin.</p>
<p>The recent decline in BNB&#8217;s price can be attributed to several factors. Firstly, the overall market sentiment has been influenced by a broader correction in the cryptocurrency market. Many altcoins, including BNB, have witnessed a decrease in value as investors take profits and adjust their portfolios. Additionally, concerns over regulatory developments and market uncertainties have added to the selling pressure on BNB.</p>
<h2><strong>Bearish Threat And Technical Indicators</strong></h2>
<p>Despite attempts by bulls to regain control, bears pose a significant threat to BNB&#8217;s price stability. The crucial resistance level of $308 has become a battleground for market participants. If the bears manage to break down this level, it could trigger a further sell-off, potentially pushing the price lower. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-538334" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image1-3-460x215.png" alt="BNB weekly chart shows sideways movement: source @Tradingview" width="460" height="215" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image1-3-460x215.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image1-3-750x351.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image1-3.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/>
<p>Technical indicators paint a cautious picture for BNB. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicator has exhibited a bearish crossover, signaling a continuation of selling pressure in the near term. Furthermore, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) currently stands at 35.63 levels, suggesting that there could be a further downside if buying pressure does not increase.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading</strong>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/pepe-jumps-nearly-10-in-24-hours-sparking-speculation-of-a-new-rally/">PEPE Jumps Nearly 10% In 24 Hours, Sparking Speculation Of A New Rally</a></p>
<p>Moreover, the 50-Weekly Moving Average positioned below the 200-Weekly MA indicates a bearish trend for BNB. This configuration suggests that the price could continue downward in the coming days unless significant positive developments or market catalysts emerge.</p>
<h2><strong>What’s Next For BNB?</strong></h2>
<p>Market participants will closely monitor the price action around the critical resistance level of $308. A successful breach above this level could ignite renewed bullish momentum, potentially leading to a recovery in BNB&#8217;s price. Traders and investors will also pay attention to any regulatory developments and market trends that could influence BNB&#8217;s performance.</p>
<p>Despite the current challenges, Binance Coin holds promise as a key player in the cryptocurrency ecosystem. As Binance continues to expand its services and offerings, including its decentralized exchange (DEX) and various partnerships, there is potential for increased adoption of BNB, which could positively impact its price in the long run.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading: </strong><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/percentage-of-eth-addresses-in-profit-reaches-5-month-low/">Percentage Of ETH Addresses In Profit Reaches 5-Month Low</a></p>
<p>It is important to note that the cryptocurrency market is highly volatile, and prices can change rapidly. Investors are advised to conduct thorough research, stay informed about market developments, and exercise caution when making investment decisions. At press time, Binance Coin (BNB) was trading at $246.2 with a daily price increase of 2.93%.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-538335" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image2-2-460x253.png" alt="Binance coin still trading below the $250 resistance mark" width="460" height="253" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image2-2-460x253.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image2-2-860x474.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image2-2-768x423.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image2-2-750x413.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image2-2.png 1080w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/>
<p><em>Featured image from iStock.com, charts from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1385861326-1-460x248.jpg" width="460" height="248" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu (SHIB) Positive Social Sentiment Sparks Bullish Speculation</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-shib-positive-social-sentiment-sparks-bullish-speculation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 11:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shina Inu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538324</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB), a cryptocurrency that has gained immense popularity and attention in recent months, is making waves once again as its price exhibits signs of recovery.  This week, the SHIB price has displayed a promising uptick, maintaining a level above the $0.0000065 range. Moreover, on-chain data analysis reveals a notable surge in positive social sentiment within the vibrant Shiba Inu community.  Related Reading: Polygon (MATIC) Sees Surge In Whale Buying Despite US Regulatory Pressure With these encouraging developments, investors and enthusiasts eagerly ponder whether this could signal a forthcoming bullish reversal for SHIB. Is it time for the Shiba Inu token to regain its momentum and embark on a new upward trajectory? Growing Optimism Among Shiba Inu Investors After a volatile start to the month, investors in SHIB are beginning to feel more optimistic about the project&#8217;s prospects. This renewed optimism can be attributed, in part, to Santiment&#8217;s Weighted Sentiment, which assesses the overall mood of a blockchain community by comparing the number of positive comments to the negative ones. SHIB weighted sentiment. Source: Santiment Adding to the positive sentiment, the Shiba Inu community received intriguing updates from notable figures within the project. Something physical is coming. #shib #shibarmy pic.twitter.com/XuAe2AkpJw — Shytoshi Kusama™ (@ShytoshiKusama) June 14, 2023 Shytoshi Kusama, a prominent Shiba Inu developer, generated excitement with a mysterious tweet teasing an upcoming product launch. Soon after, Lucie Shib, another key contributor, affirmed the project&#8217;s vitality and commitment to development in a separate tweet. We are building. We are not going anywhere.$SHIB x #Shiboshis — 𝐋𝐔𝐂𝐈𝐄 (@LucieSHIB) June 15, 2023 Recent Price Movements And Social Sentiment As per the latest data from CoinMarketCap, the current price of SHIB stands at $0.00000669, showcasing a 2.65% uptick within the past 24 hours. The past seven days also showed some price improvement for SHIB, as the meme coin gained 7.29%. Source: CoinMarketCap Examining on-chain data, it becomes evident that these critical announcements have had a positive impact on the social sentiment within the SHIB community. The Weighted Sentiment metric for SHIB began to show an upward trend around June 9, and as of June 16, it sits at approximately -1.43. This indicates a notable 13% improvement in positive sentiment over the past week. SHIB market cap currently at $4.07 billion on the weekend chart: TradingView.com Related Reading: PEPE Jumps Nearly 10% In 24 Hours, Sparking Speculation Of A New Rally Possibility For A Bullish Reversal When the Weighted Sentiment metric starts to rise during a period of price correction, it often signals the potential for a bullish reversal. Therefore, if the recent team announcement materializes into a well-received product launch, there is a possibility that the SHIB price could enter a phase of recovery in the near future.  This development has captured the attention of investors and could pave the way for an upward trajectory for the meme coin. Featured image from The Daily Hodl]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB), a cryptocurrency that has gained immense popularity and attention in recent months, is making waves once again as its price exhibits signs of recovery. </p>
<p>This week, the SHIB price has displayed a promising uptick, maintaining a level above the $0.0000065 range. Moreover, on-chain data analysis reveals a notable surge in positive social sentiment within the vibrant Shiba Inu community. </p>

<p>With these encouraging developments, investors and enthusiasts eagerly ponder whether this could signal a forthcoming bullish reversal for SHIB. Is it time for the Shiba Inu token to regain its momentum and embark on a new upward trajectory?</p>
<h2><strong>Growing Optimism Among Shiba Inu Investors</strong></h2>
<p>After a volatile start to the month, investors in SHIB are beginning to feel more optimistic about the project&#8217;s prospects. This renewed optimism can be attributed, in part, to <a href="https://embed.santiment.net/chart?ps=shiba-inu&amp;pt=SHIB&amp;df=2023-06-09T23%3A00%3A00.000Z&amp;dt=2023-06-15T23%3A00%3A00.000Z&amp;emcg=1&amp;wm=price_usd%3Bsentiment_volume_consumed_total&amp;wax=0%3B1&amp;wc=%2326C953%3B%23FFCB47&amp;ws=%7B%22interval%22%3A%221d%22%7D%3B%7B%22interval%22%3A%221h%22%7D" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Santiment&#8217;s Weighted Sentiment</a>, which assesses the overall mood of a blockchain community by comparing the number of positive comments to the negative ones.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-538327 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-102-860x406.png" alt="" width="860" height="406" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-102-860x406.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-102-460x217.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-102-768x362.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-102-1536x724.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-102-750x354.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-102-1140x538.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-102.png 1917w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>Adding to the positive sentiment, the Shiba Inu community received intriguing updates from notable figures within the project.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Something physical is coming. <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/shib?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#shib</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/shibarmy?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#shibarmy</a> <a href="https://t.co/XuAe2AkpJw" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/XuAe2AkpJw</a></p>
<p>— Shytoshi Kusama<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@ShytoshiKusama) <a href="https://twitter.com/ShytoshiKusama/status/1669033030151995393?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 14, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Shytoshi Kusama, a prominent Shiba Inu developer, generated excitement with a <a href="https://twitter.com/ShytoshiKusama/status/1669033030151995393" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">mysterious tweet</a> teasing an upcoming product launch.</p>
<p>Soon after, Lucie Shib, another key contributor, affirmed the project&#8217;s vitality and commitment to development in a <a href="https://twitter.com/LucieSHIB/status/1669283851917570051" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">separate tweet</a>.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We are building.
We are not going anywhere.<a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24SHIB&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$SHIB</a> x <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Shiboshis?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Shiboshis</a></p>
<p>— 𝐋𝐔𝐂𝐈𝐄 (@LucieSHIB) <a href="https://twitter.com/LucieSHIB/status/1669283851917570051?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<h2><strong>Recent Price Movements And Social Sentiment</strong></h2>
<p>As per the latest data from CoinMarketCap, the current price of SHIB stands at $0.00000669, showcasing a<a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> 2.65% uptick within the past 24 hours.</a> The past seven days also showed some price improvement for SHIB, as the meme coin gained 7.29%.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-538325" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-101.png" alt="" width="1157" height="91" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-101.png 1157w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-101-460x36.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-101-860x68.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-101-768x60.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-101-1140x90.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-101-750x59.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1157px) 100vw, 1157px"/></p>

<p>Examining on-chain data, it becomes evident that these critical announcements have had a positive impact on the social sentiment within the SHIB community. </p>
<p>The Weighted Sentiment metric for SHIB began to show an upward trend around June 9, and as of June 16, it sits at approximately -1.43. This indicates a notable 13% improvement in positive sentiment over the past week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/VxjZq3nf/" width="2315" height="1109"/></p>


<strong>Possibility For A Bullish Reversal</strong>
<p>When the Weighted Sentiment metric starts to rise during a period of price correction, it often signals the potential for a bullish reversal. Therefore, if the recent team announcement materializes into a well-received product launch, there is a possibility that the SHIB price could enter a phase of recovery in the near future. </p>
<p>This development has captured the attention of investors and could pave the way for an upward trajectory for the meme coin.</p>
<p><em>Featured image from The Daily Hodl</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-103-460x228.png" width="460" height="228" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>PEPE Jumps Nearly 10% In 24 Hours, Sparking Speculation Of A New Rally</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/pepe-jumps-nearly-10-in-24-hours-sparking-speculation-of-a-new-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 09:23:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538312</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Pepe (PEPE) may seize the opportunity to rally in the face of an ongoing volatility and price swings in the crypto market. With Bitcoin (BTC) recently dipping below $25,000 before swiftly rebounding to $26,000, the market has been in a state of flux. Such fluctuations often create an environment ripe for alternative cryptocurrencies to make their mark, and PEPE could be poised to do just that. PEPE’s rally comes at a time when investors are seeking alternative options beyond the dominant cryptocurrencies. While Bitcoin continues to dominate the market, its price movements can have a cascading effect on other digital assets.  That being said, can PEPE capitalize on Bitcoin&#8217;s volatility and secure its own rally to attract investors seeking new opportunities in the crypto space? PEPE Price Recovery Potential In recent market developments, PEPE has witnessed a notable rally, as reflected in its current price of $0.0000009779 on CoinMarketCap. This surge represents an impressive 8.5% increase within a 24-hour period. However, it&#8217;s important to note that this upward momentum follows a preceding seven-day slump of 7.96%, underscoring the inherent volatility that characterizes the cryptocurrency market. PEPE showing bullish signs. Source: CoinMarketCap The price of PEPE has undergone substantial fluctuations since early May, resulting in a significant decline of over 50% in its overall value. This decline has caused a shift in the market structure, signaling a bearish trend as sellers capitalized on shorting opportunities when the support levels at $0.00000162 and $0.00000115 were breached. PEPE price in the green. Source: CoinMarketCap Despite the bearish downtrend, recent price activity has hinted at the potential for a new bull run. Notably, the crucial support level at $0.00000094 demonstrated resilience in halting the downward movement.  Related Reading: Polygon (MATIC) Sees Surge In Whale Buying Despite US Regulatory Pressure The ability of the $0.00000094 support level to withstand selling pressure signifies buying interest at this level, indicating a potential for a renewed bullish sentiment in the market. Bitcoin retakes the $26K territory on the weekend chart: TradingView.com What PEPE Needs To Sustain Its Rally As PEPE aims to maintain its rally and build on the recent positive momentum, several crucial milestones need to be achieved. According to a recent PEPE price report, a bullish surge in value would require breaking and closing above the trendline located around the $0.00000100 price zone. Related Reading: Cardano (ADA) Price Sheds 19% As Bearish Sentiment Looms Large This trendline acts as a significant resistance level that needs to be surpassed for the cryptocurrency to continue its upward trajectory. Meanwhile, the meme token may be due for a recovery bounce given that PEPE has been aggressively sold off recently. This possibility is made more likely by the fact that PEPE&#8217;s 24-hour trading volume has increased from just over $50 million earlier this week to more than $100 million at the time of writing. Featured image from ArtStation]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Pepe (PEPE) may seize the opportunity to rally in the face of an ongoing volatility and price swings in the crypto market. With Bitcoin (BTC) recently dipping below $25,000 before swiftly rebounding to $26,000, the market has been in a state of flux. Such fluctuations often create an environment ripe for alternative cryptocurrencies to make their mark, and PEPE could be poised to do just that.</p>
<p>PEPE’s rally comes at a time when investors are seeking alternative options beyond the dominant cryptocurrencies. While Bitcoin continues to dominate the market, its price movements can have a cascading effect on other digital assets. </p>
<p>That being said, can PEPE capitalize on Bitcoin&#8217;s volatility and secure its own rally to attract investors seeking new opportunities in the crypto space?</p>
<h2><strong>PEPE Price Recovery Potential</strong></h2>
<p>In recent market developments, PEPE has witnessed a <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">notable rally,</a> as reflected in its current price of $0.0000009779 on CoinMarketCap. This surge represents an impressive 8.5% increase within a 24-hour period. </p>
<p>However, it&#8217;s important to note that this upward momentum follows a preceding seven-day slump of 7.96%, underscoring the inherent volatility that characterizes the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-538316" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Pepe-1.png" alt="" width="1181" height="101" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Pepe-1.png 1181w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Pepe-1-460x39.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Pepe-1-860x74.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Pepe-1-768x66.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Pepe-1-750x64.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Pepe-1-1140x97.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1181px) 100vw, 1181px"/></p>

<p>The price of PEPE has undergone substantial fluctuations since early May, resulting in a significant decline of over 50% in its overall value. This decline has caused a shift in the market structure, signaling a bearish trend as sellers capitalized on shorting opportunities when the support levels at $0.00000162 and $0.00000115 were breached.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-538317 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-99-860x425.png" alt="" width="860" height="425" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-99-860x425.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-99-460x227.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-99-768x380.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-99-750x371.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-99.png 1072w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>Despite the bearish downtrend, recent price activity has hinted at the potential for a new bull run. Notably, the crucial support level at $0.00000094 demonstrated resilience in halting the downward movement. </p>

<p>The ability of the $0.00000094 support level to withstand selling pressure signifies buying interest at this level, indicating a potential for a renewed bullish sentiment in the market.</p>
<h2><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/yhtw4mKX/" width="2315" height="1109"/></h2>

<h2><strong>What PEPE Needs To Sustain Its Rally</strong></h2>
<p>As PEPE aims to maintain its rally and build on the recent positive momentum, several crucial milestones need to be achieved. According to a <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/pepe-rises-13-9-in-24-hours-new-rally-in-works/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">recent PEPE price report</a>, a bullish surge in value would require breaking and closing above the trendline located around the $0.00000100 price zone.</p>

<p>This trendline acts as a significant resistance level that needs to be surpassed for the cryptocurrency to continue its upward trajectory.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the meme token may be due for a <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-price-prediction-as-100-million-pushes-pepe-up-10-24-hours-are-whales-buying.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">recovery bounce</a> given that PEPE has been aggressively sold off recently. This possibility is made more likely by the fact that PEPE&#8217;s 24-hour trading volume has increased from just over $50 million earlier this week to more than $100 million at the time of writing.</p>
<p><em>Featured image from ArtStation</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-100-460x206.png" width="460" height="206" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Rebounds $1,000 From $25,000 Support Level – What Are Whales Up To?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-price-rebounds-1000-from-25000-support-level-what-are-whales-up-to/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ebovictor]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 01:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bullish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538358</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A sudden upward surge has given rise to conjecture regarding the activities of influential market players, commonly called &#8220;whales,&#8221; who may leverage the price decline to amass Bitcoin holdings. Given the increasing allure of the cryptocurrency market, it is imperative to scrutinize recent occurrences that affect Bitcoin&#8217;s trajectory significantly. This examination will delve into these advancements and their possible ramifications on Bitcoin&#8217;s future prospects, particularly their impact on price patterns. Bitcoin&#8217;s price witnesses a notable bounce of $1,000 from a critical support level of $25,000, indicating a significant recovery. Dormant Bitcoin holdings, which had remained untouched for over a decade, are suddenly being moved, raising questions about the motives behind these transfers. Bitcoin gains momentum by breaking above a downward trendline resistance level of approximately $26,000, suggesting a bullish market sentiment and potential for further upward movement. Intriguing Movements And Price Implications A notable development has unfolded as a dormant stash of Bitcoin, valued at over $1.2 million, has suddenly come alive after lying dormant for over 13 years. Blockchain data reveals that a whale initiated a transfer of 50 BTC to another wallet on Thursday. These particular coins were originally mined in June 2010 and have remained untouched. This recent movement follows a trend of previously inactive Bitcoin being set into motion. Related Reading: Why Is Bitcoin Up Today? In April, a remarkable event occurred when an investor, who had held their coins for a decade, transferred a staggering $7.8 million worth of Bitcoin to new wallets. Just days later, another long-term investor or group of investors moved $11 million worth of the digital asset after 11 years of inactivity. The movement of these long-dormant Bitcoin holdings raises intriguing questions about the motivations behind such transfers. Additionally, the heightened interest and trading activity stemming from these movements can impact the dynamics of supply and demand, potentially exerting a significant influence on the overall price of Bitcoin in the near term. Bitcoin Breaking Resistance And Bullish Prospects Bitcoin has exhibited a surge in momentum as it successfully broke above significant downward trendline resistance, around $26,000. Related Reading: Bitcoin, Ethereum Prices May Drop But DigiToads Presale Investors Are Ready for a 3X Surge From a technical perspective, a closer examination of the four-hour timeframe reveals that Bitcoin has surpassed the crucial resistance level of $26,000. This level carries both psychological significance and is bolstered by a downtrend line. The closure of candles above the $26,200 level signifies a prevailing bullish sentiment in the market. Moreover, BTC peaked at approximately $26,450 before undergoing a minor bearish correction. However, it found support at the previously tested resistance level of $26,250, which now acts as a support level. With candles closing above the $26,200 mark, the bullish trend may continue, with the next resistance level at $26,850 as the target. Featured Image From iStock, Charts From TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A sudden upward surge has given rise to conjecture regarding the activities of influential market players, commonly called &#8220;whales,&#8221; who may leverage the price decline to amass <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-bullish-momentum-rise-to-27200/">Bitcoin</a> holdings.</p>
<p>Given the increasing allure of the cryptocurrency market, it is imperative to scrutinize recent occurrences that affect Bitcoin&#8217;s trajectory significantly.</p>
<p>This examination will delve into these advancements and their possible ramifications on Bitcoin&#8217;s future prospects, particularly their impact on price patterns.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-538360 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC.jpg" alt="Bitcoin " width="612" height="410" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC.jpg 612w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-460x308.jpg 460w" sizes="(max-width: 612px) 100vw, 612px"/></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin&#8217;s price witnesses a notable bounce of $1,000 from a critical support level of $25,000, indicating a significant recovery.</li>
<li>Dormant Bitcoin holdings, which had remained untouched for over a decade, are suddenly being moved, raising questions about the motives behind these transfers.</li>
<li>Bitcoin gains momentum by breaking above a downward trendline resistance level of approximately $26,000, suggesting a bullish market sentiment and potential for further upward movement.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Intriguing Movements And Price Implications</h2>
<p>A notable development has unfolded as a dormant stash of Bitcoin, valued at over $1.2 million, has suddenly come alive after lying dormant for over 13 years.</p>
<p>Blockchain data reveals that a whale initiated a transfer of 50 BTC to another wallet on Thursday.</p>
<p>These particular coins were originally mined in June 2010 and have remained untouched.</p>
<p>This recent movement follows a trend of previously inactive Bitcoin being set into motion.</p>

<p>In April, a remarkable event occurred when an investor, who had held their coins for a decade, transferred a staggering $7.8 million worth of Bitcoin to new wallets.</p>
<p>Just days later, another long-term investor or group of investors moved $11 million worth of the digital asset after 11 years of inactivity.</p>
<p>The movement of these long-dormant Bitcoin holdings raises intriguing questions about the motivations behind such transfers.</p>
<p>Additionally, the heightened interest and trading activity stemming from these movements can impact the dynamics of supply and demand, potentially exerting a significant influence on the overall price of Bitcoin in the near term.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Breaking Resistance And Bullish Prospects</h2>
<p>Bitcoin has exhibited a surge in momentum as it successfully broke above significant downward trendline resistance, around $26,000.</p>

<p>From a technical perspective, a closer examination of the four-hour timeframe reveals that Bitcoin has surpassed the crucial resistance level of $26,000.</p>
<p>This level carries both psychological significance and is bolstered by a downtrend line.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-538364 size-jnews-750x375" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-680x375.png" alt="" width="680" height="375"/>
<p>The closure of candles above the $26,200 level signifies a prevailing bullish sentiment in the market.</p>
<p>Moreover, BTC peaked at approximately $26,450 before undergoing a minor bearish correction.</p>
<p>However, it found support at the previously tested resistance level of $26,250, which now acts as a support level.</p>
<p>With candles closing above the $26,200 mark, the bullish trend may continue, with the next resistance level at $26,850 as the target.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-1-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Allegedly Attacked By SEC&#8217;s Hinman For Ethereum&#8217;s Benefit</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-allegedly-attacked-by-secs-hinman-for-ethereums-benefit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 22:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538309</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The legal battle between Ripple and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has taken a new twist as top lawyers accuse former SEC Director William Hinman of being paid to attack XRP in favor of Ethereum (ETH).  Following the release of Hinman&#8217;s emails and drafts of his June 2018 speech, pro-XRP attorney John Deaton expressed his frustration with the intent of the released documents on a recent live CryptoLaw podcast.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Bullish Momentum Building: Expert Predicts Rise To $27,200 Payments To Disparage XRP In Favor Of Ethereum? Jeremy Hogan, lawyer and cryptocurrency expert, also weighed in on the matter alleging that former SEC Director of Corporate Finance, Bill Hinman, was paid to give a speech in which he declared that Ethereum was not a security.  According to Hogan, Ripple, a leading cryptocurrency company, has suggested that Hinman was paid by the Ethereum Foundation or someone related to Ethereum to give the speech and give Ethereum a free pass. Hogan&#8217;s claims are based on email exchanges between Hinman and his colleagues, which reportedly show that Hinman had already named his first email &#8220;the Ether speech&#8221; before he began crafting the speech.  This, according to Hogan, suggests that &#8220;right from the get-go&#8221;, Hinman is saying that ETH is not a security, and that was the point of him making the speech. Hinman&#8217;s speech, which was delivered in 2018, was seen by many in the cryptocurrency industry as a landmark moment in which the SEC effectively declared that Ethereum was not a security.  This was seen as a significant victory for Ethereum and the wider cryptocurrency industry, as it provided clarity on how the SEC would regulate cryptocurrencies. However, Hogan has suggested that the speech was not only a free pass for Ethereum but also an attack on XRP, which was at the time Ethereum&#8217;s biggest competition. Hogan&#8217;s claims are based on Ripple&#8217;s ongoing legal battle with the SEC, in which Ripple has argued that XRP is not a security and should not be regulated as such. Related Reading: Percentage Of ETH Addresses In Profit Reaches 5-Month Low Hogan&#8217;s allegations are likely to fuel speculation about the relationship between the SEC and the cryptocurrency industry, and the extent to which the SEC&#8217;s decisions are influenced by external factors. However, it is important to note that Hogan&#8217;s claims are based on speculation and have not been proven. At present, the value of XRP stands at $0.4731, indicating a marginal recovery of 0.6% over the past day. This comes after a dip to $0.4564 on Wednesday. Despite the recent drop, XRP enthusiasts remain optimistic and are looking forward to a positive outcome that could potentially boost the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price to a new yearly high, surpassing the $0.5833 mark hit in May.  This could position XRP, the sixth largest cryptocurrency on the market, in a favorable position to reach the $1 milestone. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The legal battle between Ripple and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has taken a new twist as top lawyers accuse former SEC Director William Hinman of being paid to attack XRP in favor of Ethereum (ETH). </p>
<p>Following the release of Hinman&#8217;s emails and drafts of his June 2018 speech, pro-XRP attorney John Deaton <a href="https://twitter.com/DigPerspectives/status/1669071745435697153?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">expressed </a>his frustration with the intent of the released documents on a recent live CryptoLaw podcast. </p>

<h2>Payments To Disparage XRP In Favor Of Ethereum?</h2>
<p>Jeremy Hogan, lawyer and cryptocurrency expert, also weighed in on the matter alleging that former SEC Director of Corporate Finance, Bill Hinman, was paid to give a speech in which he declared that Ethereum was not a security. </p>
<p>According to Hogan, Ripple, a leading cryptocurrency company, has suggested that Hinman was paid by the Ethereum Foundation or someone related to Ethereum to give the speech and give Ethereum a free pass.</p>
<p>Hogan&#8217;s claims are based on email exchanges between Hinman and his colleagues, which reportedly show that Hinman had already named his first email &#8220;the Ether speech&#8221; before he began crafting the speech. </p>
<p>This, according to Hogan, suggests that &#8220;right from the get-go&#8221;, Hinman is saying that ETH is not a security, and that was the point of him making the speech.</p>
<p>Hinman&#8217;s speech, which was delivered in 2018, was seen by many in the cryptocurrency industry as a landmark moment in which the SEC effectively declared that Ethereum was not a security. </p>
<p>This was seen as a significant victory for Ethereum and the wider cryptocurrency industry, as it provided clarity on how the SEC would regulate cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>However, Hogan has suggested that the speech was not only a free pass for Ethereum but also an attack on XRP, which was at the time Ethereum&#8217;s biggest competition. Hogan&#8217;s claims are based on Ripple&#8217;s ongoing legal battle with the SEC, in which Ripple has argued that XRP is not a security and should not be regulated as such.</p>

<p>Hogan&#8217;s allegations are likely to fuel speculation about the relationship between the SEC and the cryptocurrency industry, and the extent to which the SEC&#8217;s decisions are influenced by external factors. However, it is important to note that Hogan&#8217;s claims are based on speculation and have not been proven.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/AtbcaRhD/" alt="XRP" width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>At present, the value of XRP stands at $0.4731, indicating a marginal recovery of 0.6% over the past day. This comes after a dip to $0.4564 on Wednesday. Despite the recent drop, XRP enthusiasts remain optimistic and are looking forward to a positive outcome that could potentially boost the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price to a new yearly high, surpassing the $0.5833 mark hit in May. </p>
<p>This could position XRP, the sixth largest cryptocurrency on the market, in a favorable position to reach the $1 milestone.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/possessed-photography-_E1PQXKUkMw-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Percentage Of ETH Addresses In Profit Reaches 5-Month Low</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/percentage-of-eth-addresses-in-profit-reaches-5-month-low/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 20:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538303</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The brutal bear market in crypto over the past few months has taken a serious toll on ETH’s price and profitability. The price of Ethereum has been stuck in a sideways range recently, and many ETH holders have been unlucky for it. According to data from Glassnode, the percentage of Ethereum addresses in profit has now dropped to a 5-month low. Percentage Of Addresses In The Green Drops To 55.414% Back in 2021, when the price of ETH was at its highest, the majority of addresses held a comfortable position. Now, two years later, for new investors who bought at higher prices, the wait for their positions to go green again has been a long one. Related Reading: Curve (CRV) Observes 7% Bounce As Short Squeeze Occurs Glassnode, a crypto analytics platform, reports that the percentage of Ethereum addresses in green while measuring over a 7-day moving average is now at a 5-month low of 55.414%. Percentage of addresses in profit drop to five-month low &#124; Source: Glassnode on Twitter This indicates that more than 44 percent of the people who own ETH are currently at a loss. In the same vein, the number of profitable addresses has dropped to its lowest point since March of this year, standing at 56,311,171.899 at the moment. Moving ETH Off Exchanges The amount of ETH held on cryptocurrency exchanges has also dropped to its lowest level in over 5 years. This means less ETH is available for trading on exchanges, which can impact the price and liquidity. Traders are withdrawing their ETH from exchanges and holding it in private digital wallets.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Bullish Momentum Building: Expert Predicts Rise To $27,200 The drop can also be linked to an all-time high level of staking in the ETH 2.0 deposit contract. Data shows that the majority of ETH held by large investors are now moving ETH into the contract, showing that interest in ETH staking is growing. This declining supply, coupled with increasing mainstream interest in ETH, could drive the price higher if demand remains strong. Ethereum Plunges Below $1,700 Meanwhile, Ethereum broke below critical price support earlier this week. The price plunged below $1,700 to $1,630 yesterday, marking its lowest value since March 16. The plunge in price and profitability is largely attributed to negative sentiment around rising inflation fears and the overall weakness in the crypto market recently. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Lead Developer Unveils Shibacals, Advancing Shibarium Development ETH has since then recovered and is now trading at $1,720, looking to retest the $1,800 resistance once more. Of course, if $1,700 fails to hold, Ethereum could fall further to test support at $1,400 or even $1,300. A drop below $1,700 again would be very bearish and see the profitability percentage drop further.  Ethereum price recovers above $1,700 &#124; Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com Featured image from The Cryptoknowmist, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The brutal bear market in crypto over the past few months has taken a serious toll on ETH’s price and profitability. The price of Ethereum has been stuck in a sideways range recently, and many ETH holders have been unlucky for it. According to data from Glassnode, the percentage of Ethereum addresses in profit has now dropped to a 5-month low.</p>
<h2>Percentage Of Addresses In The Green Drops To 55.414%</h2>
<p>Back in 2021, when the price of ETH was at its highest, the majority of addresses held a comfortable position. Now, two years later, for new investors who bought at higher prices, the wait for their positions to go green again has been a long one.</p>

<p>Glassnode, a crypto analytics platform, <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnodealerts/status/1669574431658606598?s=20" rel="nofollow">reports </a>that the percentage of Ethereum addresses in green while measuring over a 7-day moving average is now at a 5-month low of 55.414%. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-538304 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-profitability-460x230.jpeg" alt="ETH profitability" width="460" height="230" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-profitability-460x230.jpeg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-profitability-860x430.jpeg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-profitability-768x384.jpeg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-profitability-1536x768.jpeg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-profitability-2048x1024.jpeg 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-profitability-360x180.jpeg 360w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-profitability-750x375.jpeg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-profitability-1140x570.jpeg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>

<p>This indicates that more than 44 percent of the people who own ETH are currently at a loss. In the same vein, the number of profitable addresses has <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnodealerts/status/1669438475391717401?s=20" rel="nofollow">dropped </a>to its lowest point since March of this year, standing at 56,311,171.899 at the moment.</p>
<h2>Moving ETH Off Exchanges</h2>
<p>The amount of ETH held on cryptocurrency exchanges has also dropped to its lowest level in over 5 years. This means less ETH is available for trading on exchanges, which can impact the price and liquidity. Traders are withdrawing their ETH from exchanges and holding it in private digital wallets. </p>

<p>The drop can also be linked to an all-time high level of staking in the ETH 2.0 deposit contract. Data shows that the majority of ETH held by large investors are now moving ETH into the contract, showing that interest in ETH staking is growing. This declining supply, coupled with increasing mainstream interest in ETH, could drive the price higher if demand remains strong.</p>
Ethereum Plunges Below $1,700
<p>Meanwhile, Ethereum broke below critical price support earlier this week. The price plunged below $1,700 to $1,630 yesterday, marking its lowest value since March 16. The plunge in price and profitability is largely attributed to negative sentiment around rising inflation fears and the overall weakness in the crypto market recently.</p>

<p>ETH has since then recovered and is now trading at $1,720, looking to retest the $1,800 resistance once more. Of course, if $1,700 fails to hold, Ethereum could fall further to test support at $1,400 or even $1,300. A drop below $1,700 again would be very bearish and see the profitability percentage drop further. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/fPjFNAxo/" alt="Ethereum (ETH) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1610"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-dollar-460x306.jpeg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Bullish Momentum Building: Expert Predicts Rise To $27,200</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-bullish-momentum-rise-to-27200/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 19:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538295</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin has been on a rollercoaster ride recently, with sudden price drops and spikes keeping investors on their toes. Last week, the cryptocurrency failed to break through its $27,500 resistance level and dropped to a low of $24,700.  However, Bitcoin has again shown signs of regaining its bullish momentum, with a 5% increase in the last 24 hours and trading at $26,400 at the time of writing. Many analysts have predicted a continuation of the uptrend in Bitcoin&#8217;s price, which has been ongoing since January 2023. Related Reading: Curve (CRV) Observes 7% Bounce As Short Squeeze Occurs Bearish Momentum Fades As Bitcoin Retests $26,500 According to Glassnode co-founder Yan Allemann, the current stage in this trend is the retesting of the $26,200 level as bearish momentum fades.  Allemann believes that this is an important stage, as it will determine whether Bitcoin can break through its previous resistance and move toward the next target of $27,200 However, while Bitcoin is showing signs of regaining its bullish momentum, it&#8217;s important to recognize that it is still fragile at this level. Therefore, building confidence among investors is crucial to sustaining Bitcoin&#8217;s upward trend. On a positive note, BlackRock&#8217;s recent application with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for its new exchange-traded fund (ETF) has given Bitcoin holders and bulls hope.  As reported by NewsBTC, the recent announcement of BlackRock&#8217;s Bitcoin exchange-traded fund has the potential to impact BTC’s price significantly. If approved, this ETF would enable a wider range of investors to gain exposure to Bitcoin, which could drive up demand and ultimately increase its price. ETFs provide a convenient way for institutional investors to access Bitcoin, creating a new demand avenue for the cryptocurrency. This could increase buying pressure and a potential surge in Bitcoin&#8217;s price. Potential BTC Reversal From Support Bitcoin has recently bounced from its bullish trend and the top of its range, indicating that it still has some work to do before establishing a sustainable upward trend.  According to market analyst Crypto Con, one of the most accurate indicators of Bitcoin&#8217;s bullish or bearish momentum is the 140-day moving average (MA), which shows that BTC’s price is below this crucial level. The 140DMA is a widely followed indicator in the cryptocurrency market, as it clearly signals whether Bitcoin is in a bullish or bearish phase.  When BTC’s price is above the 140DMA, it&#8217;s a bullish signal, indicating that the cryptocurrency will likely continue its upward trend. Conversely, when the price is below the 140DMA, it&#8217;s a bearish signal, suggesting that the cryptocurrency will likely experience a downward trend. Bitcoin&#8217;s price is below the 140DMA, indicating that it&#8217;s in a bearish phase. However, Crypto Con hopes the cryptocurrency will experience a huge reversal from this support level, leading to a bearish fakeout of the 140DMA. This strong bullish signal could indicate that Bitcoin is ready to continue its upward trend. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Lead Developer Unveils Shibacals, Advancing Shibarium Development As BlackRock&#8217;s potential Bitcoin ETF gains attention and BTC gradually regains its bullish momentum, investors are increasingly optimistic that Bitcoin&#8217;s bottom is already behind. There is a growing belief that the largest cryptocurrency in the market is poised to reach new annual highs in 2023 and possibly even surpass its all-time high. However, for BTC to continue its upward trend, the cryptocurrency needs to maintain its current level of $26,000 throughout the weekend. A sustained price above this price mark could indicate that BTC is on track for a green week in the coming days. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has been on a rollercoaster ride recently, with sudden price drops and spikes keeping investors on their toes. Last week, the cryptocurrency failed to break through its $27,500 resistance level and dropped to a low of $24,700. </p>
<p>However, Bitcoin has again shown signs of regaining its bullish momentum, with a 5% increase in the last 24 hours and trading at $26,400 at the time of writing.</p>
<p>Many analysts have predicted a continuation of the uptrend in Bitcoin&#8217;s price, which has been ongoing since January 2023.</p>

<h2>Bearish Momentum Fades As Bitcoin Retests $26,500</h2>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/Negentropic_/status/1669758961254379545?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to Glassnode co-founder Yan Allemann, the current stage in this trend is the retesting of the $26,200 level as bearish momentum fades. </p>
<p>Allemann believes that this is an important stage, as it will determine whether Bitcoin can break through its previous resistance and move toward the next target of $27,200</p>
<p>However, while Bitcoin is showing signs of regaining its bullish momentum, it&#8217;s important to recognize that it is still fragile at this level. Therefore, building confidence among investors is crucial to sustaining Bitcoin&#8217;s upward trend.</p>
<p>On a positive note, BlackRock&#8217;s recent application with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for its new exchange-traded fund (ETF) has given Bitcoin holders and bulls hope. </p>
<p>As reported by <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/blackrock-inches-closer-to-launching-bitcoin-etf-impact-on-btc-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">NewsBTC</a>, the recent announcement of BlackRock&#8217;s Bitcoin exchange-traded fund has the potential to impact BTC’s price significantly. If approved, this ETF would enable a wider range of investors to gain exposure to Bitcoin, which could drive up demand and ultimately increase its price.</p>
<p>ETFs provide a convenient way for institutional investors to access Bitcoin, creating a new demand avenue for the cryptocurrency. This could increase buying pressure and a potential surge in Bitcoin&#8217;s price.</p>
Potential BTC Reversal From Support
<p>Bitcoin has recently bounced from its bullish trend and the top of its range, indicating that it still has some work to do before establishing a sustainable upward trend. </p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoCon_/status/1669723509780520961?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to market analyst Crypto Con, one of the most accurate indicators of Bitcoin&#8217;s bullish or bearish momentum is the 140-day moving average (MA), which shows that BTC’s price is below this crucial level.</p>
<p>The 140DMA is a widely followed indicator in the cryptocurrency market, as it clearly signals whether Bitcoin is in a bullish or bearish phase. </p>
<p>When BTC’s price is above the 140DMA, it&#8217;s a bullish signal, indicating that the cryptocurrency will likely continue its upward trend. Conversely, when the price is below the 140DMA, it&#8217;s a bearish signal, suggesting that the cryptocurrency will likely experience a downward trend.</p>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price is below the 140DMA, indicating that it&#8217;s in a bearish phase. However, Crypto Con hopes the cryptocurrency will experience a huge reversal from this support level, leading to a bearish fakeout of the 140DMA. This strong bullish signal could indicate that Bitcoin is ready to continue its upward trend.</p>

<p>As BlackRock&#8217;s potential Bitcoin ETF gains attention and BTC gradually regains its bullish momentum, investors are increasingly optimistic that Bitcoin&#8217;s bottom is already behind. There is a growing belief that the largest cryptocurrency in the market is poised to reach new annual highs in 2023 and possibly even surpass its all-time high.</p>
<p>However, for BTC to continue its upward trend, the cryptocurrency needs to maintain its current level of $26,000 throughout the weekend. A sustained price above this price mark could indicate that BTC is on track for a green week in the coming days.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/BacPd4kq/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-531282429-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
