<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"

	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 14:35:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">221170450</site>	<item>
		<title>Want A Bitcoin Spot ETF? Then Prove BTC Is Not Manipulated, Says SEC</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/sec-prove-bitcoin-is-not-manipulated/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 18:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21 Shares]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ark invest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547066</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[With multiple applications for a spot Bitcoin ETF already filed, many have continued to speculate when the SEC is likely to give its approval or otherwise. To further add to speculations, Galaxy Digital CEO Mike Novogratz, citing his sources, stated that approval was likely to come within four to six months. However, recent developments seem to suggest that the wait could be longer.  SEC Stalling? In a release dated August 11, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has moved to delay the ARK 21Shares Bitcoin ETF in a move that could be seen as a delay tactic by the regulator.  Related Reading: San Francisco’s SoFi Bank Reveals Significant Holdings In BTC, ETH, And DOGE Cathie Wood’s ARK Invest and 21Shares had collaborated again to refile for a spot Bitcoin ETF earlier this year after the SEC rejected previous applications. Following the standard procedures, the SEC was meant to approve or disapprove the application by August 13. However, with its latest order calling for public input on ARK 21 Shares application, this deadline is consequently extended.  With this, the general public has three weeks to give further comments on the proposal, while the SEC has another five weeks to respond to any comments it may receive. Furthermore, the SEC can choose to extend the deadline by 240 days at the maximum (a move that could potentially delay a final response until Jan 10, 2024). This news would most likely not come as a surprise to ARK Invest’s CEO Cathie Wood, as she had predicted a delay when speaking to Bloomberg on August 7. She also forecasted that the SEC might approve multiple Bitcoin ETF applications. However, nothing is certain, as the regulator could also deny all applications as it has done in the past. BTC price finds support above $29,300 &#124; Source: BTCUSD on Tradingview.com  Concerns Over Bitcoin Manipulation &#38; Regulation While the crypto community swallows the hard pill of the SEC’s latest move, some experts have called attention to the SEC’s multiple uses of the word “manipulation” in its latest release. This is worrisome, considering that the SEC had previously rejected spot Bitcoin ETF applications on the grounds of potential market manipulation.  Furthermore, the SEC’s continued reference to this word may also mean that the regulator, maybe in a bid to frustrate these applications, could ask that they prove that Bitcoin is not a manipulated asset class.  Related Reading: Did XRP Price Really Hit $50 On Gemini Exchange? That will undoubtedly be a huge ask considering that, over time, there have been instances that raised speculations that the crypto market can be manipulated by major players. Furthermore, Bitcoin is a borderless and decentralized currency, and even if the SEC were to move to regulate its use in the US, the ETF market could still be manipulated by external activities from outside the US. The SEC also made raised concerns about Bitcoin not having a “regulated market or significant size,” something which could hinder the approval of any spot-traded Bitcoin ETF. The agency pointed out the fact that Bitcoin Future ETFs were approved because they were regulated by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). Meanwhile, Bitcoin isn’t regulated by any agency. Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With multiple applications for a spot Bitcoin ETF already filed, many have continued to speculate when the SEC is likely to give its approval or otherwise. To further add to speculations, Galaxy Digital CEO Mike Novogratz, citing his sources, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/blackrock-first-spot-bitcoin-etf/#:~:text=Approval%20Coming%20Soon%20For%20First,next%20four%20to%20six%20months.">stated</a> that approval was likely to come within four to six months. However, recent developments seem to suggest that the wait could be longer. </p>
<h2>SEC Stalling?</h2>
<p>In a <a href="https://www.sec.gov/files/rules/sro/cboebzx/2023/34-98112.pdf" rel="nofollow">release</a> dated August 11, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has moved to delay the ARK 21Shares Bitcoin ETF in a move that could be seen as a delay tactic by the regulator. </p>

<p>Cathie Wood’s ARK Invest and 21Shares had collaborated again to refile for a spot Bitcoin ETF earlier this year after the SEC rejected previous applications. Following the standard procedures, the SEC was meant to approve or disapprove the application by August 13. However, with its latest order calling for public input on ARK 21 Shares application, this deadline is consequently extended. </p>
<p>With this, the general public has three weeks to give further comments on the proposal, while the SEC has another five weeks to respond to any comments it may receive. Furthermore, the SEC can choose to extend the deadline by 240 days at the maximum (a move that could potentially delay a final response until Jan 10, 2024).</p>
<p>This news would most likely not come as a surprise to ARK Invest’s CEO Cathie Wood, as she had predicted a delay when speaking to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-08-07/cathie-wood-says-sec-will-approve-multiple-bitcoin-etfs-at-once?sref=3REHEaVI#xj4y7vzkg" rel="nofollow">Bloomberg</a> on August 7. She also forecasted that the SEC might approve multiple Bitcoin ETF applications. However, nothing is certain, as the regulator could also deny all applications as it has done in the past.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/EmWWE82m/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart from Tradingview.com (Spot ETF)" width="2884" height="1746" loading="lazy"/></p>

<h2>Concerns Over Bitcoin Manipulation &amp; Regulation</h2>
<p>While the crypto community swallows the hard pill of the SEC’s latest move, some <a href="https://twitter.com/tedtalksmacro/status/1690013745068531712?s=20" rel="nofollow">experts</a> have called attention to the SEC’s multiple uses of the word “manipulation” in its latest release. This is worrisome, considering that the SEC had previously rejected spot Bitcoin ETF applications on the grounds of potential market manipulation. </p>
<p>Furthermore, the SEC’s continued reference to this word may also mean that the regulator, maybe in a bid to frustrate these applications, could ask that they prove that Bitcoin is not a manipulated asset class. </p>

<p>That will undoubtedly be a huge ask considering that, over time, there have been instances that raised speculations that the crypto market can be manipulated by major players. Furthermore, Bitcoin is a borderless and decentralized currency, and even if the SEC were to move to regulate its use in the US, the ETF market could still be manipulated by external activities from outside the US.</p>
<p>The SEC also made raised concerns about Bitcoin not having a “regulated market or significant size,” something which could hinder the approval of any spot-traded Bitcoin ETF. The agency pointed out the fact that Bitcoin Future ETFs were approved because they were regulated by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). Meanwhile, Bitcoin isn’t regulated by any agency.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-502544320.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547066</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Analyst Shares Bullish Insights On Chainlink As Users Accumulate 295 Million LINK</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/link/crypto-analyst-shares-bullish-insights-on-chainlink-as-users-accumulate-295-million-link/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 15:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LINK]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ali Martinez]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bullish market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chainlink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto analyst]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Link]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546985</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Chainlink (LINK) has been one of the top trending tokens in recent weeks due to a combination of an overall positive price movement as well as exciting on-chain developments.  Following a recent buying spree in the LINK market, crypto analyst Ali Martinez has taken to social media platform X, providing some insights on the token’s potential price action. Related Reading: LINK Price Prediction: Chainlink Turns Attractive On Dips 29,000 Wallets Purchase 295 Million LINK Forming Major Support Level On August 11, Ali posted on X stating that Chainlink has established a strong support zone between $6.63 and $6.88 as about 29,000 addresses purchased over 295 million LINK at this price range based on data from analytics firm IntoTheBlock. Moving on, he postulated that as long as the altcoin was trading above this price zone, investors were likely to continuously remain bullish, especially as Soon-chain data shows that there are no significant resistance levels ahead.  Source: IntoTheBlock According to Ali, a good number of LINK whales have already recognized the $6.63-6.88 zone as “robust” price support and are actively accumulating more tokens. He highlighted that in the past 14 days, LINK whales have purchased an estimated 13 million LINK worth around $91 million.  However, while these developments may be considered indications of a bullish LINK market, Ali states that traders anticipating a market breakout may still need to exercise some patience. Using data from IntoTheBlock, the crypto analyst draws attention to the declining network activity on the Chainlink network in the last three weeks.  Ali stated that during this period, the number of large LINK transactions had gone down from 527 to 118. He concluded his market report by stating a boost in this metric is likely to precede any market breakout. At the time of writing, LINK is exchanging hands at $7.44, with a 1.36% decline in the last day, according to data from CoinMarketCap. However, the token is up 3.66% and 17.67% in the last seven and thirty days, respectively. Related Reading: Chainlink (LINK) Holds Above 14% Gains As Crypto Market Slumps Heavily More Good News For Chainlink Aside from Ali’s market analysis, there has been other positive news about Chainlink in recent days. Also, on August 11, market intelligence firm Santiment reported LINK had experienced its highest level of dormant coin movements in the last six weeks. According to Santiment, this represented a decline in LINK’s mean dollar invested age curve, pointing to a decrease in the token’s time in wallets which is usually a precursor for a rise in market cap. In addition, Chainlink has maintained a rise in its development activity over the last few months. Based on data from Santiment, development activity on Chainlink went up from 1579.12 on May 31 to 1706.48 on August 3.  LINK trading at $7.432 on the daily chart &#124; Source: LINKUSD chart on Tradingview.com Featured image from Stockhead, chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chainlink (LINK) has been one of the top trending tokens in recent weeks due to a combination of an <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/chainlink/chainlink-link-holds-above-14-gains-as-crypto-market-slumps-heavily/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">overall positive price movement</a> as well as <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/chainlink-ccip-goes-live-on-mainnet-link-jumps-by-nearly-10/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">exciting on-chain developments.</a> </p>
<p>Following a recent buying spree in the LINK market, crypto analyst Ali Martinez has taken to social media platform X, providing some insights on the token’s potential price action.</p>

<h2><strong>29,000 Wallets Purchase 295 Million LINK Forming Major Support Level</strong></h2>
<p>On August 11, Ali <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1689975837980811264?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">posted</a> on X stating that Chainlink has established a strong support zone between $6.63 and $6.88 as about 29,000 addresses purchased over 295 million LINK at this price range based on data from analytics firm IntoTheBlock.</p>
<p>Moving on, he postulated that as long as the altcoin was trading above this price zone, investors were likely to continuously remain bullish, especially as Soon-chain data shows that there are no significant resistance levels ahead. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-546994 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3P-x0vWMAECGqJ.jpeg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C324" alt="LINK" width="860" height="324" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3P-x0vWMAECGqJ.jpeg?w=2338 2338w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3P-x0vWMAECGqJ.jpeg?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3P-x0vWMAECGqJ.jpeg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3P-x0vWMAECGqJ.jpeg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C324 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3P-x0vWMAECGqJ.jpeg?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3P-x0vWMAECGqJ.jpeg?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3P-x0vWMAECGqJ.jpeg?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F3P-x0vWMAECGqJ.jpeg?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" loading="lazy" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>According to Ali, a good number of LINK whales have already recognized the $6.63-6.88 zone as “robust” price support and are actively accumulating more tokens. He highlighted that in the past 14 days, LINK whales have purchased an estimated 13 million LINK worth around $91 million. </p>
<p>However, while these developments may be considered indications of a bullish LINK market, Ali states that traders anticipating a market breakout may still need to exercise some patience.</p>
<p>Using data from IntoTheBlock, the crypto analyst draws attention to the declining network activity on the Chainlink network in the last three weeks. </p>
<p>Ali stated that during this period, the number of large LINK transactions had gone down from 527 to 118. He concluded his market report by stating a boost in this metric is likely to precede any market breakout.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, LINK is exchanging hands at $7.44, with a 1.36% decline in the last day, <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/chainlink/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">according to data from CoinMarketCap</a>. However, the token is up 3.66% and 17.67% in the last seven and thirty days, respectively.</p>

<h2><strong>More Good News For Chainlink</strong></h2>
<p>Aside from Ali’s market analysis, there has been other positive news about Chainlink in recent days. Also, on August 11, market intelligence firm Santiment <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1690063262745075712?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reported</a> LINK had experienced its highest level of dormant coin movements in the last six weeks.</p>
<p>According to Santiment, this represented a decline in LINK’s mean dollar invested age curve, pointing to a decrease in the token’s time in wallets which is usually a precursor for a rise in market cap.</p>
<p>In addition, Chainlink has <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/chainlink-developer-activity-link-up-44-june-lows/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">maintained a rise in its development activity</a> over the last few months. Based on<a href="https://app.santiment.net/charts?settings=%7B%22slug%22%3A%22chainlink%22%2C%22ticker%22%3A%22LINK%22%2C%22from%22%3A%222023-02-07T20%3A59%3A59.357Z%22%2C%22to%22%3A%222023-08-07T20%3A59%3A59.357Z%22%7D&amp;widgets=%5B%7B%22widget%22%3A%22HolderDistributionCombinedBalanceWidget%22%2C%22wm%22%3A%5B%22%5B3%3Bpercent_of_holders_distribution_combined_balance%3B100k_to_1M%3B1M_to_10M%5D%22%2C%22dev_activity%22%5D%2C%22whm%22%3A%5B%5D%2C%22wax%22%3A%5B0%2C1%5D%2C%22wpax%22%3A%5B%5D%2C%22wc%22%3A%5B%22%23FFCB47%22%2C%22%238358FF%22%5D%2C%22ws%22%3A%7B%221%22%3A%7B%22interval%22%3A%227d%22%2C%22node%22%3A%22area%22%2C%22transform%22%3A%7B%22type%22%3A%22moving_average%22%2C%22movingAverageBase%22%3A42%7D%7D%7D%7D%5D&amp;layout=21256" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> data from Santiment,</a> development activity on Chainlink went up from 1579.12 on May 31 to 1706.48 on August 3. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/vmR3zc6k/" alt="LINK" width="1480" height="906" loading="lazy"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/fortune-teller-future-crystal-ball-1024x576-1.jpg?fit=460%2C259" width="460" height="259" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546985</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Thunderstruck: THORChain (RUNE) 21% Charge Emerges As Top Weekly Gainer</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/crypto-thunderstruck-thorchain-rune-21-surge-emerges-as-top-weekly-gainer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olowoporoku Adeniyi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 14:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[RUNE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thorchain]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547019</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The dynamic world of cryptocurrencies has once again witnessed a fascinating turn of events, this time with THORChain (RUNE) taking center stage. Over the past seven days, THORChain has experienced a substantial surge in its price, marking an impressive increase of 20.19%. This resurgence has sparked intrigue and excitement among crypto enthusiasts and investors, prompting a closer examination of the factors contributing to this rapid upward movement. The Catalysts Behind The Surge RUNE has made a resurgence in recent months from its lows in June to its recent highs gaining 40% during this period. However, its price is still 10% down from the start of the year and there are expectations that this could be an extended bullrun.  Related Reading: Shiba Inu Keeps Energy Alive, Snags 26% Gain – Here’s The Inside Scoop The surge in THORChain&#8217;s price invites a deeper investigation into the underlying dynamics and catalysts that have propelled this substantial price rally. While a myriad of factors often influences the cryptocurrency market, several key drivers may have played a role in THORChain&#8217;s recent surge: Substantial progress in THORChain&#8217;s underlying technology, protocol enhancements, and ecosystem expansion has triggered renewed interest and investment. Positive fundamental developments often align with price surges as investors anticipate potential long-term growth prospects. Cryptocurrency markets are renowned for their inherent volatility. While volatility can create risks, it allows traders to capitalize on price swings. The recent surge in THORChain&#8217;s price may be driven, in part, by heightened market volatility. THORChain (RUNE): Forecasting Future Trajectories Considering THORChain&#8217;s recent surge, attention naturally turns to the future prospects of this cryptocurrency. Various experts and analysts have offered their insights into THORChain&#8217;s potential trajectory. Related Reading: GMX Drops 24% in 1 Month, Whales Rapidly Selling: What’s Going On? According to short-term prediction, THORChain&#8217;s price could experience a minor retracement to $1.02 by August 16, followed by a recovery to $1.24 by September 9. This prediction underscores the inherent volatility of short-term price movements. Looking ahead to 2023, divergent forecasts paint a range of possibilities. CaptainAltCoin suggests a potential dip to $0.6726 by October, with the year closing at $0.8817. However, if the bull run continues to persist there could be a spike to $2.12 by the year&#8217;s end.  Navigating The Unpredictable Path Ahead As THORChain continues its remarkable surge, the crypto community remains captivated by its price movement. The convergence of various factors, including market sentiment, technical indicators, fundamental developments, and overall market volatility, has likely contributed to this recent rally. However, the cryptocurrency landscape is known for its unpredictability, and the path ahead for THORChain remains uncertain. (This site’s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The dynamic world of cryptocurrencies has once again witnessed a fascinating turn of events, this time with THORChain (RUNE) taking center stage. Over the past seven days, THORChain has experienced a substantial surge in its price, marking an impressive increase of 20.19%. This resurgence has sparked intrigue and excitement among crypto enthusiasts and investors, prompting a closer examination of the factors contributing to this rapid upward movement.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-547021" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image1.png?w=460&#038;resize=460%2C251" alt="THORChain (RUNE) Has experienced a significant spike in the past week: Source @Tradingview" width="460" height="251" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image1.png?w=1048 1048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image1.png?w=460&#038;resize=460%2C251 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image1.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image1.png?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image1.png?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<h2><strong>The Catalysts Behind The Surge</strong></h2>
<p>RUNE has made a resurgence in recent months from its lows in June to its recent highs gaining 40% during this period. However, its price is still 10% down from the start of the year and there are expectations that this could be an extended bullrun. </p>
<p><strong>Related Reading</strong>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/all/shiba-inu-keeps-energy-alive-snags-26-gain-heres-the-inside-scoop/">Shiba Inu Keeps Energy Alive, Snags 26% Gain – Here’s The Inside Scoop</a></p>
<p>The surge in THORChain&#8217;s price invites a deeper investigation into the underlying dynamics and catalysts that have propelled this substantial price rally. While a myriad of factors often influences the cryptocurrency market, several key drivers may have played a role in THORChain&#8217;s recent surge:</p>
<p>Substantial progress in THORChain&#8217;s underlying technology, protocol enhancements, and ecosystem expansion has triggered renewed interest and investment. Positive fundamental developments often align with price surges as investors anticipate potential long-term growth prospects. Cryptocurrency markets are renowned for their inherent volatility. While volatility can create risks, it allows traders to capitalize on price swings. The recent surge in THORChain&#8217;s price may be driven, in part, by heightened market volatility.</p>
<h2><strong>THORChain (RUNE): Forecasting Future Trajectories</strong></h2>
<p>Considering THORChain&#8217;s recent surge, attention naturally turns to the future prospects of this cryptocurrency. Various experts and analysts have offered their insights into THORChain&#8217;s potential trajectory.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading</strong>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/defi/gmx-drops-whales-selling/">GMX Drops 24% in 1 Month, Whales Rapidly Selling: What’s Going On?</a></p>
<p>According to short-term prediction, THORChain&#8217;s price could experience a minor retracement to $1.02 by August 16, followed by a recovery to $1.24 by September 9. This prediction underscores the inherent volatility of short-term price movements.</p>
<p>Looking ahead to 2023, divergent forecasts paint a range of possibilities. CaptainAltCoin suggests a potential dip to $0.6726 by October, with the year closing at $0.8817. However, if the bull run continues to persist there could be a spike to $2.12 by the year&#8217;s end. </p>
<strong>Navigating The Unpredictable Path Ahead</strong>
<p>As THORChain continues its remarkable surge, the crypto community remains captivated by its price movement. The convergence of various factors, including market sentiment, technical indicators, fundamental developments, and overall market volatility, has likely contributed to this recent rally. However, the cryptocurrency landscape is known for its unpredictability, and the path ahead for THORChain remains uncertain.</p>
<p><i>(This site’s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</i></p>
<p><i>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView</i></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-157559643.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547019</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Bitcoin ETF Approval Could See North America&#8217;s ETF Volume Rise To 99.5%</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin-etf-could-see-us-crypto-etf-volume-rise-to-99-5/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 13:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21Shares]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ark invest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Spot ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grayscale]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546993</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[North America could see its share in the global trading volume for crypto-related exchange-traded funds (ETFs) grow even further if spot Bitcoin ETFs are approved in the United States, a Bloomberg analyst said. This comes after the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) issued a delay letter regarding Ark Invest’s application for a spot Bitcoin ETF. In a widely-anticipated delay, the SEC is asking for new written comments on the spot Bitcoin application. Some of the issues raised by the commission include the suitability of Bitcoin as an underlying asset of an exchange-traded product, and the resistance of Bitcoin to price manipulation, amongst other things. The Ark Invest spot ETF, proposed by leading asset management firm ARK Invest in conjunction with Swiss-based 21Shares, would give investors indirect exposure to Bitcoin, the largest cryptocurrency in the market.  This recent setback has raised questions about the fate of the spot Bitcoin ETF applications of other asset management companies, including Blackrock, Valkyrie, WisdomTree, etc. Related Reading: Black Swan Author Warns Of Bitcoin Volume Slump As BTC Fails To Breach $30,000 North America&#8217;s Share Of Global ETF Trading Volume To Reach 99.5%? In the event that the spot Bitcoin ETF applications get greenlighted by the SEC, Bloomberg ETF analyst Eric Balchunas said that the North American region may see its percentage of the crypto ETF trading volumes reach 99.5%. According to his post on X (formerly Twitter), North America currently accounts for 97.67% of the total crypto ETF trading volume in the world. “If/when spot ETFs come out in the US this will likely go to like 99.5%,” Balchunas noted. In another post, the Bloomberg analyst disclosed that most of the best-performing equity ETFs in 2023 are crypto-related. At the top of this list is $WGMI, the Valkyrie Bitcoin Miners ETF, with a year-to-date return of 227%. This actively-managed fund invests in public companies in the Bitcoin mining industry, including Riot, Bitdeer, Cipher Mining, etc. Given the positive performance of these mining firms’ stocks, it is no surprise that investment products, like $WGMI, are doing well. Other top-performing crypto-related exchange-traded products on this list include the VanEck Digital Transformation ETF, with a YTD return of 182%; the Global X Blockchain ETF, which has returned 168% so far in 2023; and the Bitwise Crypto Industry Innovators ETF, also up by roughly 168% year to date. Pending Grayscale Lawsuit To Be Pivotal To Bitcoin ETF Approval In 2022, Grayscale Investments sued the SEC for rejecting the application to convert its flagship product, GBTC, into a spot Bitcoin ETF.  According to Nathan Geraci, president of the ETF Store, the final judgment in this lawsuit could prove pivotal in the race for Bitcoin exchange-traded fund.  Geraci commented on the delay of Ark Invest ETF:  It all comes down to the outcome of the Grayscale lawsuit &#38; SEC&#8217;s view of question #4 here (referring to the fourth subject the commission is seeking comments on). Related Reading: San Francisco’s SoFi Bank Reveals Significant Holdings In BTC, ETH, And DOGE Earlier in March, Grayscale argued against the commission, questioning the logic behind allowing Bitcoin futures ETFs while disapproving similar spot Bitcoin funds. Subsequently, the Grayscale legal team submitted a letter in July, urging the Securities and Exchange Commission to approve all eight applications for Bitcoin spot ETF. BTCUSDT trading at $29,418 &#124; Source: daily BTCUSDT chart on TradingView Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>North America could see its share in the global trading volume for crypto-related exchange-traded funds (ETFs) grow even further if spot Bitcoin ETFs are approved in the United States, a Bloomberg analyst said.</p>
<p>This comes after the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/sec-puts-brakes-on-ark-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">issued a delay letter</a> regarding Ark Invest’s application for a spot Bitcoin ETF. In a widely-anticipated delay, the SEC is asking for new written comments on the spot Bitcoin application.</p>
<p>Some of the issues raised by the commission include the suitability of Bitcoin as an underlying asset of an exchange-traded product, and the resistance of Bitcoin to price manipulation, amongst other things.</p>
<p>The Ark Invest spot ETF, proposed by leading asset management firm ARK Invest in conjunction with Swiss-based 21Shares, would give investors indirect exposure to Bitcoin, the largest cryptocurrency in the market. </p>
<p>This recent setback has raised questions about the fate of the spot Bitcoin ETF applications of other asset management companies, including Blackrock, Valkyrie, WisdomTree, etc.</p>

<h2><strong>North America&#8217;s Share Of Global ETF Trading Volume To Reach 99.5%?</strong></h2>
<p>In the event that the spot Bitcoin ETF applications get greenlighted by the SEC, Bloomberg ETF analyst Eric Balchunas said that the North American region may see its percentage of the crypto ETF trading volumes reach 99.5%.</p>
<p>According to his <a href="https://twitter.com/ericbalchunas/status/1689656052483010560?s=46&amp;t=NdGROPuRW8z8y5XsWXu40w" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a> on X (formerly Twitter), North America currently accounts for 97.67% of the total crypto ETF trading volume in the world. “If/when spot ETFs come out in the US this will likely go to like 99.5%,” Balchunas noted.</p>
<p>In another <a href="https://twitter.com/ericbalchunas/status/1689655154470232064?s=46&amp;t=NdGROPuRW8z8y5XsWXu40w" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, the Bloomberg analyst disclosed that most of the best-performing equity ETFs in 2023 are crypto-related. At the top of this list is $WGMI, the Valkyrie Bitcoin Miners ETF, with a year-to-date return of 227%.</p>
<p>This actively-managed fund invests in public companies in the Bitcoin mining industry, including Riot, Bitdeer, Cipher Mining, etc. Given the positive performance of these mining firms’ stocks, it is no surprise that investment products, like $WGMI, are doing well.</p>
<p>Other top-performing crypto-related exchange-traded products on this list include the VanEck Digital Transformation ETF, with a YTD return of 182%; the Global X Blockchain ETF, which has returned 168% so far in 2023; and the Bitwise Crypto Industry Innovators ETF, also up by roughly 168% year to date.</p>
<h2><strong>Pending Grayscale Lawsuit To Be Pivotal To Bitcoin ETF Approval</strong></h2>
<p>In 2022, Grayscale Investments sued the SEC for rejecting the application to convert its flagship product, GBTC, into a spot Bitcoin ETF. </p>
<p>According to Nathan Geraci, president of the ETF Store, the final judgment in this lawsuit could prove pivotal in the race for Bitcoin exchange-traded fund. </p>
<p>Geraci <a href="https://twitter.com/nategeraci/status/1690010384042778625?s=46&amp;t=NdGROPuRW8z8y5XsWXu40w" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">commented</a> on the delay of Ark Invest ETF: </p>
<blockquote><p>It all comes down to the outcome of the Grayscale lawsuit &amp; SEC&#8217;s view of question #4 here (referring to the fourth subject the commission is seeking comments on).</p></blockquote>

<p>Earlier in March, Grayscale argued against the commission, questioning the logic behind allowing Bitcoin futures ETFs while disapproving similar spot Bitcoin funds.</p>
<p>Subsequently, the Grayscale legal team <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/grayscale-sec-green-light-all-bitcoin-spot-etfs/amp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">submitted a letter</a> in July, urging the Securities and Exchange Commission to approve all eight applications for Bitcoin spot ETF.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/WM5Zw7Ix/" alt="Bitcoin ETF" width="1013" height="595"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1356804795.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546993</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Bull Run Beckons: Unleashing The Potential Of 2024 Halving On Prices</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/all/bitcoin-bull-run-beckons-unleashing-the-potential-of-2024-halving-on-prices/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yuna Rin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 12:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[halving]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547027</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the context of the constantly changing and complex cryptocurrency industry, Bitcoin is currently facing a critical point in its trajectory, as it confronts a range of heightened price pressures that pose significant challenges. The upcoming halving event in 2024 has generated significant anticipation, drawing attention to the complex interaction of various elements that contribute to the value and destiny of the subject in question. Bitcoin&#8217;s value has increased by 75% so far this year despite having to deal with regulatory scrutiny and fraud. The leading crypto in terms of market cap and widespread adoption has shown surprising resilience in the face of US Securities and Exchange Commission enforcement actions against key exchanges like Binance.US and Coinbase. Bitcoin&#8217;s Price Performance Currently, Bitcoin is trading around $29,411, up a meager 0.2% in the last day, but managed to gain a decent 1.4% in the last week, data from crypto market tracker Coingecko shows. Bitcoin is currently showing a neutral stance in the market and facing resistance as it tries to surpass the key $29,600 mark. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Prediction 2024/25: 4-Year Cycle And Elliot Wave Can Coexist Bitcoin price flashing green in all timeframes. Source: Coingecko If there&#8217;s a bullish breakout above $29,600, it could potentially open up the path for Bitcoin to reach the $30,200 level. The top coin has already reached the 61.8% Fibonacci retracement level, which is at $29,200. Bitcoin reached a market cap of $572 billion on the weekend chart: TradingView.com On the other hand, Bitcoin&#8217;s price could change in a big way if it can break through the support level of $30,200. This accomplishment could act as a catalyst and push the value of the coin into a new range, which is thought to be between $30,600 and $31,000. Such a breakthrough could make the market more hopeful and boost investor trust, which could set the stage for more growth. The critical zones to watch are $29,800 and $30,200. If Bitcoin&#8217;s price moves below these levels, it could indicate a bearish trend for the cryptocurrency. Related Reading: Bitcoin Retraces Back From $30,000 As Profit Taking Spikes Bitcoin Price Prediction Meanwhile, Cypherpunk figure Adam Back has bet on Bitcoin hitting six figures by March 2024. He made the wager on Twitter, predicting that Bitcoin will surpass $100,000 before the March 31, 2024 halving. The bet is with the Twitter user &#8220;Vikingo,&#8221; with the winner receiving 1 million satoshis (0.01 Bitcoin). the bet is on🚀: i bet #bitcoin reaches or exceeds $100k between now and halving (31st Mar 2024) with @vikingobitcoin9 1million sats to the winner. https://t.co/Ij7iPEYjQW pic.twitter.com/PNpAaZvl8F — Adam Back (@adam3us) August 5, 2023 For Bitcoin to meet this target, it needs a 243% increase in the next eight months. Before the previous halving in May 2020, Bitcoin saw a range-bound period without major gains. The most significant price surge occurred about six months post-halving, initiating a bullish market trend in November of that year. Understanding Bitcoin Halving Bitcoin halving refers to the occurrence where miners&#8217; rewards for validating blockchain transactions are halved. This event takes place roughly every 210,000 mined blocks, which translates to approximately every four years. Introduced by Bitcoin&#8217;s creator, Satoshi Nakamoto, in 2009, halvings serve the purpose of regulating asset supply. The mining reward reduces by half every 210,000 blocks, aligning with Nakamoto&#8217;s original vision as outlined in the white paper. This mechanism ensures the controlled creation of Bitcoin and maintains incentives for miners. The historical trend of halvings driving price escalation underscores the intricate interplay between scarcity, demand, and Bitcoin&#8217;s valuation, accentuating the anticipation surrounding the forthcoming halving&#8217;s influence on prices. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Deltec Bank &#38; Trust]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the context of the constantly changing and complex cryptocurrency industry, Bitcoin is currently facing a critical point in its trajectory, as it confronts a range of heightened price pressures that pose significant challenges.</p>
<p>The upcoming<a href="https://www.claytoncountyregister.com/news2/stock-takes-how-2024-could-cure-cryptos-winter/74749/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> halving event in 2024</a> has generated significant anticipation, drawing attention to the complex interaction of various elements that contribute to the value and destiny of the subject in question.</p>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s value has increased by 75% so far this year despite having to deal with regulatory scrutiny and fraud. The leading crypto in terms of market cap and widespread adoption has shown surprising resilience in the face of US Securities and Exchange Commission enforcement actions against key exchanges like Binance.US and Coinbase.</p>
<h2><strong>Bitcoin&#8217;s Price Performance</strong></h2>
<p>Currently, Bitcoin is trading around $29,411, up a meager 0.2% in the last day, but managed to gain a decent 1.4% in the last week, data from crypto market tracker Coingecko shows. Bitcoin is currently showing a neutral stance in the market and facing resistance as it tries to surpass the key $29,600 mark.</p>



<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-547035" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-66.png?resize=1024%2C54" alt="" width="1024" height="54" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-66.png?resize=1024%2C54?w=1138 1138w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-66.png?resize=1024%2C54?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-66.png?resize=1024%2C54?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-66.png?resize=1024%2C54?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-66.png?resize=1024%2C54?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>If there&#8217;s a bullish breakout above $29,600, it could potentially open up the path for Bitcoin to reach the $30,200 level. The top coin has already reached the 61.8% Fibonacci retracement level, which is at $29,200.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Na6OM4P8/" width="2475" height="1179"/></p>

<p>On the other hand, Bitcoin&#8217;s price could change in a big way if it can break through the support level of $30,200. This accomplishment could act as a catalyst and push the value of the coin into a new range, which is thought to be between $30,600 and $31,000.</p>
<p>Such a breakthrough could make the market more hopeful and boost investor trust, which could set the stage for more growth.</p>
<p>The critical zones to watch are $29,800 and $30,200. If Bitcoin&#8217;s price moves below these levels, it could indicate a bearish trend for the cryptocurrency.</p>



<h2><strong>Bitcoin Price Prediction</strong></h2>
<p>Meanwhile, Cypherpunk figure Adam Back has bet on <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-halving-event-2024-sparks-bullish-sentiments-time-buy-1.htm?fbclid=IwAR3RIWie_0aUvJM2nzEwxOwnc9iCcgzsP36COKNhL4Bjiqu2Q0rz3MEcNYw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Bitcoin</a> hitting six figures by March 2024. He made the wager on Twitter, predicting that Bitcoin will surpass $100,000 before the March 31, 2024 halving. The bet is with the Twitter user &#8220;Vikingo,&#8221; with the winner receiving 1 million satoshis (0.01 Bitcoin).</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">the bet is on<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />: i bet <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#bitcoin</a> reaches or exceeds $100k between now and halving (31st Mar 2024) with <a href="https://twitter.com/Vikingobitcoin9?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@vikingobitcoin9</a> 1million sats to the winner. <a href="https://t.co/Ij7iPEYjQW" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/Ij7iPEYjQW</a> <a href="https://t.co/PNpAaZvl8F" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/PNpAaZvl8F</a></p>
<p>— Adam Back (@adam3us) <a href="https://twitter.com/adam3us/status/1687867034158440448?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 5, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>For Bitcoin to meet this target, it needs a 243% increase in the next eight months. Before the previous halving in May 2020, Bitcoin saw a range-bound period without major gains. The most significant price surge occurred about six months post-halving, initiating a bullish market trend in November of that year.</p>
<h2><strong>Understanding Bitcoin Halving</strong></h2>
<p>Bitcoin halving refers to the occurrence where miners&#8217; rewards for validating blockchain transactions are halved. This event takes place roughly every 210,000 mined blocks, which translates to approximately every four years.</p>
<p>Introduced by Bitcoin&#8217;s creator, Satoshi Nakamoto, in 2009, halvings serve the purpose of <a href="https://www.bitpanda.com/academy/en/lessons/what-is-a-bitcoin-halving-and-what-happens-on-the-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">regulating asset supply.</a> The mining reward reduces by half every 210,000 blocks, aligning with Nakamoto&#8217;s original vision as outlined in the white paper. This mechanism ensures the controlled creation of Bitcoin and maintains incentives for miners.</p>
<p>The historical trend of halvings driving price escalation underscores the intricate interplay between scarcity, demand, and Bitcoin&#8217;s valuation, accentuating the anticipation surrounding the forthcoming halving&#8217;s influence on prices.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Deltec Bank &amp; Trust</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-67.png?fit=460%2C226" width="460" height="226" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547027</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polkadot Bearish Trends Set The Stage For Bullish Possibilities &#8211; Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/all/polkadot-bearish-trends-set-the-stage-for-bullish-possibilities-heres-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 11:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOT Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polkadot]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=547009</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Polkadot (DOT) has managed to capture the attention of traders and investors alike. Despite a persistently bearish market structure, recent indicators point towards a potential bullish recovery on the horizon.  As of the latest data from CoinGecko, DOT is currently trading at $5.02, with a 0.7% gain in the past 24 hours and a 1.5% increase over the past seven days. Polkadot price action today. Source: Coingecko With the broader market experiencing an upward price trajectory, DOT buyers are poised to reap potential benefits. Analyzing the market dynamics, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) has unveiled a recovering buying pressure.  Signs Of Revival Emerge Amidst Market Uncertainty A recent price analysis points out that the RSI has edged closer to the neutral 50 level, marking a significant shift from its recent spell within the oversold zone. This shift suggests an increasing appetite for DOT tokens among traders, potentially setting the stage for a bullish resurgence. Related Reading: Rising Star Hedera (HBAR) And Its 11% Climb – A Closer Look Further fueling the optimism, the Chaikin Money Flow (CMF) indicator has displayed an uptick in buyer confidence. The CMF, a measure of the volume and flow of capital into or out of a cryptocurrency, has made a decisive move from the zero mark, currently standing at +0.20. This reading highlights the influx of capital into DOT, indicating a growing sense of positivity and enthusiasm among buyers. Polkadot (DOT) market cap at $6.09 billion on the weekend chart: TradingView.com Polkadot Bulls Eye Key Price Levels, Bears Await In the coming days, bulls within the DOT market are gearing up to challenge the bears for ownership of the crucial $5.23 price level. A successful flip of this level into a support zone could potentially pave the way for further gains.  Market analysts speculate that should this support level be reclaimed, DOT could make strides towards $5.50 and potentially reach $6. However, a rejection at these levels could send DOT on a downward trajectory, with a potential dip towards the $4.5 range. $DOT #Polkadot If it goes down to the last low at $4 it would be a 16% loss. If it goes up to the big resistance at 24$ it would be a 375% profit. Do you think it&#8217;s worth the risk to buy at $5? pic.twitter.com/GPBSm7XKpM — Tony ₿itcoin⚡ (@Toni_Bitcoin) August 11, 2023 The outcome of DOT&#8217;s price movements is also tied to the performance of the broader cryptocurrency market, particularly Bitcoin (BTC). Should BTC fail to sustain its ongoing price rally, DOT&#8217;s trajectory could be influenced. Related Reading: Rollbit Coin Continues Supremacy Over Top 100 Cryptos In The Last Week While the cryptocurrency market remains inherently volatile and unpredictable, the recent indicators surrounding Polkadot signal the possibility of a bullish recovery. The resurgence in buying pressure, coupled with the growing confidence of buyers as depicted by the CMF indicator, sets an optimistic tone for the future.  As the battle between bulls and bears ensues, traders and investors alike will keenly watch the pivotal price levels, with the hope of witnessing a substantial market turnaround. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Analytics Insight]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Polkadot (DOT) has managed to capture the attention of traders and investors alike. Despite a persistently bearish market structure, recent indicators point towards a potential bullish recovery on the horizon. </p>
<p>As of the latest data from <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/polkadot" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a>, DOT is currently trading at $5.02, with a 0.7% gain in the past 24 hours and a 1.5% increase over the past seven days.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-547015" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-65.png?resize=1024%2C53" alt="" width="1024" height="53" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-65.png?resize=1024%2C53?w=1137 1137w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-65.png?resize=1024%2C53?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-65.png?resize=1024%2C53?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-65.png?resize=1024%2C53?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-65.png?resize=1024%2C53?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>With the broader market experiencing an upward price trajectory, DOT buyers are poised to reap potential benefits. Analyzing the market dynamics, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) has unveiled a recovering buying pressure. </p>
<h2><strong>Signs Of Revival Emerge Amidst Market Uncertainty</strong></h2>
<p>A recent price analysis points out that the RSI has edged closer to the neutral 50 level, marking a significant shift from its recent spell within the oversold zone. This shift suggests an increasing appetite for DOT tokens among traders, potentially setting the stage for a bullish resurgence.</p>

<p>Further fueling the optimism, the Chaikin Money Flow (CMF) indicator has displayed an uptick in buyer confidence. The CMF, a measure of the volume and flow of capital into or out of a cryptocurrency, has made a decisive move from the zero mark, currently standing at +0.20. This reading highlights the influx of capital into DOT, indicating a growing sense of positivity and enthusiasm among buyers.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/1iYbO9G8/" width="2475" height="1179"/></p>

<h2><strong>Polkadot Bulls Eye Key Price Levels, Bears Await</strong></h2>
<p>In the coming days, bulls within the DOT market are gearing up to challenge the bears for ownership of the crucial $5.23 price level. A successful flip of this level into a support zone could potentially pave the way for further gains. </p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/Toni_Bitcoin/status/1690032676571373568" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Market analysts speculate</a> that should this support level be reclaimed, DOT could make strides towards $5.50 and potentially reach $6. However, a rejection at these levels could send DOT on a downward trajectory, with a potential dip towards the $4.5 range.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24DOT&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$DOT</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Polkadot?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Polkadot</a>
If it goes down to the last low at $4 it would be a 16% loss.
If it goes up to the big resistance at 24$ it would be a 375% profit.
Do you think it&#8217;s worth the risk to buy at $5? <a href="https://t.co/GPBSm7XKpM" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/GPBSm7XKpM</a></p>
<p>— Tony ₿itcoin<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/26a1.png" alt="⚡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@Toni_Bitcoin) <a href="https://twitter.com/Toni_Bitcoin/status/1690032676571373568?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>The outcome of DOT&#8217;s price movements is also tied to the performance of the broader cryptocurrency market, particularly Bitcoin (BTC). Should BTC fail to sustain its ongoing price rally, DOT&#8217;s trajectory could be influenced.</p>

<p>While the cryptocurrency market remains inherently volatile and unpredictable, the recent indicators surrounding Polkadot signal the possibility of a bullish recovery. The resurgence in buying pressure, coupled with the growing confidence of buyers as depicted by the CMF indicator, sets an optimistic tone for the future. </p>
<p>As the battle between bulls and bears ensues, traders and investors alike will keenly watch the pivotal price levels, with the hope of witnessing a substantial market turnaround.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Analytics Insight</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-64.png?fit=460%2C268" width="460" height="268" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">547009</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana Price Sparkles With 9% Increase, But Why Do Buyers Remain Cautious?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/all/solana-price-sparkles-with-9-increase-but-why-do-buyers-remain-cautious/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 10:24:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546982</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) has managed to shake off recent price dips, rekindling bullish optimism among investors. This resurgence comes on the heels of a determined effort by sellers to flip the altcoin&#8217;s trajectory bearish, following a price rejection at the critical $29 resistance level.  However, SOL&#8217;s retreat from this resistance proved to be a strategic move as it found support in the bullish order block (OB) at $22, setting the stage for a renewed uptrend. SOL&#8217;s journey from the formidable $29 price mark to the bullish order block at $22 was pivotal. A recent price analysis has underscored the importance of this OB as a key level for the altcoin&#8217;s potential reversal of fortunes.  Related Reading: Shiba Inu Keeps Energy Alive, Snags 26% Gain – Here’s The Inside Scoop With a long-term perspective in mind, Solana&#8217;s ability to rally from this OB demonstrates the resolve of buyers to reclaim control. This recovery has not only bolstered sentiment but also signified the strategic importance of this price juncture in steering the trend. BTC&#8217;s Influence On SOL&#8217;s Trajectory One notable factor underpinning Solana&#8217;s current narrative is the role of Bitcoin (BTC), the flagship cryptocurrency. As SOL seeks to flip the $25.3 resistance level into a supportive base for further gains, its success may very well depend on the continued bullish advance of Bitcoin. The interplay between these two prominent cryptocurrencies remains a significant aspect to monitor, as BTC&#8217;s trajectory often influences the broader altcoin market sentiment. At present, Solana stands at a price of $24.50, as per CoinGecko data. Despite a slight decline of 1.0% over the last 24 hours, the altcoin has showcased a commendable seven-day rally of 8.8%, indicative of its capacity to rebound from adversities.  Solana weekend price action. Source: Coingecko However, a notable challenge emerges as SOL inches closer to the $25.7 mark. The impending supply pressure at this level could potentially stall the upward momentum, prompting a sideways trend and leading to a consolidation phase. Solana: Clearing The Path Forward Should the SOL price encounter intensified supply pressure around the $25.7 threshold, a distinct possibility is the emergence of a narrow price range during trading sessions. This consolidation phase, while seemingly a temporary lull, may serve a vital purpose. By trimming away weaker positions, this period could pave the way for a definitive directional movement. Solana market cap nearing the $10 billion level. Chart: TradingView.com Related Reading: Rising Star Hedera (HBAR) And Its 11% Climb – A Closer Look The shedding of less robust positions would ideally set the stage for a more sustainable bullish advance, as the altcoin continues its journey to reclaim lost ground. As the altcoin navigates potential consolidation, investors are watching closely, anticipating the emergence of a clearer path forward in this dynamic crypto landscape. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Ana Silva/Getty Images]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Solana (SOL) has managed to shake off recent price dips, rekindling bullish optimism among investors. This resurgence comes on the heels of a determined effort by sellers to flip the altcoin&#8217;s trajectory bearish, following a price rejection at the critical $29 resistance level. </p>
<p>However, SOL&#8217;s retreat from this resistance proved to be a strategic move as it found support in the bullish order block (OB) at $22, setting the stage for a renewed uptrend.</p>
<p>SOL&#8217;s journey from the formidable $29 price mark to the bullish order block at $22 was pivotal. A recent <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/solana-offers-bullish-movement-but-buyers-remain-cautious/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">price analysis</a> has underscored the importance of this OB as a key level for the altcoin&#8217;s potential reversal of fortunes. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-546997 size-medium" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-63.png?w=460&#038;resize=460%2C245" alt="" width="460" height="245" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-63.png?w=1396 1396w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-63.png?w=460&#038;resize=460%2C245 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-63.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-63.png?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-63.png?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-63.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>



<p>With a long-term perspective in mind, Solana&#8217;s ability to rally from this OB demonstrates the resolve of buyers to reclaim control. This recovery has not only bolstered sentiment but also signified the strategic importance of this price juncture in steering the trend.</p>
<h2><strong>BTC&#8217;s Influence On SOL&#8217;s Trajectory</strong></h2>
<p>One notable factor underpinning Solana&#8217;s current narrative is the role of Bitcoin (BTC), the flagship cryptocurrency. As SOL seeks to flip the $25.3 resistance level into a supportive base for further gains, its success may very well depend on the continued bullish advance of Bitcoin. </p>
<p>The interplay between these two prominent cryptocurrencies remains a significant aspect to monitor, as BTC&#8217;s trajectory often influences the broader altcoin market sentiment.</p>
<p>At present, Solana stands at a price of $24.50, as per <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/solana" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko data</a>. Despite a slight decline of 1.0% over the last 24 hours, the altcoin has showcased a commendable seven-day rally of 8.8%, indicative of its capacity to rebound from adversities. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-546991" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-61.png?resize=966%2C62" alt="" width="966" height="62" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-61.png?resize=966%2C62?w=966 966w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-61.png?resize=966%2C62?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-61.png?resize=966%2C62?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-61.png?resize=966%2C62?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-61.png?resize=966%2C62?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 966px) 100vw, 966px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>However, a notable challenge emerges as SOL inches closer to the $25.7 mark. The impending supply pressure at this level could potentially stall the upward momentum, prompting a sideways trend and leading to a consolidation phase.</p>
<strong>Solana: Clearing The Path Forward</strong>
<p>Should the <a href="https://coingape.com/markets/solana-price-path-to-30-double-bottom-pattern-sparks/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">SOL price</a> encounter intensified supply pressure around the $25.7 threshold, a distinct possibility is the emergence of a narrow price range during trading sessions. </p>
<p>This consolidation phase, while seemingly a temporary lull, may serve a vital purpose. By trimming away weaker positions, this period could pave the way for a definitive directional movement.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/4zC7yRye/" width="2475" height="1179"/></p>


<p>The shedding of less robust positions would ideally set the stage for a more sustainable bullish advance, as the altcoin continues its journey to reclaim lost ground.</p>
<p>As the altcoin navigates potential consolidation, investors are watching closely, anticipating the emergence of a clearer path forward in this dynamic crypto landscape.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Ana Silva/Getty Images</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-62.png?fit=460%2C285" width="460" height="285" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546982</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Keeps Energy Alive, Snags 26% Gain &#8211; Here&#8217;s The Inside Scoop</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/all/shiba-inu-keeps-energy-alive-snags-26-gain-heres-the-inside-scoop/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546962</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) has transformed its breakout into a remarkable rally, continuing to build momentum in the ever-evolving crypto landscape. The surge has not only captivated the attention of crypto enthusiasts but has also brought a considerable number of meme token holders out of the depths of losses, marking a significant turning point in their investment journey. With SHIB&#8217;s current price resting at $0.00001120 per CoinGecko, the token has showcased an impressive 12.5% surge in the past 24 hours, while its seven-day journey witnessed a striking 25.8% increase. SHIB price action today. Source: Coingecko Related Reading: Rising Star Hedera (HBAR) And Its 11% Climb – A Closer Look The breakout that commenced at $0.000094 has now solidified as a crucial support level, prompting buyers to propel the token&#8217;s value forward. The bullish sentiment has been unyielding, with sellers seemingly absent from the scene, painting a promising picture for the token&#8217;s trajectory. SHIB Targets And Challenges Ahead While the ongoing momentum keeps the market sentiment upbeat, experts point to the first significant resistance point at $0.0000106. This juncture will likely be closely monitored by traders, as potential sellers could make their presence felt. #SHIB Penetration of the Shiba candle at the resistance level is a sign of the continuation of the upward trend. #SHIBUSDT pic.twitter.com/cZ4s0BwOGC — Andrew Griffiths (@AndrewGriUK) August 11, 2023 If the bullish momentum persists, the next target for SHIB rests at $0.000012. Observing the current price action, the likelihood of SHIB reaching these levels appears favorable, painting a bright outlook for this meme coin. The transformation in SHIB&#8217;s fortunes extends beyond price fluctuations. Previously, a prolonged period of time saw over 80% of SHIB holders facing losses. However, recent data from Chain Afirk, an African web3 community on Twitter, indicates a significant shift.  The market capitalization of Shiba Inu is currently $6.4 billion. Chart: TradingView.com Approximately 33.03% of SHIB holders have now transitioned into a profitable position, signaling a shift in the memecoin&#8217;s fortunes. This change not only brings relief to long-time holders but also underlines the growing resilience of the token. Shiba Inu: The Key NVT Signal Analyzing the Network Value to Transactions (NVT) signal provides further insights into SHIB&#8217;s current state. According to Glassnode data cited by a price analysis, the NVT metric has surged to 170.52. This high NVT signal implies that SHIB&#8217;s market capitalization has surpassed its transaction volume, potentially pointing to an inflated state. This phenomenon could be indicative of the token reaching a market top, warranting vigilance from investors. Related Reading: Rollbit Coin Continues Supremacy Over Top 100 Cryptos In The Last Week Shiba Inu&#8217;s breakout has evolved into a rallying force, breathing new life into the meme-inspired token and offering a glimmer of hope to holders. The journey from underwater to profitable has been a notable shift, underscoring the dynamic nature of the cryptocurrency market.  (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Getty Images]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB) has transformed its breakout into a remarkable rally, continuing to build momentum in the ever-evolving crypto landscape. </p>
<p>The surge has not only captivated the attention of crypto enthusiasts but has also brought a considerable number of meme token holders out of the depths of losses, marking a significant turning point in their investment journey.</p>
<p>With SHIB&#8217;s current price resting at $0.00001120 per <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/shiba-inu" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a>, the token has showcased an impressive 12.5% surge in the past 24 hours, while its seven-day journey witnessed a striking 25.8% increase. <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-546968" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-57.png?resize=980%2C67" alt="" width="980" height="67" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-57.png?resize=980%2C67?w=980 980w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-57.png?resize=980%2C67?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-57.png?resize=980%2C67?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-57.png?resize=980%2C67?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-57.png?resize=980%2C67?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 980px) 100vw, 980px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>


<p>The breakout that commenced at $0.000094 has now solidified as a crucial support level, prompting buyers to propel the token&#8217;s value forward. The bullish sentiment has been unyielding, with sellers seemingly absent from the scene, painting a promising picture for the token&#8217;s trajectory.</p>
<h2><strong>SHIB Targets And Challenges Ahead</strong></h2>
<p>While the ongoing momentum keeps the market sentiment upbeat, <a href="https://twitter.com/AndrewGriUK/status/1689973959939231745" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">experts point</a> to the first significant resistance point at $0.0000106. This juncture will likely be closely monitored by traders, as potential sellers could make their presence felt.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/SHIB?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#SHIB</a> Penetration of the Shiba candle at the resistance level is a sign of the continuation of the upward trend.
<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/SHIBUSDT?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#SHIBUSDT</a> <a href="https://t.co/cZ4s0BwOGC" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/cZ4s0BwOGC</a></p>
<p>— Andrew Griffiths (@AndrewGriUK) <a href="https://twitter.com/AndrewGriUK/status/1689973959939231745?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>If the bullish momentum persists, the next target for SHIB rests at $0.000012. Observing the current price action, the likelihood of SHIB reaching these levels appears favorable, painting a bright outlook for this meme coin.</p>
<p>The transformation in SHIB&#8217;s fortunes extends beyond price fluctuations. Previously, a prolonged period of time saw over 80% of SHIB holders facing losses. However, recent <a href="https://twitter.com/ChainAfrik/status/1689887919127871488" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from Chain Afirk</a>, an African web3 community on Twitter, indicates a significant shift. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/LN09Udaf/" width="1835" height="893"/></p>

<p>Approximately 33.03% of SHIB holders have now transitioned into a profitable position, signaling a shift in the memecoin&#8217;s fortunes. This change not only brings relief to long-time holders but also underlines the growing resilience of the token.</p>
<h2><strong>Shiba Inu: The Key NVT Signal</strong></h2>
<p>Analyzing the Network Value to Transactions (NVT) signal provides further insights into SHIB&#8217;s current state. According to Glassnode data cited by a <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/age-old-shib-holders-are-no-longer-underwater/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">price analysis</a>, the NVT metric has surged to 170.52.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-546970 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-58.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C483" alt="" width="860" height="483" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-58.png?w=1324 1324w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-58.png?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-58.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-58.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C483 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-58.png?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-58.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>
<p>This high NVT signal implies that SHIB&#8217;s market capitalization has surpassed its transaction volume, potentially pointing to an inflated state. This phenomenon could be indicative of the token reaching a market top, warranting vigilance from investors.</p>

<p>Shiba Inu&#8217;s breakout has evolved into a rallying force, breathing new life into the meme-inspired token and offering a glimmer of hope to holders. The journey from underwater to profitable has been a notable shift, underscoring the dynamic nature of the cryptocurrency market. </p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Getty Images</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-18.jpg?fit=460%2C331" width="460" height="331" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546962</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>GMX Drops 24% in 1 Month, Whales Rapidly Selling: What&#8217;s Going On?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/defi/gmx-drops-whales-selling/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 01:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitrum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GMX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GMX v2 Beta]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546950</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GMX, the native token powering GMX, a decentralized perpetual exchange for trading complex crypto derivatives, is under intense selling pressure when writing on August 11. Trackers show that the governance token is down 7% on the last trading day, pushing monthly losses to 24%. This downturn has seen prices tumble close to $40, a critical support level last printed in January and June 2023.  Whales Dumping, Prices Fall Despite this setback, DeFiLlama&#8217;s data is stable as GMX&#8217;s Total Value Locked (TVL) remains over $534 million. Most of the trading platform&#8217;s liquidity is locked in Arbitrum, a layer-2 scaling solution for Ethereum. Additionally, another portion is locked on Avalanche, a fourth-generation Ethereum-compatible smart contract platform focused on decentralized finance (DeFi). The sell-off on August 11 coincides with actions by GMX &#8220;whales.&#8221; According to Lookonchain data, four whales sold 62,274 GMX worth $3 million. Address &#8220;0xb824&#8221; liquidated 19,786 GMX, translating to 514 ETH, and &#8220;0xa38a&#8221; sold 11,667 GMX for 305 ETH, losing $50,000 in the process. Meanwhile, &#8220;0X85b7&#8221; sold 20,000 GMX for 510 ETH, and &#8220;0x0b80&#8221; mirrored this move, dumping 10,820 GMX. Related Reading: Curve Finance Resurgence: 70% Of Stolen Funds Recovered, Redemption On The Horizon Whales are selling amid a constant decline in TVL in DeFi. This contraction can be traced to the general cool-off from late 2021, when crypto prices peaked before dropping in 2022, crashing on-chain activity, especially in DeFi. At spot rates, it is changing hands at $46, an almost 50% decline from $91 registered in Q2 of 2023. Even so, the token is up nearly 4X from its all-time low. Whales&#8217; action, nonetheless, could send ripples of uncertainty throughout the GMX and DeFi communities. Crypto traders actively keep track of whale activity. Usually, when they sell, as was the case today, it could sow fear, leading others to follow suit, heaping more pressure on prices. GMX Launches v2 Beta On August 6, GMX released the v2 version in beta on Arbitrum and Avalanche. The exchange said this version introduces several enhancements, including support for more assets, including XRP. With v2, users can also utilize diverse collateral types for trading positions while trading more quickly with reduced fees and lower slippage.  Related Reading: Did XRP Price Really Hit $50 On Gemini Exchange With v2, the exchange adds, is the introduction of isolated pools for liquidity providers to customize their exposure to preferred tokens. This version also incorporates augmented incentives for balancing open interest, offering a strategic avenue for hedging pools against trader profit fluctuations.  Feature image from Canva, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>GMX, the native token powering GMX, a decentralized perpetual exchange for trading complex crypto derivatives, is under intense selling pressure when writing on August 11. </p>
<p>Trackers <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.coinlore.com/coin/gmx" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">show</a> that the governance token is down 7% on the last trading day, pushing monthly losses to 24%. This downturn has seen prices tumble close to $40, a critical support level last printed in January and June 2023. </p>
<h2>Whales Dumping, Prices Fall</h2>
<p>Despite this setback, DeFiLlama&#8217;s <a href="https://defillama.com/protocol/gmx" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a> is stable as GMX&#8217;s Total Value Locked (TVL) remains over $534 million. Most of the trading platform&#8217;s liquidity is locked in Arbitrum, a layer-2 scaling solution for Ethereum. Additionally, another portion is locked on Avalanche, a fourth-generation Ethereum-compatible smart contract platform focused on decentralized finance (DeFi).</p>
<p>The sell-off on August 11 <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1689827838478921728" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">coincides</a> with actions by GMX &#8220;whales.&#8221; According to Lookonchain data, four whales sold 62,274 GMX worth $3 million. Address &#8220;0xb824&#8221; liquidated 19,786 GMX, translating to 514 ETH, and &#8220;0xa38a&#8221; sold 11,667 GMX for 305 ETH, losing $50,000 in the process. Meanwhile, &#8220;0X85b7&#8221; sold 20,000 GMX for 510 ETH, and &#8220;0x0b80&#8221; mirrored this move, dumping 10,820 GMX.</p>

<p>Whales are selling amid a constant decline in TVL in DeFi. This contraction can be traced to the general cool-off from late 2021, when crypto prices peaked before dropping in 2022, crashing on-chain activity, especially in DeFi. At spot rates, it is changing hands at $46, an almost 50% decline from $91 registered in Q2 of 2023. Even so, the token is up nearly 4X from its all-time low.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/CJjlRLiu/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/CJjlRLiu/" alt="GMX price on August 11| Source: GMXUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>
<p>Whales&#8217; action, nonetheless, could send ripples of uncertainty throughout the GMX and DeFi communities. Crypto traders actively keep track of whale activity. Usually, when they sell, as was the case today, it could sow fear, leading others to follow suit, heaping more pressure on prices.</p>
<h2>GMX Launches v2 Beta</h2>
<p>On August 6, GMX<a href="https://gmxio.substack.com/p/gmx-v2-beta-is-now-live" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> released</a> the v2 version in beta on Arbitrum and Avalanche. The exchange said this version introduces several enhancements, including support for more assets, including XRP. With v2, users can also utilize diverse collateral types for trading positions while trading more quickly with reduced fees and lower slippage. </p>

<p>With v2, the exchange adds, is the introduction of isolated pools for liquidity providers to customize their exposure to preferred tokens. This version also incorporates augmented incentives for balancing open interest, offering a strategic avenue for hedging pools against trader profit fluctuations. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/GMX-Whales-Selling.jpg?fit=460%2C260" width="460" height="260" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546950</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano Q2 Surge: Stablecoin Soars, TVL Skyrockets, And Dapp Transactions Hit Record Highs</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/ada/cardano-q2-surge-stablecoin-soars-tvl-skyrockets-and-dapp-transactions-hit-record-highs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 22:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano NFTs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546945</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA), the blockchain platform renowned for its scalability and technological approach, has made significant strides in the crypto market, as highlighted by the recently released Messari report.  The report provides valuable insights into Cardano&#8217;s achievements in Q2 2023, solidifying its position as a prominent player within the industry.  With a strong focus on fostering a robust ecosystem and pushing the boundaries of decentralized finance (DeFi) and non-fungible tokens (NFTs), Cardano is poised to reshape the landscape of blockchain technology, according to Messari.  Cardano TVL Ranking Skyrockets, Climbs From 34th to 21st Per the report, Cardano experienced substantial growth in stablecoin value, with a 34.9% quarter-over-quarter (QoQ) increase and a significant 382.1% year-to-date (YTD) surge.  Indigo Protocol emerged as a frontrunner in stablecoin and synthetic asset issuance, solidifying its dominance in the space. Furthermore, the Total Value Locked (TVL) witnessed a shift towards newer projects, as protocols created in the past six months accounted for 47.4% of TVL dominance in Q2.  Related Reading: Curve Finance Resurgence: 70% Of Stolen Funds Recovered, Redemption On The Horizon The TVL in USD rose by 9.7% QoQ and 198.6% YTD. Cardano&#8217;s TVL ranking climbed from 34th to 21st across all chains in 2023. On the other hand, average daily decentralized application (dapp) transactions on Cardano surged by 49% QoQ, marking the third consecutive quarterly increase. Moreover, Minswap, an automated market maker (AMM), showcased the largest absolute growth in transaction volume.  However, several new dapps also contributed to the overall surge. Minswap&#8217;s popularity soared in Q2, surpassing the leading NFT marketplace jpg.store regarding dapp transactions.  This trend aligned with the sectoral shift, as DeFi activity gained momentum while NFT activity experienced a decline. The overall increase in dapp transactions reached a substantial 49.0% QoQ, averaging 57,900 daily transactions. Q2 NFT Metrics Reflect Market Correction According to Messari, NFT metrics experienced a decline in Q2. Average daily NFT transactions dropped by 35.7% QoQ to 2,900, while the total quarterly trading volume fell by 41.9% QoQ to $46.2 million.  This downward trend aligned with the broader market, as even blue-chip collection floor prices declined in 2023.  Notably, NFT sales volume remained concentrated primarily in jpg.store, which dominated the marketplace with a 98% market share. Nevertheless, unique buyers continued to drive NFT activity, while a relatively small number of sellers catered to this larger pool of buyers. Messari further highlights that Cardano&#8217;s ecosystem showcased expansion in multiple sectors, particularly in DeFi. Protocols for swaps, stablecoins, synthetics, and unique Cardano-centric services like lending staking power surfaced alongside the incumbents.  Related Reading: Shiba Inu (SHIB) Rides On Bullish Waves As Shibarium Launch Nears, Buy Now? Cardano&#8217;s second quarter showed substantial growth and diversification across various sectors, including DeFi, NFTs, and Layer-2 solutions.  Key statistics revealed a surge in stablecoin value, a shift in TVL dominance towards newer projects, and an impressive increase in average daily dapp transactions.  While NFT metrics experienced a decline, the ecosystem demonstrated resilience and competition among protocols.  In contrast, Cardano&#8217;s native token, ADA, has been experiencing a decline in line with the broader market trend since April 15, after reaching its yearly peak of $0.4620. ADA is trading at $0.2933, reflecting a 1.4% decrease in the past 24 hours. Over the last fourteen days, it has declined nearly 6%. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cardano (ADA), the blockchain platform renowned for its scalability and technological approach, has made significant strides in the crypto market, as highlighted by the recently released Messari <a href="https://messari.io/report/cardano-ecosystem-analysis-q2-2023" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a>. </p>
<p>The report provides valuable insights into Cardano&#8217;s achievements in Q2 2023, solidifying its position as a prominent player within the industry. </p>
<p>With a strong focus on fostering a robust ecosystem and pushing the boundaries of decentralized finance (DeFi) and non-fungible tokens (NFTs), Cardano is poised to reshape the landscape of blockchain technology, according to Messari. </p>
<h2>Cardano TVL Ranking Skyrockets, Climbs From 34th to 21st</h2>
<p>Per the report, Cardano experienced substantial growth in stablecoin value, with a 34.9% quarter-over-quarter (QoQ) increase and a significant 382.1% year-to-date (YTD) surge. </p>
<p>Indigo Protocol emerged as a frontrunner in stablecoin and synthetic asset issuance, solidifying its dominance in the space. Furthermore, the Total Value Locked (TVL) witnessed a shift towards newer projects, as protocols created in the past six months accounted for 47.4% of TVL dominance in Q2. </p>

<p>The TVL in USD rose by 9.7% QoQ and 198.6% YTD. Cardano&#8217;s TVL ranking climbed from 34th to 21st across all chains in 2023.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-546948 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot_39.jpg?w=850&#038;resize=850%2C406" alt="Cardano" width="850" height="406" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot_39.jpg?w=850&#038;resize=850%2C406 850w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot_39.jpg?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot_39.jpg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot_39.jpg?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>On the other hand, average daily decentralized application (dapp) transactions on Cardano surged by 49% QoQ, marking the third consecutive quarterly increase. Moreover, Minswap, an automated market maker (AMM), showcased the largest absolute growth in transaction volume. </p>
<p>However, several new dapps also contributed to the overall surge. Minswap&#8217;s popularity soared in Q2, surpassing the leading NFT marketplace jpg.store regarding dapp transactions. </p>
<p>This trend aligned with the sectoral shift, as DeFi activity gained momentum while NFT activity experienced a decline. The overall increase in dapp transactions reached a substantial 49.0% QoQ, averaging 57,900 daily transactions.</p>
<h2>Q2 NFT Metrics Reflect Market Correction</h2>
<p>According to Messari, NFT metrics experienced a decline in Q2. Average daily NFT transactions dropped by 35.7% QoQ to 2,900, while the total quarterly trading volume fell by 41.9% QoQ to $46.2 million. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-546947" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot_40.jpg?w=846&#038;resize=846%2C423" alt="Cardano " width="846" height="423" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot_40.jpg?w=846&#038;resize=846%2C423 846w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot_40.jpg?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot_40.jpg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot_40.jpg?w=360 360w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot_40.jpg?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 846px) 100vw, 846px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>This downward trend aligned with the broader market, as even blue-chip collection floor prices declined in 2023. </p>
<p>Notably, NFT sales volume remained concentrated primarily in jpg.store, which dominated the marketplace with a 98% market share. Nevertheless, unique buyers continued to drive NFT activity, while a relatively small number of sellers catered to this larger pool of buyers.</p>
<p>Messari further highlights that Cardano&#8217;s ecosystem showcased expansion in multiple sectors, particularly in DeFi. Protocols for swaps, stablecoins, synthetics, and unique Cardano-centric services like lending staking power surfaced alongside the incumbents. </p>

<p>Cardano&#8217;s second quarter showed substantial growth and diversification across various sectors, including DeFi, NFTs, and Layer-2 solutions. </p>
<p>Key statistics revealed a surge in stablecoin value, a shift in TVL dominance towards newer projects, and an impressive increase in average daily dapp transactions. </p>
<p>While NFT metrics experienced a decline, the ecosystem demonstrated resilience and competition among protocols. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/DhUk63sa/" alt="Cardano " width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>In contrast, Cardano&#8217;s native token, ADA, has been experiencing a decline in line with the broader market trend since April 15, after reaching its yearly peak of $0.4620.</p>
<p>ADA is trading at $0.2933, reflecting a 1.4% decrease in the past 24 hours. Over the last fourteen days, it has declined nearly 6%.</p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Downloader.la-64d6961d9edbd.jpg?fit=460%2C188" width="460" height="188" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546945</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
