<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 20:55:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ethereum Reaches New Three-Week High Above $1,300, But Will Rally Last?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-reaches-new-three-week-high/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 23:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[whales]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515375</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum, just like bitcoin, saw a relief rally that pushed its price to a new three-week high. The digital asset is now trading above $1,300 for the first time since mid-December 2021, and so far, has been able to hold its gains in the market. However, not everyone is betting on the continued growth of the cryptocurrency, which could end up being a deterrent to further upside for the digital asset. Ethereum Whales Go Short Chinese journalist Colin Wu, popularly known as Wu Blockchain on Twitter posted a screenshot that showed that ethereum whales were still very bearish on the digital asset. For one, there were 26,000 put options for the cryptocurrency at a strike price of $400. This is a more than 200% decrease from the current price of the asset. Related Reading: Solana’s BONK Crashes 50% In 24 Hours, Is It Time To Get Out? The traders were placed on Saturday, December 7, according to the photo, showing a high conviction of an expected price drawdown in the coming months. These options were also set to expire on June 30, giving them a five-month runway to hit this price. Recently, there has been a large order of 26,000 ETH put options with a strike price of $400 and an expiration date of Jun 30. Some traders believe this is the tail management behavior of crypto whales. According to @Blofin_Official pic.twitter.com/VmYC44939h &#8212; Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) January 7, 2023 Ethereum’s price has already seen a recovery since this trade was placed. But with such a long runway and the expected sell pressure to come from the Shanghai upgrade and withdrawal capabilities for staked ETH, it still remains a possibility that the digital asset would hit this price. ETH at $1,319 &#124; Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com Not Everyone Is Bearish On ETH  Despite such a large put position on a potential descent of atheneum’s price, not everyone is bearish on the asset. One Chinese miner Jiang Zhuoer took to social media to share his bullish executions of the cryptocurrency. Zhuoer says he expects ETH to lead the market bull run of 2023. In fact, the miner explains that ETH will actually begin to move before BTC. He also predicts that ethereum will soon break out of its six-month-long consolidation soon. 11/ I expect #Ethereum (ETH) to start rising earlier than #Bitcoin (BTC) as the leader of the next bull market. This should occur between March and May 2023, the ETH price woule be permanently out of the current bottom range. &#8212; Jiang Zhuoer BTC.TOP (@JiangZhuoer) January 9, 2023 As for ETH, the digital asset has fared well as the new week rolls around. It is already up 3.80% in the last day, and its gains on the 7-day chart have risen above 8%. This price increase sees it trading currently at a price of $1,311 with indicators pointing toward more upside, at least for the short term, as it moves above its 50-day moving average. Related Reading: Cardano Whales Start 2023 With Accumulation Trend That Could Be Bullish For ADA The next significant resistance now sits at $1,350 where bears are making their stand once more. This was also the local peak before the December 14 market crash, so this is an important point to beat if ETH is to see more gains. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from Reuters, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Ethereum, just like bitcoin, saw a relief rally that pushed its price to a new three-week high. The digital asset is now trading above $1,300 for the first time since mid-December 2021, and so far, has been able to hold its gains in the market. However, not everyone is betting on the continued growth of the cryptocurrency, which could end up being a deterrent to further upside for the digital asset.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Ethereum Whales Go Short</h2>
<p class="p2">Chinese journalist Colin Wu, popularly known as Wu Blockchain on Twitter posted a screenshot that showed that ethereum whales were still very bearish on the digital asset. For one, there were 26,000 put options for the cryptocurrency at a strike price of $400. This is a more than 200% decrease from the current price of the asset.</p>

<p class="p2">The traders were placed on Saturday, December 7, according to the photo, showing a high conviction of an expected price drawdown in the coming months. These options were also set to expire on June 30, giving them a five-month runway to hit this price.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Recently, there has been a large order of 26,000 ETH put options with a strike price of $400 and an expiration date of Jun 30. Some traders believe this is the tail management behavior of crypto whales. According to <a href="https://twitter.com/Blofin_Official?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@Blofin_Official</a> <a href="https://t.co/VmYC44939h" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/VmYC44939h</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1611642723299364867?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 7, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p class="p2">Ethereum’s price has already seen a recovery since this trade was placed. But with such a long runway and the expected sell pressure to come from the Shanghai upgrade and withdrawal capabilities for staked ETH, it still remains a possibility that the digital asset would hit this price.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/JGXxSwZr/" alt="Ethereum (ETH) price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1646" /></p>

<h2 class="p2">Not Everyone Is Bearish On ETH </h2>
<p class="p2">Despite such a large put position on a potential descent of atheneum’s price, not everyone is bearish on the asset. One Chinese miner Jiang Zhuoer took to social media to <a href="https://twitter.com/JiangZhuoer/status/1612354771809374215?s=20&amp;t=e7-bfBfMVWedXfyGCG0xUw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">share</a> his bullish executions of the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p class="p2">Zhuoer says he expects ETH to lead the market bull run of 2023. In fact, the miner explains that ETH will actually begin to move before BTC. He also predicts that ethereum will soon break out of its six-month-long consolidation soon.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">11/  I expect <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Ethereum?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#Ethereum</a> (ETH) to start rising earlier than <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#Bitcoin</a> (BTC) as the leader of the next bull market. This should occur between March and May 2023, the ETH price woule be permanently out of the current bottom range.</p>
<p>&mdash; Jiang Zhuoer BTC.TOP (@JiangZhuoer) <a href="https://twitter.com/JiangZhuoer/status/1612354771809374215?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 9, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p class="p2">As for ETH, the digital asset has fared well as the new week rolls around. It is already up 3.80% in the last day, and its gains on the 7-day chart have risen above 8%. This price increase sees it trading currently at a price of $1,311 with indicators pointing toward more upside, at least for the short term, as it moves above its 50-day moving average.</p>

<p class="p2">The next significant resistance now sits at $1,350 where bears are making their stand once more. This was also the local peak before the December 14 market crash, so this is an important point to beat if ETH is to see more gains.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-460x295.jpeg" width="460" height="295" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why GALA&#8217;s 190% Rally May Be Just Getting Started</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/why-gala-190-rally-may-be-just-getting-started/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 20:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GALA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GALAUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Metaverse]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515451</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GALA, the native token of the non-fungible token (NFT) gaming project, has recently seen significant bullish price action. The token moved independently during these periods, with larger cryptocurrencies barely catching up on this massive rally. Related Reading: This Sub-$1 Billion Crypto Is Leading Market Gains, Here’s The Reason As of this writing, GALA’s price trades at $0.04 with a 16% profit in the last 24 hours. Since late December 2022, the token has recorded a 194% rally and stands amongst the best-performing digital assets in the sector. Is the rally sustainable, or will the token retrace on its recent gains? GALA With More Room To Grow Data from analytics firm Santiment indicates that GALA was able to trend to the upside due to a spike in on-chain activity. An increase in whale activity supported the token’s price action and allowed it to push beyond resistance at $0.048. The last time GALA saw its current levels was in Q4, 2022. At that time, the cryptocurrency crashed behind a market-wide downtrend. The chart below shows that the spike in activity preceded the rally and suggests further appreciation. Santiment noted: Amongst the many surging altcoins in 2023, $GALA has been making a tremendous run. The price of the #Ethereum-based asset is up +194% since December 30th, and has exceed $0.048 for the first time since mid-September, backed by big whale transactions. Further data provided by Santiment indicate that GALA’s upside move was supported by negative overall market sentiment. As digital assets trended to the upside, sentiment went to a bearish extreme and hinted at a bounce to squeeze short positions. Santiment added: Altcoins have continued aggressively pumping throughout the weekend. As we have seen time and time again, markets move in the direction of the crowd&#8217;s unlikeliest expectation. NFT Gaming And Metaverse With Strong Long-Term Fundamentals The mini-altcoin season will continue if investors allocate capital to the NFT gaming and Metaverse sector. Coingecko records appreciation for similar projects, such as Decentraland (40%+), and The Sandbox (34%), in the previous seven days. In addition, at the Consumer Electronics Shows (CES) 2023, several companies and providers announced their Metaverse-related products. The sector has created much buzz in major markets and is likely to continue seeing interest from investors. Related Reading: Is The Bitcoin Bottom In Yet? Here’s What aSOPR Metric Suggests According to the CEO of OVR Technology, Aaron Wisniewski, the Metaverse is here to stay. Crypto and GALA are bound to operate a critical components for this sector. Wisniewski said: We are entering an era in which extended reality will drive commerce, entertainment, education, social connection, and wellbeing. The quality of these experiences will be measured by how immersive and emotionally engaging they are. Scent imbues them with an unmatched power.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>GALA, the native token of the non-fungible token (NFT) gaming project, has recently seen significant bullish price action. The token moved independently during these periods, with larger cryptocurrencies barely catching up on this massive rally. </strong></p>

<p>As of this writing, GALA’s price trades at $0.04 with a 16% profit in the last 24 hours. Since late December 2022, the token has recorded a 194% rally and stands amongst the best-performing digital assets in the sector. Is the rally sustainable, or will the token retrace on its recent gains?</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-515462 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GALA-GALAUSDT-860x376.png" alt="GALA GALAUSDT" width="860" height="376" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GALA-GALAUSDT-860x376.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GALA-GALAUSDT-460x201.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GALA-GALAUSDT-768x336.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GALA-GALAUSDT-1536x671.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GALA-GALAUSDT-750x328.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GALA-GALAUSDT-1140x498.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GALA-GALAUSDT.png 1814w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<h2>GALA With More Room To Grow</h2>
<p>Data from analytics firm Santiment <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1612516028516569088" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">indicates</a> that GALA was able to trend to the upside due to a spike in on-chain activity. An increase in whale activity supported the token’s price action and allowed it to push beyond resistance at $0.048.</p>
<p>The last time GALA saw its current levels was in Q4, 2022. At that time, the cryptocurrency crashed behind a market-wide downtrend. The chart below shows that the spike in activity preceded the rally and suggests further appreciation. Santiment noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>Amongst the many surging altcoins in 2023, $GALA has been making a tremendous run. The price of the #Ethereum-based asset is up +194% since December 30th, and has exceed $0.048 for the first time since mid-September, backed by big whale transactions.</p></blockquote>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-515461 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GALA-GALAUSDT-Chart-2-860x559.jpeg" alt="GALA GALAUSDT Chart 2" width="860" height="559" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GALA-GALAUSDT-Chart-2-860x559.jpeg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GALA-GALAUSDT-Chart-2-460x299.jpeg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GALA-GALAUSDT-Chart-2-768x500.jpeg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GALA-GALAUSDT-Chart-2-1536x999.jpeg 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GALA-GALAUSDT-Chart-2-2048x1332.jpeg 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GALA-GALAUSDT-Chart-2-750x488.jpeg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GALA-GALAUSDT-Chart-2-1140x742.jpeg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>Further data provided by Santiment indicate that GALA’s upside move was supported by negative overall market sentiment. As digital assets trended to the upside, sentiment went to a bearish extreme and hinted at a bounce to squeeze short positions. Santiment <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1612340270422700034?s=20&amp;t=QiBHWs457G3gf_AaagE12Q" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">added</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>Altcoins have continued aggressively pumping throughout the weekend. As we have seen time and time again, markets move in the direction of the crowd&#8217;s unlikeliest expectation.</p></blockquote>
NFT Gaming And Metaverse With Strong Long-Term Fundamentals
<p>The mini-altcoin season will continue if investors allocate capital to the NFT gaming and Metaverse sector. Coingecko records appreciation for similar projects, such as Decentraland (40%+), and The Sandbox (34%), in the previous seven days.</p>
<p>In addition, at the<a href="https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/ces-2023-smelling-touching-center-stage-metaverse-96296236" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> Consumer Electronics Shows (CES) 2023, several companies and providers announced their Metaverse-related products</a>. The sector has created much buzz in major markets and is likely to continue seeing interest from investors.</p>

<p>According to the CEO of OVR Technology, Aaron Wisniewski, the Metaverse is here to stay. Crypto and GALA are bound to operate a critical components for this sector. Wisniewski said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We are entering an era in which extended reality will drive commerce, entertainment, education, social connection, and wellbeing. The quality of these experiences will be measured by how immersive and emotionally engaging they are. Scent imbues them with an unmatched power.</p></blockquote>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GALA-GALAUSDT-Crypto-NFTs-NFT-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is The Bitcoin Bottom In Yet? Here&#8217;s What aSOPR Metric Suggests</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-bottom-yet-asopr-metric-suggests/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 19:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin aSOPR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin bear market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bottom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515401</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A quant has explained using past trends of the Bitcoin adjusted Spent Output Profit Ratio (aSOPR) whether the current cycle has yet met all the bottom conditions. Bitcoin aSOPR EMAs Are Approaching Golden Cross As an analyst in a CryptoQuant post explained, the aSOPR EMAs are looking to form a golden cross soon. The &#8220;Spent Output Profit Ratio&#8221; (SOPR) indicates whether the average Bitcoin investor is selling at a profit or at a loss right now. The &#8220;Adjusted SOPR&#8221; (aSOPR) is a modified version of this metric that excludes from the data all selling done within an hour of first purchasing the coins. The advantage of doing this is that such short-term transactions are noise in the data and, thus, don&#8217;t have any significant implications on the market. When the value of this indicator is greater than 1, it means the holders are selling coins at some profit right now. On the other hand, values below the threshold suggest the overall market realizes some loss at the moment. Related Reading: This Week In Bitcoin And Crypto: Key Dates To Watch Naturally, the aSOPR being exactly equal to 1 implies that the investors are just breaking even on their current selling. Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin aSOPR, as well as its 50-day and 100-day exponential moving averages (EMAs) during the 2014-2015 and 2018-2019 bear markets: The trends in the metric during the previous bear market bottoms &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As shown in the above graph, the quant marked the relevant zones for the indicator in the previous two cycles. It looks like the aSOPR hit bottom values below one and then caught an overall uptrend as the price of Bitcoin itself bottomed out in both cycles. The indicator hitting low levels under one like this suggests that the investors heavily capitulated then, which detoxed the market from weak hands and hence helped the price finally bottom out. Also, in both these bear markets, the 100-day EMA declined to the same lowest level (as represented by the lower dotted line in the chart) and rebounded back from it as this bottoming process took place. It also seems like a return to a bullish trend started with a golden cross of the two EMAs, with the 50-day crossing back above the 100-day. Related Reading: Ethereum 1-Month Realized Volatility Drops To Rare Level Seen Only Thrice In History Now, here is a chart that displays how the aSOPR and its EMAs are looking in the current cycle so far: The value of the metric seems to have been climbing recently &#124; Source: CryptoQuant The chart shows that the same pattern of the Bitcoin aSOPR forming a bottom and then catching an overall uptrend has already appeared for the current cycle. The two EMAs are also looking on track to complete the golden cross soon. However, the analyst has pointed out that the 100-day EMA is yet to touch the dotted level in this cycle. The period spent so far in the recovery of the metric (the uptrend from the bottom) has also been only about half of what previous cycles saw (the yellow bars). Based on this, the quant believes there could still be one more drop in the price left, before these conditions are fulfilled and the real bottom is in. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $17,200, up 3% in the last week. Looks like BTC has sharply surged &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Dmitry Demidko on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A quant has explained using past trends of the Bitcoin adjusted Spent Output Profit Ratio (aSOPR) whether the current cycle has yet met all the bottom conditions.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin aSOPR EMAs Are Approaching Golden Cross</h2>
<p>As an analyst in a CryptoQuant post explained, the aSOPR EMAs are looking to form a golden cross soon. The &#8220;<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-30-long-term-holder-sopr-bottom-values/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Spent Output Profit Ratio</a>&#8221; (SOPR) indicates whether the average Bitcoin investor is selling at a profit or at a loss right now.</p>
<p>The &#8220;<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-capitulation-asopr-plunges-dec-2018-lows/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Adjusted SOPR</a>&#8221; (aSOPR) is a modified version of this metric that excludes from the data all selling done within an hour of first purchasing the coins. The advantage of doing this is that such short-term transactions are noise in the data and, thus, don&#8217;t have any significant implications on the market.</p>
<p>When the value of this indicator is greater than 1, it means the holders are selling coins at some profit right now. On the other hand, values below the threshold suggest the overall market realizes some loss at the moment.</p>

<p>Naturally, the aSOPR being exactly equal to 1 implies that the investors are just breaking even on their current selling. Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin aSOPR, as well as its 50-day and 100-day exponential moving averages (EMAs) during the 2014-2015 and 2018-2019 bear markets:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/405217/quicktake/dCHQv80_88a5d4f503b26504ed25f8cf38a0b97ddfd234c4f024896a96a3fa363de0660b.png" alt="Bitcoin aSOPR" width="1280" height="545" /></p>

<p>As shown in the above graph, the quant marked the relevant zones for the indicator in the previous two cycles. It looks like the aSOPR hit bottom values below one and then caught an overall uptrend as the price of Bitcoin itself bottomed out in both cycles. The indicator hitting low levels under one like this suggests that the investors heavily capitulated then, which detoxed the market from weak hands and hence helped the price finally bottom out.</p>
<p>Also, in both these bear markets, the 100-day EMA declined to the same lowest level (as represented by the lower dotted line in the chart) and rebounded back from it as this bottoming process took place. It also seems like a return to a bullish trend started with a golden cross of the two EMAs, with the 50-day crossing back above the 100-day.</p>

<p>Now, here is a chart that displays how the aSOPR and its EMAs are looking in the current cycle so far:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/405217/quicktake/SFFbc8aFG_4c468b3b16999fd9578189576d5f770cb4a16ad9fca0e798a251f00a54a87c5d.png" alt="Bitcoin Bear Market aSOPR" width="1280" height="548" /></p>

<p>The chart shows that the same pattern of the Bitcoin aSOPR forming a bottom and then catching an overall uptrend has already appeared for the current cycle. The two EMAs are also looking on track to complete the golden cross soon.</p>
<p>However, the analyst has pointed out that the 100-day EMA is yet to touch the dotted level in this cycle. The period spent so far in the recovery of the metric (the uptrend from the bottom) has also been only about half of what previous cycles saw (the yellow bars).</p>
<p>Based on this, the quant believes there could still be one more drop in the price left, before these conditions are fulfilled and the real <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-exchange-transaction-4-low-bottom/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bottom</a> is in.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $17,200, up 3% in the last week.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-515440 size-large aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-11-860x483.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="860" height="483" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-11-860x483.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-11-460x258.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-11-768x431.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-11-750x421.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-11.png 971w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/dmitry-demidko-OG3A-ilG8AY-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Sub-$1 Billion Crypto Is Leading Market Gains, Here’s The Reason</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/altcoin/sub-1-billion-crypto-leads-gains/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GALA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GALA Films]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GALA performance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GALA price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GALAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GALAUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515376</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The crypto market is in another full recovery mode and bitcoin has since crossed the elusive $17,000 price level. However, while the largest digital assets in the space are seeing a lot of green, one underdog is taking the space by storm. GALA is right at the top of the list of gainers for the past 24 hours, surpassing second-place Zilliqa (ZIL) by a considerable margin. Why Is GALA Pumping So Much? In the early hours of Monday, Gala Games took to Twitter to announce a new partnership. The blockchain gaming company which had been working on its film projects revealed that it had gotten movie stars Dwayne “The Rock” Johnson and Mark Wahlberg to star in its film. But this was not the only bullish development of the company. Related Reading: Cardano Whales Start 2023 With Accumulation Trend That Could Be Bullish For ADA Another revelation from the Twitter post was that moviegoers would be able to scan a QR code on a purchased ticket to claim a digital item that is being sold on different marketplaces. Furthermore, Gala Games also put another use case where QR codes could pop up to claim an item while viewers were watching a movie on a streaming platform such as Netflix. “That item has been selling on OpenSea so why wouldn’t you at least take a look?” the announcement said. The GALA token fits into all of this by being the gas token of Gala Film, which is the blockchain that powers the film arm. These items from the movies are not limited to Gala users, so individuals who want to claim items from the scanned QR codes will need to purchase GALA tokens to use as gas fees; therefore increasing the demand for the cryptocurrency. Just a little bit of information regarding our ongoing work with @TheRock and @markwahlberg.$GALA is the gas token in @GoGalaFilms and @GoGalaMusic as well! pic.twitter.com/u9fdXoNte1 &#8212; Gala Games (@GoGalaGames) January 9, 2023 Leading Crypto Market Gains The price of GALA has responded positively to the news of Johnson and Wahlberg working with the ecosystem. It has seen the highest gains of any digital asset over the last 24 hours, rising over 67% in this time period, more than 100% of the gains posted by ZIL (29%) which is the second-highest in the space. GALA tops list of gainers &#124; Source: Coinmarketcap It has wiped out losses from GALA over the last week and the coin is now seeing gains above 114% in the 7-day period. Interestingly, this is a digital asset with a less than $300 million market cap, but trading volume for the last day was almost $1 billion, an almost 400% increase from the previous day. Related Reading: Solana’s BONK Crashes 50% In 24 Hours, Is It Time To Get Out? GALA is currently changing hands at a price of $0.0366 at the time of this writing after being rejected at the $0.04 resistance point. This has now become the level to beat and if the bulls are able to pull above $0.04 while the trading volume remains elevated, then it will flip this to support and reach $0.045. GALA jumps 60% to $0.038 &#124; Source: GALAUSD on TradingView.com Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from Pandaily, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">The crypto market is in another full recovery mode and bitcoin has since crossed the elusive $17,000 price level. However, while the largest digital assets in the space are seeing a lot of green, one underdog is taking the space by storm. GALA is right at the top of the list of gainers for the past 24 hours, surpassing second-place Zilliqa (ZIL) by a considerable margin.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Why Is GALA Pumping So Much?</h2>
<p class="p2">In the early hours of Monday, Gala Games took to Twitter to announce a new partnership. The blockchain gaming company which had been working on its film projects revealed that it had gotten movie stars Dwayne “The Rock” Johnson and Mark Wahlberg to star in its film. But this was not the only bullish development of the company.</p>

<p class="p2">Another revelation from the Twitter post was that moviegoers would be able to scan a QR code on a purchased ticket to claim a digital item that is being sold on different marketplaces. Furthermore, Gala Games also put another use case where QR codes could pop up to claim an item while viewers were watching a movie on a streaming platform such as Netflix. “That item has been selling on OpenSea so why wouldn’t you at least take a look?” the announcement said.</p>
<p class="p2">The GALA token fits into all of this by being the gas token of Gala Film, which is the blockchain that powers the film arm. These items from the movies are not limited to Gala users, so individuals who want to claim items from the scanned QR codes will need to purchase GALA tokens to use as gas fees; therefore increasing the demand for the cryptocurrency.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Just a little bit of information regarding our ongoing work with <a href="https://twitter.com/TheRock?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@TheRock</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/markwahlberg?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@markwahlberg</a>.<a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24GALA&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$GALA</a> is the gas token in <a href="https://twitter.com/GoGalaFilms?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@GoGalaFilms</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/GoGalaMusic?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@GoGalaMusic</a> as well! <a href="https://t.co/u9fdXoNte1" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/u9fdXoNte1</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Gala Games (@GoGalaGames) <a href="https://twitter.com/GoGalaGames/status/1612299581731086337?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 9, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<h2 class="p2">Leading Crypto Market Gains</h2>
<p class="p2">The price of GALA has responded positively to the news of Johnson and Wahlberg working with the ecosystem. It has seen the <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/gainers-losers/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">highest gains of any digital asset over the last 24 hours</a>, rising over 67% in this time period, more than 100% of the gains posted by ZIL (29%) which is the second-highest in the space.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-515404 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GALA-top-gainers-460x246.png" alt="GALA top gainers" width="460" height="246" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GALA-top-gainers-460x246.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GALA-top-gainers-860x461.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GALA-top-gainers-768x411.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GALA-top-gainers-750x402.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GALA-top-gainers-1140x611.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GALA-top-gainers.png 1404w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p class="p2">It has wiped out losses from GALA over the last week and the coin is now seeing gains above 114% in the 7-day period. Interestingly, this is a digital asset with a less than $300 million market cap, but trading volume for the last day was almost $1 billion, an almost 400% increase from the previous day.</p>

<p class="p2">GALA is currently changing hands at a price of $0.0366 at the time of this writing after being rejected at the $0.04 resistance point. This has now become the level to beat and if the bulls are able to pull above $0.04 while the trading volume remains elevated, then it will flip this to support and reach $0.045.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/j7mt7NuJ/" alt="Gala price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1646" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/GALA-crypto-460x239.jpeg" width="460" height="239" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano Follows Bullish Sentiment, Why ADA Could Become Top 3 Coin</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-sentiment-ada-become-top-3-coin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515434</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) follows the market&#8217;s general sentiment and records positive price action on a low timeframe. The cryptocurrency has been trading heavily since the sector took another dive into its current levels, but there is light at the of the tunnel. Related Reading: Top 5 Crypto To Watch As CPI Data Is Released This Week Cardano (ADA) trades at $0.32, with a 12% rally in the last 24 hours. Over the previous week, the token records a 29% profit and stands as the best-performing crypto asset for this period. Other cryptocurrencies in the top 10 are seeing similar price action.  Cardano Will Take Over Higher Spots In Top 10 By Market Cap According to a pseudonym Cardano bull, the cryptocurrency is underpriced. The token has suffered along with other risks on assets due to tighter macroeconomic conditions. Despite the downside trend, ADA remained one of the largest cryptocurrencies by market capitalization.  Cardano first entered this ranking in late 2021, at the high of the previous crypto bullish cycle. At that time, the company behind its development introduced a series of improvements and rollout smart contract capabilities on the platform.  These improvements made Cardano compatible with decentralized finance (DeFi) applications and took it to the top of several metrics, including monthly contributions from developers. The ADA ecosystem bloomed.  Two weeks ago, as NewsBTC reported, there was another spike in Cardano&#8217;s on-chain activity. These metrics support ADA&#8217;s bullish thesis as they hint at seller exhaustion following a massive downtrend and substantial accumulation from mid to large investors, as seen in the chart below.  The pseudonym analyst wrote the following about ADA&#8217;s future and its potential to see further profits: (…) I believe that&#8217;s where it fairly belongs. Socials drive crypto value and this is the 3rd largest community, at least. The 2020-22 VC driven TPS, TVL, ponzinomics psyops are coming to an end. Cardano will assume its rightful place. ADA Out Of The Crypto Top 10 By Market Cap? On the other hand, ADA&#8217;s detractors posted their 2023 predictions for the token. Crypto personality Eric Wall forecasted that ADA would &#8220;finally drop&#8221; from the top 10 by market cap.  Related Reading: Ethereum 1-Month Realized Volatility Drops To Rare Level Seen Only Thrice In History The Cardano community rejected the prediction; some believe ADA will exit the general group and enter the top 3, thus fulfilling the prophecy. While others have different expectations and, while bullish on ADA, acknowledge the ranking fluctuations. One User wrote: Can&#8217;t pretend it&#8217;s not possible (for Cardano to exit the top 10). Perfect storm of Elon tweets some crap about doge, polygon partners with meta, sol VCs decide to pump all at the same time. Insurance is that the same people shorting ADA seem to also be shorting sol, so they both go up with a squeeze.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Cardano (ADA) follows the market&#8217;s general sentiment and records positive price action on a low timeframe. The cryptocurrency has been trading heavily since the sector took another dive into its current levels, but there is light at the of the tunnel.</strong></p>

<p>Cardano (ADA) trades at $0.32, with a 12% rally in the last 24 hours. Over the previous week, the token records a 29% profit and stands as the best-performing crypto asset for this period. Other cryptocurrencies in the top 10 are seeing similar price action. </p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-515444 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-ADAUSDT-860x376.png" alt="Cardano ADA ADAUSDT" width="860" height="376" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-ADAUSDT-860x376.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-ADAUSDT-460x201.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-ADAUSDT-768x336.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-ADAUSDT-1536x671.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-ADAUSDT-750x328.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-ADAUSDT-1140x498.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-ADAUSDT.png 1814w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<h2>Cardano Will Take Over Higher Spots In Top 10 By Market Cap</h2>
<p>According to a pseudonym Cardano bull, the cryptocurrency is underpriced. The token has suffered along with other risks on assets due to tighter macroeconomic conditions. Despite the downside trend, ADA remained one of the largest cryptocurrencies by market capitalization. </p>
<p>Cardano first entered this ranking in late 2021, at the high of the previous crypto bullish cycle. At that time, the company behind its development introduced a series of improvements and rollout smart contract capabilities on the platform. </p>
<p>These improvements made Cardano compatible with decentralized finance (DeFi) applications and took it to the top of several metrics, including monthly contributions from developers. The ADA ecosystem bloomed. </p>
<p>Two weeks ago, as NewsBTC <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-ada-undervalued-on-chain-data/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a>, there was another spike in Cardano&#8217;s on-chain activity. These metrics support ADA&#8217;s bullish thesis as they hint at seller exhaustion following a massive downtrend and substantial accumulation from mid to large investors, as seen in the chart below. </p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-513981 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Cardano-ADA-11.23.52-28-Dec-2022-860x291.png" alt="Cardano (ADA) Santiment" width="860" height="291" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Cardano-ADA-11.23.52-28-Dec-2022-860x291.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Cardano-ADA-11.23.52-28-Dec-2022-460x156.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Cardano-ADA-11.23.52-28-Dec-2022-768x260.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Cardano-ADA-11.23.52-28-Dec-2022-1536x520.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Cardano-ADA-11.23.52-28-Dec-2022-2048x693.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Cardano-ADA-11.23.52-28-Dec-2022-750x254.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Cardano-ADA-11.23.52-28-Dec-2022-1140x386.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>The pseudonym analyst <a href="https://mobile.twitter.com/cardano_whale/status/1612254868546392064" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">wrote</a> the following about ADA&#8217;s future and its potential to see further profits:</p>
<blockquote><p>(…) I believe that&#8217;s where it fairly belongs. Socials drive crypto value and this is the 3rd largest community, at least. The 2020-22 VC driven TPS, TVL, ponzinomics psyops are coming to an end. Cardano will assume its rightful place.</p></blockquote>
ADA Out Of The Crypto Top 10 By Market Cap?
<p>On the other hand, ADA&#8217;s detractors posted their 2023 predictions for the token. Crypto personality Eric Wall forecasted that ADA would &#8220;finally drop&#8221; from the top 10 by market cap. </p>

<p>The Cardano community rejected the prediction; some believe ADA will exit the general group and enter the top 3, thus fulfilling the prophecy. While others have different expectations and, while bullish on ADA, acknowledge the ranking fluctuations. One User <a href="https://twitter.com/TrevorMundane/status/1612376646564151297?s=20&amp;t=bgf9QhNWMl61dJLDJqIoQg" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">wrote</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>Can&#8217;t pretend it&#8217;s not possible (for Cardano to exit the top 10). Perfect storm of Elon tweets some crap about doge, polygon partners with meta, sol VCs decide to pump all at the same time. Insurance is that the same people shorting ADA seem to also be shorting sol, so they both go up with a squeeze.</p></blockquote>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/traxer-jz6mrH9lnt0-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top 5 Crypto To Watch As CPI Data Is Released This Week</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/top-5-crypto-to-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sol]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515436</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The crypto market has been very bullish in the past week as the turn of the year sparked positive investor sentiment for the industry, especially to our top 5 crypto to watch this week. Since January 1st, the total market cap of crypto rose by 8.25% which shows a complete reversal of investor sentiment on the market.  As market optimism grows for an economic soft landing, crypto is poised for a recovery after a year of complete disaster. The market was devastated after multiple high-profile collapses, leaving investors as the biggest losers and driving fear, uncertainty, and doubt higher. The broader financial market is eyeing the release of the Consumer Price Index (CPI) data for December. These Are The Top 5 Crypto To Watch This Week:  Litecoin (LTC)  The ol’ reliable token of the crypto world, this altcoin recently recorded its 140 millionth transaction. Litecoin accomplished that with nearly a 100% uptime, which is a rare occurrence in an era of smart contract providers.  The altcoin is also growing in adoption with LTC gaining traction as a means for payment. With this in mind, LTC would definitely have a strong and significant role once the bear market cycle starts.  At the current price of $81.92, the token will have a significant part in the next bull market. However, if macroeconomic data trends down or stagnate, LTC will definitely have a tough time climbing back up. Shiba Inu. Image: WBUR Shiba Inu (SHIB) The original rival to Dogecoin (DOGE), this memecoin has grown in popularity and utility and makes it to our top 5 crypto list. The Shiba Inu community is also trying to distance itself from its memecoin origins which is more apparent as one reads the details of the Shibarium upgrade.  At the current market market price of $0.00000887, SHIB has some wiggle room for growth as Shibarium’s launch nears. But investors and traders should pay attention to macroeconomic trends because of the token’s high correlation with Bitcon and Ethereum.  Related Reading: IMX Spikes 10% In Last 24 Hours – Will It Start The Week Strong? Polygon (MATIC) Polygon&#8217;s native token MATIC has been pumping in price since Mastercard announced its partnership with the ecosystem for its Web3 Artist Acceleration Program. Recent migrations of y00ts and DeGods would also contribute to this bullish action.  With MATIC trading at $0.865, any good development macro-wise would mean big gains for the token’s investors and traders.  Image: Cryptocurrency News Bitcoin (BTC) Of course, Bitcoin will always be in the top 5 crypto roster. As Bitcoin stands at $17,252, the king crypto leads the charge for recovery against the bear market. BTC holders are especially bullish on the 4-year cycle that the top cryptocurrency followed during past bear markets.  Although the token lost its status as an alternative to gold, the coin breaking the $17k resistance is a significantly bullish signal for investors and traders to watch for. With Bitcoin being correlated with almost the entire crypto market, any movements by BTC would mean gains or losses for the entire market.  Related Reading: Dogecoin (DOGE) Is Now 4th Most Popular Cryptocurrency On BitPay Crypto total market cap finally breaches the $700 billion mark and now at $811 billion on the weekend chart &#124; Chart: TradingView.com Solana (SOL) SOL has been hit hard by the bear market of 2022. With the token down 88% year-to-date, the ecosystem might seem dead to some people. However, with the release of Bonk, SOL has been going up in the past week and rounds up the top 5 crypto list for today.  Bonk is the new memecoin that created buzz around it as it pumped by 1,600% in the past week. This led to a spike in network activity, thus pushing the price of Solana upwards as well. But with Bonk’s big pump, a correction might also hurt SOL.  As of writing, SOL’s price of $16.43 would definitely experience pain if macro trends stagnate or remain bearish.  -Featured image: Built In]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto market has been very bullish in the past week as the turn of the year sparked positive investor sentiment for the industry, especially to our top 5 crypto to watch this week.</p>
<p>Since January 1st, the <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/chart/Hn7IK90F/?symbol=CRYPTOCAP%3ATOTAL" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">total market cap</a> of crypto rose by 8.25% which shows a complete reversal of investor sentiment on the market. </p>
<p>As market optimism <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/us-likely-headed-for-economic-soft-landing-white-houses-boushey/ar-AA163Jw0" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">grows</a> for an economic soft landing, crypto is poised for a recovery after a year of complete disaster. </p>
<p>The market was devastated after multiple <a href="https://www.bing.com/ck/a?!&amp;&amp;p=37c3e95c99f32e0bJmltdHM9MTY3MzIyMjQwMCZpZ3VpZD0wMDcxNGJlNS0zYzkwLTYyNWUtMjNhNC01OTc3M2Q5MTYzOTImaW5zaWQ9NTE4NA&amp;ptn=3&amp;hsh=3&amp;fclid=00714be5-3c90-625e-23a4-59773d916392&amp;u=a1aHR0cHM6Ly90YWxrbWFya2V0cy5jb20vY29udGVudC9maW5hbmNpYWwvY3J5cHRvLWNvbGxhcHNlLTUtbWFqb3ItY3J5cHRvLWZpcm1zLXRoYXQtYml0LXRoZS1kdXN0LWluLTIwMjI_cG9zdD0zNjE5ODA&amp;ntb=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">high-profile collapses</a>, leaving investors as the <a href="https://www.foxbusiness.com/markets/ftx-smallest-investors-biggest-losers-crypto-collapse" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">biggest losers</a> and driving fear, uncertainty, and doubt higher.</p>
<p>The broader financial market is eyeing the release of the Consumer Price Index (CPI) data for December.</p>
<h2><strong>These Are The Top 5 Crypto To Watch This Week: </strong></h2>
<h2><strong>Litecoin (LTC) </strong></h2>
<p>The ol’ reliable token of the crypto world, this altcoin recently recorded its <a href="https://twitter.com/LTCFoundation/status/1611779694126587904?s=20&amp;t=zE8nQTSHkjxIw03Xsz0xPQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">140 millionth transaction</a>. Litecoin accomplished that with nearly a <a href="https://www.bing.com/ck/a?!&amp;&amp;p=fbc6234cbbd49e2cJmltdHM9MTY3MzIyMjQwMCZpZ3VpZD0wMDcxNGJlNS0zYzkwLTYyNWUtMjNhNC01OTc3M2Q5MTYzOTImaW5zaWQ9NTE3OQ&amp;ptn=3&amp;hsh=3&amp;fclid=00714be5-3c90-625e-23a4-59773d916392&amp;u=a1aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cubGF0ZXN0bHkuY29tL3NvY2lhbGx5L3RlY2hub2xvZ3kvbGl0ZWNvaW4taXMtdGhlLWxvbmdlc3QtcnVubmluZy1jcnlwdG9jdXJyZW5jeS13aXRoLTEwMC11cHRpbWUtbGF0ZXN0LXR3ZWV0LWJ5LWxpdGVjb2luLTM4OTg0MTEuaHRtbA&amp;ntb=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">100% uptime</a>, which is a rare occurrence in an era of <a href="https://www.bing.com/ck/a?!&amp;&amp;p=932702494141ae7bJmltdHM9MTY3MzIyMjQwMCZpZ3VpZD0wMDcxNGJlNS0zYzkwLTYyNWUtMjNhNC01OTc3M2Q5MTYzOTImaW5zaWQ9NTE1OQ&amp;ptn=3&amp;hsh=3&amp;fclid=00714be5-3c90-625e-23a4-59773d916392&amp;u=a1aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuc2VjdXJpdGllcy5pby9zb2xhbmEtaXMtY2FydmluZy1hLXJlcHV0YXRpb24tZm9yLWRvd250aW1lcy1zaG91bGQtaW52ZXN0b3JzLWJlLWNvbmNlcm5lZC8&amp;ntb=1" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">smart contract providers</a>. </p>
<p>The altcoin is also growing in adoption with LTC gaining traction as a <a href="https://bitpay.com/blog/litecoin-payments-on-the-rise/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">means for payment</a>. With this in mind, LTC would definitely have a strong and significant role once the bear market cycle starts. </p>
<p>At the current price of $81.92, the token will have a significant part in the next bull market. However, if macroeconomic data trends down or stagnate, LTC will definitely have a tough time climbing back up.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-199888 aligncenter" src="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Shiba-Inu-623x420.png" alt="Shiba Inu" width="623" height="420" /></p>

<strong>Shiba Inu (SHIB)</strong>
<p>The original <a href="https://www.ibtimes.com/dogecoin-vs-shiba-inu-which-better-meme-coin-3653222" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">rival</a> to Dogecoin (DOGE), this memecoin has grown in popularity and <a href="https://coinmarketbag.com/jeff-bezos-revealed-when-shiba-inu-will-hit-0-10-with-new-amazon-shib-partnership/#:~:text=Shiba%20Inu%20Coin%2C%20a%20new%20Dogecoin-inspired%20cryptocurrency%20launched,big%20win%20for%20Shiba%20Inu%20and%20its%20investors." target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">utility</a> and makes it to our top 5 crypto list. The Shiba Inu community is also trying to distance itself from its memecoin origins which is more apparent as one reads the details of the <a href="https://www.ibtimes.com/shiba-inu-team-prepares-l2-beta-roll-out-reveals-major-shibarium-feature-3654632" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Shibarium upgrade</a>. </p>
<p>At the current market market price of $0.00000887, SHIB has some wiggle room for growth as Shibarium’s launch nears. But investors and traders should pay attention to macroeconomic trends because of the token’s high correlation with Bitcon and Ethereum. </p>



<strong>Polygon (MATIC)</strong>
<p>Polygon&#8217;s native token MATIC has been <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/polygon" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">pumping</a> in price since Mastercard <a href="https://egamers.io/mastercard-launches-artist-accelerator-program-with-polygon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced</a> its partnership with the ecosystem for its Web3 Artist Acceleration Program. Recent <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/polygon-paid-top-solana-projects-y00ts-and-degods-3m-to-migrate-chains/ar-AA163OzW" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">migrations</a> of y00ts and DeGods would also contribute to this bullish action. </p>
<p>With MATIC trading at $0.865, any good development macro-wise would mean big gains for the token’s investors and traders. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-210530 aligncenter" src="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-6-630x420.png" alt="Bitcoin" width="630" height="420" /></p>

<strong>Bitcoin (BTC)</strong>
<p>Of course, Bitcoin will always be in the top 5 crypto roster. As Bitcoin stands at $17,252, the king crypto leads the charge for recovery against the bear market. BTC holders are especially bullish on the <a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1611352510731632640?s=20&amp;t=zE8nQTSHkjxIw03Xsz0xPQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">4-year cycle</a> that the top cryptocurrency followed during past bear markets. </p>
<p>Although the token <a href="https://www.bing.com/ck/a?!&amp;&amp;p=0d42907f7fcefdedJmltdHM9MTY3MzIyMjQwMCZpZ3VpZD0wMDcxNGJlNS0zYzkwLTYyNWUtMjNhNC01OTc3M2Q5MTYzOTImaW5zaWQ9NTE1Ng&amp;ptn=3&amp;hsh=3&amp;fclid=00714be5-3c90-625e-23a4-59773d916392&amp;u=a1aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuY25iYy5jb20vMjAyMi8wMi8yMy90aGUtY2FzZS1mb3ItYml0Y29pbi1hcy1kaWdpdGFsLWdvbGQtaXMtZmFsbGluZy1hcGFydC5odG1s&amp;ntb=1" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">lost</a> its status as an alternative to gold, the coin breaking the $17k resistance is a significantly bullish signal for investors and traders to watch for. </p>
<p>With Bitcoin being correlated with almost the entire crypto market, any movements by BTC would mean gains or losses for the entire market. </p>



<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/NFAXDZ5Q/" width="2047" height="916" /></p>

<strong>Solana (SOL)</strong>
<p>SOL has been hit hard by the bear market of 2022. With the token <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/solana" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">down</a> 88% year-to-date, the ecosystem might seem dead to some people. However, with the release of <a href="https://twitter.com/bonk_inu" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Bonk</a>, SOL has been going up in the past week and rounds up the top 5 crypto list for today. </p>
<p>Bonk is the new memecoin that created buzz around it as it <a href="https://www.cnbctv18.com/cryptocurrency/a-look-at-bonk-the-solana-meme-coin-thats-up-1600-over-the-last-week-15607101.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">pumped</a> by 1,600% in the past week. This led to a spike in network activity, thus pushing the price of Solana upwards as well. But with Bonk’s big pump, a correction might also hurt SOL. </p>
<p>As of writing, SOL’s price of $16.43 would definitely experience pain if macro trends stagnate or remain bearish. </p>
<p><em>-Featured image: Built In</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/top-5-460x267.png" width="460" height="267" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum 1-Month Realized Volatility Drops To Rare Level Seen Only Thrice In History</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-realized-volatility-drops-rare/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 15:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum 1-Month Realized Volatility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Realized Volatility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515351</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that Ethereum realized volatility has now declined to rare levels observed only three times before in history. Ethereum 1-Month Realized Volatility Has Plummeted To Just 39.8% As per data from the on-chain analytics firm Glassnode, the month of December 2022 was historically quiet for both Ethereum and Bitcoin. The &#8220;realized volatility&#8221; is an indicator that measures the standard deviation of daily returns from the mean for the market in question. The indicator is usually taken over a rolling window, with the one-week and one-month versions being generally the most useful timespans for it. In the context of the current discussion, the relevant metric is the one-month realized volatility. When the value of the metric is high, it means the asset&#8217;s price has been showing greater fluctuations from the average recently. Such a trend implies that the market is providing a high trading risk currently. On the other hand, low values suggest returns haven&#8217;t deviated much from the mean, and hence that the price has been stuck in stale consolidation. Related Reading: Bitcoin Exchange Depositing Transactions At 4-Year Low, Bottom Signal? Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the one-month Ethereum realized volatility over the last few years: Looks like the value of the metric has declined in recent days &#124; Source: Glassnode on Twitter As displayed in the above graph, the Ethereum one-month realized volatility has plunged to just 39.8% recently, suggesting that the past month has had very little diversity in day-to-day returns. This current level of the indicator is actually a historically low value, and as is apparent from the chart, there have only been three instances in the history of the crypto where the price has been this stable. Related Reading: This Week In Bitcoin And Crypto: Key Dates To Watch Interestingly, after each occurrence of the volatility hitting these lows, the price has made a sharp move and the indicator has jumped back up. An important example of this was back in November 2018, when the value of ETH collapsed toward the bottom of the bear market in a sudden move, after the metric had reached these rare levels. Glassnode also points out that, just like for Ethereum, the one-month realized volatility for Bitcoin has also plunged to historical lows recently, as the below chart highlights. The value of the metric seems to have hit very low values recently &#124; Source: Glassnode on Twitter As you can see above, the Bitcoin one-month realized volatility has only been lower than the current value (24.6%) a few times in the entire history of the crypto. A notable instance here was also in November 2018, where, just like ETH, BTC crashed down to form its bottom. If these historical trends are anything to consider, then the current extremely low values in the one-month volatility for Ethereum and Bitcoin could mean both the cryptos may soon see a significant spike in the metric soon, but the accompanying price move could be toward either direction. ETH Price At the time of writing, Ethereum&#8217;s price floats around $1,300, up 8% in the last week. ETH has shot up during the past day &#124; Source: ETHUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Glassnode.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows that Ethereum realized volatility has now declined to rare levels observed only three times before in history.</p>
<h2>Ethereum 1-Month Realized Volatility Has Plummeted To Just 39.8%</h2>
<p>As per data from the on-chain analytics firm <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1611553408020017155" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Glassnode</a>, the month of December 2022 was historically quiet for both Ethereum and Bitcoin. The &#8220;<a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-volatility-hits-all-time-low/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">realized volatility</a>&#8221; is an indicator that measures the standard deviation of daily returns from the mean for the market in question.</p>
<p>The indicator is usually taken over a rolling window, with the one-week and one-month versions being generally the most useful timespans for it. In the context of the current discussion, the relevant metric is the one-month realized volatility.</p>
<p>When the value of the metric is high, it means the asset&#8217;s price has been showing greater fluctuations from the average recently. Such a trend implies that the market is providing a high trading risk currently. On the other hand, low values suggest returns haven&#8217;t deviated much from the mean, and hence that the price has been stuck in stale consolidation.</p>

<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the one-month Ethereum realized volatility over the last few years:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/Fl1isLIacAEb90H?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Ethereum Realized Volatility " width="4096" height="2359" /></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the Ethereum one-month realized volatility has plunged to just 39.8% recently, suggesting that the past month has had very little diversity in day-to-day returns. This current level of the indicator is actually a historically low value, and as is apparent from the chart, there have only been three instances in the history of the crypto where the price has been this stable.</p>

<p>Interestingly, after each occurrence of the volatility hitting these lows, the price has made a sharp move and the indicator has jumped back up. An important example of this was back in <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/will-bitcoin-see-a-repeat-of-november-2018/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">November 2018</a>, when the value of ETH collapsed toward the bottom of the bear market in a sudden move, after the metric had reached these rare levels.</p>
<p>Glassnode also points out that, just like for Ethereum, the one-month realized volatility for Bitcoin has also plunged to historical lows recently, as the below chart highlights.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/Fl1iAe2aUAAORPx?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Bitcoin 1-month realized volatility" width="4096" height="2359" /></p>

<p>As you can see above, the Bitcoin one-month realized volatility has only been lower than the current value (24.6%) a few times in the entire history of the crypto. A notable instance here was also in November 2018, where, just like ETH, BTC crashed down to form its bottom.</p>
<p>If these historical trends are anything to consider, then the current extremely low values in the one-month volatility for Ethereum and Bitcoin could mean both the cryptos may soon see a significant spike in the metric soon, but the accompanying price move could be toward either direction.</p>
<h2>ETH Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-climbs-1300/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum&#8217;s price</a> floats around $1,300, up 8% in the last week.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-515362 size-large aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-10-860x482.png" alt="Ethereum Price Chart" width="860" height="482" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-10-860x482.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-10-460x258.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-10-768x430.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-10-750x420.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-10.png 975w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/kanchanara-jpsocjU9R7s-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cosmos (ATOM) Jumps Over 12% In One Day As Market Recovers</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/cosmos-atom/cosmos-jumps-12-in-one-day/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jammyhunts]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 14:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cosmos (ATOM)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ATOM ANALYSIS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ATOM PRICE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmos Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515374</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cosmos traded in a highly volatile crypto market in 2022, but 2023 is showing signs of recovery. CoinMarketCap shows that the global crypto market cap has increased in 24 hours. The trading volume of cryptocurrencies in the market has also increased within 24 hours. This data proves that there is still much global interest in cryptocurrencies. According to a poll conducted on Twitter, 53.8 % of participants see the early part of 2023 to be bullish. In contrast, 46.2% predict a bearish market trend for early 2023. However, Twitter user Neon Panda states that these predictions are speculative since crypto is complicated. Related Reading: IMX Spikes 10% In Last 24 Hours – Will It Start The Week Strong? Cosmos (ATOM), ranked number 20 on the crypto market list, has shown signs of a recovery in its price today, January 9. Cosmos has benefitted from this improved market outlook as its native token ATOM is also in the green today.  The price change in 24 hours is $1.24, a 12.34% increase. This increment reflects in the trading volume of the asset, which is up by 265.39% How Long Will Cosmos (ATOM) Ride The Bullish Trend? ATOM is currently on a bullish trend at the start of the year. The formation of longer green candles shows that the bulls have the upper hand in the market. The asset has broken out of the sideways trend and has continued to rise on the chart. Its support level of $8.441 held as the price increased. Atom will face resistance at $14.458 and $15.817. However, since these levels are below its all-time high of $44.70, it remains a possibility. The asset is trading above its 50-day and 200-day Simple Moving Averages (SMA). It implies that both the short-term and long-term sentiments are currently bullish. Also, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) is giving off similar signals with the reading at 75.87, which is in the overbought region. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) is also bullish. The MACD is above its signal line, which is a buy signal. It implies that ATOM might continue its price increase in the coming weeks without negative occurrences. However, note that if a digital asset falls by 50%, it would need to recover by 100% to return to its previous price. This feat might be complex to accomplish for altcoins. Also, investors should consider that altcoins are more volatile than large-cap cryptocurrencies like bitcoin. What Is Driving Cosmos (ATOM)’ Resurgence? Although the crypto market has shown signs of recovery, it is still largely volatile. Several factors are responsible for a price change of a digital asset in the crypto market. Cosmos (ATOM) is enjoying a price resurgence due to increased trading activity, according to data from CoinGecko. The Cosmos Network seeks to serve as a bridge connecting other blockchains to communicate seamlessly.  Also, the provision of regular upgrades on the network, such as Web3 solutions, has helped its popularity. On the Cosmos network, blog users receive regular updates about events.  Related Reading: Cardano (ADA) Up Nearly 20%, Aiming For A Higher High? Cosmos has a community with a rich following where information and communication remain a priority. Developers can also communicate and exchange ideas in the community. The network also supports up to 266 modern apps and services. With a thriving ecosystem and everyday use case, it is easy to see why the token is enjoying a resurgence. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cosmos traded in a highly volatile crypto market in 2022, but 2023 is showing signs of recovery. <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinMarketCap</a> shows that the global crypto market cap has increased in 24 hours. </p>
<p>The trading volume of cryptocurrencies in the market has also increased within 24 hours. This data proves that there is still much global interest in cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://twitter.com/CoinMarketCap/status/1608829184150994946" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">poll</a> conducted on Twitter, 53.8 % of participants see the early part of 2023 to be bullish. In contrast, 46.2% predict a bearish market trend for early 2023. However, Twitter user <a href="https://twitter.com/The_Neon_Panda/status/1480043036117766151" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Neon Panda</a> states that these predictions are speculative since crypto is complicated.</p>

<p>Cosmos (ATOM), ranked number 20 on the crypto market list, has shown signs of a recovery in its price today, January 9. Cosmos has benefitted from this improved market outlook as its native token ATOM is also <a href="https://twitter.com/The_Neon_Panda/status/1480043036117766151" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">in the green today</a>. </p>
<p>The price change in 24 hours is $1.24, a 12.34% increase. This increment reflects in the trading volume of the asset, which is up by 265.39%</p>
<h2>How Long Will Cosmos (ATOM) Ride The Bullish Trend?</h2>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/CosmosATOMDaily" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ATOM</a> is currently on a bullish trend at the start of the year. The formation of <a href="https://www.wikihow.com/Do-Technical-Analysis" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">longer green candles</a> shows that the bulls have the upper hand in the market. The asset has broken out of the sideways trend and has continued to rise on the chart.</p>
<p>Its support level of $8.441 held as the price increased. Atom will face resistance at $14.458 and $15.817. However, since these levels are below its all-time high of $44.70, it remains a possibility.</p>
<p>The asset is trading above its 50-day and 200-day <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Moving_average" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Simple Moving Averages</a> (SMA). It implies that both the short-term and long-term sentiments are currently bullish. Also, the Relative Strength Index (<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Relative_strength_index" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">RSI</a>) is giving off similar signals with the reading at 75.87, which is in the overbought region.</p>
<p>The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/MACD" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">MACD)</a> is also bullish. The MACD is above its signal line, which is a buy signal. It implies that ATOM might continue its price increase in the coming weeks without negative occurrences.</p>
<p>However, note that if a digital asset falls by 50%, it would need to recover by 100% to return to its previous price. This feat might be complex to accomplish for altcoins. Also, investors should consider that altcoins are more <a href="https://edition.cnn.com/videos/business/2022/05/15/crypto-market-volatility-stablecoins-sanchez-pkg-newday-vpx.cnn" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">volatile</a> than large-cap cryptocurrencies like bitcoin.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-515378" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ATOMUSD_2023-01-09_17-16-08.png" alt="ATOMUSD" width="856" height="538" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ATOMUSD_2023-01-09_17-16-08.png 856w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ATOMUSD_2023-01-09_17-16-08-460x289.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ATOMUSD_2023-01-09_17-16-08-768x483.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ATOMUSD_2023-01-09_17-16-08-750x471.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 856px) 100vw, 856px" />
<h2>What Is Driving Cosmos (ATOM)’ Resurgence?</h2>
<p>Although the crypto market has shown signs of recovery, it is still largely volatile. Several factors are responsible for a price change of a digital asset in the crypto market.</p>
<p>Cosmos (ATOM) is enjoying a price resurgence due to increased trading activity, according to data from <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/cosmos-hub" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a>. The Cosmos Network seeks to serve as a bridge <a href="https://v1.cosmos.network/resources/whitepaper" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">connecting other blockchains</a> to communicate seamlessly. </p>
<p>Also, the provision of regular upgrades on the network, such as <a href="https://blog.cosmos.network/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Web3 solutions</a>, has helped its popularity. On the Cosmos network, blog users receive regular updates about events. </p>

<p>Cosmos has a <a href="https://v1.cosmos.network/community" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">community</a> with a rich following where information and communication remain a priority. Developers can also communicate and exchange ideas in the community.</p>
<p>The network also supports up to <a href="https://cosmos.network/ecosystem/apps/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">266 modern apps and services</a>. With a thriving ecosystem and everyday use case, it is easy to see why the token is enjoying a resurgence.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cosmos-460x325.jpg" width="460" height="325" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple (XRP) Related Flare Network Token Airdrop: FLR dumps by 71%</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/ripple/ripple-xrp-related-flare-airdrop-flr-dumps/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 13:40:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Flare]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FLR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515371</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In late 2020, the Flare Network attracted a lot of attention in the Ripple (XRP) community. The creators wanted to open up the DeFi space for Ripple and announced an airdrop of Flare (FLR) tokens for all XRP holders. However, holders of XRP had to be patient for a long time. The launch was postponed several times. But today is finally the day: at 6:59 p.m. EST, the distribution of FLR tokens will take place. The FLR Token Distribution event is just 24 hours away. Join the #Flare team and guests on Twitter tomorrow. The distribution starts at 23:59 UTC sharp. The stream will start a few minutes before.#ConnectEverything pic.twitter.com/CLtmUird1Z &#8212; Flare ☀️ (@FlareNetworks) January 8, 2023 However, there is also bad news. Just before the launch, the FLR/USDT trading pair is seeing a massive dump of around 71% on Bitrue. The exchange was the only trading platform besides Poloniex to date where FLR could be traded as an IOU. As can be seen in the 1-day chart from TradingView, the FLR/USDT pair has seen a massive dip over the last two days on Bitrue. The token was trading at $0.5394 yesterday and crashed to a low of $0.1559 at times today before recovering to $0.2395 at press time. With this, the FLR token is still posting a loss of around 55% compared to two days ago. Airdrop For XRP Holders Is Finally Here &#8211; Too Late? When the project started, the narrative was clear: Ripple (XRP) lacked access to the booming sector of decentralized finance (DeFi). This has since changed, at least in part. Ripple has been developing a bridge to Ethereum (ETH) on its own to enable smart contracts and DeFi. Moreover, the XRP Ledger now has a DEX and its own NFT standard. Related Reading: XRP Price Primed For Future Rally Following Ripple’s MENA Expansion To adapt to it, the project now aims to provide smart contract capabilities for blockchains without them, starting with Ripple (XRP). Flare Network is a layer 1 Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) based interoperable blockchain based on the Proof of Stake (PoS) consensus mechanism. Related Reading: XRP Whales Move Assets As Price Dips, What’s Next? However, whether Flare Network can convince investors after its 2-year delay with its new approach or whether there will be another dump tonight when the majority of Ripple (XRP) investors receive their FLR tokens, remains to be seen. Today&#8217;s dump suggests that some investors may not be interested in FLR in the long term. FLR Token Distribution For every 1 XRP in the snapshot (taken in December 2020), 1.0073 FLR will be airdropped. Today, the first 15% of this amount will be distributed via airdrop. The remaining 85% of the tokens will be paid out in 36 monthly installments. The method of distribution depends on the outcome of the community vote on the Flare Improvement Proposal 01 (FIP.01). If the community approves the proposal, the remaining 36 monthly distributions will be decentralized on the chain. The tokens will be divided among the wallets that packaged FLR tokens (WFLR). If the community rejects the proposal, the same self-storage wallets and the same centralized exchanges that received the initial airdrop will receive one airdrop per month for 36 months. Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In late 2020, the Flare Network attracted a lot of attention in the Ripple (XRP) community. The creators wanted to open up the DeFi space for Ripple and announced an airdrop of Flare (FLR) tokens for all XRP holders.</p>
<p>However, holders of XRP had to be patient for a long time. The launch was postponed several times. But today is finally the day: at 6:59 p.m. EST, the distribution of FLR tokens will take place.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The FLR Token Distribution event is just 24 hours away.</p>
<p>Join the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Flare?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#Flare</a> team and guests on Twitter tomorrow. The distribution starts at 23:59 UTC sharp. The stream will start a few minutes before.<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ConnectEverything?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#ConnectEverything</a> <a href="https://t.co/CLtmUird1Z" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/CLtmUird1Z</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Flare <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2600.png" alt="☀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@FlareNetworks) <a href="https://twitter.com/FlareNetworks/status/1612237590857486336?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 8, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>However, there is also bad news. Just before the launch, the FLR/USDT trading pair is seeing a massive dump of around 71% on Bitrue.</p>
<p>The exchange was the only trading platform besides Poloniex to date where FLR could be traded as an IOU. As can be seen in the 1-day chart from TradingView, the FLR/USDT pair has seen a massive dip over the last two days on Bitrue.</p>
<p>The token was trading at $0.5394 yesterday and crashed to a low of $0.1559 at times today before recovering to $0.2395 at press time. With this, the FLR token is still posting a loss of around 55% compared to two days ago.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-515377 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/FLRUSDT_2023-01-09_13-12-42.png" alt="FLR USDT" width="2932" height="1537" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/FLRUSDT_2023-01-09_13-12-42.png 2932w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/FLRUSDT_2023-01-09_13-12-42-460x241.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/FLRUSDT_2023-01-09_13-12-42-860x451.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/FLRUSDT_2023-01-09_13-12-42-768x403.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/FLRUSDT_2023-01-09_13-12-42-1536x805.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/FLRUSDT_2023-01-09_13-12-42-2048x1074.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/FLRUSDT_2023-01-09_13-12-42-750x393.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/FLRUSDT_2023-01-09_13-12-42-1140x598.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2932px) 100vw, 2932px" />
<h2>Airdrop For XRP Holders Is Finally Here &#8211; Too Late?</h2>
<p>When the project started, the narrative was clear: Ripple (XRP) lacked access to the booming sector of decentralized finance (DeFi). This has since changed, at least in part. Ripple has been developing a bridge to Ethereum (ETH) on its own to enable smart contracts and DeFi. Moreover, the XRP Ledger now has a DEX and its own NFT standard.</p>

<p>To adapt to it, the project now aims to provide smart contract capabilities for blockchains without them, starting with Ripple (XRP). Flare Network is a layer 1 Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) based interoperable blockchain based on the Proof of Stake (PoS) consensus mechanism.</p>

<p>However, whether Flare Network can convince investors after its 2-year delay with its new approach or whether there will be another dump tonight when the majority of Ripple (XRP) investors receive their FLR tokens, remains to be seen. Today&#8217;s dump suggests that some investors may not be interested in FLR in the long term.</p>
<h2>FLR Token Distribution</h2>
<p>For every 1 XRP in the snapshot (taken in December 2020), 1.0073 FLR will be airdropped. Today, the first 15% of this amount will be <a href="https://flare.network/tde-faqs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">distributed</a> via airdrop. The remaining 85% of the tokens will be paid out in 36 monthly installments. The method of distribution depends on the outcome of the community vote on the Flare Improvement Proposal 01 (FIP.01).</p>
<p>If the community approves the proposal, the remaining 36 monthly distributions will be decentralized on the chain. The tokens will be divided among the wallets that packaged FLR tokens (WFLR).</p>
<p>If the community rejects the proposal, the same self-storage wallets and the same centralized exchanges that received the initial airdrop will receive one airdrop per month for 36 months.</p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/iStock-933090786-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>IMX Spikes 10% In Last 24 Hours &#8211; Will It Start The Week Strong?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/imx-spikes-10-in-last-24-hrs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 11:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GameFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ImmutableX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515350</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[IMX (ImmutableX) has been on a roll lately, being one of the few altcoins to have significant gains in the past month or so. According to tracking by CoinGecko, IMX was up 10% in the daily timeframe with its biggest gain at the weekly timescale at nearly 19%.  Related Reading: Dogecoin (DOGE) Is Now 4th Most Popular Cryptocurrency On BitPay IMX: What Drove Prices Up?  Although the past year saw the token drop by 87%, it also saw some significant developments for the L2 ecosystem. For their push to become the leading competitor in the NFT space, Gamestop partnered with ImmutableX for their NFT marketplace.  This placed ImmutableX on the spotlight as it was just a startup company back then. Both companies also created a $100 million fund for NFT developers to boost their projects if granted.  The partnership created buzz around the time as this sort of legitimized NFTs in the eyes of gamers and collectible enthusiasts as NFTs sought an audience with this crowd of consumers. Image: CoinJournal But with NFT interest dwindling, the technology will continually be a hard-sell to consumers as it is still in its infancy.  The real growth, however, is in the GameFi space. According to ImmutableX, the ecosystem edged Polygon in terms of exclusive on-chain GameFi development with ImmutableX catching up on cross-chain development.  These developments are also courtesy of Immutable’s previous wins. Most notable of these is the $200 million that they raised during its Series C funding with gaming industry companies and venture funds.  IMX Riding Bullish Momentum ImmutableX’s native token IMX seems to be riding the bullish wave that’s taken over major cryptos Bitcoin and Ethereum. As of writing, the two are up 1.5% and 2.5%, respectively.  This is a good wave for IMX to ride on. However, this manifests a very real risk of a huge correction if macroeconomic indicators show a worsening economic situation. But with the White House announcing that the economy is heading for a soft landing, investor sentiment should reverse back to positive on both stocks and riskier assets like cryptocurrencies.  Related Reading: Ethereum Classic (ETC) Price Balloons To Nearly 30% In Last 7 Days Crypto total market cap at $810 billion on the weekend chart &#124; Chart: TradingView.com For IMX to continue its bullishness, the token needs to break its sideways movement that formed because of FTX’s collapse. The primary resistance level at $0.4726 should be broken as this was the main resistance that kept the price downwards.  With major cryptos going bullish, IMX riding the wave to break through this resistance can help it turn $0.4726 to support. Investors and traders, however, should keep watch as the Consumer Price Index (CPI) will be released this week.  If the CPI stagnates and remains high, the U.S. Federal Reserve might be on another interest rate hike later this year.  -Featured Image from TechFi]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>IMX (ImmutableX) has been on a roll lately, being one of the few altcoins to have significant gains in the past month or so. </p>
<p>According to tracking by <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/immutablex" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a>, IMX was up 10% in the daily timeframe with its biggest gain at the weekly timescale at nearly 19%. </p>

<h2><strong>IMX: What Drove Prices Up? </strong></h2>
<p>Although the past year saw the token drop by 87%, it also saw some significant developments for the L2 ecosystem. For their push to become the leading competitor in the NFT space, Gamestop <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/gamestop-taps-immutable-x-nft-marketplace-2022-02-03/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">partnered</a> with ImmutableX for their NFT marketplace. </p>
<p>This placed ImmutableX on the spotlight as it was just a startup company back then. Both companies also <a href="https://www.bing.com/ck/a?!&amp;&amp;p=373fd430f90ff356JmltdHM9MTY3MzEzNjAwMCZpZ3VpZD0wMDcxNGJlNS0zYzkwLTYyNWUtMjNhNC01OTc3M2Q5MTYzOTImaW5zaWQ9NTM5Mw&amp;ptn=3&amp;hsh=3&amp;fclid=00714be5-3c90-625e-23a4-59773d916392&amp;u=a1aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZm9yYmVzLmNvbS9zaXRlcy9wYXVsdGFzc2kvMjAyMi8wMi8wMy9nYW1lc3RvcHMtMTAwLW1pbGxpb24tbmZ0LW1hcmtldHBsYWNlLWlzLWdvaW5nLXRvLWdvLXBvb3JseS8jOn46dGV4dD1UaGUlMjBXYWxsJTIwU3RyZWV0JTIwSm91cm5hbCUyMGlzJTIwcmVwb3J0aW5nJTIwdGhhdCUyMEdhbWVTdG9wLGl0cyUyMG1hcmtldHBsYWNlJTIwdGhhdCUyMGNvdWxkJTIwYmUlMjB1c2VkJTIwaW4lMjBnYW1lcy4&amp;ntb=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">created</a> a $100 million fund for NFT developers to boost their projects if granted. </p>
<p>The partnership created buzz around the time as this sort of legitimized NFTs in the eyes of gamers and collectible enthusiasts as NFTs sought an audience with this crowd of consumers.</p>

<p>But with NFT interest <a href="https://www.bing.com/ck/a?!&amp;&amp;p=204b238ca4bc5772JmltdHM9MTY3MzEzNjAwMCZpZ3VpZD0wMDcxNGJlNS0zYzkwLTYyNWUtMjNhNC01OTc3M2Q5MTYzOTImaW5zaWQ9NTM5MQ&amp;ptn=3&amp;hsh=3&amp;fclid=00714be5-3c90-625e-23a4-59773d916392&amp;u=a1aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cudG9kYXluZnRuZXdzLmNvbS90b3RhbC1uZnQtc2FsZXMtYXJlLWRvd24tNzYteW95LWluLTIwMjItd2hhdC1kb2VzLTIwMjMtbG9vay1saWtlLyM6fjp0ZXh0PVRoZSUyMHRvdGFsJTIwbW9udGhseSUyME5GVCUyMHNhbGVzJTIwcmVhY2hlZCUyMGFib3V0JTIwJTI0Mi44LG1vbnRobHklMjBORlQlMjBzYWxlJTIwdG90YWxlZCUyMG1vcmUlMjB0aGFuJTIwJTI0Mi41JTIwYmlsbGlvbi4&amp;ntb=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">dwindling</a>, the technology will continually be a <a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-56371912" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">hard-sell</a> to consumers as it is still in its infancy. </p>
<p>The real growth, however, is in the GameFi space. According to <a href="https://members.delphidigital.io/reports/the-year-ahead-for-gaming#infrastructure" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ImmutableX</a>, the ecosystem edged Polygon in terms of exclusive on-chain GameFi development with ImmutableX catching up on cross-chain development. </p>
<p>These developments are also courtesy of Immutable’s previous wins. Most notable of these is the <a href="https://twitter.com/Immutable/status/1605292879982694401?s=20&amp;t=tLFn5JLXIvzfGITKn7AUGQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">$200 million</a> that they raised during its Series C funding with gaming industry companies and venture funds. </p>
<h2><strong>IMX Riding Bullish Momentum</strong></h2>
<p>ImmutableX’s native token IMX seems to be riding the bullish wave that’s taken over major cryptos <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/bitcoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Bitcoin</a> and <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/ethereum" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Ethereum</a>. As of writing, the two are up 1.5% and 2.5%, respectively. </p>
<p>This is a good wave for IMX to ride on. However, this manifests a very real risk of a huge correction if macroeconomic indicators show a worsening economic situation. </p>
<p>But with the White House <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/us-likely-headed-for-economic-soft-landing-white-houses-boushey/ar-AA163zsB" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announcing</a> that the economy is heading for a soft landing, investor sentiment should reverse back to <a href="https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/markets/stocks/news/optimism-makes-a-comeback-on-wall-street-on-hopes-of-soft-landing/articleshow/96840803.cms" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">positive</a> on both stocks and riskier assets like cryptocurrencies. </p>

<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/nxy4I5gF/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>

<p>For IMX to continue its bullishness, the token needs to break its sideways movement that formed because of FTX’s collapse. The primary resistance level at $0.4726 should be broken as this was the main resistance that kept the price downwards. </p>
<p>With major cryptos going bullish, IMX riding the wave to break through this resistance can help it turn $0.4726 to support. Investors and traders, however, should keep watch as the Consumer Price Index (CPI) will be released this week. </p>
<p>If the <a href="https://www.fxstreet.com/analysis/earnings-and-cpi-should-make-for-a-bumpy-ride-ahead-202301082230" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CPI</a> stagnates and remains high, the U.S. Federal Reserve might be on another interest rate hike later this year. </p>
<p><em>-Featured Image from TechFi</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/imx-460x260.png" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
