<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 03:19:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Signaled “Sell” And Remains At Risk of More Losses</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-signaled-sell-1920/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 03:19:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528420</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum price is showing bearish signs below $1,920 against the US Dollar. ETH could continue to move down if it clears the $1,800 support zone. Ethereum failed to recover and stayed well below the $1,920 resistance. The price is trading below $1,900 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,845 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could start an upside correction if it clears the $1,850 and $1,880 levels. Ethereum Price Takes A Hit Ethereum’s price attempted a short-term upside correction from the $1,820 zone. ETH climbed above the $1,850 resistance zone but upsides were limited, similar to Bitcoin. Ether traded as high as $1,889 and recently started a fresh decline. There was a break below the $1,820 level. A new weekly low is formed near $1,807 and the price is now consolidating losses. It is trading below $1,900 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,845 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. Immediate resistance is near the $1,845 zone and the trend line. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $1,889 high to the $1,807 low. The next major resistance is near $1,860 or the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $1,889 high to the $1,807 low. An upside break above $1,860 might send Ethereum toward $1,900. The main resistance is still near the $1,920 level. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com If the bulls can push Ether above the $1,920 level, there could be a steady increase. In the stated case, the price could rise toward the $2,000 resistance. Any more gains could send Ether toward the $2,080 resistance. More Losses in ETH? If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,845 resistance, it could continue to move down. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,810 level. The next major support is near the $1,800 zone, below which ether price might gain bearish momentum. In the stated case, the price might decline toward $1,765. Any more losses may perhaps take the price toward $1,700. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now gaining momentum in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is below the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,800 Major Resistance Level – $1,920]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum price is showing bearish signs below $1,920 against the US Dollar. ETH could continue to move down if it clears the $1,800 support zone.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum failed to recover and stayed well below the $1,920 resistance.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $1,900 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,845 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start an upside correction if it clears the $1,850 and $1,880 levels.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Takes A Hit</h2>
<p>Ethereum’s price attempted a short-term upside correction from the $1,820 zone. ETH climbed above the $1,850 resistance zone but upsides were limited, similar to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-vulnerable-28k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p>Ether traded as high as $1,889 and recently started a fresh decline. There was a break below the $1,820 level. A new weekly low is formed near $1,807 and the price is now consolidating losses. It is trading below $1,900 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-vulnerable-1920/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">100-hourly Simple Moving Average</a>.</p>
<p>There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,845 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. Immediate resistance is near the $1,845 zone and the trend line. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $1,889 high to the $1,807 low.</p>
<p>The next major resistance is near $1,860 or the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $1,889 high to the $1,807 low. An upside break above $1,860 might send Ethereum toward $1,900. The main resistance is still near the $1,920 level.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ethereum-15.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-528422" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ethereum-15.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ethereum-15.png 1834w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ethereum-15-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ethereum-15-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ethereum-15-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ethereum-15-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ethereum-15-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ethereum-15-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>If the bulls can push Ether above the $1,920 level, there could be a steady increase. In the stated case, the price could rise toward the $2,000 resistance. Any more gains could send Ether toward the $2,080 resistance.</p>
<h2>More Losses in ETH?</h2>
<p>If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,845 resistance, it could continue to move down. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,810 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $1,800 zone, below which ether price might gain bearish momentum. In the stated case, the price might decline toward $1,765. Any more losses may perhaps take the price toward $1,700.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is now gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,800</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,920</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Depositphotos_179456522_s-2019-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Topside Bias Vulnerable Unless It Surges Past $28K</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-vulnerable-28k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 02:27:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528417</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is showing bearish signs below the $28,000 zone. BTC must clear $28,000 to avoid more losses in the coming sessions. Bitcoin struggled to gain pace above the $28,000 resistance zone. The price is trading below $27,800 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $27,650 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could start a decent recovery wave if there is a close above $28,000. Bitcoin Price Remains At a Risk Bitcoin price found support near the $27,200 zone and started an upside correction. BTC climbed above the $27,800 level but upsides were limited. It tested the $28,000 resistance zone. A high was formed near $28,000 and the price reacted to the downside. It broke the $27,200 support zone and tested $27,000. A low is formed near $26,969 and the price is again attempting an upside correction. Bitcoin climbed above the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $28,000 high to the $26,969 low. However, it is still trading below $27,800 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. Besides, there is a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $27,650 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Immediate resistance is near the $27,650 level and the trend line. The trend line coincides with the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $28,000 high to the $26,969 low. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The next major resistance sits near the $28,000 zone. A close above the $28,000 resistance could start a decent increase. In the stated case, the price may perhaps rise toward the $28,400 resistance zone. Any more gains could open the doors for a test of $29,200. More Losses in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $27,650 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $27,100 level. The next major support is near the $27,000 zone. A downside break and close below the $27,000 support might push the price toward the $26,500 support. Any more losses might take Bitcoin toward $26,000. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now below the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $27,100, followed by $27,000. Major Resistance Levels – $27,650, $28,000, and $28,400.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is showing bearish signs below the $28,000 zone. BTC must clear $28,000 to avoid more losses in the coming sessions.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin struggled to gain pace above the $28,000 resistance zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $27,800 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $27,650 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a decent recovery wave if there is a close above $28,000.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Remains At a Risk</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-increase-28k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">found support near the $27,200 zone</a> and started an upside correction. BTC climbed above the $27,800 level but upsides were limited.</p>
<p>It tested the $28,000 resistance zone. A high was formed near $28,000 and the price reacted to the downside. It broke the $27,200 support zone and tested $27,000. A low is formed near $26,969 and the price is again attempting an upside correction.</p>
<p>Bitcoin climbed above the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $28,000 high to the $26,969 low. However, it is still trading below $27,800 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-could-revisit-27-2k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>.</p>
<p>Besides, there is a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $27,650 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Immediate resistance is near the $27,650 level and the trend line. The trend line coincides with the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $28,000 high to the $26,969 low.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-15.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-528418" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-15.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-15.png 1834w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-15-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-15-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-15-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-15-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-15-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin-15-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The next major resistance sits near the $28,000 zone. A close above the $28,000 resistance could start a decent increase. In the stated case, the price may perhaps rise toward the $28,400 resistance zone. Any more gains could open the doors for a test of $29,200.</p>
<h2>More Losses in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $27,650 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $27,100 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $27,000 zone. A downside break and close below the $27,000 support might push the price toward the $26,500 support. Any more losses might take Bitcoin toward $26,000.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $27,100, followed by $27,000.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $27,650, $28,000, and $28,400.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/shutterstock_773873392-460x268.jpg" width="460" height="268" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Filecoin Experiences Sharp Sell-Off, Potential For Price To Drop Below $5</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/filecoin/filecoin-experiences-sharp-sell-off-potential-for-price-to-drop-below-5/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 21:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Filecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fil]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[filecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[filusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FILUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528349</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The bearish onslaught has taken a toll on the price of Filecoin, which slipped below the $6 mark, and the bears now have a strong foothold. On the one-day chart, Filecoin is showing consolidation with a loss of 1.1%. Over the last week, the coin has depreciated by nearly 17%. The technical outlook for Filecoin indicates bearish pressure, with a drop in demand and accumulation. If sellers push further, it will add to the bearish pressure. Related Reading: Losses Dominate Crypto Over The Weekend, Has The Bear Market Returned? Bitcoin&#8217;s struggle to stay above $30,000 has affected other altcoins, keeping them below their immediate resistance levels. The demand must recover in the next trading sessions for FIL to jump above the $5.50 price. The decline in the market capitalization of Filecoin over the past day also indicates growing selling pressure. Broader market strength remains crucial for the altcoin&#8217;s price movement over the subsequent trading sessions. Filecoin Price Analysis: One-Day Chart At the time of writing, the trading price for FIL was $5.26. Following its drop below the $6 mark, Filecoin has experienced a continuous free fall. The coin faces overhead resistance at $5.60; surpassing this level will push the coin towards $6, with a potential attempt to trade at $6.30. Conversely, failing to trade at the current level will establish local support for the coin at $4.90. If the price falls below this level, it will reach $3.80, strengthening the bears. In the last session, the amount of Filecoin traded was in the red, indicating a drop in demand. Technical Analysis Over the past few trading sessions, the buying strength for FIL has decreased considerably due to a fall in demand. The Relative Strength Index showed that the buying strength had depreciated, and selling strength had taken over, as the index was below the 40 mark. Additionally, the FIL price dropped below the 20-Simple Moving Average line, indicating that sellers had taken control and were driving the price momentum in the market. However, if Filecoin surpasses the $5.60 mark, the coin may rise above the 20-SMA line, bringing back the bulls. At the time of writing, Filecoin gave sell signals in line with other technical indicators. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence showed red histograms, indicating sell signals for price momentum and trend reversals. Related Reading: ADA Price (Cardano) Close Below $0.38 Could Spark Larger Degree Correction These signals suggested that FIL may experience further decline over the next trading sessions. The Awesome Oscillator, which measures price momentum and movement on the chart, formed red bars under the half-line, indicating that sellers had taken control of the market price and that FIL was experiencing bearish momentum. For the coin to initiate its recovery, FIL must surpass the overhead ceiling. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The bearish onslaught has taken a toll on the price of Filecoin, which slipped below the $6 mark, and the bears now have a strong foothold. On the one-day chart, Filecoin is showing consolidation with a loss of 1.1%. Over the last week, the coin has depreciated by nearly 17%.</p>
<p>The technical outlook for Filecoin indicates bearish pressure, with a drop in demand and accumulation. If sellers push further, it will add to the bearish pressure.</p>

<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s struggle to stay above $30,000 has affected other altcoins, keeping them below their immediate resistance levels.</p>
<p>The demand must recover in the next trading sessions for FIL to jump above the $5.50 price. The decline in the market capitalization of Filecoin over the past day also indicates growing selling pressure. Broader market strength remains crucial for the altcoin&#8217;s price movement over the subsequent trading sessions.</p>
<h2>Filecoin Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-528369 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSD_2023-04-24_20-23-31.png" alt="Filecoin" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSD_2023-04-24_20-23-31.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSD_2023-04-24_20-23-31-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSD_2023-04-24_20-23-31-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSD_2023-04-24_20-23-31-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSD_2023-04-24_20-23-31-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSD_2023-04-24_20-23-31-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSD_2023-04-24_20-23-31-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>At the time of writing, the trading price for FIL was $5.26. Following its drop below the $6 mark, Filecoin has experienced a continuous free fall. The coin faces overhead resistance at $5.60; surpassing this level will push the coin towards $6, with a potential attempt to trade at $6.30.</p>
<p>Conversely, failing to trade at the current level will establish local support for the coin at $4.90. If the price falls below this level, it will reach $3.80, strengthening the bears. In the last session, the amount of Filecoin traded was in the red, indicating a drop in demand.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-528371 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSD_2023-04-24_20-24-12.png" alt="Filecoin" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSD_2023-04-24_20-24-12.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSD_2023-04-24_20-24-12-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSD_2023-04-24_20-24-12-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSD_2023-04-24_20-24-12-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSD_2023-04-24_20-24-12-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSD_2023-04-24_20-24-12-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSD_2023-04-24_20-24-12-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>Over the past few trading sessions, the buying strength for FIL has decreased considerably due to a fall in demand. The Relative Strength Index showed that the buying strength had depreciated, and selling strength had taken over, as the index was below the 40 mark.</p>
<p>Additionally, the FIL price dropped below the 20-Simple Moving Average line, indicating that sellers had taken control and were driving the price momentum in the market. However, if Filecoin surpasses the $5.60 mark, the coin may rise above the 20-SMA line, bringing back the bulls.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-528372 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSD_2023-04-24_20-24-44.png" alt="Filecoin" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSD_2023-04-24_20-24-44.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSD_2023-04-24_20-24-44-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSD_2023-04-24_20-24-44-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSD_2023-04-24_20-24-44-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSD_2023-04-24_20-24-44-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSD_2023-04-24_20-24-44-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/FILUSD_2023-04-24_20-24-44-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>At the time of writing, Filecoin gave sell signals in line with other technical indicators. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence showed red histograms, indicating sell signals for price momentum and trend reversals.</p>

<p>These signals suggested that FIL may experience further decline over the next trading sessions. The Awesome Oscillator, which measures price momentum and movement on the chart, formed red bars under the half-line, indicating that sellers had taken control of the market price and that FIL was experiencing bearish momentum. For the coin to initiate its recovery, FIL must surpass the overhead ceiling.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/traxer-_nSOrTpoEDI-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin&#8217;s Upcycle Shows Small Drawdowns, Report</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-upcycle-shows-small-drawdowns-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 20:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528381</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin (BTC) market has faced some resistance this week, according to a report by cryptocurrency analytics firm Glassnode. The market reverted from a weekly high of over $31,000 to a low of $27,000, signaling a potential correction in the market. Despite this recent dip, Glassnode&#8217;s analysis shows that the opening to 2023 has been historically strong for Bitcoin, with remarkably few significant corrections. The largest correction seen so far has been -18.6%, a relatively small drawdown compared to past cycles. Related Reading: Solana (SOL) Rebounding After A Major Drop, Will It Recover Previous Losses? Bitcoin Market Sees Transition From Loss To Profit According to the report by Glassnode, the aggregate market for Bitcoin has confidently transitioned out of a period of unrealized loss and into one of unrealized profit. This is evidenced by the sharp divergence between supply held in profit versus supply held at a loss. As this shift occurs, the incentive to take profits grows, also reflected in the ratio between supply in profit and supply at a loss. Glassnode&#8217;s analysis shows that this oscillator has achieved escape velocity in 2023, confirming the transition out of a regime of loss dominance near cycle lows. This phenomenon has only been observed on 415 out of 4,638 trading days, or just 9% of the time. This shift in the market is significant because it suggests that investors are becoming more confident in Bitcoin&#8217;s long-term prospects. As more investors move into a position of unrealized profit, they may be more likely to hold onto their investments rather than take profits and risk missing out on potential gains. Will BTC Retest The $25,000 Support? Altcoin Sherpa, a well-known cryptocurrency analyst, recently shared his thoughts on the current state of Bitcoin. He believes that if the current market area fails, the next area up is around $25k. He also noted that the .382 fib level, a technical indicator, usually gets tapped as a retest eventually. Despite this potential dip, Altcoin Sherpa maintains a bullish outlook on Bitcoin&#8217;s market structure.  On the same note, Michael Van de Pope, a crypto analyst and trader, suggests that the market is seeking a higher low (HL) in the weekly timeframe, potentially around the $26,500-27,000 range or even as low as $25,000. This suggests that there may be some downside risk in the short term. However, Van de Pope notes that breaking back above $27,800 could lead to a strong upwards reaction for Bitcoin, potentially continuing the uptrend toward $29,000. Related Reading: Cardano At Risk Of Falling 8% If It Doesn’t Hold Above Key Support Line At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading at $27,300, representing a 0.8% decrease over the past 24 hours. Despite this drop, Bitcoin is holding above its last major resistance level of $27,100. However, some analysts are predicting a potential retest of the $25,000 support floor, which could lead to further downside potential for the largest cryptocurrency in the market. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin (BTC) market has faced some resistance this week, according to a <a href="https://insights.glassnode.com/the-week-onchain-week-17-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report </a>by cryptocurrency analytics firm Glassnode. The market reverted from a weekly high of over $31,000 to a low of $27,000, signaling a potential correction in the market.</p>
<p>Despite this recent dip, Glassnode&#8217;s analysis shows that the opening to 2023 has been historically strong for Bitcoin, with remarkably few significant corrections. The largest correction seen so far has been -18.6%, a relatively small drawdown compared to past cycles.</p>

<h2><b>Bitcoin Market Sees Transition From Loss To Profit</b></h2>
<p>According to the report by Glassnode, the aggregate market for Bitcoin has confidently transitioned out of a period of unrealized loss and into one of unrealized profit. This is evidenced by the sharp divergence between supply held in profit versus supply held at a loss.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-528384" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Group-3006-860x496.png" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="496" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Group-3006-860x496.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Group-3006-460x265.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Group-3006-768x443.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Group-3006-1536x885.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Group-3006-750x432.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Group-3006-1140x657.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Group-3006.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>As this shift occurs, the incentive to take profits grows, also reflected in the ratio between supply in profit and supply at a loss. Glassnode&#8217;s analysis shows that this oscillator has achieved escape velocity in 2023, confirming the transition out of a regime of loss dominance near cycle lows. This phenomenon has only been observed on 415 out of 4,638 trading days, or just 9% of the time.</p>
<p>This shift in the market is significant because it suggests that investors are becoming more confident in Bitcoin&#8217;s long-term prospects. As more investors move into a position of unrealized profit, they may be more likely to hold onto their investments rather than take profits and risk missing out on potential gains.</p>
<b>Will BTC Retest The $25,000 Support?</b>
<p>Altcoin Sherpa, a well-known cryptocurrency analyst, recently <a href="https://twitter.com/AltcoinSherpa/status/1650523481539321857?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shared </a>his thoughts on the current state of Bitcoin. He believes that if the current market area fails, the next area up is around $25k. He also noted that the .382 fib level, a technical indicator, usually gets tapped as a retest eventually. Despite this potential dip, Altcoin Sherpa maintains a bullish outlook on Bitcoin&#8217;s market structure. </p>
<p>On the same note, Michael Van de Pope, a crypto analyst and trader, <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1650062257613676545?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">suggests </a>that the market is seeking a higher low (HL) in the weekly timeframe, potentially around the $26,500-27,000 range or even as low as $25,000. This suggests that there may be some downside risk in the short term.</p>
<p>However, Van de Pope notes that breaking back above $27,800 could lead to a strong upwards reaction for Bitcoin, potentially continuing the uptrend toward $29,000.</p>

<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/wwH6v3KY/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1813" height="858" />
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading at $27,300, representing a 0.8% decrease over the past 24 hours. Despite this drop, Bitcoin is holding above its last major resistance level of $27,100. However, some analysts are predicting a potential retest of the $25,000 support floor, which could lead to further downside potential for the largest cryptocurrency in the market.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/kanchanara-rhm7H8X5J98-unsplash-1-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>CELR On A 16% Bear Strike, Bulls Must Hold The Line At This Level</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/celr-on-a-16-bear-strike-bulls-must-hold-the-line-at-this-level/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mudiaga Iritare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 19:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitrum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celer Network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celr]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CELR Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zkSync]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528361</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CELR, the official native token of Celer Network, is down badly from its previous week&#8217;s highs of $0.031, recording a disappointing -16% in today&#8217;s trade session. While several cryptocurrencies have shown price weakness, the Celer Network token has been the biggest loser over the past 24 hours. In recent times, the general market sentiment has drastically changed. Most traders who called for a bull market after BTC&#8217;s previous week&#8217;s rally are now bearish due to a price retracement on major cryptocurrencies. However, will bulls show strength and prevent the next outcome for Celer&#8217;s Network token? Related Reading: FTT Token On a 8% Rockslide Despite FTX Ray Of Hope. Here’s Why CELR Bears On A Mission, Further Losses Imminent? Bears are on a mission as they move on a trail to wipe out two-week gains of the Celer Network token. The current price action results from CELR investors taking profits on the recent Bitcoin price rally, which saw the cryptocurrency move past $30,000 for the first time since June 2022. The native token of the Celer Network was on the move and recorded a 7-day high of $0.031 after BTC bulls pushed the price upwards and lifted the entire market with the digital asset. At the time of writing,  Coinmarketcap data reveals CELR to be trading at $0.023, a notable dump from where it was in price last week. Bulls may now need to act to defend what is left of the previous week&#8217;s gains of the Celer Network token. CELR price retraces back to key support after previous week gains &#124; Source: CELRUSD on TradingView CELR is currently trading at a key support price zone of $0.023 and might be at just the right spot for bulls to pick up steam and reverse the bearish trend. However, the price of Bitcoin is a major price decider for the crypto market and could dictate CELR&#8217;s fate in the coming days. At the time of writing, Bitcoin trades at $27,327  and is currently faced with resistance at $27,800, according to a recent tweet by crypto analyst Michael Van De Poppe. Rejecting that resistance level may see Bitcoin sweeping further lows until it can bounce up. Same old, same old for #Bitcoin. Isn&#39;t able to break through $27,800 as resistance point. Would be looking at a sweep of the lows until we can have a bounce. However, $27,800 is crucial for a trend reversal, not $28,800. pic.twitter.com/7U7MS1lcus &#8212; Michaël van de Poppe (@CryptoMichNL) April 24, 2023 A further Bitcoin price depreciation could mean dire consequences for CELR, thereby inviting bears to sweep off the remaining gains of the previous two-week candles. Celer Network Token Price Unshaken By Recent Platform Development Despite Celer Network&#8217;s recent development to its platform, a corresponding bullish impact is yet to be seen in the price of its native token. One recent development expands Celer&#8217;s bridging support for Izumi Finance native token (IZI) and the IUSD stablecoin. Celer Network users can now seamlessly and securely bridge the tokens mentioned above between Arbitrum, Ethereum, Polygon, and ZKsync networks at low transaction costs. Related Reading: Losses Dominate Crypto Over The Weekend, Has The Bear Market Returned? Featured Image from Istock.Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CELR, the official native token of Celer Network, is down badly from its previous week&#8217;s highs of $0.031, recording a disappointing -16% in today&#8217;s trade session. While several cryptocurrencies have shown price weakness, the Celer Network token has been the biggest loser over the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>In recent times, the general market sentiment has drastically changed. Most traders who called for a bull market after BTC&#8217;s previous week&#8217;s rally are now bearish due to a price retracement on major cryptocurrencies. However, will bulls show strength and prevent the next outcome for Celer&#8217;s Network token?</p>

<h2>CELR Bears On A Mission, Further Losses Imminent?</h2>
<p>Bears are on a mission as they move on a trail to wipe out two-week gains of the Celer Network token. The current price action results from CELR investors taking profits on the recent Bitcoin price rally, which saw the cryptocurrency move past $30,000 for the first time since June 2022.</p>
<p>The native token of the Celer Network was on the move and recorded a 7-day high of $0.031 after BTC bulls pushed the price upwards and lifted the entire market with the digital asset.</p>
<p>At the time of writing,  Coinmarketcap <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/celer-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a> reveals CELR to be trading at $0.023, a notable dump from where it was in price last week. Bulls may now need to act to defend what is left of the previous week&#8217;s gains of the Celer Network token.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/E6dnPW3O/" alt="CELR" width="1079" height="595" /></p>

<p>CELR is currently trading at a key support price zone of $0.023 and might be at just the right spot for bulls to pick up steam and reverse the bearish trend. However, the price of Bitcoin is a major price decider for the crypto market and could dictate CELR&#8217;s fate in the coming days.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin trades at $27,327  and is currently faced with resistance at $27,800, according to a recent tweet by crypto analyst Michael Van De Poppe. Rejecting that resistance level may see Bitcoin sweeping further lows until it can bounce up.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Same old, same old for <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p>Isn&#39;t able to break through $27,800 as resistance point. </p>
<p>Would be looking at a sweep of the lows until we can have a bounce.</p>
<p>However, $27,800 is crucial for a trend reversal, not $28,800. <a href="https://t.co/7U7MS1lcus" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/7U7MS1lcus</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Michaël van de Poppe (@CryptoMichNL) <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1650517447894605830?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">April 24, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>A further Bitcoin price depreciation could mean dire consequences for CELR, thereby inviting bears to sweep off the remaining gains of the previous two-week candles.</p>
<h2>Celer Network Token Price Unshaken By Recent Platform Development</h2>
<p>Despite Celer Network&#8217;s recent development to its platform, a corresponding bullish impact is yet to be seen in the price of its native token. One recent development expands Celer&#8217;s bridging support for Izumi Finance native token (IZI) and the IUSD stablecoin.</p>
<p>Celer Network users can now seamlessly and securely bridge the tokens mentioned above between Arbitrum, Ethereum, Polygon, and ZKsync networks at low transaction costs.</p>





]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/iStock-1270504858-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Standard Chartered Predicts Bitcoin Could Reach $100,000 By End of 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/standard-chartered-predicts-bitcoin-could-reach-100000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 18:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528347</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin, the world&#8217;s most well-known cryptocurrency, has been on a wild ride over the past few years, with its price surging to new highs before crashing back down.  Despite this, some experts still believe the asset could record new significant highs in a few years to come. At current market prices, Bitcoin has currently decreased by 60% from its all-time high of $69,000 seen in November 2021. BTC Could Reach $100,000 According to a note from Standard Chartered&#8217;s head of digital assets research, Geoff Kendrick, the &#8220;crypto winter&#8221; may finally be over, and Bitcoin could reach $100,000 by the end of 2024. Kendrick attributes this potential surge in Bitcoin&#8217;s price to a number of factors. These include recent turmoil in the banking sector, a stabilization of risk assets as the US Federal Reserve ends its rate-hiking cycle, and the improved profitability of crypto mining.  Related Reading: Bitcoin (BTC) To Tap Into $30,000 Region Before A Slow Down, Here’s Why Kendrick said these factors are making the pathway to the $100,000 level &#8220;becoming clearer.&#8221; But while Kendrick acknowledges that there are still sources of uncertainty surrounding Bitcoin, he believes that the potential for Bitcoin to reach $100,000 is very real.  This prediction is particularly noteworthy given that Bitcoin&#8217;s price has already surged so far this year. It rose above $30,000 in April for the first time in 10 months. Bitcoin Price Action In The Past 7 Days Bitcoin has experienced a tumultuous journey in the last week, with its price surging to as high as $30,000 on April 18 to crashing back down below $28,000 over the weekend. Over the past 7 days, Bitcoin has been in a downtrend down by nearly 10% in just a week.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Traders Count Losses As Total Liquidations Approach $300 Million The asset&#8217;s market cap has also lost some value, as it lost over $20 billion from its market capitalization in the last week. Bitcoin currently trades at $27,479 at the time of writing down by 0.6% in the last 24 hours. Several factors contributed to the initial surge in Bitcoin&#8217;s price. This includes the fall of United States dollar dominance and the rising US banking crisis, which prompted several traditional bankers to seek another store of value. However, the surge was short-lived, and Bitcoin&#8217;s price crashed back down in the past seven days. This sudden drop in Bitcoin&#8217;s price was likely caused by a combination of profit-taking from investors who had bought in at lower prices last year, and concerns over increased regulatory scrutiny. Despite this recent volatility, many experts remain bullish on Bitcoin&#8217;s long-term prospects. As more and more institutions adopt cryptocurrency and retail investors get involved, it seems that Bitcoin will continue to play a significant role in the financial markets for years to come. Standard Chartered&#8217;s prediction of a $100,000 Bitcoin price by the end of 2024 may seem ambitious. But it is not an isolated forecast. According to a survey conducted by London-based crypto hedge fund Nickel Digital Asset Management, the majority of professional investors believe that Bitcoin is becoming more mainstream and that this trend is likely to continue in the coming years. Several other experts including former Coinbase Chief Technology Officer (CTO) Balaji Srinivasan have made similar predictions, suggesting that Bitcoin could go as high as $1 million in the long run. The Coinbase executive went as far as making a bold bet on the future of Bitcoin, claiming that the cryptocurrency will surge to $1 million by June 17th. This optimistic forecast is attributed to the rapid devaluation of the US dollar. However, it&#8217;s important to remember that cryptocurrency prices are notoriously volatile and difficult to predict. Though Bitcoin&#8217;s price has been on an upward trajectory in recent months, it&#8217;s entirely possible that it could experience significant pullbacks or corrections in the future. Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin, the world&#8217;s most well-known cryptocurrency, has been on a wild ride over the past few years, with its price surging to new highs before crashing back down. </p>
<p>Despite this, some experts still believe the asset could record new significant highs in a few years to come. At current market prices, Bitcoin has currently decreased by 60% from its all-time high of $69,000 seen in November 2021.</p>
<h2>BTC Could Reach $100,000</h2>
<p>According to a <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/bitcoin-could-hit-100000-by-end-2024-standard-chartered-says-2023-04-24/" rel="nofollow">note</a> from Standard Chartered&#8217;s head of digital assets research, Geoff Kendrick, the &#8220;crypto winter&#8221; may finally be over, and Bitcoin could reach $100,000 by the end of 2024.</p>
<p>Kendrick attributes this potential surge in Bitcoin&#8217;s price to a number of factors. These include recent turmoil in the banking sector, a stabilization of risk assets as the US Federal Reserve ends its rate-hiking cycle, and the improved profitability of crypto mining. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-btc-would-tap-into-30000-region-before/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin (BTC) To Tap Into $30,000 Region Before A Slow Down, Here’s Why</a></p>
<p>Kendrick said these factors are making the pathway to the $100,000 level &#8220;becoming clearer.&#8221; But while Kendrick acknowledges that there are still sources of uncertainty surrounding Bitcoin, he believes that the potential for Bitcoin to reach $100,000 is very real. </p>
<p>This prediction is particularly noteworthy given that Bitcoin&#8217;s price has already surged so far this year. It rose above $30,000 in April for the first time in 10 months.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Action In The Past 7 Days</h2>
<p>Bitcoin has experienced a tumultuous journey in the last week, with its price surging to as <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-btc-would-tap-into-30000-region-before/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">high as $30,000</a> on April 18 to crashing back down <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-market-update-27000-local-bottom/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">below $28,000</a> over the weekend. Over the past 7 days, Bitcoin has been in a downtrend down by nearly 10% in just a week. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/all/bitcoin-traders-count-losses-as-liquidations-approach-300-million/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin Traders Count Losses As Total Liquidations Approach $300 Million</a></p>
<p>The asset&#8217;s market cap has also lost some value, as it lost over $20 billion from its market capitalization in the last week. Bitcoin currently trades at $27,479 at the time of writing down by 0.6% in the last 24 hours.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/WkAw4XkS/" alt="Bitcoin price chart on TradingView" width="2768" height="1372" />
<p>Several factors contributed to the initial surge in Bitcoin&#8217;s price. This includes the fall of United States dollar dominance and the rising US banking crisis, which prompted several traditional bankers to seek another store of value.</p>
<p>However, the surge was short-lived, and Bitcoin&#8217;s price <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/behind-bitcoin-drop-what-on-chain-data-says/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crashed back down</a> in the past seven days. This sudden drop in Bitcoin&#8217;s price was likely caused by a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/all/bitcoin-traders-count-losses-as-liquidations-approach-300-million/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">combination of profit-taking from investors</a> who had bought in at lower prices last year, and concerns over increased regulatory scrutiny.</p>
<p>Despite this recent volatility, many experts <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-increase-28k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">remain bullish</a> on Bitcoin&#8217;s long-term prospects. As more and more institutions adopt cryptocurrency and retail investors get involved, it seems that Bitcoin will continue to play a significant role in the financial markets for years to come.</p>
<p>Standard Chartered&#8217;s prediction of a $100,000 Bitcoin price by the end of 2024 may seem ambitious. But it is not an isolated forecast.</p>
<p>According to a survey conducted by London-based crypto hedge fund Nickel Digital Asset Management, the majority of professional investors believe that Bitcoin is <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crypto-will-become-mainstream-says-most-professional-investors-study-190006088.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">becoming more mainstream</a> and that this trend is likely to continue in the coming years. </p>
<p>Several other experts including former Coinbase Chief Technology Officer (CTO) Balaji Srinivasan have made similar predictions, suggesting that <a href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/bitcoin-1-million-former-coinbase-125846701.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Bitcoin could go as high as $1 million</a> in the long run. </p>
<p>The Coinbase executive went as far as making a <a href="https://twitter.com/balajis/status/1637025637901938689?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1637025637901938689%7Ctwgr%5Ec9c3651e99ae5ae4f7b848c78c548c115311e6af%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fcryptopotato.com%2Fcrypto-twitter-betting-on-hyperinflation-catapulting-btc-to-1-million-in-3-months%2F" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">bold bet</a> on the future of Bitcoin, claiming that the cryptocurrency will surge to $1 million by June 17th. This optimistic forecast is attributed to the rapid devaluation of the US dollar.</p>
<p>However, it&#8217;s important to remember that cryptocurrency prices are notoriously volatile and difficult to predict. Though Bitcoin&#8217;s price has been on an upward trajectory in recent months, it&#8217;s entirely possible that it could experience significant pullbacks or corrections in the future.</p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Bitcoin-shorts-460x306.jpeg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Bitcoin May Have Completed The &#8220;Perfect&#8221; Pullback</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/why-bitcoin-may-have-completed-the-perfect-pullback/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 18:06:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528396</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is trading at around $27,000 per coin after failing to hold above $30,000. Crypto market sentiment would suggest that BTC is already back at lows, ready for a fresh decline. However, if a perfected TD buy setup is an indication, then BTC might have just finished its pullback and is ready to continue upward with renewed momentum. A Perfect Pullback For Buying The Dip In Bitcoin? The cryptocurrency community has been on a rollercoaster ride of emotions the past several weeks. Bitcoin&#8217;s early 2023 rally caught bears by surprise. Rising beyond $30,000, however, was an opportunity to strike while bulls were blinded by euphoria from recent returns. Much more quickly than bulls became exuberant over the top crypto asset by market cap doubling in value since bear market lows, bears are celebrating a continuation of crypto winter without so much as a sign of a symbolic snowflake. Related Reading: Time To Pay Attention: Bitcoin Reaches &#8220;Logical&#8221; Level Another sign has triggered elsewhere. In this case, a perfected TD8 buy setup has appeared on daily BTCUSD spot exchange charts. A perfected signal arrives when a new low is made. The buy setup usually reaches a full TD9 count, but has perfected ahead of schedule. This could still mean another low to put in a perfected TD9, but the 8-count could also do the trick. Will Bitcoin bounce on the perfected TD8? &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com BTCUSD Triggers TD8 Setup On Daily Price Charts The TD Sequential is a market timing tool created by Thomas Demark. It counts a sequence of up and down candles, until the sequence is satisfied, and the count reaches 9. If the TD9 setup fails to produce the expected reversal, a countdown to TD13 begins. Related Reading: Brace Yourself: The Most Explosive Move In Bitcoin In Years Has Begun A TD13 signals trend exhaustion. Both the TD9 and 13 don&#8217;t necessarily guarantee a reversal, but it does improve the probability if at a key level. The tool has worked well on the buy side of BTCUSD daily charts since the local bottom was put in. As you can see, past perfected TD setups led to an immediate upside reaction. However, it is important to note that each of the above signals are TD9s and not a TD8. As notable as the signal appearing today is, the reaction over the next 24-48 hours is what matters the most. If BTCUSD fends off more significant downside and buying kicks in here at this signal, it could tell the market the correction is over, and the bull run is going to continue. Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for exclusive daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/time-to-pay-attention-bitcoin-reaches-logical-level/?swcfpc=1">Bitcoin price</a> is trading at around $27,000 per coin after failing to hold above $30,000. Crypto market sentiment would suggest that BTC is already back at lows, ready for a fresh decline.</p>
<p>However, if a perfected TD buy setup is an indication, then BTC might have just finished its pullback and is ready to continue upward with renewed momentum.</p>
<h2>A Perfect Pullback For Buying The Dip In Bitcoin?</h2>
<p>The cryptocurrency community has been on a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-bollinger-bands-signal-rollercoaster/">rollercoaster</a> ride of emotions the past several weeks. Bitcoin&#8217;s early 2023 rally caught bears by surprise. Rising beyond $30,000, however, was an opportunity to strike while bulls were blinded by euphoria from recent returns.</p>
<p>Much more quickly than bulls became exuberant over the top crypto asset by market cap doubling in value since bear market lows, bears are celebrating a continuation of crypto winter without so much as a sign of a symbolic snowflake.</p>

<p>Another sign has triggered elsewhere. In this case, a perfected TD8 buy setup has appeared on daily BTCUSD spot exchange charts. A perfected signal arrives when a new low is made. The buy setup usually reaches a full TD9 count, but has perfected ahead of schedule. This could still mean another low to put in a perfected TD9, but the 8-count could also do the trick.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-large wp-image-528400 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-24_13-34-33-860x425.png" alt="BTCUSD_2023-04-24_13-34-33" width="860" height="425" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-24_13-34-33-860x425.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-24_13-34-33-460x228.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-24_13-34-33-768x380.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-24_13-34-33-1536x760.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-24_13-34-33-2048x1013.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-24_13-34-33-750x371.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD_2023-04-24_13-34-33-1140x564.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>

<h2>BTCUSD Triggers TD8 Setup On Daily Price Charts</h2>
<p>The TD Sequential is a market timing tool created by Thomas Demark. It counts a sequence of up and down candles, until the sequence is satisfied, and the count reaches 9. If the TD9 setup fails to produce the expected reversal, a countdown to TD13 begins.</p>



<p>A TD13 signals trend exhaustion. Both the TD9 and 13 don&#8217;t necessarily guarantee a reversal, but it does improve the probability if at a key level. The tool has worked well on the buy side of BTCUSD daily charts since the local bottom was put in.</p>
<p>As you can see, past perfected TD setups led to an immediate upside reaction. However, it is important to note that each of the above signals are TD9s and not a TD8. As notable as the signal appearing today is, the reaction over the next 24-48 hours is what matters the most.</p>
<p>If BTCUSD fends off more significant downside and buying kicks in here at this signal, it could tell the market the correction is over, and the bull run is going to continue.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/iStock-1326070271-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin &#8216;ESR&#8217; Continues To Show Bullish Divergence, Will Price Follow?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-esr-continues-bullish-divergence-price-follow/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 17:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bullish Divergence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Exchange Stablecoin Ratio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528294</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin on-chain indicator Exchange Stablecoin Ratio (ESR) has continued to show bullish divergence recently. Will the price also mimic this? Bitcoin ESR Has Continued To Sharply Ascend In Recent Weeks As explained by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, the ESR is currently acting as a leading indicator for BTC&#8217;s price. A relevant metric here is the &#8220;exchange reserve,&#8221; which measures the total amount of a cryptocurrency that&#8217;s currently sitting in the wallets of all centralized exchanges. The &#8220;ESR&#8221; is an indicator that tells us about the ratio between the exchange reserve for Bitcoin and that for the combined stablecoins market (both denominated in USD). Generally, investors shift assets like BTC into stables whenever they want to escape the volatility associated with the former. When holders like these eventually want to switch back into the volatile markets, they deposit their stablecoins into exchanges to do so. The coins they exchange their stables for naturally feel a buying pressure from the conversion. Because of this reason, the stablecoin exchange reserve may be looked at as the &#8220;available buying power&#8221; for other cryptocurrencies like BTC. Related Reading: What’s Behind The Recent Bitcoin Drop? Here’s What On-Chain Data Says The exchange reserve for Bitcoin itself, however, represents the selling supply in the market, as investors generally deposit their BTC into these platforms for selling purposes. Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the BTC ESR over the last year: Looks like the value of the metric has rapidly risen in recent weeks &#124; Source: CryptoQuant According to the quant, the Bitcoin price and ESR were showing convergence during the year 2021, meaning that the two curves were moving in close tandem. This convergence continued in early 2022, as the chart above displays. However, the convergence broke with the 3AC bankruptcy in June of that year, as the price of the asset plummeted, but the ESR didn&#8217;t register any significant fluctuations at all. In late 2022, a positive divergence started forming between the two lines, as the ESR began to climb while Bitcoin continued to move sideways around the post-FTX crash lows. In January of this year, the BTC price also finally started following in the direction of the indicator, as it began its rally. The ESR has continued to sharply climb since then, while BTC has also generally observed strong upwards momentum. An interesting trend was seen back at the beginning of March when the ESR had taken a plunge. Not too long after this drawdown in the indicator occurred, the BTC price also plummeted down. Related Reading: Bitcoin Market Update: Is $27,000 The Local Bottom? But while this decline in the price was happening, the metric had already reversed back to an uptrend. As it turned out, the cryptocurrency also did the same after finishing its drop. &#8220;In the current market structure, ESR acts as a magnet to Bitcoin&#8217;s spot price,&#8221; explains the analyst. Earlier this month, the ESR again observed some decline, but it wasn&#8217;t long before the metric reversed its trend and resumed the upward trajectory. Recently, BTC has also been plunging, as its price has now gone below the $28,000 level. If the pattern that followed earlier is anything to go by, this divergence between the two lines should mean that BTC will also reverse its current decline, in order to mimic what the ESR has been doing. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $27,600, down 6% in the last week. BTC has plunged in the last few days &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin on-chain indicator Exchange Stablecoin Ratio (ESR) has continued to show bullish divergence recently. Will the price also mimic this?</p>
<h2>Bitcoin ESR Has Continued To Sharply Ascend In Recent Weeks</h2>
<p>As explained by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/644606d6e76d1277fe421afa-The-Accumulation-Cycle-Still-Intact-Despite-the-Recent-Correction" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, the ESR is currently acting as a leading indicator for BTC&#8217;s price. A relevant metric here is the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-bearish-signal-exchanges-growing-reserves/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">exchange reserve</a>,&#8221; which measures the total amount of a cryptocurrency that&#8217;s currently sitting in the wallets of all centralized exchanges.</p>
<p>The &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/quant-explains-bitcoin-esr-leading-indicator-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ESR</a>&#8221; is an indicator that tells us about the ratio between the exchange reserve for Bitcoin and that for the combined stablecoins market (both denominated in USD).</p>
<p>Generally, investors shift assets like BTC into stables whenever they want to escape the volatility associated with the former. When holders like these eventually want to switch back into the volatile markets, they deposit their stablecoins into exchanges to do so.</p>
<p>The coins they exchange their stables for naturally feel a buying pressure from the conversion. Because of this reason, the stablecoin exchange reserve may be looked at as the &#8220;available buying power&#8221; for other cryptocurrencies like BTC.</p>

<p>The exchange reserve for Bitcoin itself, however, represents the selling supply in the market, as investors generally deposit their BTC into these platforms for selling purposes.</p>
<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the BTC ESR over the last year:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/30509/quicktake/LP2Tz_30895459f677c13d97c69b7832d9ebd5a6eb703cc829473f9c7eda85dc5945e6.png" alt="Bitcoin ESR" width="1280" height="598" /></p>

<p>According to the quant, the Bitcoin price and ESR were showing convergence during the year 2021, meaning that the two curves were moving in close tandem. This convergence continued in early 2022, as the chart above displays.</p>
<p>However, the convergence broke with the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/crypto-hedge-fund-3-arrows-capital-3ac-files-for-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">3AC bankruptcy</a> in June of that year, as the price of the asset plummeted, but the ESR didn&#8217;t register any significant fluctuations at all.</p>
<p>In late 2022, a positive divergence started forming between the two lines, as the ESR began to climb while Bitcoin continued to move sideways around the post-FTX crash lows.</p>
<p>In January of this year, the BTC price also finally started following in the direction of the indicator, as it began its rally. The ESR has continued to sharply climb since then, while BTC has also generally observed strong upwards momentum.</p>
<p>An interesting trend was seen back at the beginning of March when the ESR had taken a plunge. Not too long after this drawdown in the indicator occurred, the BTC price also plummeted down.</p>

<p>But while this decline in the price was happening, the metric had already reversed back to an uptrend. As it turned out, the cryptocurrency also did the same after finishing its drop. &#8220;In the current market structure, ESR acts as a magnet to Bitcoin&#8217;s spot price,&#8221; explains the analyst.</p>
<p>Earlier this month, the ESR again observed some decline, but it wasn&#8217;t long before the metric reversed its trend and resumed the upward trajectory. Recently, BTC has also been plunging, as its price has now gone below the $28,000 level.</p>
<p>If the pattern that followed earlier is anything to go by, this divergence between the two lines should mean that BTC will also reverse its current decline, in order to mimic what the ESR has been doing.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $27,600, down 6% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/IengeLko/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1533" height="911" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/kanchanara-8x1m8LytApU-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano At Risk Of Falling 8% If It Doesn&#8217;t Hold Above Key Support Line</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-at-risk-of-falling-8/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 16:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[adausd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528309</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Cardano price surged as it broke through a critical resistance trendline on its chart, a few days ago. However, the bullish momentum was short-lived, and ADA has since lost 0.5% of its value on the daily chart. The past week saw a significant depreciation of 14% in ADA&#8217;s value, with demand and accumulation both falling. As Bitcoin retraces on its chart, most altcoins have followed the same price direction. The technical outlook of the altcoin has also sided with the bears. For Cardano to regain momentum, buying strength needs to pick up over the next trading sessions. However, another push from the sellers can potentially cause ADA to lose its local support level, leading to a considerable fall in prices. Related Reading: MATIC Below Key Support Levels: What’s Next? Cardano has also formed a v-shaped top reversal pattern, indicating a decline in demand over the last trading sessions. The market capitalization of Cardano has fallen, suggesting increased sell orders at the time of writing. Cardano Price Analysis: One-Day Chart At the time of writing, ADA was trading at $0.38, experiencing a significant drop since losing the $0.40 price mark. Overhead resistance for the altcoin is currently at $0.40 and then at $0.42. Breaching the $0.42 price level could trigger bullish momentum. However, if Cardano fails to maintain its price above the immediate support level of $0.37, the bears could push the price down to $0.35. In the last trading session, the amount of Cardano traded was red, indicating that selling pressure had increased at press time. Technical Analysis Demand for Cardano has seen a steep decline following its loss of the $0.40 support line. At the time of writing, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) was parked below the 50-mark, forming a downtick, indicating that sellers had outnumbered buyers. Similarly, Cardano has fallen below the 20-Simple Moving Average line, implying that sellers are driving the price momentum in the market. Reclaiming the $0.40 mark could help Cardano rise above the 20-SMA, potentially aiding the coin&#8217;s recovery. At the time of writing, Cardano&#8217;s technical indicators showed sell signals in accordance with other indicators. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicated the price momentum and trend reversals via red histograms. These histograms are associated with the coin&#8217;s sell signal, indicating that the price could drop further before a reversal occurs. Related Reading: What’s Next For Ethereum Price As It Drops Below $2,000? Additionally, the Bollinger Bands, which measure price volatility and asset fluctuations, had opened up, signaling that Cardano may experience fluctuations. The upper band of the indicator serves as a critical resistance level for the altcoin. Moreover, broader market sentiment remains a significant factor influencing the asset&#8217;s price direction. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Cardano price surged as it broke through a critical resistance trendline on its chart, a few days ago. However, the bullish momentum was short-lived, and ADA has since lost 0.5% of its value on the daily chart. The past week saw a significant depreciation of 14% in ADA&#8217;s value, with demand and accumulation both falling.</p>
<p>As Bitcoin retraces on its chart, most altcoins have followed the same price direction. The technical outlook of the altcoin has also sided with the bears.</p>
<p>For Cardano to regain momentum, buying strength needs to pick up over the next trading sessions. However, another push from the sellers can potentially cause ADA to lose its local support level, leading to a considerable fall in prices.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/matic/matic-below-key-support-levels-whats-next/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MATIC Below Key Support Levels: What’s Next?</a></p>
<p>Cardano has also formed a v-shaped top reversal pattern, indicating a decline in demand over the last trading sessions. The market capitalization of Cardano has fallen, suggesting increased sell orders at the time of writing.</p>
<h2>Cardano Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-528321 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSD_2023-04-24_18-10-58.png" alt="Cardano" width="1816" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSD_2023-04-24_18-10-58.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSD_2023-04-24_18-10-58-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSD_2023-04-24_18-10-58-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSD_2023-04-24_18-10-58-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSD_2023-04-24_18-10-58-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSD_2023-04-24_18-10-58-750x343.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSD_2023-04-24_18-10-58-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>At the time of writing, ADA was trading at $0.38, experiencing a significant drop since losing the $0.40 price mark. Overhead resistance for the altcoin is currently at $0.40 and then at $0.42. Breaching the $0.42 price level could trigger bullish momentum.</p>
<p>However, if Cardano fails to maintain its price above the immediate support level of $0.37, the bears could push the price down to $0.35. In the last trading session, the amount of Cardano traded was red, indicating that selling pressure had increased at press time.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-528325 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSD_2023-04-24_18-11-40.png" alt="Cardano" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSD_2023-04-24_18-11-40.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSD_2023-04-24_18-11-40-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSD_2023-04-24_18-11-40-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSD_2023-04-24_18-11-40-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSD_2023-04-24_18-11-40-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSD_2023-04-24_18-11-40-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSD_2023-04-24_18-11-40-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>Demand for Cardano has seen a steep decline following its loss of the $0.40 support line. At the time of writing, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) was parked below the 50-mark, forming a downtick, indicating that sellers had outnumbered buyers.</p>
<p>Similarly, Cardano has fallen below the 20-Simple Moving Average line, implying that sellers are driving the price momentum in the market. Reclaiming the $0.40 mark could help Cardano rise above the 20-SMA, potentially aiding the coin&#8217;s recovery.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-528335 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSD_2023-04-24_18-12-11.png" alt="Cardano" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSD_2023-04-24_18-12-11.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSD_2023-04-24_18-12-11-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSD_2023-04-24_18-12-11-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSD_2023-04-24_18-12-11-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSD_2023-04-24_18-12-11-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSD_2023-04-24_18-12-11-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ADAUSD_2023-04-24_18-12-11-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>At the time of writing, Cardano&#8217;s technical indicators showed sell signals in accordance with other indicators. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicated the price momentum and trend reversals via red histograms.</p>
<p>These histograms are associated with the coin&#8217;s sell signal, indicating that the price could drop further before a reversal occurs.</p>

<p>Additionally, the Bollinger Bands, which measure price volatility and asset fluctuations, had opened up, signaling that Cardano may experience fluctuations.</p>
<p>The upper band of the indicator serves as a critical resistance level for the altcoin. Moreover, broader market sentiment remains a significant factor influencing the asset&#8217;s price direction.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/michael-fortsch-6CiqXsgGaM-unsplash-4-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana (SOL) Rebounding After A Major Drop, Will It Recover Previous Losses?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/solana/solana-sol-rebounding-after-a-major-drop-will-it-recover-previous-losses/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli Dambel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 15:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bear trend]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=528326</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Many investors are unsure what will happen to the Solana (SOL) price going forward after its recent 7 days decline of 13%. Will SOL make a strong comeback?  Solana has emerged as one of the most popular blockchains in the cryptocurrency industry due to its fast transactions and expanding ecosystem. However, it had a rough year in 2022, like others, and even worse due to the crash of FTX. Fast-forward to January 2023, SOL started the year at $9.9610 and steadily rose above $20. At one point, SOL traded at $26, but it declined to $21.65% today due to a market-wide bearish trend. As a result, both investors and retail traders wonder if there&#8217;ll be a potential rebound or more dips in the future. Reason Behind The SOL Pullback Solana (SOL), like many other cryptocurrencies, has been affected by the recent market collapse. SOL&#8217;s price may drop further due to a loss in demand, general negative sentiment, and selling pressure in the cryptocurrency market. Also, the sudden decline of other significant cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum has impacted SOL negatively, leading to a decrease in its price. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Whales On Buying Spree, Add 311 Billion Tokens During Price Dip SOL had a busy few weeks, reaching a remarkable high of $24.7 on April 15. Besides, futures traders with long positions incurred losses of about $650 million due to the falling price of major crypto assets. The liquidations were worse in Binance and OKX and continued till Sunday, April 23. Solana Bearish Trend Continues, When Will It End? A negative trend remains as SOL dropped to $21.33 today after encountering a resistance level of $22.35 earlier. SOL has been trading in a downtrend pattern since today&#8217;s trading session. It appears that the bears are holding their ground as SOL is trading at $21.57, with a minor recovery. SOL must protect $21.11 as its first defense against further losses, and the next significant support level will be below the $20 level if the bears continue to be in charge. If the market&#8217;s structure changes, the resistance to any further gains may be located near $22.35 at this time. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Price Holds Above $0.00001 – Is It Time For A Rally? The price has fluctuated between $21.11 and $21.40 during the last few hours, making it difficult for the bulls to push it beyond $22.35. Technical indicators like the RSI and MACD exhibit a gloomy picture. The RSI is currently at 41.83, indicating that the market is close to the oversold region and that SOL may decline further if the buyers don&#8217;t take back control.  Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Many investors are unsure what will happen to the Solana (SOL) price going forward after its recent 7 days decline of 13%. Will SOL make a strong comeback? </p>
<p>Solana has emerged as one of the most popular blockchains in the cryptocurrency industry due to its fast transactions and expanding ecosystem. However, it had a rough year in 2022, like others, and even worse due to the crash of FTX.</p>
<p>Fast-forward to January 2023, SOL started the year at $9.9610 and steadily rose above $20. At one point, SOL traded at $26, but it declined to $21.65% today due to a market-wide bearish trend. As a result, both investors and retail traders wonder if there&#8217;ll be a potential rebound or more dips in the future.</p>
<h2><b>Reason Behind The SOL Pullback</b></h2>
<p>Solana (SOL), like many other cryptocurrencies, has been affected by the recent market collapse. SOL&#8217;s price may drop further due to a loss in demand, general negative sentiment, and selling pressure in the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p>Also, the sudden decline of other significant cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum has impacted SOL negatively, leading to a decrease in its price.</p>

<p>SOL had a busy few weeks, reaching a remarkable high of $24.7 on April 15. Besides, futures traders with <a href="https://twitter.com/defispotlight/status/1650456680965246977" rel="nofollow">long positions</a> incurred losses of about $650 million due to the falling price of major crypto assets. The liquidations were worse in Binance and OKX and continued till Sunday, April 23.</p>
<h2><b>Solana Bearish Trend Continues, When Will It End?</b></h2>
<p>A negative trend remains as SOL dropped to $21.33 today after encountering a resistance level of $22.35 earlier. SOL has been trading in a downtrend pattern since today&#8217;s trading session. It appears that the bears are holding their ground as SOL is trading at $21.57, with a minor recovery.</p>
<p>SOL must protect $21.11 as its first defense against further losses, and the next significant support level will be below the $20 level if the bears continue to be in charge. If the market&#8217;s structure changes, the resistance to any further gains may be located near $22.35 at this time.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-price-holds-support-is-it-time-for-a-rally/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Shiba Inu Price Holds Above $0.00001 – Is It Time For A Rally?</a></p>
<p>The price has fluctuated between $21.11 and $21.40 during the last few hours, making it difficult for the bulls to push it beyond $22.35.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-528331 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-24_17-57-24-860x501.png" alt="Solana (SOL) Rebounding After A Major Drop, Will It Recover Previous Losses?" width="860" height="501" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-24_17-57-24-860x501.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-24_17-57-24-460x268.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-24_17-57-24-768x447.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-24_17-57-24-750x437.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-24_17-57-24-1140x664.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/SOLUSD_2023-04-24_17-57-24.png 1437w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>Technical indicators like the RSI and MACD exhibit a gloomy picture. The RSI is currently at 41.83, indicating that the market is close to the oversold region and that SOL may decline further if the buyers don&#8217;t take back control. </p>
<p>Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Solana-1260x787-1-1-460x287.png" width="460" height="287" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
