<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:49:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Stablecoin Exchange Deposits Remain Low, What Does It Mean For Bitcoin?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/stablecoin/stablecoin-exchange-deposits-remain-low-mean-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 14:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin Exchange Deposits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin Exchange Withdrawals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542899</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the stablecoin exchange deposits have remained low recently. Here&#8217;s what this may mean for Bitcoin. Stablecoin Exchange Deposits Stay Low, While Withdrawals Jump As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, the fact that the stablecoin exchange withdrawals have spiked while deposits have stayed low may be slightly alarming for BTC. There are two indicators of relevance here: the &#8220;stablecoin exchange withdrawing transactions&#8221; and the &#8220;stablecoin exchange depositing transactions.&#8221; As their names already imply, these metrics track the total number of withdrawals and deposit transfers, respectively, that investors of the ERC-20 stables are making right now. Generally, investors seek the safety of these fiat-tied tokens whenever they want to escape the volatility associated with the other assets in the sector. Eventually, when these holders think that the prices are right to jump back into the volatile markets, they swap their stables back for their desired cryptocurrency. These investors usually make use of centralized exchanges for this purpose. So, when the exchange withdrawing transactions are high, it can be a sign that holders are exchanging coins like Bitcoin for stablecoins right now. Related Reading: Here’s What On-Chain Data Reveals About XRP Rally On the other hand, the deposits being high can imply these investors are looking to buy volatile assets using their stables. Naturally, in the former case, Bitcoin and others may feel a bearish effect from the selling, while in the latter case, the prices might see a bullish boost. Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the stablecoin exchange withdrawing and depositing transactions over the past couple of years: Looks like only one of these two metrics has had a high value recently &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As displayed in the above graph, the stablecoin exchange depositing transactions metric has been relatively low for a while now. This would suggest that there may not be enough demand for converting stables into other assets right now. From the graph, it&#8217;s visible that the last time the indicator spiked was back in March of this year. Following the deposits back then, Bitcoin observed a sharp rebound in its price as the rally saw a revival. The timing of these inflows might mean that it was the buying from these stablecoin holders that had provided the fuel for the BTC surge. Related Reading: Bitcoin MVRV At Critical Level: Will A Break Happen? In the graph, the quant has marked other similar past instances as well. It looks like the BTC price generally observes a rise after stablecoin deposits spike, given that the withdrawals are low at the same time. Recently, however, only the stablecoin withdrawals have observed a spike, implying that investors are taking these tokens away from exchanges, likely to hold onto them for extended periods in self-custody. As there aren&#8217;t any deposits happening to counteract this, the BTC price has been struggling recently. If the trend continues and more stablecoin withdrawals continue to take place, it&#8217;s possible that the cryptocurrency could take a hit in the short term. Bitcoin Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $30,200, up 1% in the last week. BTC has taken a hit recently &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from iStock.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows the stablecoin exchange deposits have remained low recently. Here&#8217;s what this may mean for Bitcoin.</p>
<h2>Stablecoin Exchange Deposits Stay Low, While Withdrawals Jump</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/64b48531d3b74754036d682e-Retail-Demand-Weakening" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, the fact that the stablecoin exchange withdrawals have spiked while deposits have stayed low may be slightly alarming for BTC.</p>
<p>There are two indicators of relevance here: the &#8220;stablecoin exchange withdrawing transactions&#8221; and the &#8220;stablecoin exchange depositing transactions.&#8221; As their names already imply, these metrics track the total number of withdrawals and deposit transfers, respectively, that investors of the ERC-20 stables are making right now.</p>
<p>Generally, investors seek the safety of these <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/stablecoin/stablecoins-market-cap-shows-rise-why-bullish-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">fiat-tied tokens</a> whenever they want to escape the volatility associated with the other assets in the sector. Eventually, when these holders think that the prices are right to jump back into the volatile markets, they swap their stables back for their desired cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>These investors usually make use of centralized exchanges for this purpose. So, when the exchange withdrawing transactions are high, it can be a sign that holders are exchanging coins like Bitcoin for stablecoins right now.</p>

<p>On the other hand, the deposits being high can imply these investors are looking to buy volatile assets using their stables. Naturally, in the former case, Bitcoin and others may feel a bearish effect from the selling, while in the latter case, the prices might see a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/exchanges-large-stablecoin-inflows-what-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">bullish boost</a>.</p>
<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the stablecoin exchange withdrawing and depositing transactions over the past couple of years:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/148277/quicktake/QNL53ERXk_3be09f44191d25a3cc63140518c3bd97943329e7792b60a59df90872cbddb6a8.png" alt="Stablecoin Deposits And Bitcoin" width="1280" height="527"/></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the stablecoin exchange depositing transactions metric has been relatively low for a while now. This would suggest that there may not be enough demand for converting stables into other assets right now.</p>
<p>From the graph, it&#8217;s visible that the last time the indicator spiked was back in March of this year. Following the deposits back then, Bitcoin observed a sharp rebound in its price as the rally saw a revival. The timing of these inflows might mean that it was the buying from these stablecoin holders that had provided the fuel for the BTC surge.</p>

<p>In the graph, the quant has marked other similar past instances as well. It looks like the BTC price generally observes a rise after stablecoin deposits spike, given that the withdrawals are low at the same time.</p>
<p>Recently, however, only the stablecoin withdrawals have observed a spike, implying that investors are taking these tokens away from exchanges, likely to hold onto them for extended periods in self-custody.</p>
<p>As there aren&#8217;t any deposits happening to counteract this, the BTC price has been <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-stuck-tight-range-btc-decompress-big-move/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">struggling</a> recently. If the trend continues and more stablecoin withdrawals continue to take place, it&#8217;s possible that the cryptocurrency could take a hit in the short term.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $30,200, up 1% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/pbJn5tNc/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1359416693-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Celsius Is Selling, More Pain For BNB, LINK, And SNX?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/celsius-is-selling-more-pain-for-bnb-link-and-snx/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 13:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BONE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celsius]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FalconX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OKX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ZRX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542947</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Celsius, the bankrupt crypto lender, has started selling its non-Bitcoin and non-Ethereum crypto assets, records on July 17 indicate. According to on-chain data from Lookonchain, Celsius has transferred approximately $23.5 million of various cryptocurrencies, including BNB, ZRX, LINK, BONE, and SNX, to FalconX and OKX, respectively. Different amounts of these tokens were transferred by Celsius, a move that, while it could be positive for creditors, may impact the token valuations of those projects. Celsius Selling Altcoins  Lookonchain revealed that Celsius moved $8.5 million worth of LINK, the native currency of Chainlink, a middleware protocol linking on-chain smart contracts to external but verified data. At the same time, it also moved $7.84 million worth of SNX, the native token of Synthetix, a protocol allowing users to trade derivatives called synths, was transferred. Celsius also went on to move $3 million worth of BNB, the coin behind the sprawling Binance ecosystem, $2.26 million worth of 1INCH, the token aggregator, and $1.9 million worth of ZRX, the token behind one of the first decentralized finance platforms, Ox Protocol. The bankrupt lender also moved $709,678 worth of FTT, the token behind the collapsed FTX exchange, to FalconX. In response, FalconX has started depositing these tokens to Binance for selling. Related Reading: $18 Billion Worth Of Bitcoin Accumulated At $30,200 – BTC Bull Run Incoming? The only token moved to a different exchange was BONE, where Celsius moved $235,000 of the meme token to the popular cryptocurrency exchange, OKX. While OKX caters to retail and institutional investors, FalconX serves institutional investors, offering diverse services, including liquidity provision and risk management. So far, a large tranche of tokens held by Celsius has moved through FalconX. In late June, Judge Martin Glenn of the Southern District of New York allowed Celsius to start converting all their tokens to either Bitcoin or Ethereum, the two currencies that would be allowed to pay back creditors. All conversions were set to begin on July 1. Altcoins Taking A Hit The transfer also comes amid a favorable ruling that saw a US Judge say XRP, one of the major altcoins, is not a security and can be traded like a commodity, just like Bitcoin. However, even though news pumped altcoins, mostly XRP, momentum tapered during the weekend, and most altcoins fell back from last week&#8217;s highs. Related Reading: XRP Whales Ride The Crypto Surge, As Ripple Token Notches 62% Price Spike Among the impacted tokens included BNB, the native currency behind Binance, the world&#8217;s largest ecosystem. The coin currently oscillates within a $30 range as bears dominate price action. From the daily chart, BNB has resistance at $260 and is down over 30% from April 2023 highs.  LINK and SNX are seeing similar price actions, both recording losses on the 24-hour chart. LINK is down 2.97% to be trading at $6.63, while SNX is nursing 3.94% losses, bringing its price to $2.64. Feature image from Canva, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Celsius, the bankrupt crypto lender, has started selling its non-Bitcoin and non-Ethereum crypto assets, records on July 17 indicate. According to on-chain data from Lookonchain, Celsius has transferred approximately $23.5 million of various cryptocurrencies, including BNB, ZRX, LINK, BONE, and SNX, to FalconX and OKX, respectively. </p>
<p>Different amounts of these tokens were transferred by Celsius, a move that, while it could be positive for creditors, may impact the token valuations of those projects.</p>
<h2>Celsius Selling Altcoins </h2>
<p>Lookonchain <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1680790940842340357?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">revealed</a> that Celsius moved $8.5 million worth of LINK, the native currency of Chainlink, a middleware protocol linking on-chain smart contracts to external but verified data. At the same time, it also moved $7.84 million worth of SNX, the native token of Synthetix, a protocol allowing users to trade derivatives called synths, was transferred. </p>
<p>Celsius also went on to move $3 million worth of BNB, the coin behind the sprawling Binance ecosystem, $2.26 million worth of 1INCH, the token aggregator, and $1.9 million worth of ZRX, the token behind one of the first decentralized finance platforms, Ox Protocol. </p>
<p>The bankrupt lender also moved $709,678 worth of FTT, the token behind the collapsed FTX exchange, to FalconX. In response, FalconX has <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1680793493701292033" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">started</a> depositing these tokens to Binance for selling.</p>

<p>The only token moved to a different exchange was BONE, where Celsius moved $235,000 of the meme token to the popular cryptocurrency exchange, OKX. </p>
<p>While OKX caters to retail and institutional investors, FalconX serves institutional investors, offering diverse services, including liquidity provision and risk management. So far, a large tranche of tokens held by Celsius has moved through FalconX.</p>
<p>In late June, Judge Martin Glenn of the Southern District of New York <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cases.stretto.com/public/x191/11749/PLEADINGS/1174906302380000000027.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">allowed</a> Celsius to start converting all their tokens to either Bitcoin or Ethereum, the two currencies that would be allowed to pay back creditors. All conversions were set to begin on July 1.</p>
<h2>Altcoins Taking A Hit</h2>
<p>The transfer also comes amid a favorable ruling that saw a US Judge say XRP, one of the major altcoins, is not a security and can be traded like a commodity, just like Bitcoin. However, even though news pumped altcoins, mostly XRP, momentum tapered during the weekend, and most altcoins fell back from last week&#8217;s highs.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/xrp-whales-ride-the-crypto-surge-as-ripple-token-notches-62-price-spike/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">XRP Whales Ride The Crypto Surge, As Ripple Token Notches 62% Price Spike</a></p>
<p>Among the impacted tokens included BNB, the native currency behind Binance, the world&#8217;s largest ecosystem. The coin currently oscillates within a $30 range as bears dominate price action. From the daily chart, BNB has resistance at $260 and is down over 30% from April 2023 highs. </p>
<p>LINK and SNX are seeing similar price actions, both recording losses on the 24-hour chart. LINK is down 2.97% to be trading at $6.63, while SNX is nursing 3.94% losses, bringing its price to $2.64.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/DdcSOCjJ/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/DdcSOCjJ/" alt="BNB price on July 17| Source: BNBUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Celsius-BNB-Bitcoin-Ethereum-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polkadot (DOT) Price Momentum Builds As Open Interest Climbs &#8211; Details</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/polkadot-dot-price-momentum-builds-as-open-interest-climbs-details/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 12:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOT Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polkadot]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542923</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Polkadot (DOT) has enjoyed a successful three-week period, with bullish investors maintaining their position at the forefront despite fluctuations in the market. In addition, the recent legal victory of Ripple against the US Securities and Exchange Commission triggered a positive response across the entire market, benefiting not only significant cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) but also altcoins in general. Nevertheless, it is essential to note that Bitcoin and Ether experienced notable downward corrections in the short term after they attempted to surge higher last week. As a result, there might be some selling pressure soon for these leading cryptocurrencies, which could potentially harm the price of DOT. Given this scenario, how can DOT bulls regain control and overcome a potential market correction? DOT Price Update: Minor Dip, But Open Interest Improves The latest update on DOT&#8217;s price from CoinGecko shows that it currently stands at $5.30. While the cryptocurrency experienced a slight decline of 1.7% over the past 24 hours, it still managed to maintain a seven-day rally of 4.8%. However, a closer analysis of the DOT price report shows some concerning indicators. Source: Coingecko According to a report, by mid-June, the Open Interest had significantly diminished compared to its April levels, signaling a bearish sentiment. However, as the month advanced, a reversal in this trend emerged. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Encounters Familiar Resistance, Prompting Concerns About Bull Run Source: Coinglass/AMBCrypto The declining Open Interest in April, which refers to the number of open contracts in the market, served as an early indicator that hinted at the forthcoming bearish sentiment. As traders and investors reduced their positions and interest waned, it reflected a growing caution and skepticism in the market. This downward trend in Open Interest implied a decrease in market participation and a potential lack of confidence in the prevailing bullish trends. Related Reading: USTC Surprises With Nearly 60% Rally – What’s Going On? However, as June unfolded, a gradual and encouraging shift in market sentiment began to take shape. Market participants started to exhibit a more optimistic outlook, which was reflected in the increasing Open Interest. This surge in OI suggested renewed interest and activity, as traders and investors re-entered the market and established new positions. DOT market cap currently at $6.3 billion. Chart: TradingView.com Polkadot Potential Rebound Tied To Bitcoin&#8217;s Resilience On the other hand, if BTC can stabilize or even climb back above $31,000, DOT will likely follow suit. The correlation between BTC and altcoins like DOT has been a well-established trend in the cryptocurrency market. BTC, the dominant cryptocurrency and a significant influencer of market sentiment, often sets the tone for the overall market direction. If Bitcoin regains stability and exhibits a bullish move, it tends to ignite a favorable view among traders and investors. This positive sentiment, in turn, could extend to altcoins like DOT. DOT seven-day price movement. Source: CoinMarketCap Therefore, for DOT bulls looking to reclaim their yard and counteract the potential negative impact of a market correction, monitoring BTC&#8217;s performance closely becomes crucial. If Bitcoin can stabilize or, ideally, recover above the significant resistance level of $31k, it would likely create a favorable environment for DOT to regain momentum. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from VOA News]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Polkadot (DOT) has enjoyed a successful three-week period, with bullish investors maintaining their position at the forefront despite fluctuations in the market. </p>
<p>In addition, the recent legal victory of Ripple against the US Securities and Exchange Commission triggered a positive response across the entire market, benefiting not only significant cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) but also altcoins in general.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, it is essential to note that Bitcoin and Ether experienced notable downward corrections in the short term after they attempted to surge higher last week. As a result, there might be some selling pressure soon for these leading cryptocurrencies, which could potentially harm the price of DOT.</p>
<p>Given this scenario, how can DOT bulls regain control and overcome a potential market correction?</p>
<h2><strong>DOT Price Update: Minor Dip, But Open Interest Improves</strong></h2>
<p>The latest update on <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/polkadot" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">DOT&#8217;s price from CoinGecko</a> shows that it currently stands at $5.30. While the cryptocurrency experienced a slight decline of 1.7% over the past 24 hours, it still managed to maintain a seven-day rally of 4.8%. However, a closer analysis of the DOT price report shows some concerning indicators.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-542936" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-106.png" alt="" width="1139" height="62" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-106.png 1139w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-106-460x25.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-106-860x47.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-106-768x42.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-106-750x41.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1139px) 100vw, 1139px"/></p>

<p><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://ambcrypto.com/polkadot-on-the-verge-of-initiating-another-rally-as/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According to a report</a>, by mid-June, the Open Interest had significantly diminished compared to its April levels, signaling a bearish sentiment. However, as the month advanced, a reversal in this trend emerged.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-encounters-familiar-resistance/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Shiba Inu Encounters Familiar Resistance, Prompting Concerns About Bull Run</a></p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-542951 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-109-860x259.png" alt="" width="860" height="259" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-109-860x259.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-109-460x139.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-109-768x232.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-109-750x226.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-109-1140x344.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-109.png 1453w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>The declining Open Interest in April, which refers to the number of open contracts in the market, served as an early indicator that hinted at the forthcoming bearish sentiment.</p>
<p>As traders and investors reduced their positions and interest waned, it reflected a growing caution and skepticism in the market. This downward trend in Open Interest implied a decrease in market participation and a potential lack of confidence in the prevailing bullish trends.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ustc-surprises-with-nearly-60-rally-whats-going-on/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">USTC Surprises With Nearly 60% Rally – What’s Going On?</a></p>
<p>However, as June unfolded, a gradual and encouraging shift in market sentiment began to take shape. Market participants started to exhibit a more optimistic outlook, which was reflected in the increasing Open Interest. This surge in OI suggested renewed interest and activity, as traders and investors re-entered the market and established new positions.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/r0mjpf8c/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>

<h2><strong>Polkadot Potential Rebound Tied To Bitcoin&#8217;s Resilience</strong></h2>
<p>On the other hand, if <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-dips-over-weekend-other-013056846.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTC can stabilize</a> or even climb back above $31,000, DOT will likely follow suit. The correlation between BTC and altcoins like DOT has been a well-established trend in the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p>BTC, the dominant cryptocurrency and a significant influencer of market sentiment, often sets the tone for the overall market direction. If Bitcoin regains stability and exhibits a bullish move, it tends to ignite a favorable view among traders and investors. This positive sentiment, in turn, could extend to altcoins like DOT.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-542940 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-107-860x378.png" alt="" width="860" height="378" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-107-860x378.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-107-460x202.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-107-768x338.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-107-750x330.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-107.png 1034w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>Therefore, for DOT bulls looking to reclaim their yard and counteract the potential negative impact of a market correction, monitoring BTC&#8217;s performance closely becomes crucial. If Bitcoin can stabilize or, ideally, recover above the significant resistance level of $31k, it would likely create a favorable environment for DOT to regain momentum.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from VOA News</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-108-460x310.png" width="460" height="310" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Big Bitcoin Move Ahead: Bollinger Bands See Extreme Squeeze</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/big-bitcoin-move-ahead-bollinger-bands-see-extreme-squeeze/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bollinger bands]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542925</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Since the Bitcoin price reached a new yearly high of $31,840 last week, only to invalidate the bullish breakout within a few hours and fall towards $30,000, there has been a strange tranquility in the market. Already since June 23, BTC has been in the trading range between $29,800 and $31,300, with every breakout attempt to the upside and downside having failed within a very short period of time. However, one of the most prominent technical indicators, the Bollinger Bands, predict that this calm may soon be over. Created by the esteemed trader John Bollinger, these bands provide invaluable insights into market volatility and potential price levels. Bollinger Bands Predict Big Move For Bitcoin The Bollinger Bands consist of three distinct lines on a price chart: the middle band, the upper band, and the lower band. The middle band is a simple moving average (SMA) that represents the average price over a specified period. The upper and lower bands are derived from the middle band, with the upper band usually set two standard deviations above the SMA, and the lower band set two standard deviations below it. Related Reading: $18 Billion Worth Of Bitcoin Accumulated At $30,200 – BTC Bull Run Incoming? The primary purpose of the Bollinger Bands is to measure market volatility. When the price of an asset experiences significant fluctuations, the bands widen, indicating increased volatility. Conversely, during periods of reduced price movement, the bands contract, indicating lower volatility. This contraction is commonly referred to as a &#8220;squeeze,&#8221; where the upper and lower bands come closer together, forming a narrowing price channel. When the Bollinger Bands squeeze, the potential for a significant price movement looms. The squeeze suggests that the market is in a state of temporary equilibrium, akin to a coiled spring ready to release its stored energy. The direction of the breakout determines whether it&#8217;s a bullish or bearish signal. Up Or Down? Glassnode, a respected on-chain data provider, highlighted today the current state of the Bitcoin market, noting a remarkably low volatility environment. The 20-day Bollinger Bands are experiencing an extreme squeeze, with a mere 4.2% price range separating the upper and lower bands. This suggests that Bitcoin is currently in a period of limited price movement, “making this the quietest Bitcoin market since the lull in early January.” As Bitcoin investors may remember, the Bollinger Bands squeeze in January marked the end of a lengthy downtrend. After the FTX collapse, the BTC market was in a state of shock paralysis, which was ultimately resolved by Bollinger Bands squeeze, leading to a 42% price increase in 26 days. Related Reading: Perfect Storm: Why Bitcoin &#38; Crypto Are Poised For A Dramatic Recovery The Bollinger Bands&#8217; squeeze, combined with diminishing trading volumes, creates a scenario of mounting pressure in the Bitcoin market. As trading volume declines, the potential energy stored in this coiled spring intensifies. According to the analysts at CryptoCon, the bullish scenario is the one to be favored at the moment. &#8220;When Bitcoin volatility gets low in a bear market, it&#8217;s very bearish. When volatility gets low in a bull market, it&#8217;s insanely bullish,&#8221; the analysts say. As Bitcoin is unanimously seen to be at the start of a new bull market, a strong move to the upside could be in store. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Since the Bitcoin price reached a new yearly high of $31,840 last week, only to invalidate the bullish breakout within a few hours and fall towards $30,000, there has been a strange tranquility in the market. Already since June 23, BTC has been in the trading range between $29,800 and $31,300, with every breakout attempt to the upside and downside having failed within a very short period of time.</p>
<p>However, one of the most prominent technical indicators, the Bollinger Bands, predict that this calm may soon be over. Created by the esteemed trader John Bollinger, these bands provide invaluable insights into market volatility and potential price levels.</p>
<h2>Bollinger Bands Predict Big Move For Bitcoin</h2>
<p>The Bollinger Bands consist of three distinct lines on a price chart: the middle band, the upper band, and the lower band. The middle band is a simple moving average (SMA) that represents the average price over a specified period. The upper and lower bands are derived from the middle band, with the upper band usually set two standard deviations above the SMA, and the lower band set two standard deviations below it.</p>

<p>The primary purpose of the Bollinger Bands is to measure market volatility. When the price of an asset experiences significant fluctuations, the bands widen, indicating increased volatility. Conversely, during periods of reduced price movement, the bands contract, indicating lower volatility. This contraction is commonly referred to as a &#8220;squeeze,&#8221; where the upper and lower bands come closer together, forming a narrowing price channel.</p>
<p>When the Bollinger Bands squeeze, the potential for a significant price movement looms. The squeeze suggests that the market is in a state of temporary equilibrium, akin to a coiled spring ready to release its stored energy. The direction of the breakout determines whether it&#8217;s a bullish or bearish signal.</p>
<h2>Up Or Down?</h2>
<p>Glassnode, a respected on-chain data provider, highlighted today the current state of the Bitcoin market, <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1680875530244042752" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">noting</a> a remarkably low volatility environment. The 20-day Bollinger Bands are experiencing an extreme squeeze, with a mere 4.2% price range separating the upper and lower bands. This suggests that Bitcoin is currently in a period of limited price movement, “making this the quietest Bitcoin market since the lull in early January.”</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-542937 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1OrNtyX0AMroPu-scaled.jpg" alt="Bitcoin Bollinger Bands" width="2560" height="1475" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1OrNtyX0AMroPu-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1OrNtyX0AMroPu-460x265.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1OrNtyX0AMroPu-860x496.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1OrNtyX0AMroPu-768x443.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1OrNtyX0AMroPu-1536x885.jpg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1OrNtyX0AMroPu-2048x1180.jpg 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1OrNtyX0AMroPu-750x432.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1OrNtyX0AMroPu-1140x657.jpg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px"/>
<p>As Bitcoin investors may remember, the Bollinger Bands squeeze in January marked the end of a lengthy downtrend. After the FTX collapse, the BTC market was in a state of shock paralysis, which was ultimately resolved by Bollinger Bands squeeze, leading to a 42% price increase in 26 days.</p>

<p>The Bollinger Bands&#8217; squeeze, combined with diminishing trading volumes, creates a scenario of mounting pressure in the Bitcoin market. As trading volume declines, the potential energy stored in this coiled spring intensifies.</p>
<p>According to the analysts at CryptoCon, the bullish scenario is the one to be <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoCon_/status/1677692883627831296" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">favored</a> at the moment. &#8220;When Bitcoin volatility gets low in a bear market, it&#8217;s very bearish. When volatility gets low in a bull market, it&#8217;s insanely bullish,&#8221; the analysts say. As Bitcoin is unanimously seen to be at the start of a new bull market, a strong move to the upside could be in store.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-542939 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-17_12-53-24.png" alt="Bitcoin price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-17_12-53-24.png 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-17_12-53-24-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-17_12-53-24-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-17_12-53-24-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-17_12-53-24-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-17_12-53-24-2048x944.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-17_12-53-24-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-17_12-53-24-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3628px) 100vw, 3628px"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1305769484-1-460x272.jpg" width="460" height="272" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Whales Ride The Crypto Surge, As Ripple Token Notches 62% Price Spike</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/xrp-whales-ride-the-crypto-surge-as-ripple-token-notches-62-price-spike/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 10:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542912</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[XRP is now witnessing a surge in network activity as prominent holders of the cryptocurrency make their moves.  The latest findings from Lookonchain, a renowned data analytics firm, shed light on the purchase and sale patterns of XRP whales on the Binance Smart Chain (BSC), signaling a potential rise in selling activity within the market. Ripple&#8217;s triumph over the SEC has undoubtedly injected a fresh wave of confidence into the XRP community. With the regulatory cloud dissipating, investors and holders are now eager to capitalize on the newfound clarity surrounding the token&#8217;s status. As a result, the actions of these notable whales have become a focal point of interest for market observers and enthusiasts alike. Related Reading: USTC Surprises With Nearly 60% Rally – What’s Going On? XRP Whales&#8217; Purchasing Habits Revealed: Insight From Lookonchain Based on analysis by Lookonchain, the transactional behavior of four influential whales has come to light. Each of these whales demonstrates distinct patterns in their purchasing habits, shedding light on their strategies within the crypto market. 1/ Did whales sell $XRP as the price of $XRP rises? Let&#8217;s check the top 4 whales of $XRP on the #BSC.👇 pic.twitter.com/cwkXIcK6s2 — Lookonchain (@lookonchain) July 15, 2023 One of the whales, known as &#8220;0xf522,&#8221; has amassed a staggering 25 million XRP, equivalent to $18 million, between April 22 and November 24, 2022. Interestingly, this particular whale has refrained from selling any of their holdings thus far.  Source: Lookonchain Another notable participant, identified as &#8220;0x513d,&#8221; acquired 10 million units of the coin at an average price of $0.45 per token. Following the recent surge in XRP&#8217;s value, this whale has deposited 5.4 million XRP, worth around $4.3 million, into Binance. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Encounters Familiar Resistance, Prompting Concerns About Bull Run By taking advantage of the recent price rally, &#8220;0x513d&#8221; demonstrates a more proactive approach, capitalizing on the upward momentum of XRP. Source: Coingecko At present, Coingecko displays XRP&#8217;s price at $0.7412, reflecting a 2.9% rally within the past 24 hours alone. Over the course of the previous seven days, XRP has experienced a remarkable surge of 58.6%.  Ex-Ripple Chief Affirms Company&#8217;s Limited Market Influence Amid XRP&#8217;s Surge Meanwhile, Matt Hamilton, the former Director of Developer Relations at Ripple, clarified on Twitter that Ripple&#8217;s influence on the market is relatively constrained when considering the global daily sales volume of XRP. Ripple are the single largest holder of XRP with something like 48B XRP. Most of it is held in escrow contracts that release each month. Ripple sell a small portion of that and put the rest back in new escrow contracts. — Matt Hamilton (@HammerToe) July 16, 2023 This assertion holds true even in light of the recent surge in XRP&#8217;s value following the resolution of the Ripple-SEC case.  He stressed that the price movements of XRP are primarily governed by market forces and the performance of Bitcoin (BTC), underscoring the interplay between these factors in shaping the cryptocurrency&#8217;s trajectory. XRP market cap closing in to the $39 billion level. Chart: TradingView.com Hamilton explicitly stated that Ripple does not have authority over either XRP or the XRP Ledger (XRPL), ensuring any misunderstandings are clarified. In order to stress this notion further, he proposed the potential scenario where Ripple&#8217;s complete XRP holdings could be eradicated if the XRP community deemed it appropriate. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Blockchain News]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>XRP is now witnessing a surge in network activity as prominent holders of the cryptocurrency make their moves. </p>
<p>The latest findings from Lookonchain, a renowned data analytics firm, shed light on the purchase and <a href="https://u.today/xrp-whales-in-spotlight-as-cryptocurrency-prices-soar" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">sale patterns of XRP whales</a> on the Binance Smart Chain (BSC), signaling a potential rise in selling activity within the market.</p>
<p>Ripple&#8217;s triumph over the SEC has undoubtedly injected a fresh wave of confidence into the XRP community. With the regulatory cloud dissipating, investors and holders are now eager to capitalize on the newfound clarity surrounding the token&#8217;s status. </p>
<p>As a result, the actions of these notable whales have become a focal point of interest for market observers and enthusiasts alike.</p>

<h2><strong>XRP Whales&#8217; Purchasing Habits Revealed: Insight From Lookonchain</strong></h2>
<p>Based on analysis by <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1680240044261670913" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Lookonchain</a>, the transactional behavior of four influential whales has come to light. Each of these whales demonstrates distinct patterns in their purchasing habits, shedding light on their strategies within the crypto market.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">1/ Did whales sell <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24XRP&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$XRP</a> as the price of <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24XRP&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$XRP</a> rises?</p>
<p>Let&#8217;s check the top 4 whales of <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24XRP&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$XRP</a> on the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BSC?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#BSC</a>.<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f447.png" alt="👇" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/cwkXIcK6s2" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/cwkXIcK6s2</a></p>
<p>— Lookonchain (@lookonchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1680240044261670913?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>One of the whales, known as &#8220;0xf522,&#8221; has amassed a staggering 25 million XRP, equivalent to $18 million, between April 22 and November 24, 2022. Interestingly, this particular whale has refrained from selling any of their holdings thus far. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-542920 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-104-860x443.png" alt="" width="860" height="443" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-104-860x443.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-104-460x237.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-104-768x396.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-104-1536x791.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-104-750x386.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-104-1140x587.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-104.png 1598w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>Another notable participant, identified as &#8220;0x513d,&#8221; acquired 10 million units of the coin at an average price of $0.45 per token. Following the recent surge in XRP&#8217;s value, this whale has deposited 5.4 million XRP, worth around $4.3 million, into Binance.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-encounters-familiar-resistance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Shiba Inu Encounters Familiar Resistance, Prompting Concerns About Bull Run</a></p>
<p>By taking advantage of the recent price rally, &#8220;0x513d&#8221; demonstrates a more proactive approach, capitalizing on the upward momentum of XRP.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-542917" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-103.png" alt="" width="1156" height="59" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-103.png 1156w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-103-460x23.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-103-860x44.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-103-768x39.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-103-1140x58.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-103-750x38.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1156px) 100vw, 1156px"/></p>

<p>At present, <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/xrp" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Coingecko</a> displays XRP&#8217;s price at $0.7412, reflecting a 2.9% rally within the past 24 hours alone. Over the course of the previous seven days, XRP has experienced a remarkable surge of 58.6%. </p>
<h2><strong>Ex-Ripple Chief Affirms Company&#8217;s Limited Market Influence Amid XRP&#8217;s Surge</strong></h2>
<p>Meanwhile, Matt Hamilton, the former Director of Developer Relations at Ripple, <a href="https://twitter.com/HammerToe/status/1680418001500110848" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">clarified on Twitter</a> that Ripple&#8217;s influence on the market is relatively constrained when considering the global daily sales volume of XRP. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Ripple are the single largest holder of XRP with something like 48B XRP. Most of it is held in escrow contracts that release each month. Ripple sell a small portion of that and put the rest back in new escrow contracts.</p>
<p>— Matt Hamilton (@HammerToe) <a href="https://twitter.com/HammerToe/status/1680418001500110848?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>This assertion holds true even in light of the recent surge in XRP&#8217;s value following the resolution of the Ripple-SEC case. </p>
<p>He stressed that the price movements of XRP are primarily governed by market forces and the performance of Bitcoin (BTC), underscoring the interplay between these factors in shaping the cryptocurrency&#8217;s trajectory.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/OwgYMs1w/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>

<p>Hamilton explicitly stated that Ripple does not have authority over either XRP or the XRP Ledger (XRPL), ensuring any misunderstandings are clarified. In order to stress this notion further, he proposed the potential scenario where Ripple&#8217;s complete XRP holdings could be eradicated if the XRP community deemed it appropriate.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Blockchain News</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-105-460x241.png" width="460" height="241" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>$18 Billion Worth Of Bitcoin Accumulated At $30,200 &#8211; BTC Bull Run Incoming?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/520000-bitcoin-accumulated-at-30000-btc-bull-run/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 09:19:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin bulls]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ERPD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NVT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542858</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A record 592,000 Bitcoin, or roughly $17.8 billion, was accumulated when the coin was trading at $30,200, recent Glassnode data indicates. At this accumulation rate, suggesting possible demand, more entities bought more coins at the second fastest pace in the network&#8217;s history. This record was only broken when 637,000 BTC were bought at an average price of $16,500. 592,000 Bitcoin Bought At $30,200 The spike in Bitcoin accumulated at this price point preceded the decision by a United States court to rule that XRP, an altcoin issued from the XRP Ledger (XRPL), is a commodity, just like Bitcoin. The ruling on Friday, July 14, was received positively by the crypto community and temporarily lifted prices, sustaining Bitcoin above the psychological $30,000 mark. According to Glassnode, the Bitcoin Entity-Adjusted Economic Ratio Per Day (ERPD) is a metric designed to assess economic activity within the network, considering the number of entities participating. This metric is calculated by dividing the Network Value to Transactions (NVT) ratio by the entity-adjusted on-chain volume. In on-chain analysis, the NVT ratio represents the relationship between the market capitalization and the recorded on-chain trading volumes at a specific price point. A higher NVT ratio indicates a greater value than recorded trading volumes. Related Reading: Synthetix (SNX) Up By 35% In Anticipation Of New Decentralized Exchange While the NVT reading can be useful, it can also be misleading if the entities, or clustered addresses, involved in transactions are not accounted for. To correct this error, the ERPD integrates addresses involved at that price point, used in taking account of the market cap. This way, it can be easy to gauge the entities and total coins involved. Shifting Sentiment? The surge in Bitcoin ERPD development will also likely impact altcoins. Considering its liquidity and support across the board, Bitcoin sets the tone for other altcoins in crypto. Its performance and transactions can gauge market-wide sentiment, which might, in turn, change how altcoins are perceived in the current market conditions. Related Reading: Stablecoin TrueUSD To Be Fully Controlled By Asian Owner Still, some commentators on Twitter were unsure if the metric was a positive development or a position for further price crashes. One believes that most such transactions are conducted by &#8220;paper hands&#8221; who buy Bitcoin when the price increases and are set to sell at any moment of negative news. The spike in ERPD is also ahead of the Bitcoin halving event in 2024, which, reading on historical performances, may impact prices positively, even triggering a bull run. After halving, miners would receive fewer coins, releasing even fewer for circulation, a supply shock that may support prices. Feature image from Canva, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A record 592,000 Bitcoin, or roughly $17.8 billion, was accumulated when the coin was trading at $30,200, recent Glassnode <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1678357739905400832" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a> indicates. At this accumulation rate, suggesting possible demand, more entities bought more coins at the second fastest pace in the network&#8217;s history. This record was only broken when 637,000 BTC were bought at an average price of $16,500.</p>
<h2><strong>592,000 Bitcoin Bought At $30,200</strong></h2>
<p>The spike in Bitcoin accumulated at this price point preceded the decision by a United States court to rule that XRP, an altcoin issued from the XRP Ledger (XRPL), is a commodity, just like Bitcoin. The ruling on Friday, July 14, was received positively by the crypto community and temporarily lifted prices, sustaining Bitcoin above the psychological $30,000 mark.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/1oocVkq3/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/1oocVkq3/" alt="Bitcoin price on July 16| Source: BTCUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>
<p>According to Glassnode, the Bitcoin Entity-Adjusted Economic Ratio Per Day (ERPD) is a metric designed to assess economic activity within the network, considering the number of entities participating. This metric is calculated by dividing the Network Value to Transactions (NVT) ratio by the entity-adjusted on-chain volume. </p>
<p>In on-chain analysis, the NVT ratio represents the relationship between the market capitalization and the recorded on-chain trading volumes at a specific price point. A higher NVT ratio indicates a greater value than recorded trading volumes.</p>

<p>While the NVT reading can be useful, it can also be misleading if the entities, or clustered addresses, involved in transactions are not accounted for. To correct this error, the ERPD integrates addresses involved at that price point, used in taking account of the market cap. This way, it can be easy to gauge the entities and total coins involved.</p>
<h2><strong>Shifting Sentiment?</strong></h2>
<p>The surge in Bitcoin ERPD development will also likely impact altcoins. Considering its liquidity and support across the board, Bitcoin sets the tone for other altcoins in crypto. Its performance and transactions can gauge market-wide sentiment, which might, in turn, change how altcoins are perceived in the current market conditions.</p>

<p>Still, some commentators on Twitter were unsure if the metric was a positive development or a position for further price crashes. One <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/HamzaAa68799909/status/1680230591458066432" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">believes</a> that most such transactions are conducted by &#8220;paper hands&#8221; who buy Bitcoin when the price increases and are set to sell at any moment of negative news.</p>
<p>The spike in ERPD is also ahead of the Bitcoin halving event in 2024, which, reading on historical performances, may impact prices positively, even triggering a bull run. After halving, miners would receive fewer coins, releasing even fewer for circulation, a supply shock that may support prices.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Crypto-news-Template25-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Encounters Familiar Resistance, Prompting Concerns About Bull Run</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-encounters-familiar-resistance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 08:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542895</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) has faced a significant challenge in the form of the December 2022 low. This crucial level has proved a formidable barrier for SHIB bulls, thwarting their attempts to increase prices.  Despite recent upside movements, the resistance at this level has proven to be persistent, creating a precarious situation for the cryptocurrency.  As the price of SHIB hovers in this area, the question arises: Will the selling pressure overpower the bulls&#8217; determination and cause a reversal in the price action? Shiba Inu Faces Bearish Order Block And Potential Liquidity Hunt SHIB faces a significant challenge as its December 2022 low coincides with a bearish order block (OB) ranging from $0.00000785 to $0.00000824. This particular range, as highlighted in a recent SHIB price report, could serve as a stronghold for bearish sentiment in the market. Related Reading: USTC Surprises With Nearly 60% Rally – What’s Going On? Consequently, the possibility of a liquidity hunt in this region cannot be disregarded, potentially leading sellers to extend their gains toward the immediate support level at $0.00000711. Source: Coingecko Amid recent market fluctuations, SHIB is currently trading at $0.00000788, based on data by crypto market tracker Coingecko. This reflects a decline of 3.4% over the past 24 hours. However, despite this short-term setback, SHIB has also notched a seven-day rally of 3.4%, showcasing its inherent resilience and potential for recovery in the long run. Decrease In SHIB Token Burns: Implications For Supply, Demand Meanwhile, Shibburn reported a notable decline in the number of tokens burned within the past 24 hours. A mere 1,233,806 SHIB tokens were burned in a single transaction, representing a sharp 91.59% decrease in the daily burn rate and in contrast, the previous week witnessed the burning of nearly 1 billion SHIB tokens. In the last 7 days, there have been a total of 915,371,832 $SHIB tokens burned and 139 transactions. #shib — Shibburn (@shibburn) July 16, 2023 This decline in token burns carries several implications for the SHIB ecosystem. Firstly, burning tokens plays a crucial role in reducing the overall supply of SHIB, potentially exerting upward pressure on its price.  Related Reading: Dogecoin Engagement Fails To Impress, Raising Concerns About Broader Interest However, with the significant decrease in the daily burn rate, the rate at which new tokens are being removed from circulation has slowed down considerably. This could impact the potential scarcity and perceived value of SHIB in the market. Shiba Inu (SHIB) market cap currently at $4.6 billion on the daily chart: TradingView.com Moreover, the reduced token burns may suggest a shift in market sentiment and investor behavior. It could indicate a decreased demand for burning tokens or a temporary lull in activity within the SHIB community. Market participants and SHIB token holders will closely monitor the implications of this decline in burns on future price movements and the overall supply-demand dynamics of the cryptocurrency. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Bodybuilding.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB) has faced a significant challenge in the form of the December 2022 low. This crucial level has proved a formidable barrier for SHIB bulls, thwarting their attempts to increase prices. </p>
<p>Despite recent upside movements, the resistance at this level has proven to be persistent, creating a precarious situation for the cryptocurrency. </p>
<p>As the price of SHIB hovers in this area, the question arises: Will the selling pressure overpower the bulls&#8217; determination and cause a reversal in the price action?</p>
<h2><strong>Shiba Inu Faces Bearish Order Block And Potential Liquidity Hunt</strong></h2>
<p>SHIB faces a significant challenge as its December 2022 low coincides with a bearish order block (OB) ranging from $0.00000785 to $0.00000824. This particular range, as highlighted in a recent <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://ambcrypto.com/shiba-inu-hits-familiar-hurdle-risks-a-correction/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">SHIB price report</a>, could serve as a stronghold for bearish sentiment in the market.</p>

<p>Consequently, the possibility of a liquidity hunt in this region cannot be disregarded, potentially leading sellers to extend their gains toward the immediate support level at $0.00000711.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-542896" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-101.png" alt="" width="938" height="68" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-101.png 938w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-101-460x33.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-101-860x62.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-101-768x56.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-101-750x54.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 938px) 100vw, 938px"/></p>

<p>Amid recent market fluctuations, SHIB is currently trading at $0.00000788, based on data by crypto market tracker <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/shiba-inu" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Coingecko</a>. This reflects a decline of 3.4% over the past 24 hours. </p>
<p>However, despite this short-term setback, SHIB has also notched a seven-day rally of 3.4%, showcasing its inherent resilience and potential for recovery in the long run.</p>
<h2><strong>Decrease In SHIB Token Burns: Implications For Supply, Demand</strong></h2>
<p>Meanwhile, <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/shibburn/status/1680427061901508609" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Shibburn reported</a> a notable decline in the number of tokens burned within the past 24 hours. A mere 1,233,806 SHIB tokens were burned in a single transaction, representing a sharp 91.59% decrease in the daily burn rate and in contrast, the previous week witnessed the burning of nearly 1 billion SHIB tokens.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">In the last 7 days, there have been a total of 915,371,832 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24SHIB&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$SHIB</a> tokens burned and 139 transactions. <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/shib?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#shib</a></p>
<p>— Shibburn (@shibburn) <a href="https://twitter.com/shibburn/status/1680427061901508609?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>This decline in token burns carries several implications for the SHIB ecosystem. Firstly, burning tokens plays a crucial role in reducing the overall supply of SHIB, potentially exerting upward pressure on its price. </p>

<p>However, with the significant decrease in the daily burn rate, the rate at which new tokens are being removed from circulation has slowed down considerably. This could impact the potential scarcity and perceived value of SHIB in the market.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/YqMd30xF/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>

<p>Moreover, the reduced token burns may suggest a shift in market sentiment and investor behavior. It could indicate a decreased demand for burning tokens or a temporary lull in activity within the SHIB community. </p>
<p>Market participants and SHIB token holders will closely monitor the implications of this decline in burns on future price movements and the overall supply-demand dynamics of the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Bodybuilding.com</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-102-460x259.png" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Vs. SEC: XRP Investors Need To Know This Next Deadline</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ripple/ripple-sec-xrp-investors-need-to-know-deadline/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 07:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Appeal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542878</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the legal battle between Ripple Labs and the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), the recent order granting in part and denying in part the motion for Summary Judgment by Judge Torres has left many XRP investors eagerly awaiting the next steps. To shed some light on the situation, prominent attorney Jeremy Hogan has shared his thoughts on the matter, offering valuable insights into the potential appeal process with deadlines and its implications for both parties involved. Ripple Vs. SEC: The Next Possible Deadline Hogan, a seasoned attorney with experience in appeals, cautions that appeals are typically pursued after a case is completely finished. “After the final judgment is entered, either party has 60 days to appeal,” says Hogan who emphasized that the Ripple case is not yet finalized, any potential appeal at this stage would be considered an &#8220;interlocutory appeal.&#8221; Related Reading: XRP Explodes With 1,300% Surge In Trading Volume As crypto Exchanges Jump On Board “As far as I can see in the Rules, you have 10 days to notice an interlocutory appeal”, states Hogan. Since the Summary Judgment was issued on July 13, an appeal by the SEC or Ripple Labs would have to be filed by July 23 at the latest (or by July 24 if the deadline does not start until the following day). This means that next Monday at the latest it will become public whether one of the parties files an appeal. But an interlocutory appeal is rarely granted and generally requires compelling reasons, such as the release of significant information that could impact the case. However, Hogan points out that Judge Torres did not certify her ruling for immediate review, indicating that an interlocutory appeal might not be granted in this scenario. This suggests that the SEC and Ripple would need to wait for a final judgment before pursuing an appeal. Hogan believes that both parties might ultimately choose not to appeal for various reasons. According to the lawyer, the SEC might hesitate to appeal because, even if successful, it could potentially jeopardize their overall case. Winning the appeal would retract some unfavorable aspects of the trial-level case. However, if the SEC were to lose at the appellate level, it could set a precedent that all courts in the 2nd DCA (Second District Court of Appeals) would have to follow, amplifying the impact of their loss. Related Reading: Large Exchanges Relist XRP Following Ripple Victory Over SEC On the other hand, Hogan believes that Ripple may opt not to appeal if it can afford to pay the fine and if the ruling&#8217;s effect on its business, particularly the aspect concerning the On-Demand Liquidity (ODL) feature, is manageable. These factors, combined with the fact that Ripple secured a favorable outcome in the ruling, might dissuade them from pursuing an appeal. When considering the potential difficulties in winning an appeal, Hogan emphasizes that Judge Torres is the one who has meticulously reviewed the entire case record. This makes the appellate process inherently challenging for either party, further reducing the likelihood of an appeal. Regarding the SEC&#8217;s challenge in appealing the secondary market sales aspect, which presents a problematic area for the regulatory body, Hogan admits that he hasn&#8217;t solidified his thoughts on the matter yet. XRP Price The XRP price has taken a breather after the stunning rally following the Ripple summary judgment. After being rejected at the 38.2% Fibonacci retracement level at $0.93, the XRP price is currently trading at $0.7481. After a possible retest of the 23.6% Fibonacci retracement level at $0.68, the impulsive move may see a continuation. The final verdict in the Ripple v. SEC case and possible appeals will certainly continue to have a strong impact on the price. Featured image from Outlook India, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the legal battle between Ripple Labs and the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), the recent <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/ripple-victory-against-the-sec-may-be-short-lived/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">order</a> granting in part and denying in part the motion for Summary Judgment by Judge Torres has left many XRP investors eagerly awaiting the next steps. To shed some light on the situation, prominent attorney Jeremy Hogan has <a href="https://twitter.com/attorneyjeremy1/status/1680806791633072129" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shared</a> his thoughts on the matter, offering valuable insights into the potential appeal process with deadlines and its implications for both parties involved.</p>
<h2>Ripple Vs. SEC: The Next Possible Deadline</h2>
<p>Hogan, a seasoned attorney with experience in appeals, cautions that appeals are typically pursued after a case is completely finished. “After the final judgment is entered, either party has 60 days to appeal,” says Hogan who emphasized that the Ripple case is not yet finalized, any potential appeal at this stage would be considered an &#8220;interlocutory appeal.&#8221;</p>

<p>“As far as I can see in the Rules, you have 10 days to notice an interlocutory appeal”, states Hogan. Since the Summary Judgment was issued on July 13, an appeal by the SEC or Ripple Labs would have to be filed by July 23 at the latest (or by July 24 if the deadline does not start until the following day). This means that next Monday at the latest it will become public whether one of the parties files an appeal.</p>
<p>But an interlocutory appeal is rarely granted and generally requires compelling reasons, such as the release of significant information that could impact the case. However, Hogan points out that Judge Torres did not certify her ruling for immediate review, indicating that an interlocutory appeal might not be granted in this scenario. This suggests that the SEC and Ripple would need to wait for a final judgment before pursuing an appeal. Hogan believes that both parties might ultimately choose not to appeal for various reasons.</p>
<p>According to the lawyer, the SEC might hesitate to appeal because, even if successful, it could potentially jeopardize their overall case. Winning the appeal would retract some unfavorable aspects of the trial-level case. However, if the SEC were to lose at the appellate level, it could set a precedent that all courts in the 2nd DCA (Second District Court of Appeals) would have to follow, amplifying the impact of their loss.</p>

<p>On the other hand, Hogan believes that Ripple may opt not to appeal if it can afford to pay the fine and if the ruling&#8217;s effect on its business, particularly the aspect concerning the On-Demand Liquidity (ODL) feature, is manageable. These factors, combined with the fact that Ripple secured a favorable outcome in the ruling, might dissuade them from pursuing an appeal.</p>
<p>When considering the potential difficulties in winning an appeal, Hogan emphasizes that Judge Torres is the one who has meticulously reviewed the entire case record. This makes the appellate process inherently challenging for either party, further reducing the likelihood of an appeal.</p>
<p>Regarding the SEC&#8217;s challenge in appealing the secondary market sales aspect, which presents a problematic area for the regulatory body, Hogan admits that he hasn&#8217;t solidified his thoughts on the matter yet.</p>
<h2>XRP Price</h2>
<p>The XRP price has taken a breather after the stunning rally <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/ripples-legal-victory-boosts-xrp-price-could-reach-1-soon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">following</a> the Ripple summary judgment. After being rejected at the 38.2% Fibonacci retracement level at $0.93, the XRP price is currently trading at $0.7481. After a possible retest of the 23.6% Fibonacci retracement level at $0.68, the impulsive move may see a continuation. The final verdict in the Ripple v. SEC case and possible appeals will certainly continue to have a strong impact on the price.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-542885 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSD_2023-07-17_08-35-21.png" alt="XRP price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSD_2023-07-17_08-35-21.png 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSD_2023-07-17_08-35-21-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSD_2023-07-17_08-35-21-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSD_2023-07-17_08-35-21-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSD_2023-07-17_08-35-21-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSD_2023-07-17_08-35-21-2048x944.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSD_2023-07-17_08-35-21-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSD_2023-07-17_08-35-21-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3628px) 100vw, 3628px"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/IMAGE_1671014556-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>USTC Surprises With Nearly 60% Rally &#8211; What’s Going On?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ustc-surprises-with-nearly-60-rally-whats-going-on/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 06:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TerraUSD Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542871</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The value and popularity of TerraUSD Classic, or USTC, the algorithmic stablecoin of the Terra Classic (LUNC) ecosystem, have skyrocketed recently. Today, the stablecoin makes a surprise rally, sparking a great deal of interest among investors and cryptocurrency aficionados. The sharp growth in USTC could be an indication of a sharp rise in demand and emphasizes the market&#8217;s rising confidence in this stablecoin. Data from crypto market tracker Coingecko shows USTC trading at $0.0186, notching a 24-hour increase in value of 21.4%. In the last seven days, the stablecoin registered an impressive 58% rally, causing its trading volume to balloon to a solid 409%. Source: Coingecko USTC Organic Growth Pushes Stablecoin Up Despite the fact that the causes of this upswing are yet unknown, the recent spike in USTC&#8217;s value shows organic growth. &#8220;Organic growth&#8221; refers to the increase in value of USTC that occurs naturally, without the influence of external factors or artificial means. Related Reading: Dogecoin Engagement Fails To Impress, Raising Concerns About Broader Interest It suggests that the growth is the result of the company&#8217;s internal operations, strategies, and market dynamics, rather than being driven by external factors such as acquisitions, mergers, or financial manipulations. After it was de-pegged more than a year ago, USTC saw a huge price decline. Since USTC is a stablecoin with a 1:1 tie to the USD, its price should always be $1. The stablecoin has since traded at lower prices, reaching a 52-week high of $0.06 during that time. There are signs, nevertheless, that USTC could revisit the $1 level and recoup its worth. Total market cap of cryptocurrencies as of today stood at $1.17 trillion. Chart: TradingView.com The TerraUSD Classic de-pegging caused major difficulties for the larger digital currency ecosystem, and its effects are still being felt today. A few Web3.0 firms with exposure to its parent company Terraform Labs went out of business in addition to the more than 99% decline in price of its linked cryptocurrency, Terra Classic. Related Reading: BNB Chain Inks New Record With Soaring User Activity – A Boost For Price? The implosion of FTX Derivatives Exchange was finally driven by the bankruptcies of Celsius Network and Voyager Digital, which prolonged the crypto winter even further. Meanwhile, in order to expand supply and rekindle interest in the stablecoin, the Terra Classic community is launching projects like staking and burning LUNC tokens while also working to improve infrastructure. Source: Coingecko Will The Terra Classic Stablecoin Retest $1? There is growing consensus that the TerraUSD Classic token is steadily approaching a retesting of the significant $1 price level. Among investors and enthusiasts alike, this strong rising trend has spurred new optimism. As the TerraUSD Classic token gains momentum, it boosts community members&#8217; faith in its capability to uphold its pegged value and function as a dependable digital asset. The community may become excited and eager in anticipation of a probable retest of the $1 price level, which would improve the outlook for TerraUSD Classic&#8217;s long-term prospects. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Analytics Insight]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The value and popularity of TerraUSD Classic, or USTC, the algorithmic stablecoin of the Terra Classic (LUNC) ecosystem, have skyrocketed recently.</p>
<p>Today, the stablecoin makes a surprise rally, sparking a great deal of interest among investors and cryptocurrency aficionados.</p>
<p>The sharp growth in USTC could be an indication of a sharp rise in demand and emphasizes the market&#8217;s rising confidence in this stablecoin.</p>
<p>Data from crypto market tracker Coingecko shows <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/?page=2" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">USTC trading at $0.0186</a>, notching a 24-hour increase in value of 21.4%. In the last seven days, the stablecoin registered an impressive 58% rally, causing its trading volume to balloon to a solid 409%.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-542874" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/USTC.png" alt="" width="1136" height="62" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/USTC.png 1136w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/USTC-460x25.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/USTC-860x47.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/USTC-768x42.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/USTC-750x41.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1136px) 100vw, 1136px"/></p>

<h2><strong>USTC Organic Growth Pushes Stablecoin Up</strong></h2>
<p>Despite the fact that the causes of this upswing are yet unknown, the recent spike in USTC&#8217;s value shows <a href="https://thegww.com/huge-surge-in-value-and-trading-volume-of-terrausd-classic-delights-investors/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">organic growth.</a></p>
<p>&#8220;Organic growth&#8221; refers to the increase in value of USTC that occurs naturally, without the influence of external factors or artificial means.</p>

<p>It suggests that the growth is the result of the company&#8217;s internal operations, strategies, and market dynamics, rather than being driven by external factors such as acquisitions, mergers, or financial manipulations.</p>
<p>After it was de-pegged more than a year ago, USTC saw a huge price decline. Since USTC is a stablecoin with a 1:1 tie to the USD, its price should always be $1.</p>
<p>The stablecoin has since traded at lower prices, reaching a 52-week high of $0.06 during that time. There are signs, nevertheless, that USTC could revisit the $1 level and recoup its worth.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/t3Q7AuiJ/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>

<p>The TerraUSD Classic de-pegging caused major difficulties for the larger digital currency ecosystem, and its effects are still being felt today.</p>
<p>A few Web3.0 firms with exposure to its parent company Terraform Labs went out of business in addition to the more than 99% decline in price of its linked cryptocurrency, Terra Classic.</p>

<p>The implosion of FTX Derivatives Exchange was finally driven by the bankruptcies of Celsius Network and Voyager Digital, which prolonged the crypto winter even further.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, in order to expand supply and rekindle interest in the stablecoin, the Terra Classic community is launching projects like staking and burning LUNC tokens while also working to improve infrastructure.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-542877" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-99.png" alt="" width="745" height="478" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-99.png 745w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-99-460x295.png 460w" sizes="(max-width: 745px) 100vw, 745px"/></p>

<h2><strong>Will The Terra Classic Stablecoin Retest $1?</strong></h2>
<p>There is growing consensus that the TerraUSD Classic token is steadily approaching a retesting of the significant $1 price level. Among investors and enthusiasts alike, this strong rising trend has spurred new optimism.</p>
<p>As the TerraUSD Classic token gains momentum, it boosts community members&#8217; faith in its capability to uphold its pegged value and function as a dependable digital asset.</p>
<p>The community may become excited and eager in anticipation of a probable retest of the $1 price level, which would improve the outlook for TerraUSD Classic&#8217;s long-term prospects.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Analytics Insight</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-98-460x261.png" width="460" height="261" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Uniswap’s UNI Price Could Soon Rally Above $6 – Here’s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/uni/uniswaps-uni-price-rally-6/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 05:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[UNI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uniswap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uniusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UNIUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542868</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Uniswap’s UNI started a decent increase above $5.35 against the US Dollar. The price is likely to continue higher above $6.00 and $6.20 in the near term. UNI started a fresh increase after forming a base above the $4.75 level against the US dollar. The price is trading above $5.65 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break above a major contracting triangle with resistance near $5.35 on the 4-hour chart of the UNI/USD pair (data source from Kraken). The pair is likely to continue higher if it clears the $6.00 and $6.20 resistance levels in the near term. Uniswap’s UNI Regains Traction After forming a support base above $5.00, UNI started a fresh increase. The bulls were able to push Uniswap’s price above the $5.25 and $5.30 resistance levels, similar to Bitcoin and Ethereum. There was also a break above a major contracting triangle with resistance near $5.35 on the 4-hour chart of the UNI/USD pair. The pair gained pace and tested the $6.30 zone. A high is formed near $6.291 and the price started a downside correction. There was a break below the $6.00 level. UNI price tested the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $5.09 low to the $6.291 high. Source: UNIUSD on TradingView.com The price is now trading above $5.50 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, the price is facing hurdles near $6.00 and $6.10. A close above the $6.10 level could open the doors for more gains in the near term. The next key resistance could be near $6.30, above which the bulls are likely to aim a test of the $6.80 level. Any more gains might send UNI toward $7.00. Dips Supported? If UNI price fails to climb above $6.00 or $6.20, it could correct further lower. The first major support is near the $5.70 level. The next major support is near the $5.50 level. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $5.09 low to the $6.291 high. A downside break below the $5.50 support might open the doors for a push toward the key $5.10. Technical Indicators 4-Hours MACD – The MACD for UNI/USD is gaining momentum in the bullish zone. 4-Hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for UNI/USD is well above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $5.65, $5.50 and $5.10. Major Resistance Levels – $6.00, $6.30 and $6.80.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Uniswap’s UNI started a decent increase above $5.35 against the US Dollar. The price is likely to continue higher above $6.00 and $6.20 in the near term.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>UNI started a fresh increase after forming a base above the $4.75 level against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $5.65 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a major contracting triangle with resistance near $5.35 on the 4-hour chart of the UNI/USD pair (data source from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair is likely to continue higher if it clears the $6.00 and $6.20 resistance levels in the near term.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Uniswap’s UNI Regains Traction</h2>
<p>After forming a support base above $5.00, UNI started a fresh increase. The bulls were able to push Uniswap’s price above the $5.25 and $5.30 resistance levels, similar to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-aims-31k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a> and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-move-1900/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum</a>.</p>
<p>There was also a break above a major contracting triangle with resistance near $5.35 on the 4-hour chart of the UNI/USD pair. The pair gained pace and tested the $6.30 zone. A high is formed near $6.291 and the price started a downside correction.</p>
<p>There was a break below the $6.00 level. UNI price tested the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $5.09 low to the $6.291 high.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-542869" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Uniswap-UNI.png" alt="Uniswap’s UNI Price" width="1950" height="894" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Uniswap-UNI.png 1950w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Uniswap-UNI-460x211.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Uniswap-UNI-860x394.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Uniswap-UNI-768x352.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Uniswap-UNI-1536x704.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Uniswap-UNI-750x344.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Uniswap-UNI-1140x523.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1950px) 100vw, 1950px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/UNIUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">UNIUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The price is now trading above $5.50 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, the price is facing hurdles near $6.00 and $6.10. A close above the $6.10 level could open the doors for more gains in the near term. The next key resistance could be near $6.30, above which the bulls are likely to aim a test of the $6.80 level. Any more gains might send UNI toward $7.00.</p>
<h2>Dips Supported?</h2>
<p>If UNI price fails to climb above $6.00 or $6.20, it could correct further lower. The first major support is near the $5.70 level. The next major support is near the $5.50 level.</p>
<p>It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $5.09 low to the $6.291 high. A downside break below the $5.50 support might open the doors for a push toward the key $5.10.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>4-Hours MACD – The MACD for UNI/USD is gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4-Hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for UNI/USD is well above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $5.65, $5.50 and $5.10.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $6.00, $6.30 and $6.80.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/shutterstock_716909917-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
