<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 03:07:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Aims $26,200 But 100 SMA Hold The Key In Short-Term</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-aims-26200/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 03:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538182</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is attempting a recovery wave above the $25,200 resistance. BTC must clear the 100 hourly SMA to continue higher in the near term. Bitcoin is slowly recovering higher above the $25,200 support. The price is trading below $25,750 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $25,680 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could rise further if it clears $25,750 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. Bitcoin Price Attempts Recovery Bitcoin price remained in a bearish zone below the $26,200 resistance zone. BTC extended its decline below the $25,500 support and even spiked below $25,000. A low is formed near $24,751 and the price is now attempting a recovery wave. There was a clear move above the $25,000 and $25,200 resistance levels. The price climbed above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $26,062 swing high to the $24,751 low. Bitcoin price is now trading below $25,750 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. Besides, there is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $25,680 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. The pair is now facing resistance near the trend line and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $26,062 swing high to the $24,751 low. The next major resistance is near the $25,750 level. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com A clear move above the $25,750 resistance might start a fresh increase. The next major resistance is near the $26,200 level, above which the bulls might send BTC toward the $26,500 resistance zone. Fresh Decline in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $25,750 resistance, it could start another decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $25,200 level. The next major support is near the $24,820 level, below which the price might start another major decline. In the stated case, the price could drop toward the $24,000 support in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $25,200, followed by $24,820. Major Resistance Levels – $25,680, $25,750, and $26,200.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is attempting a recovery wave above the $25,200 resistance. BTC must clear the 100 hourly SMA to continue higher in the near term.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is slowly recovering higher above the $25,200 support.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $25,750 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $25,680 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could rise further if it clears $25,750 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Attempts Recovery</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price remained in a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-plunges-24k-next/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">bearish zone below the $26,200 resistance zone</a>. BTC extended its decline below the $25,500 support and even spiked below $25,000.</p>
<p>A low is formed near $24,751 and the price is now attempting a recovery wave. There was a clear move above the $25,000 and $25,200 resistance levels. The price climbed above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $26,062 swing high to the $24,751 low.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is now trading below $25,750 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. Besides, there is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $25,680 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>The pair is now facing resistance near the trend line and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-recovery-toward-27k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $26,062 swing high to the $24,751 low. The next major resistance is near the $25,750 level.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-538183" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-11.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-11.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-11-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-11-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-11-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-11-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-11-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-11-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>A clear move above the $25,750 resistance might start a fresh increase. The next major resistance is near the $26,200 level, above which the bulls might send BTC toward the $26,500 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Fresh Decline in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $25,750 resistance, it could start another decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $25,200 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $24,820 level, below which the price might start another major decline. In the stated case, the price could drop toward the $24,000 support in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $25,200, followed by $24,820.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $25,680, $25,750, and $26,200.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/shutterstock_555674926-460x313.jpg" width="460" height="313" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Holders Show No Panic Loss Selling, What Does It Mean?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-holders-show-no-panic-loss-selling-what-does-it-mean/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 20:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin capitulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Loss Selling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Realized Loss]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538132</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that Bitcoin investors aren&#8217;t participating in any significant amounts of loss selling right now. Here&#8217;s what it may mean. Bitcoin Entity-Adjusted Realized Loss Has Remained Low Recently According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Glassnode, coins transacted recently were mostly acquired close to the current spot price. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;entity-adjusted realized loss,&#8221; which measures the total loss investors realize through their current selling. This metric works by going through the on-chain history of each being sold to see what price it was bought at. If this previous price for any coin was more than the current spot price (that it&#8217;s now being moved at), then the coin&#8217;s sale is leading to the realization of a loss. Naturally, the coin would be moving at a profit in the opposite case. The indicator has &#8220;entity-adjusted&#8221; because it only counts transactions/sales between different entities rather than individual wallets. An entity here refers to a single or a group of addresses controlled by the same investor, as determined by Glassnode&#8217;s analysis. As transfers between the addresses of the same investor wouldn&#8217;t count as selling, it makes sense to filter such transfers out of the data for the realized loss. Related Reading: Bitcoin Sentiment On Social Media Now Most Red Since COVID Crash, Bottom Signal? Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin entity-adjusted realized loss over the last few years: The value of the metric seems to have been moving sideways in recent days &#124; Source: Glassnode on Twitter As the above graph shows, the Bitcoin entity-adjusted realized loss has been at relatively low values for a few months. The rally in the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price has taken place during this period, so it would make sense that investors wouldn&#8217;t have any need to sell at a loss while the surge has gone on. Related Reading: Here’s Why The Tether FUD Could Be Good For Bitcoin However, recently, things have been different. BTC has been going down during the past few weeks, but there has still not been any change in the indicator&#8217;s value. This is unlike what&#8217;s generally observed during drawdowns in the asset. Even earlier in the current year, when the rally had temporarily taken a hiatus in March and the cryptocurrency&#8217;s value had seen a deep plunge, there was an uplift in the realized loss, although not anything too significant. The recent low values are also despite the FUD that has spread around the sector following the SEC charges against Binance and Coinbase. In the past day, the market has again stumbled as the Fed has revealed its decision to pause interest rate hikes for now but has also communicated that more increases would be coming later in the year. Despite this fresh hit that the Bitcoin price has taken, the realized loss has still not registered any uptick, as its value is still just $91.3 million, significantly less than in past capitulation events. The fact that investors haven&#8217;t started selling at a loss would imply that there is still not enough panic in the market yet; investors holding at a loss are content to ride the current market phaseout. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $25,000, down 5% in the last week. Looks like BTC has observed a sharp drop today &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Thought Catalog on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Glassnode.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows that Bitcoin investors aren&#8217;t participating in any significant amounts of loss selling right now. Here&#8217;s what it may mean.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Entity-Adjusted Realized Loss Has Remained Low Recently</h2>
<p>According to data from the on-chain analytics firm <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1669276292129144834/photo/1" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Glassnode</a>, coins transacted recently were mostly acquired close to the current spot price. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-realized-loss-low-despite-volatility-what-mean/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">entity-adjusted realized loss</a>,&#8221; which measures the total loss investors realize through their current selling.</p>
<p>This metric works by going through the on-chain history of each being sold to see what price it was bought at. If this previous price for any coin was more than the current spot price (that it&#8217;s now being moved at), then the coin&#8217;s sale is leading to the realization of a loss. Naturally, the coin would be moving at a profit in the opposite case.</p>
<p>The indicator has &#8220;entity-adjusted&#8221; because it only counts transactions/sales between different entities rather than individual wallets. An entity here refers to a single or a group of addresses controlled by the same investor, as determined by Glassnode&#8217;s analysis.</p>
<p>As transfers between the addresses of the same investor wouldn&#8217;t count as selling, it makes sense to filter such transfers out of the data for the realized loss.</p>

<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin entity-adjusted realized loss over the last few years:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/Fyp1tsTXsAMidmN?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Bitcoin Realized Loss" width="4052" height="2334"/></p>

<p>As the above graph shows, the Bitcoin entity-adjusted realized loss has been at relatively low values for a few months. The rally in the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price has taken place during this period, so it would make sense that investors wouldn&#8217;t have any need to sell at a loss while the surge has gone on.</p>

<p>However, recently, things have been different. BTC has been going down during the past few weeks, but there has still not been any change in the indicator&#8217;s value. This is unlike what&#8217;s generally observed during drawdowns in the asset.</p>
<p>Even earlier in the current year, when the rally had temporarily taken a hiatus in March and the cryptocurrency&#8217;s value had seen a deep plunge, there was an uplift in the realized loss, although not anything too significant. The recent low values are also despite the FUD that has spread around the sector following the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/crypto-market-bleeds-as-sec-pressures-mount-is-it-time-to-buy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">SEC charges</a> against Binance and Coinbase.</p>
<p>In the past day, the market has again stumbled as the Fed has <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin-price-hammered-below-25000-amid-the-feds-hawkish-tone-sec-lawsuits/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">revealed</a> its decision to pause interest rate hikes for now but has also communicated that more increases would be coming later in the year.</p>
<p>Despite this fresh hit that the Bitcoin price has taken, the realized loss has still not registered any uptick, as its value is still just $91.3 million, significantly less than in past capitulation events.</p>
<p>The fact that investors haven&#8217;t started selling at a loss would imply that there is still not enough panic in the market yet; investors holding at a loss are content to ride the current market phaseout.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $25,000, down 5% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/vd2IHboC/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="911"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/thought-catalog-I0TDRP0fj6Y-unsplash-3-460x345.jpg" width="460" height="345" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Headed for Another Crash? Over $100 Billion in Liquidations Suggests Trouble Ahead</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-headed-for-another-crash-over-100-billion-in-liquidations-suggests-trouble-ahead/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 18:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538174</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC), the largest cryptocurrency in the market, was expected to continue its bull run after consolidating its gains. However, on June 14th, just before its daily close, Bitcoin suffered a 3% decline, dropping below $25,000 and reaching as low as $24,700, a price level not seen since mid-March. In light of these developments and the mounting regulatory pressure from the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on the nascent industry, many are starting to believe that the recent bull run for BTC was nothing more than a fakeout. Related Reading: XRP Exhibits Bearish Chart Pattern – Where Could The Price Head Next? Bitcoin On The Brink With Massive Amount Of Liquidations Looming Bitcoin has been facing a lot of turbulence recently, and the troubles don&#8217;t seem to be stopping anytime soon.  The latest data shows that Bitcoin is facing trouble as over $100 billion in liquidations loom, signaling the potential for another crash in the cryptocurrency market. Despite attempting to surpass its nearest resistance levels, Bitcoin has been struggling, with the potential for further downside movements and increased selling pressure. According to the latest data provided by the trader and crypto analyst under the pseudonym “Bleeding Crypto”, there is a total of $63.9 billion worth of liquidations at the $24,200 price level and $52.3 billion worth of liquidations at the $21,800 mark. The increased selling pressure in Bitcoin could potentially result in further liquidations and a subsequent crash in the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price, delaying any further uptrends and causing a return to the lower price levels seen at the beginning of the year. This could induce fear among investors, further fueling short positions and potentially leading to a vicious cycle. However, if that&#8217;s the case, it&#8217;s important to note that there&#8217;s also a possibility of a contrary situation, where institutional investors hunt for short position liquidations, leading to a surge in buying pressure and propelling the price of Bitcoin to the upside. BTC’s Open Interest Skyrockets Crypto analyst and Crypto Quant author Maartun has recently warned that volatility is incoming in the world of Bitcoin. According to him, although BTC’s price has been going sideways, the open interest in the cryptocurrency has increased by $439 million. Maartun’s analysis suggests that a significant amount of money is being poured into the market, which could lead to a significant increase in volatility. Maartun notes that this situation differs from previous occasions, as the funding rates for Bitcoin are trending down and are close to neutral. This means that longs and shorts are in almost perfect balance, creating a situation where any significant move in either direction could trigger a cascade of buying or selling. Open interest refers to the total number of outstanding contracts in a particular market yet to be settled. In the case of Bitcoin, an increase in open interest typically indicates that more traders are entering the market, which could lead to increased volatility.  The impact of the increase in open interest on Bitcoin&#8217;s price and market direction is unclear. While an increase in open interest can suggest a growing interest in Bitcoin and potentially lead to upward price movements, it can also lead to greater volatility and downward price movements if the market sentiment turns negative. Alternately, according to the latest data from Glassnode, the amount of illiquid Bitcoin supply continues to grow at a rate of 119,000 BTC per month. This suggests that Bitcoin holders are becoming increasingly reluctant to sell or move their coins, leading to a concentration of coins in wallets with a sparse spending history.  Related Reading: Ethereum Plunges Below $1,700, Here’s The Metric That Signaled This In Advance This is an important trend to watch, as it suggests that Bitcoin holders remain confident in the long-term potential of the cryptocurrency. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC), the largest cryptocurrency in the market, was expected to continue its bull run after consolidating its gains. However, on June 14th, just before its daily close, Bitcoin suffered a 3% decline, dropping below $25,000 and reaching as low as $24,700, a price level not seen since mid-March.</p>
<p>In light of these developments and the mounting regulatory pressure from the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on the nascent industry, many are starting to believe that the recent bull run for BTC was nothing more than a fakeout.</p>

<h2>Bitcoin On The Brink With Massive Amount Of Liquidations Looming</h2>
<p>Bitcoin has been facing a lot of turbulence recently, and the troubles don&#8217;t seem to be stopping anytime soon. </p>
<p>The latest data shows that Bitcoin is facing trouble as over $100 billion in liquidations loom, signaling the potential for another crash in the cryptocurrency market. Despite attempting to surpass its nearest resistance levels, Bitcoin has been struggling, with the potential for further downside movements and increased selling pressure.</p>
<p>According to the latest <a href="https://twitter.com/Bleeding_Crypto/status/1669116793741520896?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data </a>provided by the trader and crypto analyst under the pseudonym “Bleeding Crypto”, there is a total of $63.9 billion worth of liquidations at the $24,200 price level and $52.3 billion worth of liquidations at the $21,800 mark.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-538177" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fynkv-QaQAEdkuy-860x450.jpg" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="450" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fynkv-QaQAEdkuy-860x450.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fynkv-QaQAEdkuy-460x241.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fynkv-QaQAEdkuy-768x402.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fynkv-QaQAEdkuy-1536x804.jpg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fynkv-QaQAEdkuy-2048x1073.jpg 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fynkv-QaQAEdkuy-750x393.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fynkv-QaQAEdkuy-1140x597.jpg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>The increased selling pressure in Bitcoin could potentially result in further liquidations and a subsequent crash in the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price, delaying any further uptrends and causing a return to the lower price levels seen at the beginning of the year. This could induce fear among investors, further fueling short positions and potentially leading to a vicious cycle.</p>
<p>However, if that&#8217;s the case, it&#8217;s important to note that there&#8217;s also a possibility of a contrary situation, where institutional investors hunt for short position liquidations, leading to a surge in buying pressure and propelling the price of Bitcoin to the upside.</p>
BTC’s Open Interest Skyrockets
<p>Crypto analyst and Crypto Quant author Maartun has recently <a href="https://twitter.com/JA_Maartun/status/1669211536118759424?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">warned </a>that volatility is incoming in the world of Bitcoin. According to him, although BTC’s price has been going sideways, the open interest in the cryptocurrency has increased by $439 million.</p>
<p>Maartun’s analysis suggests that a significant amount of money is being poured into the market, which could lead to a significant increase in volatility.</p>
<p>Maartun notes that this situation differs from previous occasions, as the funding rates for Bitcoin are trending down and are close to neutral. This means that longs and shorts are in almost perfect balance, creating a situation where any significant move in either direction could trigger a cascade of buying or selling.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-538176" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fyo6VN9XoAEeyE6-860x430.jpg" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="430" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fyo6VN9XoAEeyE6-860x430.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fyo6VN9XoAEeyE6-460x230.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fyo6VN9XoAEeyE6-768x384.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fyo6VN9XoAEeyE6-360x180.jpg 360w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fyo6VN9XoAEeyE6-750x375.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fyo6VN9XoAEeyE6-1140x570.jpg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fyo6VN9XoAEeyE6.jpg 1271w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>Open interest refers to the total number of outstanding contracts in a particular market yet to be settled. In the case of Bitcoin, an increase in open interest typically indicates that more traders are entering the market, which could lead to increased volatility. </p>
<p>The impact of the increase in open interest on Bitcoin&#8217;s price and market direction is unclear. While an increase in open interest can suggest a growing interest in Bitcoin and potentially lead to upward price movements, it can also lead to greater volatility and downward price movements if the market sentiment turns negative.</p>
<p>Alternately, <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1669295668911919106?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">according </a>to the latest data from Glassnode, the amount of illiquid Bitcoin supply continues to grow at a rate of 119,000 BTC per month. This suggests that Bitcoin holders are becoming increasingly reluctant to sell or move their coins, leading to a concentration of coins in wallets with a sparse spending history. </p>

<p>This is an important trend to watch, as it suggests that Bitcoin holders remain confident in the long-term potential of the cryptocurrency.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/3L8Z1Tr0/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1188004097-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlackRock Inches Closer To Launching Bitcoin ETF: Potential Impact On BTC Price</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/blackrock-inches-closer-to-launching-bitcoin-etf-impact-on-btc-price/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538154</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Financial circles are buzzing with the news that BlackRock, the world&#8217;s largest asset manager, is considering applying for a Bitcoin Exchange Traded Fund (ETF). This development signifies a substantial move by one of the most influential financial institutions into the world of cryptocurrencies. The anticipation is growing amid revelations that BlackRock plans to use Coinbase Custody for the ETF, alongside the crypto exchange&#8217;s spot market data for pricing. This alliance represents a significant step in legitimizing cryptocurrencies in traditional finance. Notably, Bitcoin (BTC) and Coinbase (COIN) have not reacted to the news but have only continued to dwell in red, with both assets down 3.9% and 2.81%, respectively, in the past 24 hours. Related Reading: Data Reveals Short-Term Bitcoin Holders Refuse To Sell Despite SEC Crackdown BlackRock’s Foray Into Crypto The move marks a continuation of the collaboration that started last year when BlackRock partnered with Coinbase to offer crypto directly to institutional investors. As of yet, the specifics about the nature of the ETF – whether it will be spot or futures – remain undisclosed. Notably, The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), responsible for regulating ETFs in the U.S., has previously turned down every application for a spot Bitcoin ETF. However, several Bitcoin futures ETFs have gained the regulatory body&#8217;s approval for trading, indicating a gradually warming stance towards cryptocurrencies. Potential Impact On Bitcoin Price The news of BlackRock&#8217;s potential Bitcoin ETF could significantly affect BTC&#8217;s price. Creating such an ETF would allow a broader spectrum of investors to gain exposure to Bitcoin, possibly driving up demand and its price. ETFs make it easy for institutional investors to gain exposure to Bitcoin, opening up a substantial new demand avenue. Analyst crypto Daan Crypto reported that Bitcoin had recorded a strong spot bid on Binance in the past few hours – a move that has not been seen for the past few days. According to the trader, Bitcoin&#8217;s local bottom is more likely in if the asset continues to the downside in the coming days. At the time of writing, BTC currently trades at $24,977, down by nearly 4%. Its trading volume has also spiked over the past 7 days indicating massive trading activity. Notably, from a technical perspective, BTC could still be prone to a continuous downtrend, given that the asset hasn&#8217;t hit major support, which can be found in the order block at $24,500. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price On Shaky Ground: Market Analysts Warn Of Potential Fall To $20,000 Level Furthermore, the association with BlackRock, a globally recognized asset management name, could lend credibility and legitimacy to Bitcoin. This increased trust could lead to greater adoption rates and an upward price trajectory for Bitcoin in the long run. As observed in the past, any positive development or news about BTC ETFs has often led to a spike in Bitcoin&#8217;s price due to increased demand from retail and institutional investors. Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Financial circles are buzzing with the news that BlackRock, the world&#8217;s largest asset manager, is considering <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/06/15/blackrock-close-to-filing-bitcoin-etf-source/?utm_source=twitter&amp;utm_term=organic&amp;utm_campaign=coindesk_main&amp;utm_content=editorial&amp;utm_medium=social" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">applying</a> for a Bitcoin Exchange Traded Fund (ETF). This development signifies a substantial move by one of the most influential financial institutions into the world of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>The anticipation is growing amid revelations that BlackRock plans to use Coinbase Custody for the ETF, alongside the crypto exchange&#8217;s spot market data for pricing. This alliance represents a significant step in legitimizing cryptocurrencies in traditional finance.</p>
<p>Notably, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-btc-stored-on-exchanges-plummets-amid-regulatory/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin (BTC)</a> and Coinbase (COIN) have not reacted to the news but have only continued to dwell in red, with both assets down 3.9% and 2.81%, respectively, in the past 24 hours.</p>

<h2>BlackRock’s Foray Into Crypto</h2>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">The move marks a continuation of the collaboration that started last year when <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/coinbase-selected-by-blackrock-provide-aladdin-clients-access-to-crypto-trading-and-custody-via" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BlackRock partnered with Coinbase</a> to offer crypto directly to institutional investors. </p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">As of yet, the specifics about the nature of the ETF – whether it will be spot or futures – remain undisclosed. Notably, The <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/data-reveals-short-term-bitcoin-holders-refuse-to-sell/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)</a>, responsible for regulating ETFs in the U.S., has previously turned down every application for a spot Bitcoin ETF. </p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">However, several Bitcoin futures ETFs have gained the regulatory body&#8217;s approval for trading, indicating a gradually warming stance towards cryptocurrencies.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Potential Impact On Bitcoin Price</h2>
<p>The news of BlackRock&#8217;s potential Bitcoin ETF could significantly affect BTC&#8217;s price. Creating such an ETF would allow a broader spectrum of investors to gain exposure to Bitcoin, possibly driving up demand and its price. </p>
<p>ETFs make it easy for institutional investors to gain exposure to Bitcoin, opening up a substantial new demand avenue. Analyst crypto Daan Crypto <a href="https://twitter.com/DaanCrypto/status/1669343023061409803?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reported</a> that Bitcoin had recorded a strong spot bid on Binance in the past few hours – a move that has not been seen for the past few days.</p>
<p>According to the trader, Bitcoin&#8217;s local bottom is <a href="https://twitter.com/DaanCrypto/status/1669297863480713217?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">more likely</a> in if the asset continues to the downside in the coming days. At the time of writing, BTC currently trades at $24,977, down by nearly 4%. Its trading volume has also spiked over the past 7 days indicating massive trading activity.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/UlBTt7W7/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC)’s price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<p>Notably, from a technical perspective, BTC could still be prone to a continuous downtrend, given that the asset hasn&#8217;t hit major support, which can be found in the order block at <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/crypto-market-turmoil-bitcoin-slips-26000-triggers-liquidations/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$24,500</a>.</p>

<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Furthermore, the association with BlackRock, a globally recognized asset management name, could lend credibility and legitimacy to Bitcoin. This increased trust could lead to greater adoption rates and an upward price trajectory for Bitcoin in the long run.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">As observed in the past, any positive development or news about BTC ETFs has often led to a spike in Bitcoin&#8217;s price due to increased demand from retail and institutional investors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/andre-francois-mckenzie-iGYiBhdNTpE-unsplash-2-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Exhibits Bearish Chart Pattern &#8211; Where Could The Price Head Next?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-exhibits-bearish-chart-pattern-where-could-the-price-head-next/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538104</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the past 48 hours, the price of XRP has experienced notable volatility, dropping below $0.50. The crypto market is closely focused on XRP due to a recent favorable development in the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) vs. Ripple lawsuit. The emergence of the Hinman documents has sparked inquiries into the actions of the Securities and Exchange Commission. Although XRP witnessed positive price action earlier this year, the altcoin has faced challenges due to ongoing market volatility. This has led to a break below significant support levels. Related Reading: Ethereum Plunges Below $1,700, Here’s The Metric That Signaled This In Advance Over the last 24 hours, XRP has seen a close to 7% dip. There has been an 8% depreciation on the weekly chart. Both the demand and accumulation of the asset have remained low. This indicated a dominant bearish trend. The fear index remains high in the market, contributing to a decline in investor confidence. Failure to surpass the $0.50 level may result in a significant loss of value for XRP during the next trading session. Furthermore, the decrease in the altcoin&#8217;s market capitalization reinforces the weak buying power reflected on the chart. XRP Price Analysis: One-Day Chart As of the time of writing, the altcoin XRP was trading at $0.47. Following the rejection of the bulls at $0.50, XRP has been experiencing a downward trend. The coin faced resistance at $0.50, and it is anticipated that it may encounter even stronger resistance at $0.55. If the altcoin fails to surpass the $0.55 mark, it will likely dip to its local support level of $0.46 and potentially further down to $0.43. Moreover, the altcoin has formed a bearish double-top pattern, indicating a potential reversal in its price trend as it moves downward on the chart. The trading volume of XRP has also declined in the last session, suggesting that sellers have taken control of the asset. Technical Analysis During the majority of this month, XRP witnessed a decline in demand. This was reflected by the Relative Strength Index (RSI) falling below the half-line, indicating that sellers had taken control of the asset. Additionally, XRP fell below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA), suggesting low demand and indicating that sellers were driving the price momentum in the market. However, if the altcoin trades near the $0.50 price mark, it can potentially bring the price back above the 20-SMA line. This would essentially indicate a resurgence in demand for the asset. In addition to the mentioned technical indicators, other signals on the chart for the altcoin indicate selling pressure. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) formed red histograms, signalling sell signals for the altcoin and indicating a bearish sentiment in the market. Related Reading: Ethereum Bears Set Their Sights On Next Downside Target If $1,700 Support Breaks Furthermore, the Bollinger Bands have widened, indicating increased volatility and potential price fluctuations for the altcoin in the upcoming trading sessions. This suggests that the price of XRP may experience significant changes and unpredictability in the near term. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the past 48 hours, the price of XRP has experienced notable volatility, dropping below $0.50. The crypto market is closely focused on XRP due to a recent favorable development in the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) vs. Ripple lawsuit.</p>
<p>The emergence of the Hinman documents has sparked inquiries into the actions of the Securities and Exchange Commission. Although XRP witnessed positive price action earlier this year, the altcoin has faced challenges due to ongoing market volatility. This has led to a break below significant support levels.</p>

<p>Over the last 24 hours, XRP has seen a close to 7% dip. There has been an 8% depreciation on the weekly chart. Both the demand and accumulation of the asset have remained low. This indicated a dominant bearish trend. The fear index remains high in the market, contributing to a decline in investor confidence.</p>
<p>Failure to surpass the $0.50 level may result in a significant loss of value for XRP during the next trading session. Furthermore, the decrease in the altcoin&#8217;s market capitalization reinforces the weak buying power reflected on the chart.</p>
<h2>XRP Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-538111 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-15_15-34-35.png" alt="XRP" width="1816" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-15_15-34-35.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-15_15-34-35-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-15_15-34-35-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-15_15-34-35-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-15_15-34-35-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-15_15-34-35-750x343.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-15_15-34-35-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>
<p>As of the time of writing, the altcoin XRP was trading at $0.47. Following the rejection of the bulls at $0.50, XRP has been experiencing a downward trend.</p>
<p>The coin faced resistance at $0.50, and it is anticipated that it may encounter even stronger resistance at $0.55. If the altcoin fails to surpass the $0.55 mark, it will likely dip to its local support level of $0.46 and potentially further down to $0.43.</p>
<p>Moreover, the altcoin has formed a bearish double-top pattern, indicating a potential reversal in its price trend as it moves downward on the chart. The trading volume of XRP has also declined in the last session, suggesting that sellers have taken control of the asset.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-538136 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-15_15-35-25.png" alt="XRP" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-15_15-35-25.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-15_15-35-25-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-15_15-35-25-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-15_15-35-25-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-15_15-35-25-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-15_15-35-25-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-15_15-35-25-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>
<p>During the majority of this month, XRP witnessed a decline in demand. This was reflected by the Relative Strength Index (RSI) falling below the half-line, indicating that sellers had taken control of the asset.</p>
<p>Additionally, XRP fell below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA), suggesting low demand and indicating that sellers were driving the price momentum in the market.</p>
<p>However, if the altcoin trades near the $0.50 price mark, it can potentially bring the price back above the 20-SMA line. This would essentially indicate a resurgence in demand for the asset.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-538140 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-15_15-36-39.png" alt="XRP" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-15_15-36-39.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-15_15-36-39-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-15_15-36-39-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-15_15-36-39-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-15_15-36-39-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-15_15-36-39-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSD_2023-06-15_15-36-39-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>In addition to the mentioned technical indicators, other signals on the chart for the altcoin indicate selling pressure. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) formed red histograms, signalling sell signals for the altcoin and indicating a bearish sentiment in the market.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-bears-set-their-sights-on-next-downside-target-if-1700-support-breaks/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum Bears Set Their Sights On Next Downside Target If $1,700 Support Breaks</a></p>
<p>Furthermore, the Bollinger Bands have widened, indicating increased volatility and potential price fluctuations for the altcoin in the upcoming trading sessions. This suggests that the price of XRP may experience significant changes and unpredictability in the near term.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/dmitry-demidko-91bKtpRpBfc-unsplash-4-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price On Shaky Ground: Market Analysts Warn Of Potential Fall To $20,000 Level</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-price-on-shaky-ground-market-analysts-warn-potential-fall/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 14:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market analyst]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538123</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin, the world&#8217;s largest crypto by market cap, is currently under pressure, as it broke the significant $25,000 mark in the last 24 hours. This development has spurred a sense of urgency among traders and market analysts who are bracing for a possible further dip in the value of Bitcoin (BTC). At the time of writing, BTC is trading at $24,872. The past week has been less than favorable for the cryptocurrency. The asset has plunged 4.2% in the past 24 hours, pushing its price to trade below $25,000. This downward trend has negatively impacted Bitcoin&#8217;s weekly performance, resulting in a 6% loss. Traders And Analysts Voice Concerns Several traders and analysts have shared their predictions for the leading cryptocurrency in response to its downturn. Notably, a trader identified as Bluntz conveyed that the critical test for Bitcoin would be to reclaim the $25,600 mark in the ensuing days.  Related Reading: Bitcoin (BTC) Stored On Exchanges Plummets Amid Regulatory Uncertainties: Santiment In another corner, a trader called Rekt Capital raised concerns about a possible slide of Bitcoin&#8217;s price to lower $20,000. This prediction followed Bitcoin&#8217;s break below another weekly support level situated around $26,600. If Bitcoin faces rejection at this price point in the next few days, Rekt Capital posits that BTC will likely descend to the $20,000 level. Meanwhile, CryptoCon, another analyst, offered his perspective on the Bitcoin situation. In his tweet, CryptoCon pointed out an interesting correlation with the past, stating that Bitcoin found resistance at $31,000, which was also a key resistance level back in 2016. According to his analysis, not only did BTC meet rejection at this resistance level, but it also found support when the price broke below its current all-time high.  Bitcoin Latest Price Action It is worth noting that Bitcoin has been in a notable bearish trend in the past week. The largest crypto asset by market capitalization has recorded a downward movement falling by more than 5% in the past 7 days. BTC has continued the downtrend over the past 24 hours, seeing a 4.2% loss. At the time of writing, BTC trades at $24,925 after moving slightly above $26,000 on Sunday. Bitcoin’s trading volume has spiked over the past 7 days from below $10 billion earlier this Monday to $14 billion in the past 24 hours, indicating massive trading activity, which could turn into a violent sell-off given its current price. However, the asset’s market capitalization has seen a more than $30 billion loss in the past 7 days. BTC’s market cap has plummeted from $518 billion last Thursday to $483 billion. Related Reading: Data Reveals Short-Term Bitcoin Holders Refuse To Sell Despite SEC Crackdown While the regulatory pressure on crypto has continued to intensify, it is important to note that these projections from these traders and market analysts offer a glimpse into the Bitcoin possible potential movements as the regulatory saga unfolds. Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin, the world&#8217;s largest crypto by market cap, is currently under pressure, as it broke the significant $25,000 mark in the last 24 hours. This development has spurred a sense of urgency among traders and market analysts who are bracing for a possible further dip in the value of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-dominance-records-shifting-trends-stablecoin-flows/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin (BTC)</a>. </p>
<p>At the time of writing, BTC is <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/crypto-market-turmoil-bitcoin-slips-26000-triggers-liquidations/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">trading at $24,872</a>. The past week has been less than favorable for the cryptocurrency. The asset has plunged 4.2% in the past 24 hours, pushing its price to trade below $25,000. This downward trend has negatively impacted Bitcoin&#8217;s weekly performance, resulting in a 6% loss.</p>
<h2>Traders And Analysts Voice Concerns</h2>
<p>Several traders and analysts have shared their predictions for the leading cryptocurrency in response to its downturn. Notably, a trader identified as Bluntz <a href="https://twitter.com/Bluntz_Capital/status/1669109382762876929?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">conveyed</a> that the critical test for Bitcoin would be to reclaim the $25,600 mark in the ensuing days. </p>

<p>In another corner, a trader called Rekt Capital <a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1669035211215056896?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">raised concerns</a> about a possible slide of Bitcoin&#8217;s price to lower $20,000. This prediction followed Bitcoin&#8217;s break below another weekly support level situated around $26,600.</p>
<p>If Bitcoin faces rejection at this price point in the next few days, Rekt Capital posits that BTC will likely descend to the $20,000 level.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, CryptoCon, another analyst, offered his perspective on the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-btc-stored-on-exchanges-plummets-amid-regulatory/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin situation</a>. In his <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoCon_/status/1669005146506788864?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">tweet</a>, CryptoCon pointed out an interesting correlation with the past, stating that Bitcoin found resistance at $31,000, which was also a key resistance level back in 2016.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-538129 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fyl9UROXgAQLleB-860x574.jpeg" alt="Bitcoin MRVRV Z-Score." width="860" height="574" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fyl9UROXgAQLleB-860x574.jpeg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fyl9UROXgAQLleB-460x307.jpeg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fyl9UROXgAQLleB-768x513.jpeg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fyl9UROXgAQLleB-750x501.jpeg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fyl9UROXgAQLleB-1140x761.jpeg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fyl9UROXgAQLleB.jpeg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>According to his analysis, not only did BTC meet rejection at this resistance level, but it also found support when the price broke below its current all-time high. </p>
<h2>Bitcoin Latest Price Action</h2>
<p>It is worth noting that Bitcoin has been in a notable bearish trend in the past week. The largest crypto asset by market capitalization has recorded a downward movement falling by more than 5% in the past 7 days. BTC has continued the downtrend over the past 24 hours, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/binance-australia-unveils-bitcoin-discount-in-countdown/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">seeing a 4.2% loss</a>.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/U2wLQvVZ/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC)’s price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<p>At the time of writing, BTC trades at $24,925 after moving slightly above $26,000 on Sunday. <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/data-reveals-short-term-bitcoin-holders-refuse-to-sell/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin’s trading volume</a> has spiked over the past 7 days from below $10 billion earlier this Monday to $14 billion in the past 24 hours, indicating massive trading activity, which could turn into a violent sell-off given its current price.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">However, the asset’s market capitalization has seen a more than $30 billion loss in the past 7 days. BTC’s market cap has plummeted from $518 billion last Thursday to $483 billion.</p>

<p dir="ltr">While the regulatory pressure on crypto has continued to intensify, it is important to note that these projections from these traders and market analysts offer a glimpse into the Bitcoin possible potential movements as the regulatory saga unfolds.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Bitcoin-460x329.jpeg" width="460" height="329" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Plunges Below $1,700, Here&#8217;s The Metric That Signaled This In Advance</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-plunges-1700-metric-signaled-in-advance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 13:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Plunge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538085</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum has plunged below $1,700 during the past day. Here&#8217;s the on-chain indicator that may have signaled this dip in advance. Ethereum Age Consumed Metric Saw A Spike Before The Price Decline According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, institutional investors look to have been expecting the move to take place. The indicator of interest here is the &#8220;ETH age consumed,&#8221; which first finds the total number of coins moving on the Ethereum blockchain. Then it multiplies this value by the days these coins had been dormant before their movement. So, in this way, the metric keeps track of how many coins are being sold/moved each day and uses their age as a weighting factor. This means that many old coins are moved to the network whenever this indicator&#8217;s value is high. Naturally, low values of the metric, on the other hand, would imply that there aren&#8217;t many coins moving on the chain right now or some coins with a low average age are being transferred. Related Reading: XRP And Ethereum Seeing Increased Social Media Talk As Bitcoin Loses Interest Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Ethereum age consumed over the past month: Looks like the value of the metric has been quite high in recent days &#124; Source: Santiment on Twitter As displayed in the above graph, the Ethereum age consumed metric had recently registered a very large spike. This would suggest the potential movement of many dormant coins on the chain during this surge. Generally, when such large spikes in the indicator are observed, it&#8217;s a sign of selling from the long-term holders (LTHs). The LTH cohort includes all the investors holding onto their coins since more than 155 days ago. These holders are the experienced hands in the market who don&#8217;t easily sell even when the market is distressed. Because of this reason, their movements can be something to watch out for, as when they do finally sell, it&#8217;s usually not a positive sign for the price. The chart shows that the LTHs had also shown a large move earlier in the month. Shortly after these investors became active, the cryptocurrency price plunged. Related Reading: Bitcoin Sentiment On Social Media Now Most Red Since COVID Crash, Bottom Signal? This time, the spike in the Ethereum age consumed also seems to have preceded a price decline, as the cryptocurrency&#8217;s value has now dropped below the $1,700 level. This latest price plunge has come after the news that the US Federal Reserve isn&#8217;t raising interest rates this time, but more hikes would be coming later in the year to fight inflation. Santiment suggests that the spike in the age consumed metric before the price decline could imply that the institutions already expected the move, hence why they shifted their coins early. ETH Price At the time of writing, Ethereum is trading around $1,600, down 11% in the last week. ETH has taken a plunge recently &#124; Source: ETHUSD on TradingView Featured image from iStock.com, charts from TradingView.com, Santiment.net]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum has plunged below $1,700 during the past day. Here&#8217;s the on-chain indicator that may have signaled this dip in advance.</p>
<h2>Ethereum Age Consumed Metric Saw A Spike Before The Price Decline</h2>
<p>According to data from the on-chain analytics firm <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1669084533684326400" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Santiment</a>, institutional investors look to have been expecting the move to take place. The indicator of interest here is the &#8220;ETH <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-binary-cdd-stays-low-heres-what-this-means/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">age consumed</a>,&#8221; which first finds the total number of coins moving on the Ethereum blockchain. Then it multiplies this value by the days these coins had been dormant before their movement.</p>
<p>So, in this way, the metric keeps track of how many coins are being sold/moved each day and uses their age as a weighting factor. This means that many old coins are moved to the network whenever this indicator&#8217;s value is high.</p>
<p>Naturally, low values of the metric, on the other hand, would imply that there aren&#8217;t many coins moving on the chain right now or some coins with a low average age are being transferred.</p>

<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Ethereum age consumed over the past month:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FynHFqBacAAOFkQ?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Ethereum Age Consumed" width="2797" height="1796"/></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the Ethereum age consumed metric had recently registered a very large spike. This would suggest the potential movement of many dormant coins on the chain during this surge.</p>
<p>Generally, when such large spikes in the indicator are observed, it&#8217;s a sign of selling from the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-long-term-holders-holding-price-decline/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">long-term holders</a> (LTHs). The LTH cohort includes all the investors holding onto their coins since more than 155 days ago.</p>
<p>These holders are the experienced hands in the market who don&#8217;t easily sell even when the market is distressed. Because of this reason, their movements can be something to watch out for, as when they do finally sell, it&#8217;s usually not a positive sign for the price.</p>
<p>The chart shows that the LTHs had also shown a large move earlier in the month. Shortly after these investors became active, the cryptocurrency price plunged.</p>

<p>This time, the spike in the Ethereum age consumed also seems to have preceded a price decline, as the cryptocurrency&#8217;s value has now dropped below the $1,700 level.</p>
<p>This latest price plunge has come after the news that the US Federal Reserve <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin-price-hammered-below-25000-amid-the-feds-hawkish-tone-sec-lawsuits/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">isn&#8217;t raising interest rates</a> this time, but more hikes would be coming later in the year to fight inflation.</p>
<p>Santiment suggests that the spike in the age consumed metric before the price decline could imply that the institutions already expected the move, hence why they shifted their coins early.</p>
<h2>ETH Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Ethereum is trading around $1,600, down 11% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/8qdULZQ3/" alt="Ethereum Price Chart" width="1534" height="911"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1386847296-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here&#8217;s Why The Tether FUD Could Be Good For Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/heres-why-tether-fud-could-be-good-for-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 12:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538109</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin market is once again in turmoil, and the reason is an old acquaintance: no, not the US Federal Reserve, but the worries and rumors about Tether&#8217;s stablecoin, USDT. Anyone who has been active in the Bitcoin and crypto market for a while knows that rumors about USDT&#8217;s lack of backing are part of every bear market. And this bear market seems to mean it particularly &#8220;well&#8221; as the Tether FUD is now making a reappearance in this cycle. As NewsBTC reported earlier today, USDT has slightly lost its peg to the US dollar as the Curve 3Pool has lost its balance. The reason for this is that whales are selling USDT and trading it for USDC as well as DAI. However, according to Tether CTO Paolo Arduino, the company is &#8220;ready to redeem any amount 1:1 against US dollars&#8221;. Historically, the de-pegging of USDT is not an uncommon occurrence. Samson Mow, CEO of Bitcoin focused company JAN3, writes: Tether FUD is always the FUD bottom. It&#8217;s what they pull out when there&#8217;s nothing left. Up soon. Analyst Miles Deutscher has a similar view. He explained: &#8220;Fun Fact: Stablecoin FUD often marks local bottoms,&#8221; and shared the following chart. Bottom Signal For The Bitcoin Price? As can be seen in the chart, the Tether FUD first surfaced at the end of June 2022. At the time, news emerged that hedge fund Fir Tree Capital Management was shorting Tether after the Terra ecosystem stablecoin Terra USD collapsed. Contrary to speculation, however, Tether was able to process all USDT redemptions, even though the value of USDT had fallen to $0.9520 temporarily. Related Reading: Tether (USDT) De-Pegs As Crypto Market Stumbles, More Downside Coming? In mid-November 2022, the cryptocurrency exchange FTX went bankrupt after its competitor Binance backed out of a purchase agreement. The Tether FUD hit a 6-month high and the price of USDT fell to $0.9970. Again, Tether was able to handle all redemptions, while the market found a local bottom. Most recently, USDC depegging provided the local bottom signal in March this year. The event was caused by the collapse of the counterparty from stablecoin issuer Circle, Silicon Valley Bank (SVB). Crypto whales had also tried to take profits from the situation at the time, while other USDC holders sold out of panic. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Hammered Below $25,000 Amid Fed’s Hawkish Tone, SEC Lawsuits Tether emerged as the clear winner from the latter situation and was able to capture large market shares from USDC since then. Most recently, Tether reported huge profits, some of which they are investing in Bitcoin, as NewsBTC reported. This is another reason why crypto expert Thor Hartvigsen believes that the likelihood of Tether not having enough funds to settle all USDT redemptions is &#8220;pretty low&#8221;, adding: &#8220;According to Tether, the company made $1.48b in profits in Q1 alone which brought the reserve surplus to $2.44b. They&#8217;ve further been winding down bank deposits (hold less than $0.5b here) and acquired over $53b in US treasuries throughout 2022.&#8221; Remarkably, the price of USDT has already returned to its default level at press time. After the USDC/ USDT price on Binance climbed temporarily to $1.0042, it was now already back at $1.0019. As of press time, the Bitcoin price was bucking the Tether FUD and holding slightly above $25,000. However, the drop below the 200-day EMA (blue line) is somewhat critical. Most recently, BTC fell below this indicator which is known as the &#8220;bull line&#8221; during the USDC de-pegging. Therefore, Bitcoin bulls are advised to stage a similar reaction as in March to prevent a further plunge. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin market is once again in turmoil, and the reason is an old acquaintance: no, not the US Federal Reserve, but the worries and rumors about Tether&#8217;s stablecoin, USDT. Anyone who has been active in the Bitcoin and crypto market for a while knows that rumors about USDT&#8217;s lack of backing are part of every bear market. And this bear market seems to mean it particularly &#8220;well&#8221; as the Tether FUD is now making a reappearance in this cycle.</p>
<p>As NewsBTC <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/tether-usdt-de-pegs-as-crypto-market-stumbles/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">reported</a> earlier today, USDT has slightly lost its peg to the US dollar as the Curve 3Pool has lost its balance. The reason for this is that whales are selling USDT and trading it for USDC as well as DAI. However, according to Tether CTO Paolo Arduino, the company is &#8220;ready to redeem any amount 1:1 against US dollars&#8221;.</p>
<p>Historically, the de-pegging of USDT is not an uncommon occurrence. Samson Mow, CEO of Bitcoin focused company JAN3, <a href="https://twitter.com/Excellion/status/1669278944854523907" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">writes</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>Tether FUD is always the FUD bottom. It&#8217;s what they pull out when there&#8217;s nothing left. Up soon.</strong></p></blockquote>
<p>Analyst Miles Deutscher has a similar view. He explained: &#8220;Fun Fact: Stablecoin FUD often marks local bottoms,&#8221; and shared the following chart.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-538114 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fyp8A2VaIAID6dX.jpg" alt="Stablecoin FUD marking the local bottom?" width="2048" height="1243" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fyp8A2VaIAID6dX.jpg 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fyp8A2VaIAID6dX-460x279.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fyp8A2VaIAID6dX-860x522.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fyp8A2VaIAID6dX-768x466.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fyp8A2VaIAID6dX-1536x932.jpg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fyp8A2VaIAID6dX-750x455.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fyp8A2VaIAID6dX-1140x692.jpg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2048px) 100vw, 2048px"/>
<h2>Bottom Signal For The Bitcoin Price?</h2>
<p>As can be seen in the chart, the Tether FUD first surfaced at the end of June 2022. At the time, news emerged that hedge fund Fir Tree Capital Management was shorting Tether after the Terra ecosystem stablecoin Terra USD collapsed. Contrary to speculation, however, Tether was able to process all USDT redemptions, even though the value of USDT had fallen to $0.9520 temporarily.</p>

<p>In mid-November 2022, the cryptocurrency exchange FTX went bankrupt after its competitor Binance backed out of a purchase agreement. The Tether FUD hit a 6-month high and the price of USDT fell to $0.9970. Again, Tether was able to handle all redemptions, while the market found a local bottom.</p>
<p>Most recently, USDC depegging provided the local bottom signal in March this year. The event was caused by the collapse of the counterparty from stablecoin issuer Circle, Silicon Valley Bank (SVB). Crypto whales had also tried to take profits from the situation at the time, while other USDC holders sold out of panic.</p>

<p>Tether emerged as the clear winner from the latter situation and was able to capture large market shares from USDC since then. Most recently, Tether reported huge profits, some of which they are investing in Bitcoin, as NewsBTC <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/tether-bets-on-bitcoin-allocates-up-to-15-of-profits-for-btc-purchases/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">reported</a>.</p>
<p>This is another reason why crypto expert Thor Hartvigsen believes that the likelihood of Tether not having enough funds to settle all USDT redemptions is &#8220;pretty low&#8221;, <a href="https://twitter.com/ThorHartvigsen/status/1669280809449078784" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">adding</a>: &#8220;According to Tether, the company made $1.48b in profits in Q1 alone which brought the reserve surplus to $2.44b. They&#8217;ve further been winding down bank deposits (hold less than $0.5b here) and acquired over $53b in US treasuries throughout 2022.&#8221;</p>
<p>Remarkably, the price of USDT has already returned to its default level at press time. After the USDC/ USDT price on Binance climbed temporarily to $1.0042, it was now already back at $1.0019.</p>
<p>As of press time, the Bitcoin price was bucking the Tether FUD and holding slightly above $25,000. However, the drop below the 200-day EMA (blue line) is somewhat critical. Most recently, BTC fell below this indicator which is known as the &#8220;bull line&#8221; during the USDC de-pegging. Therefore, Bitcoin bulls are advised to stage a similar reaction as in March to prevent a further plunge.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-538118 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-15_13-49-30.png" alt="Bitcoin price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-15_13-49-30.png 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-15_13-49-30-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-15_13-49-30-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-15_13-49-30-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-15_13-49-30-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-15_13-49-30-2048x944.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-15_13-49-30-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-15_13-49-30-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3628px) 100vw, 3628px"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1412367772-460x248.jpg" width="460" height="248" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Price Sheds 19% As Bearish Sentiment Looms Large</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano-ada-price-sheds-19/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 10:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538090</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) experienced a significant upswing in March, reaching a year-to-date high of $0.4622. Excitement spread among ADA investors as the price climbed, but unfortunately, it was short-lived. The price faced rejection at that level, causing ADA to plummet to the $0.3760 support level.  However, despite this setback, ADA managed to find some stability as the bulls defended this crucial support level. Throughout May, the price of ADA fluctuated above and below the support level, giving hope to investors. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Collapses: How Long Can The Meme Coin Climb Back Up? However, the tides turned in June when intense selling pressure gripped the market. ADA, like many other altcoins, found itself caught in the aftermath of regulatory issues with its supposed security label. The market sentiment turned bearish, and altcoins suffered significant losses as a result. ADA Not A Security: Gensler Once Again Getting Ahead of Himself #Cardano #cardanofeed #ADA #crypto #cardanocommunity #bitcoin #CoinMarketCap #blockchain #cryptocurrency #CardanoADA #btc $ADAhttps://t.co/cwM1SD0Brm — Cardano Feed ($ADA) (@CardanoFeed) June 14, 2023 Now, the question arises: What lies ahead for ADA as the bearish sentiment continues to loom? The Correlation Between Bitcoin Price, Altcoin Performance At the time of writing, Bitcoin (BTC) is trading below the $25,000 level, exerting its influence on the broader cryptocurrency market. The price decline of BTC has had a profound impact on altcoins, causing a ripple effect throughout the entire crypto ecosystem. Source: Coingecko Altcoins, including Cardano&#8217;s ADA, have been significantly affected by Bitcoin&#8217;s downturn. ADA, currently priced at $0.259126 at CoinGecko, has experienced a 7.3% slump in the past 24 hours alone, contributing to a substantial seven-day decline of 22%. These figures illustrate the strong correlation between Bitcoin&#8217;s price movements and the performance of altcoins. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Hammered Below $25,000 Amid Fed’s Hawkish Tone, SEC Lawsuits Bitcoin, being the largest and most established cryptocurrency, often serves as the bellwether for the entire crypto market. When Bitcoin experiences a price drop, it tends to instigate a domino effect, triggering a widespread sell-off across various digital assets. This correlation stems from the fact that many altcoin traders and investors use Bitcoin as a benchmark or a base currency for trading. ADA market cap slightly below $9 billion. Chart: TradingView.com Furthermore, Bitcoin&#8217;s price movements often reflect the overall market sentiment and investor confidence in the cryptocurrency industry. When Bitcoin faces significant challenges or negative news, it creates a sense of uncertainty and fear among market participants. As a result, investors may seek to reduce their exposure to riskier assets like altcoins, leading to a decline in their prices. Waning Interest In Cardano Bullish Rally According to data provided by Coinalyze on the four-hour timeframe, it has been observed that the Open Interest (OI) for ADA has been decreasing. The diminishing Open Interest suggests that market speculators are displaying a lack of enthusiasm toward a potential bullish rally for ADA. ADA Open Interest down. Source: Coinalyze Similarly, the Spot CVD (Cumulative Volume Delta) has been consistently on a downward trend, highlighting the prevailing bearish sentiment in the market. This further emphasizes the dominance of bearish market forces, indicating a negative outlook for ADA. Featured image from CoinChapter]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cardano (ADA) experienced a significant upswing in March, reaching a year-to-date high of $0.4622. Excitement spread among ADA investors as the price climbed, but unfortunately, it was short-lived. The price faced rejection at that level, causing ADA to plummet to the $0.3760 support level. </p>
<p>However, despite this setback, ADA managed to find some stability as the bulls defended this crucial support level. Throughout May, the <a href="https://www.nasdaq.com/market-activity/cryptocurrency/ada/historical" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">price of ADA fluctuated</a> above and below the support level, giving hope to investors.</p>

<p>However, the tides turned in June when intense selling pressure gripped the market. ADA, like many other altcoins, found itself caught in the aftermath of regulatory issues with its <a href="https://twitter.com/CardanoFeed/status/1668950862771765250" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">supposed security label</a>. The market sentiment turned bearish, and altcoins suffered significant losses as a result.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">ADA Not A Security: Gensler Once Again Getting Ahead of Himself <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Cardano?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Cardano</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/cardanofeed?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#cardanofeed</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ADA?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#ADA</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/crypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#crypto</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/cardanocommunity?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#cardanocommunity</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#bitcoin</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/CoinMarketCap?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#CoinMarketCap</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/blockchain?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#blockchain</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/cryptocurrency?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#cryptocurrency</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/CardanoADA?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#CardanoADA</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/btc?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#btc</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ADA&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$ADA</a><a href="https://t.co/cwM1SD0Brm" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/cwM1SD0Brm</a></p>
<p>— Cardano Feed ($ADA) (@CardanoFeed) <a href="https://twitter.com/CardanoFeed/status/1668950862771765250?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 14, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Now, the question arises: What lies ahead for ADA as the bearish sentiment continues to loom?</p>
<h2><strong>The Correlation Between Bitcoin Price, Altcoin Performance</strong></h2>
<p>At the time of writing, <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/bitcoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Bitcoin (BTC) is trading below the $25,000 level</a>, exerting its influence on the broader cryptocurrency market. The price decline of BTC has had a profound impact on altcoins, causing a ripple effect throughout the entire crypto ecosystem.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-538093" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-92.png" alt="" width="1134" height="64" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-92.png 1134w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-92-460x26.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-92-860x49.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-92-768x43.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-92-750x42.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1134px) 100vw, 1134px"/></p>

<p>Altcoins, including Cardano&#8217;s ADA, have been significantly affected by Bitcoin&#8217;s downturn. ADA, currently priced at $0.259126 at <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/cardano" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a>, has experienced a 7.3% slump in the past 24 hours alone, contributing to a substantial seven-day decline of 22%. These figures illustrate the strong correlation between Bitcoin&#8217;s price movements and the performance of altcoins.</p>

<p>Bitcoin, being the largest and most established cryptocurrency, often serves as the bellwether for the entire crypto market. When Bitcoin experiences a price drop, it tends to instigate a domino effect, triggering a widespread sell-off across various digital assets. </p>
<p>This correlation stems from the fact that many altcoin traders and investors use Bitcoin as a benchmark or a base currency for trading.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/jorf89b9/" width="2314" height="1109"/></p>

<p>Furthermore, Bitcoin&#8217;s price movements often reflect the overall market sentiment and investor confidence in the cryptocurrency industry. When Bitcoin faces significant challenges or negative news, it creates a sense of uncertainty and fear among market participants. As a result, investors may seek to reduce their exposure to riskier assets like altcoins, leading to a decline in their prices.</p>
<h2><strong>Waning Interest In Cardano Bullish Rally</strong></h2>
<p>According to data provided by Coinalyze on the four-hour timeframe, it has been observed that the <a href="https://coinalyze.net/cardano/open-interest/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Open Interest (OI) for ADA</a> has been decreasing. The diminishing Open Interest suggests that market speculators are displaying a lack of enthusiasm toward a potential bullish rally for ADA.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-538098 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-94-860x145.png" alt="" width="860" height="145" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-94-860x145.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-94-460x77.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-94-768x129.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-94-750x126.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-94-1140x192.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-94.png 1497w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>Similarly, the Spot CVD (Cumulative Volume Delta) has been consistently on a downward trend, highlighting the prevailing bearish sentiment in the market. This further emphasizes the dominance of bearish market forces, indicating a negative outlook for ADA.</p>
<p><em>Featured image from CoinChapter</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-93-460x261.png" width="460" height="261" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tether (USDT) De-Pegs As Crypto Market Stumbles, More Downside Coming?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/tether-usdt-de-pegs-as-crypto-market-stumbles/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538063</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin and crypto markets are deep in the red today. Even though the US Federal Reserve announced the hoped-for interest rate pause yesterday, the release of the updated dot plot was a nasty surprise for the financial markets. The Fed revealed in its updated dot plot that it sees the average terminal interest rate at 5.6% instead of 5.1% for 2023. As Fed Chairman Jerome Powell explained, almost all FOMC members think further hikes are reasonable. And the resulting price slump in the crypto markets is also having an impact on Tether&#8217;s stablecoin, USDT, at the moment. Tether (USDT) De-Pegs Slightly USDT has slightly lost its peg to the US dollar at the time of writing. On Binance, the USDC / USDT exchange rate was at 1.0030. The reason for this seems to be Curve&#8217;s 3Pool, which is one of the most important pools for stablecoin trading in decentralized finance. Currently USDT accounts for 73.79% of the Curve 3Pool, DAI for 13.05% and USDC for 13.16%. Apparently, users are rushing to exchange tens of millions of USDT in favor of the stablecoins USD Coin (USDC) and Dai (DAI). The ideal balance of the Curve 3Pool should be 33.33% for each of the three stablecoins. Due to the imbalance, USDT is currently de-pegging. Related Reading: Crypto Market Bleeds As SEC Pressures Mount, Is It Time To Buy? Chinese journalist Collin Wu also reports that in Aave V2, the USDT lending rate skyrocketed, including the deposit rate by more than 20% and the loan rate by more than 30%. Some big whales are borrowing USDT on Aave and selling it on DEX like Curve. One of them is Ethereum whale @samczsun. He borrowed 31.5 million USDT from Aave V2 using 17,000 ETH and 14,000 stETH as collateral, and then exchanged all the borrowed USDT for USDC on 1inch. The borrower then deposited USDC 10 million and USDC 21 million to V2 and V3 respectively. This guy then borrowed 12 million USDT from V3 and deposited it with V2. Wu further explains: Twenty minutes after czsamsun.eth borrowed USDT, another address (0xd2&#8230;0701) mortgaged 52,200 stETH through Aave V2 and borrowed 50 million USDC, using USDC&#62;USDT de-peg, with a few million USDC converts USDC from Curve to USDT in batches at a time, and each operation can obtain an additional 1000-8000 USDT. However, Tether CTO Paolo Arduino remains calm. On Twitter, he commented that &#8220;markets are edgy in these days,&#8221; adding: &#8220;so it&#8217;s easy for attackers to capitalize on this general sentiment. But at Tether we&#8217;re ready as always. Let them come. We&#8217;re ready to redeem any amount.&#8221; Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Hammered Below $25,000 Amid Fed’s Hawkish Tone, SEC Lawsuits The last time Curve 3Pool was unbalanced was in mid-March, when the balance of USDC and DAI rose to over 45% each. Moreover, there was also an imbalance in November 2022 when FTX and in May 2022 when the Terra ecosystem collapsed. Will The Crypto Market Continue To Fall? Bitcoin, as the leading indicator for the crypto market, is in a critical situation. For the first time since the mid-March crash, the BTC price has fallen below the extremely important 200-day EMA (blue line). A recapture of the price level currently at $25,290 could be of high importance to create a recovery similar to mid-March 2023. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin and crypto markets are deep in the red today. Even though the US Federal Reserve announced the hoped-for interest rate pause yesterday, the release of the updated dot plot was a nasty surprise for the financial markets.</p>
<p>The Fed revealed in its updated dot plot that it sees the average terminal interest rate at 5.6% instead of 5.1% for 2023. As Fed Chairman Jerome Powell explained, almost all FOMC members think further hikes are reasonable. And the resulting price slump in the crypto markets is also having an impact on Tether&#8217;s stablecoin, USDT, at the moment.</p>
<h2>Tether (USDT) De-Pegs Slightly</h2>
<p>USDT has slightly lost its peg to the US dollar at the time of writing. On Binance, the USDC / USDT exchange rate was at 1.0030. The reason for this seems to be Curve&#8217;s 3Pool, which is one of the most important pools for stablecoin trading in decentralized finance.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-538072 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/USDC-USDT-Binance.png" alt="crypto USDC USDT" width="3797" height="1777" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/USDC-USDT-Binance.png 3797w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/USDC-USDT-Binance-460x215.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/USDC-USDT-Binance-860x402.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/USDC-USDT-Binance-768x359.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/USDC-USDT-Binance-1536x719.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/USDC-USDT-Binance-2048x958.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/USDC-USDT-Binance-750x351.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/USDC-USDT-Binance-1140x534.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3797px) 100vw, 3797px"/>
<p>Currently USDT accounts for 73.79% of the Curve 3Pool, DAI for 13.05% and USDC for 13.16%. Apparently, users are rushing to exchange tens of millions of USDT in favor of the stablecoins USD Coin (USDC) and Dai (DAI).</p>
<p>The ideal balance of the Curve 3Pool should be 33.33% for each of the three stablecoins. Due to the imbalance, USDT is currently de-pegging.</p>

<p>Chinese journalist Collin Wu also reports that in Aave V2, the USDT lending rate skyrocketed, including the deposit rate by more than 20% and the loan rate by more than 30%. Some big whales are borrowing USDT on Aave and selling it on DEX like Curve.</p>
<p>One of them is Ethereum whale @samczsun. He borrowed 31.5 million USDT from Aave V2 using 17,000 ETH and 14,000 stETH as collateral, and then exchanged all the borrowed USDT for USDC on 1inch. The borrower then deposited USDC 10 million and USDC 21 million to V2 and V3 respectively. This guy then borrowed 12 million USDT from V3 and deposited it with V2. Wu further <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1669244069128855552" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">explains</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>Twenty minutes after czsamsun.eth borrowed USDT, another address (0xd2&#8230;0701) mortgaged 52,200 stETH through Aave V2 and borrowed 50 million USDC, using USDC&gt;USDT de-peg, with a few million USDC converts USDC from Curve to USDT in batches at a time, and each operation can obtain an additional 1000-8000 USDT.</strong></p></blockquote>
<p>However, Tether CTO Paolo Arduino remains calm. On Twitter, he <a href="https://twitter.com/paoloardoino/status/1669223742831042562" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">commented</a> that &#8220;markets are edgy in these days,&#8221; adding: &#8220;so it&#8217;s easy for attackers to capitalize on this general sentiment. But at Tether we&#8217;re ready as always. Let them come. We&#8217;re ready to redeem any amount.&#8221;</p>

<p>The last time Curve 3Pool was unbalanced was in mid-March, when the balance of USDC and DAI rose to over 45% each. Moreover, there was also an imbalance in November 2022 when FTX and in May 2022 when the Terra ecosystem collapsed.</p>
<h2>Will The Crypto Market Continue To Fall?</h2>
<p>Bitcoin, as the leading indicator for the crypto market, is in a critical situation. For the first time since the mid-March crash, the BTC price has fallen below the extremely important 200-day EMA (blue line). A recapture of the price level currently at $25,290 could be of high importance to create a recovery similar to mid-March 2023.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-538079 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-15_10-47-07.png" alt="Bitcoin price" width="3625" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-15_10-47-07.png 3625w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-15_10-47-07-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-15_10-47-07-860x397.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-15_10-47-07-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-15_10-47-07-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-15_10-47-07-2048x945.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-15_10-47-07-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-15_10-47-07-1140x526.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3625px) 100vw, 3625px"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1402102628-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
