<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"

	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:32:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">221170450</site>	<item>
		<title>Terra Luna Token Burn Proposal Greenlit &#8211; Could $1 Be Hittable?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/all/terra-luna-token-burn-proposal-greenlit-could-1-be-hittable/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 13:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNC burn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNC price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra Luna Classic]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546196</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Terra Luna has seen the successful approval of community proposals 11658 and 11660, authorizing the retrieval and subsequent incineration of a total of 800 million USTC. The prevailing sentiment within the community leans towards directing these USTC tokens towards the burn address as opposed to reintegrating them into the community pool. Conversely, a noteworthy shift has been detected in LUNC&#8217;s staking ratio within the past day, where a previous upward trajectory has now given way to a decline. This alteration in the staking ratio commonly signifies reduced assurance among stakers regarding a specific asset. Related Reading: Can Litecoin Bulls Turn The Tide On Recent Declines? A Closer Look Here’s what’s going on within the struggling Terra community: Recent Community Decisions Shape Terra Luna Future In a significant turn of events, Proposal 11658 titled &#8220;Return of Community funds not used,&#8221; presented by Vegas, a former member of the ex-Terra Rebels developer group, has achieved approval with an affirmative vote percentage of 70.27%. And it seems that once again.someone is fighting against us&#8230; So the 200 milion ustc that RH have &#8220;missed&#8221; used.. is one of the reasons that I was so vocal to not send all the rest of the funds to the CP. Now seems that is already moviments asking the signers to not do,the 11658… — Vegas (@VegasMorph) August 8, 2023 Vegas has advocated for the reintegration of 800 million USTC on-chain funds back into the Terra Luna Classic community pool. This proposition stems from the observation that the Ozone Protocol project is presently deviating from the proposed development plan. In a parallel development, Proposal 11660, labeled &#8220;Burn 100% of Funds Should Prop: 11658 Pass,&#8221; has garnered substantial support, amassing a &#8220;Yes&#8221; vote share of 82.55%. This counter-proposal asserts that a substantial segment of the community is advocating for the incineration of the 800 million tokens. Consequently, even if Proposal 11658 is ratified, the counter-proposal is poised to take precedence due to its higher vote count. Total crypto market cap reaches $1.12 trillion today. Chart: TradingView.com Awaiting the community&#8217;s consideration is another proposal, suggesting the burning of 80% of the funds while allocating the remaining 20% to the community pool designated for developers. Notably, this proposal has encountered limited favor, with only 46% of the community showing agreement. The aftermath of these recent updates has naturally sparked curiosity regarding their impact on the price dynamics of LUNC. How are these decisions influencing the valuation of the token? Staking Confidence Wanes As LUNC Faces Price Challenges Bringing the most recent developments to the forefront, there has been a notable decrease in the percentage of LUNC staked within the past 24 hours. This shift indicates that holders and users are opting to un-stake their holdings, signifying a diminished level of trust and confidence in the token&#8217;s performance. The implications of this trend raise questions about the current sentiment surrounding LUNC. Related Reading: PEPE’s Future: Will Prices Of Meme Coins Continue To Drop? A fresh analysis of LUNC&#8217;s price dynamics reveals that the token&#8217;s staking ratio now stands at 14.92%. This percentage signifies the portion of LUNC holdings that have been committed to staking, underscoring the level of engagement and commitment from the community. Source: Coingecko Meanwhile, as observed on CoinGecko, LUNC is presently valued at $0.000077. Over the preceding 24 hours, the token&#8217;s price has experienced a reduction of 1.3%, while its value has declined by 2.7% over the past seven days. These figures shed light on the challenges LUNC currently faces within the market and the potential impact on investor sentiment. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Analytics Insight]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Terra Luna has seen the successful approval of community proposals 11658 and 11660, authorizing the retrieval and subsequent incineration of a total of 800 million USTC. The prevailing sentiment within the community leans towards directing these USTC tokens towards the burn address as opposed to reintegrating them into the community pool.</p>
<p>Conversely, a noteworthy shift has been detected in LUNC&#8217;s staking ratio within the past day, where a previous upward trajectory has now given way to a decline. This alteration in the staking ratio commonly signifies reduced assurance among stakers regarding a specific asset.</p>

<p>Here’s what’s going on within the struggling Terra community:</p>
<h2><strong>Recent Community Decisions Shape Terra Luna Future</strong></h2>
<p>In a significant turn of events, Proposal 11658 titled &#8220;Return of Community funds not used,&#8221; <a href="https://twitter.com/VegasMorph/status/1688814245104807936" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">presented by Vegas</a>, a former member of the ex-Terra Rebels developer group, has achieved approval with an affirmative vote percentage of 70.27%.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">And it seems that once again.someone is fighting against us&#8230; So the 200 milion ustc that RH have &#8220;missed&#8221; used.. is one of the reasons that I was so vocal to not send all the rest of the funds to the CP. Now seems that is already moviments asking the signers to not do,the 11658…</p>
<p>— Vegas (@VegasMorph) <a href="https://twitter.com/VegasMorph/status/1688814245104807936?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 8, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Vegas has advocated for the reintegration of 800 million USTC on-chain funds back into the Terra Luna Classic community pool. This proposition stems from the observation that the Ozone Protocol project is presently deviating from the proposed development plan.</p>
<p>In a parallel development, Proposal 11660, labeled &#8220;Burn 100% of Funds Should Prop: 11658 Pass,&#8221; has garnered substantial support, amassing a &#8220;Yes&#8221; vote share of 82.55%. This counter-proposal asserts that a substantial segment of the community is advocating for the incineration of the 800 million tokens. </p>
<p>Consequently, even if Proposal 11658 is ratified, the counter-proposal is poised to take precedence due to its higher vote count.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/3JWNo8JQ/" width="2475" height="1179"/></p>

<p>Awaiting the community&#8217;s consideration is another proposal, suggesting the <a href="https://coingape.com/terra-luna-classic-proposals-to-burn-800-million-tokens-officially-passed-ustc-lunc-to-1" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">burning of 80% of the funds</a> while allocating the remaining 20% to the community pool designated for developers. Notably, this proposal has encountered limited favor, with only 46% of the community showing agreement.</p>
<p>The aftermath of these recent updates has naturally sparked curiosity regarding their impact on the price dynamics of LUNC. How are these decisions influencing the valuation of the token?</p>
<h2><strong>Staking Confidence Wanes As LUNC Faces Price Challenges</strong></h2>
<p>Bringing the most recent developments to the forefront, there has been a notable decrease in the percentage of LUNC staked within the past 24 hours. This shift indicates that holders and users are opting to un-stake their holdings, signifying a diminished level of trust and confidence in the token&#8217;s performance. </p>
<p>The implications of this trend raise questions about the current sentiment surrounding LUNC.</p>

<p>A fresh analysis of <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/will-terra-classic-price-action-help-its-staking-ecosystem-grow/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">LUNC&#8217;s price dynamics</a> reveals that the token&#8217;s staking ratio now stands at 14.92%. This percentage signifies the portion of LUNC holdings that have been committed to staking, underscoring the level of engagement and commitment from the community.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-546198" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-33.png?resize=1024%2C57" alt="" width="1024" height="57" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-33.png?resize=1024%2C57?w=1136 1136w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-33.png?resize=1024%2C57?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-33.png?resize=1024%2C57?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-33.png?resize=1024%2C57?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-33.png?resize=1024%2C57?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>Meanwhile, as observed on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/terra-luna-classic" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a>, LUNC is presently valued at $0.000077. Over the preceding 24 hours, the token&#8217;s price has experienced a reduction of 1.3%, while its value has declined by 2.7% over the past seven days. </p>
<p>These figures shed light on the challenges LUNC currently faces within the market and the potential impact on investor sentiment.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Analytics Insight</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-14.jpg?fit=460%2C256" width="460" height="256" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546196</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Analyst Deciphers XRP Price Movement: What&#8217;s Next For The Altcoin?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/crypto-analyst-deciphers-xrp-price-movement/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 12:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin n]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546187</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[One of the leading names in the crypto analysis sector, Michael van de Poppe, recently shed light on XRP&#8217;s price movements. Known for his crypto observations, his latest tweet has stirred conversations in the crypto community, especially pertaining to Ripple’s native cryptocurrency, XRP. In his most recent analysis, van de Poppe indicated that XRP&#8217;s price movement is now at a critical juncture.  XRP Entering The &#8216;Area Of Interest&#8217; Particularly, according to Michael van de Poppe&#8217;s tweet, XRP is currently moving into what he terms an &#8216;area of interest&#8217; on its weekly chart. This essentially points towards potential pivotal moments in the coin&#8217;s price trajectory that can be significant for traders. Related Reading: Ripple Report Foresees Blockchain Saving Financial Institutions $10 Billion By 2030 It&#8217;s $XRP which is getting into the area of interests. Just be able to buy the dip. pic.twitter.com/mBc71YtC2j — Michaël van de Poppe (@CryptoMichNL) August 7, 2023 Based on his analysis, the current position of XRP may soon pave the way for a favorable long-trade entry, aligning with the upcoming market cycle. Further expanding on this, he advised traders to remain vigilant and consider buying the dip in the impending weeks. This comes at a time when XRP&#8217;s price has seen a decline of over 10% in the past two weeks, a movement influenced heavily by developments with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). As recent data shows, the altcoin experienced a decrease of 10.8% over the previous seven days, positioning its trading value above $0.6. Understanding The Factors Behind The Dip So, what prompted this dip in XRP&#8217;s value? Van de Poppe&#8217;s analysis provides a perspective. He emphasizes that the significant price fall XRP experienced over the last month is majorly attributed to long-term holders. These holders, witnessing the surge or &#8220;heavy impulse&#8221; in XRP&#8217;s price, saw it as an opportune moment to offload their holdings. Additionally, another notable observation from van de Poppe is the current &#8220;lack of interest&#8221; in the cryptocurrency markets. This diminished interest, according to the analyst, is responsible for more pronounced price corrections compared to what&#8217;s usually seen during bull market cycles. Such market sentiment can significantly influence how cryptocurrencies, including XRP, perform and are perceived by potential investors. Related Reading: XRP Journey To $10: Unveiling The Forces That Could Trigger An Upward Momentum Over the past 24 hours, XRP has seen a slight dip of 0.5%. This price action has brought the altcoin to currently trade at a price of $0.61, at the time of writing. Notably, alongside its value, the asset&#8217;s market capitalization has also seen a significant plunge dropping by more than $4 billion, in the past week. XRP&#8217;s market cap is currently valued at $32.5 billion as of today, losing almost $4 billion compared to the value of $36.3 billion seen last Tuesday. Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the leading names in the crypto analysis sector, Michael van de Poppe, recently shed light on XRP&#8217;s price movements. Known for his crypto observations, his latest <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1688603409870475264?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">tweet</a> has stirred conversations in the crypto community, especially pertaining to Ripple’s native cryptocurrency, XRP.</p>
<p>In his most recent analysis, van de Poppe indicated that XRP&#8217;s price movement is now at a critical juncture. </p>
<h2>XRP Entering The &#8216;Area Of Interest&#8217;</h2>
<p>Particularly, according to Michael van de Poppe&#8217;s tweet, XRP is currently moving into what he terms an &#8216;area of interest&#8217; on its weekly chart. This essentially points towards potential pivotal moments in the coin&#8217;s price trajectory that can be significant for traders.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/ripple-2/ripple-report-foresees-blockchain-saving-financial-institutions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ripple Report Foresees Blockchain Saving Financial Institutions $10 Billion By 2030</a></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">It&#8217;s <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24XRP&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$XRP</a> which is getting into the area of interests.</p>
<p>Just be able to buy the dip. <a href="https://t.co/mBc71YtC2j" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/mBc71YtC2j</a></p>
<p>— Michaël van de Poppe (@CryptoMichNL) <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1688603409870475264?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 7, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Based on his analysis, the current position of XRP may soon <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/ripple-2/ripple-report-foresees-blockchain-saving-financial-institutions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">pave the way</a> for a favorable long-trade entry, aligning with the upcoming market cycle. Further expanding on this, he advised traders to remain vigilant and consider buying the dip in the impending weeks.</p>
<p>This comes at a time when XRP&#8217;s price has seen a decline of over 10% in the past two weeks, a movement influenced heavily by <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/press-releases/ripple-xrp-sec-case-update-is-this-a-bullish-signal-for-xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">developments with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)</a>. As recent data shows, the altcoin experienced a decrease of 10.8% over the previous seven days, positioning its trading value above $0.6.</p>
<h2>Understanding The Factors Behind The Dip</h2>
<p>So, what prompted this dip in <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/all/xrp-journey-to-10-unveiling-the-forces-that-could-trigger-an-upward-momentum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">XRP&#8217;s value</a>? Van de Poppe&#8217;s analysis provides a perspective. He emphasizes that the significant price fall XRP experienced over the last month is majorly attributed to long-term holders. These holders, witnessing the surge or &#8220;heavy impulse&#8221; in XRP&#8217;s price, saw it as an opportune moment to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-whales-trigger-price-decline/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">offload their holdings</a>.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="css-9pa8cd" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/F276FETWYAAZSqE?format=webp&amp;name=medium" alt="XRP analysis by Michaël van de Poppe" width="1200" height="573"/>
<p>Additionally, another notable observation from van de Poppe is the current &#8220;lack of interest&#8221; in the cryptocurrency markets. This diminished interest, according to the analyst, is responsible for more pronounced price corrections compared to what&#8217;s usually seen during bull market cycles. </p>
<p>Such market sentiment can significantly influence how cryptocurrencies, including XRP, perform and are perceived by potential investors.</p>

<p>Over the past 24 hours, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/all/xrp-performance-woes-how-might-its-price-respond-to-current-market-realities/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">XRP</a> has seen a slight dip of 0.5%. This price action has brought the altcoin to currently trade at a price of $0.61, at the time of writing. Notably, alongside its value, the asset&#8217;s market capitalization has also seen a significant plunge dropping by more than $4 billion, in the past week.</p>
<p>XRP&#8217;s market cap is currently valued at $32.5 billion as of today, losing almost $4 billion compared to the value of $36.3 billion seen last Tuesday.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Rwi9OD9S/" alt="XRP price chart on TradingView.com" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<p>Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/XRP-2.jpeg?fit=460%2C329" width="460" height="329" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546187</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Valkyrie Unveils Double-Barreled Approach To Launch An Ethereum ETF Alongside A Bitcoin ETF</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/valkyrie-ethereum-bitcoin-etf/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 11:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[valkyrie]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546186</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Valkyrie has applied to the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to add ETH futures contracts to its Valkyrie Bitcoin Strategy ETF (BTF).  Valkyrie Makes A Move To Stay Ahead Of The Crowd Valkyrie’s application represents a move to stay ahead of the crowd. While many have applied to launch their respective Ethereum (ETH) Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs), Valkyrie has simply moved to include exposure to ETH futures contracts in their existing investment strategy.  Related Reading: Crypto Adoption: Singapore Red Cross To Accept BTC, ETH, USDT, And USDC While the likelihood of the SEC’s approving these Ethereum ETFs or in what order remains uncertain, Valkyrie plans to introduce its double-barreled approach on or around October 3, putting its launch date ahead of that of other competitors.  Part of the filing reads: In addition, on or about October 3, 2023, the Fund’s name is expected to change to Valkyrie Bitcoin and Ether Strategy ETF. The Fund is expected to continue to trade on The Nasdaq Stock Market LLC under the ticker symbol “BTF”. The foregoing changes will only take effect and are conditioned upon the effectiveness of the Trust’s Post-Effective Amendment No. 23 under the Securities Act of 1933, including any amendments thereto, which has been filed with the Securities and Exchange Commission on August 4, 2023 and contains further information about the changes to the Fund’s name and investment strategy. Going by SEC Rule 485(a), those who applied for the Ether ETFs can launch 75 days from their respective filing dates if none of the applications before the SEC gets denied. In tandem with the 75 days, the earliest any of these fund managers (the first being Volatility Shares, who applied on July 28) can launch is October 12 (9 days after Valkyrie’s proposed launch if their application gets greenlit by the SEC). ETH retains $1,800 level &#124; Source: ETHUSD on Tradingview.com This first-mover advantage can be critical when looking back at history. Although Valkyrie launched its Bitcoin fund in October 2021, it wasn’t the first to do so, as ProShares had already launched its Bitcoin Strategy ETF (BITO).  Many believe that BITO launching first is one of the reasons it has enjoyed more success compared to Valkyrie’s Bitcoin Strategy ETF (BTF). BITO now has over $1 billion in assets under management (AuM) compared to BTF’s AuM of about $30 million. Deja Vu? As Bloomberg Senior ETF Analyst Eric Balchunas noted in a tweet, this isn’t the first time someone is moving to amend an existing fund to launch the first such product in the industry.  Related Reading: Ripple Is Now A Member Of Trade Organization That Hosts The Likes Of BlackRock ETF Managers Group has previously moved to convert a Latin American real estate ETF to the ETFMG Alternative Harvest ETF (MJ), so it could be first in line to launch marijuana ETFs in the US &#8211; something which has been compared to what Valkyrie is trying to do. Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Valkyrie has <a href="https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1877493/000138713123009336/valkyrie-497_080423.htm" rel="nofollow">applied</a> to the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to add ETH futures contracts to its Valkyrie Bitcoin Strategy ETF (BTF). </p>
<h2>Valkyrie Makes A Move To Stay Ahead Of The Crowd</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/valkyrie-follows-in-blackrocks-footsteps-refiles-for-spot-bitcoin-etf/">Valkyrie’s application</a> represents a move to stay ahead of the crowd. While many have <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-etf-race-gets-hotter/">applied</a> to launch their respective Ethereum (ETH) Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs), Valkyrie has simply moved to include exposure to ETH futures contracts in their existing investment strategy. </p>

<p>While the likelihood of the SEC’s approving these Ethereum ETFs or in what order remains uncertain, Valkyrie plans to introduce its double-barreled approach on or around October 3, putting its launch date ahead of that of other competitors. </p>
<p>Part of the filing reads:</p>
<blockquote><p>In addition, on or about October 3, 2023, the Fund’s name is expected to change to Valkyrie Bitcoin and Ether Strategy ETF. The Fund is expected to continue to trade on The Nasdaq Stock Market LLC under the ticker symbol “BTF”. The foregoing changes will only take effect and are conditioned upon the effectiveness of the Trust’s Post-Effective Amendment No. 23 under the Securities Act of 1933, including any amendments thereto, which has been filed with the Securities and Exchange Commission on August 4, 2023 and contains further information about the changes to the Fund’s name and investment strategy.</p></blockquote>
<p>Going by SEC Rule 485(a), those who applied for the Ether ETFs can launch 75 days from their respective filing dates if none of the applications before the SEC gets denied. In tandem with the 75 days, the earliest any of these fund managers (the first being Volatility Shares, who applied on July 28) can launch is October 12 (9 days after Valkyrie’s proposed launch if their application gets greenlit by the SEC).</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/JaxdyyYU/" alt="Ethereum (ETH) price chart from Tradingview.com (Valkyrie Bitcoin ETF)" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<p>This first-mover advantage can be critical when looking back at history. Although Valkyrie launched its <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/when-blackrock-bitcoin-etf-timeline-implications/">Bitcoin fund</a> in October 2021, it wasn’t the first to do so, as ProShares had already launched its Bitcoin Strategy ETF (BITO). </p>
<p>Many believe that BITO launching first is one of the reasons it has enjoyed more success compared to Valkyrie’s Bitcoin Strategy ETF (BTF). BITO now has over $1 billion in assets under management (AuM) compared to BTF’s AuM of about $30 million.</p>
<h2>Deja Vu?</h2>
<p>As Bloomberg Senior ETF Analyst Eric Balchunas noted in a <a href="https://twitter.com/EricBalchunas/status/1687566431502716928?s=20" rel="nofollow">tweet</a>, this isn’t the first time someone is moving to amend an existing fund to launch the first such product in the industry. </p>

<p>ETF Managers Group has previously moved to convert a Latin American real estate ETF to the ETFMG Alternative Harvest ETF (MJ), so it could be first in line to launch marijuana ETFs in the US &#8211; something which has been compared to what <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/valkyrie-follows-in-blackrocks-footsteps-refiles-for-spot-bitcoin-etf/">Valkyrie</a> is trying to do.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-912157946.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546186</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>PayPal’s PYUSD Launch Triggers Calls For Stablecoin Bill</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/stablecoin/paypal-pyusd-launch-triggers-calls-for-stablecoin-bill/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PYUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin bill]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546185</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[United States Republican Patrick T. McHenry, Chair of the House Financial Services Committee, has released a statement calling for the need to pass the Stablecoin Bill in the wake of PayPal’s launch of its own stablecoin PYUSD.  The Call For A Stablecoin Law According to the statement, McHenry believes stablecoins are the “pillar of our 21st-century payments system.” However, they must be regulated to reach their full potential.  Related Reading: TRON’s Justin Sun Reassures Crypto Community That Huobi Exchange Is Solvent  Part of the statement read: This announcement [Paypal’s PYUSD Launch] is a clear signal that stablecoins—if issued under a clear regulatory framework—hold promise as a pillar of our 21st century payments system,” said Chairman McHenry. “Clear regulations and robust consumer protections are essential to enabling stablecoins to achieve their full potential. That’s why it’s more important than ever that Congress enact legislation to provide comprehensive digital asset regulation, especially for stablecoins.&#8221; McHenry also recognizes the role of Congress in providing regulatory certainty to the crypto industry and the need to enact these laws that can keep the US at the “forefront of digital innovation.&#8221; The bipartisan Clarity for Payment Stablecoins Act recognizes the strong role that states have played in regulating digital asset firms and builds on successful state regimes, like New York’s. We are currently at a crossroads to keep America at the forefront of digital asset innovation. Congress is making significant, bipartisan progress on legislation to ensure the U.S. leads the financial system of the future. We must finish the job. The bipartisan Clarity for Payment Stablecoins Act, which was advanced by the House Financial Services Committee last month, is a legislative framework that seeks to regulate payment stablecoins. Many will be hoping that this bill could spearhead the passing of other crypto-related bills.  PayPal Continues Journey Into Web3 On August 7, payment platform PayPal announced the launch of its dollar-backed stablecoin, PayPal (PYUSD), in collaboration with Paxos (Paxos also happens to be the issuer of Binance’s BUSD). This is part of Paypal’s efforts to increase its Web3 offerings as the company believes that fully-backed, regulated stablecoins can transform payments in the Web3 space. Related Reading: Ethereum Whale $4.5 Million Burn Shocks ETH Community, What’s Going On? &#8220;The shift toward digital currencies requires a stable instrument that is both digitally native and easily connected to fiat currency like the U.S. dollar,&#8221; said Paypal’s President and CEO Dan Schulman. &#8220;Our commitment to responsible innovation and compliance, and our track record delivering new experiences to our customers, provides the foundation necessary to contribute to the growth of digital payments through PayPal USD.&#8221; This isn’t Paypal’s first attempt at launching a stablecoin. In 2021, the company explored the possibility of launching a stablecoin but faced a setback following heightened regulatory scrutiny from the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).  Total market cap sitting at $1.125 trillion &#124; Source: Crypto Total Market Cap on Tradingview.com Featured image from History Computer, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>United States Republican Patrick T. McHenry, Chair of the House Financial Services Committee, has released a <a href="https://financialservices.house.gov/news/documentsingle.aspx?DocumentID=408945" rel="nofollow">statement</a> calling for the need to pass the Stablecoin Bill in the wake of PayPal’s launch of its own stablecoin PYUSD. </p>
<h2>The Call For A Stablecoin Law</h2>
<p>According to the statement, McHenry believes stablecoins are the “pillar of our 21st-century payments system.” However, they must be regulated to reach their full potential. </p>



<p> Part of the statement read:</p>
<blockquote><p>This announcement [Paypal’s PYUSD Launch] is a clear signal that stablecoins—if issued under a clear regulatory framework—hold promise as a pillar of our 21st century payments system,” said Chairman McHenry. “Clear regulations and robust consumer protections are essential to enabling stablecoins to achieve their full potential. That’s why it’s more important than ever that Congress enact legislation to provide comprehensive digital asset regulation, especially for stablecoins.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>McHenry also recognizes the role of Congress in providing regulatory certainty to the crypto industry and the need to enact these laws that can keep the US at the “forefront of digital innovation.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote><p>The bipartisan Clarity for Payment Stablecoins Act recognizes the strong role that states have played in regulating digital asset firms and builds on successful state regimes, like New York’s. We are currently at a crossroads to keep America at the forefront of digital asset innovation. Congress is making significant, bipartisan progress on legislation to ensure the U.S. leads the financial system of the future. We must finish the job.</p></blockquote>
<p>The bipartisan Clarity for Payment Stablecoins Act, which was advanced by the House Financial Services Committee last month, is a legislative framework that seeks to regulate payment stablecoins. Many will be hoping that this bill could spearhead the passing of other crypto-related bills. </p>
<h2>PayPal Continues Journey Into Web3</h2>
<p>On August 7, payment platform PayPal <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/breaking-paypal-unveils-dollar-backed-stablecoin/" rel="nofollow">announced</a> the launch of its dollar-backed stablecoin, PayPal (PYUSD), in collaboration with Paxos (Paxos also happens to be the issuer of Binance’s BUSD). This is part of Paypal’s efforts to increase its Web3 offerings as the company believes that fully-backed, regulated stablecoins can transform payments in the Web3 space.</p>



<p>&#8220;The shift toward digital currencies requires a stable instrument that is both digitally native and easily connected to fiat currency like the U.S. dollar,&#8221; said Paypal’s President and CEO Dan Schulman. &#8220;Our commitment to responsible innovation and compliance, and our track record delivering new experiences to our customers, provides the foundation necessary to contribute to the growth of digital payments through PayPal USD.&#8221;</p>
<p>This isn’t Paypal’s first attempt at launching a stablecoin. In 2021, the company explored the possibility of launching a stablecoin but faced a setback following heightened regulatory scrutiny from the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/9d75DGUi/" alt="Crypto Total Market Cap chart from Tradingview.com (PayPal PYUSD stablecoin)" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/PayPal-PYUSD-Stablecoin.jpeg?fit=460%2C306" width="460" height="306" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546185</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Price Prediction: 28% Upswing Or 23% Drop Coming Next?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-ada-price-prediction-28-upswing-23-drop/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 09:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[adausd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano whales]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546171</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) is currently trading at a pivotal $0.291. The question is: Will ADA experience a 28% upswing or is a 23% drop on the horizon? Remarkably, the ADA price still remains in bearish territory, but the potential for a trend reversal is palpable. Price Analysis: 4-Hour Chart The 4-hour chart paints a picture of ADA trading just a smidge above the 23.6% Fibonacci retracement level, which stands at $0.286. Notably, on Monday, ADA briefly dipped below this level but was buoyed by the ascending trend line (black line) that was established in mid-June. This trend line is the bulls&#8217; last stand; a breach could see a bearish descent to the year&#8217;s low of $0.22. Adding another layer of complexity, the 200-EMA (blue line) on the 4-hour chart is converging towards the 23.6% Fibonacci level. ADA&#8217;s recent inability to surpass the 20-EMA (red line) is concerning. With the moving averages trending downward, a compression between $0.28 and $0.30 seems inevitable. However, if ADA remains resilient above the 23.6% Fibonacci retracement level and the trendline, and manages to break the moving averages, especially the 200-EMA, then the bulls might just have a fighting chance. Related Reading: Can The Cardano Mithril Protocol Propel ADA To $1 This Year? In this scenario, the 38.2% Fibonacci at $0.319, the 50% Fibonacci at $0.346, and the 61.8% Fibonacci at $0.378 become the next logical targets. A daily close above $0.38 (July&#8217;s high) would be a clarion call for the bulls, marking a 28% rallye from the recent price. Bullish Arguments for Cardano The recent price movements by Cardano might be bearish, but there are compelling arguments in favor of ADA&#8217;s potential resurgence. Santiment, a renowned analytics platform, recently tweeted: As Cardano sits just above $0.29, whales and sharks holding between 100K-10M ADA have accumulated back to their highest level since September, 2022. Additionally, on-chain transaction volume has been rising nearly every week for the past 6 months. Related Reading: Cardano (ADA) Price Remains Muted Despite Significant Milestones, Why? This statement is supported by data indicating ADA&#8217;s transaction volume surged above a staggering 67 billion ADA in consecutive weeks, a peak not seen since September 2021. Such heightened network activity is often interpreted as a bullish sign, indicative of increased user engagement and interest. Furthermore, ADA wallets holding between 100K-10M ADA now account for a significant 34.04% of all circulating tokens, suggesting strong confidence among larger investors. Also, Messari&#8217;s recent report on Cardano offers more reasons for optimism. The report delves deep into Cardano&#8217;s ecosystem, financial trends, and network performance. One of the standout revelations is the surge in decentralized app (dapp) activities. For the third consecutive quarter, Cardano has seen a remarkable uptick in dapp transactions, boasting a 49.0% quarter-over-quarter increase in Q2, averaging 57,900 daily transactions. State of @Cardano Q2 2023 With a dedicated community of users and developers, Cardano has demonstrated staying power. In Q2, average daily dapp transactions were up 49%, TVL up 10%, and 199% YTD.@redvelvetzip dives in. https://t.co/MNhyNJvIPq — Messari (@MessariCrypto) August 4, 2023 Featured image from Coinbase, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cardano (ADA) is currently trading at a pivotal $0.291. The question is: Will ADA experience a 28% upswing or is a 23% drop on the horizon? Remarkably, the ADA price still remains in bearish territory, but the potential for a trend reversal is palpable.</p>
<h2>Price Analysis: 4-Hour Chart</h2>
<p>The 4-hour chart paints a picture of ADA trading just a smidge above the 23.6% Fibonacci retracement level, which stands at $0.286. Notably, on Monday, ADA briefly dipped below this level but was buoyed by the ascending trend line (black line) that was established in mid-June. This trend line is the bulls&#8217; last stand; a breach could see a bearish descent to the year&#8217;s low of $0.22.</p>
<p>Adding another layer of complexity, the 200-EMA (blue line) on the 4-hour chart is converging towards the 23.6% Fibonacci level. ADA&#8217;s recent inability to surpass the 20-EMA (red line) is concerning. With the moving averages trending downward, a compression between $0.28 and $0.30 seems inevitable.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-546179 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/ADAUSD_2023-08-08_10-15-03.png?resize=3628%2C1673" alt="Cardano ADA price" width="3628" height="1673" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/ADAUSD_2023-08-08_10-15-03.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=3628 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/ADAUSD_2023-08-08_10-15-03.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/ADAUSD_2023-08-08_10-15-03.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/ADAUSD_2023-08-08_10-15-03.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/ADAUSD_2023-08-08_10-15-03.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/ADAUSD_2023-08-08_10-15-03.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/ADAUSD_2023-08-08_10-15-03.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/ADAUSD_2023-08-08_10-15-03.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=1140 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/ADAUSD_2023-08-08_10-15-03.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=3000 3000w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>However, if ADA remains resilient above the 23.6% Fibonacci retracement level and the trendline, and manages to break the moving averages, especially the 200-EMA, then the bulls might just have a fighting chance.</p>

<p>In this scenario, the 38.2% Fibonacci at $0.319, the 50% Fibonacci at $0.346, and the 61.8% Fibonacci at $0.378 become the next logical targets. A daily close above $0.38 (July&#8217;s high) would be a clarion call for the bulls, marking a 28% rallye from the recent price.</p>
<h2>Bullish Arguments for Cardano</h2>
<p>The recent price movements by Cardano might be bearish, but there are compelling arguments in favor of ADA&#8217;s potential resurgence. Santiment, a renowned analytics platform, recently <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1688789040815075328" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">tweeted</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>As Cardano sits just above $0.29, whales and sharks holding between 100K-10M ADA have accumulated back to their highest level since September, 2022. Additionally, on-chain transaction volume has been rising nearly every week for the past 6 months.</strong></p></blockquote>

<p>This statement is supported by data indicating ADA&#8217;s transaction volume surged above a staggering 67 billion ADA in consecutive weeks, a peak not seen since September 2021. Such heightened network activity is often interpreted as a bullish sign, indicative of increased user engagement and interest.</p>
<p>Furthermore, ADA wallets holding between 100K-10M ADA now account for a significant 34.04% of all circulating tokens, suggesting strong confidence among larger investors.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-546180 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F2_G43ibMAEHkjK.jpg?resize=2778%2C1800" alt="Cardano is seeing accumulation by large investors" width="2778" height="1800" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F2_G43ibMAEHkjK.jpg?resize=2778%2C1800?w=2778 2778w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F2_G43ibMAEHkjK.jpg?resize=2778%2C1800?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F2_G43ibMAEHkjK.jpg?resize=2778%2C1800?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F2_G43ibMAEHkjK.jpg?resize=2778%2C1800?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F2_G43ibMAEHkjK.jpg?resize=2778%2C1800?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F2_G43ibMAEHkjK.jpg?resize=2778%2C1800?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F2_G43ibMAEHkjK.jpg?resize=2778%2C1800?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F2_G43ibMAEHkjK.jpg?resize=2778%2C1800?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>Also, Messari&#8217;s recent report on Cardano offers more reasons for optimism. The report delves deep into Cardano&#8217;s ecosystem, financial trends, and network performance. One of the standout revelations is the surge in decentralized app (dapp) activities. For the third consecutive quarter, Cardano has seen a remarkable uptick in dapp transactions, boasting a 49.0% quarter-over-quarter increase in Q2, averaging 57,900 daily transactions.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">State of <a href="https://twitter.com/Cardano?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@Cardano</a> Q2 2023</p>
<p>With a dedicated community of users and developers, Cardano has demonstrated staying power.</p>
<p>In Q2, average daily dapp transactions were up 49%, TVL up 10%, and 199% YTD.<a href="https://twitter.com/redvelvetzip?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@redvelvetzip</a> dives in. <a href="https://t.co/MNhyNJvIPq" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/MNhyNJvIPq</a></p>
<p>— Messari (@MessariCrypto) <a href="https://twitter.com/MessariCrypto/status/1687475880757489664?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 4, 2023</a></p></blockquote>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Cardano.png?fit=460%2C264" width="460" height="264" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546171</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Can Litecoin Bulls Turn The Tide On Recent Declines? A Closer Look</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/all/can-litecoin-bulls-turn-the-tide-on-declines/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 08:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[halving event]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546154</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Litecoin (LTC) has recently faced a period of bearish pressure that has taken a toll on its market performance. The months of July and August have witnessed a shift in sentiment, as bearish forces began to dominate the crypto market.  As of the latest update, LTC finds itself trading within a critical support zone, prompting discussions among traders and analysts about its potential trajectory. With the value of LTC hovering just below the $80 mark, market observers are closely monitoring whether this level will hold against the prevailing bearish sentiment. Related Reading: PEPE’s Future: Will Prices Of Meme Coins Continue To Drop? Litecoin Vital Support Zone Tested A recent price analysis has underscored the significance of the $80 threshold, suggesting that a breach below this point could potentially trigger an extended downtrend for Litecoin. The current market figures reflect a small 24-hour uptick of 0.2% and a seven-day decline of 8.5% with a current price of $82.57 on CoinGecko, painting a cautious picture for LTC&#8217;s short-term performance. The fluctuations in price during this period have sparked discussions about the factors contributing to Litecoin&#8217;s recent struggles. Source: Coingecko Halving Event And Its Impact The crypto community is no stranger to the phenomenon of halving, an event embedded in the genes of cryptocurrencies like Litecoin. In 2019, Litecoin underwent its second halving, a pre-programmed event that occurs approximately every four years. This event, characterized by a reduction in block rewards issued to miners, has historically carried significant implications for price trends. LTC weekly price movement. Source: CoinMarketCap Related Reading: XRP Journey To $10: Unveiling The Forces That Could Trigger An Upward Momentum The halving event in 2019 witnessed a fascinating sequence of events. In the lead-up to the halving, Litecoin&#8217;s price experienced a rally, generating excitement among investors. However, the post-halving scenario took an unexpected turn as an extended downtrend followed, lasting for over 500 days. This downtrend was succeeded by a period of consolidation, marking the complexity of crypto market dynamics and the interplay between halving events and price trends. Litecoin market cap currently at $6 billion. Chart: TradingView.com LTC&#8217;s Third Halving Event And Network Fundamentals Fast-forward to August 2, 2023, and Litecoin&#8217;s blockchain has just experienced its third halving event. Occurring at block 2,520,000, this event has effectively slashed mining rewards to 6.25 LTC per block. Despite the prevailing lull in price action, Litecoin&#8217;s network fundamentals remain robust.  Litecoin&#8217;s Hashrate is currently at getting close to hitting a new all time high. Currently at 933.2 TH/s, with difficultly just touching on a new ATH. $LTC is stronger than ever! Despite what you may read in the &#8216;press&#8217;. pic.twitter.com/0hEgED09kd — Litecoin (@litecoin) August 6, 2023 Meanwhile, Litecoin&#8217;s hashrate is poised to achieve an all-time high, exemplifying the network&#8217;s resilience and ongoing miner participation. Presently boasting a difficulty level of 933.2 TH/s, Litecoin inches closer to establishing a new record, highlighting its secure and decentralized network infrastructure.  The strengthening hashrate and its associated positive network indicators underline Litecoin&#8217;s capacity to withstand market fluctuations and continue to evolve in the face of external pressures. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from The Currency Analytics]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin (LTC) has recently faced a period of bearish pressure that has taken a toll on its market performance. The months of July and August have witnessed a shift in sentiment, as bearish forces began to dominate the crypto market. </p>
<p>As of the latest update, LTC finds itself trading within a critical support zone, prompting discussions among traders and analysts about its potential trajectory.</p>
<p>With the value of LTC hovering just below the $80 mark, market observers are closely monitoring whether this level will hold against the prevailing bearish sentiment.</p>

<h2><strong>Litecoin Vital Support Zone Tested</strong></h2>
<p>A recent <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/litecoin-bulls-have-a-shot-at-reversing-recent-losses-heres-how/" rel="nofollow">price analysis</a> has underscored the significance of the $80 threshold, suggesting that a breach below this point could potentially trigger an extended downtrend for Litecoin.</p>
<p>The current market figures reflect a small 24-hour uptick of 0.2% and a seven-day decline of 8.5% with a current price of $82.57 on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/litecoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a>, painting a cautious picture for LTC&#8217;s short-term performance. </p>
<p>The fluctuations in price during this period have sparked discussions about the factors contributing to Litecoin&#8217;s recent struggles.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-546160" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-30.png?resize=1024%2C55" alt="" width="1024" height="55" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-30.png?resize=1024%2C55?w=1139 1139w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-30.png?resize=1024%2C55?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-30.png?resize=1024%2C55?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-30.png?resize=1024%2C55?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-30.png?resize=1024%2C55?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<h2><strong>Halving Event And Its Impact</strong></h2>
<p>The crypto community is no stranger to the phenomenon of halving, an event embedded in the genes of cryptocurrencies like Litecoin. In 2019, Litecoin underwent its second halving, a pre-programmed event that occurs approximately every four years. </p>
<p>This event, characterized by a reduction in block rewards issued to miners, has historically carried significant implications for price trends.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-546166 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-32.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C378" alt="" width="860" height="378" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-32.png?w=1033 1033w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-32.png?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-32.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-32.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C378 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-32.png?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>


<p>The halving event in 2019 witnessed a fascinating sequence of events. In the lead-up to the halving, Litecoin&#8217;s price experienced a rally, generating excitement among investors. However, the post-halving scenario took an unexpected turn as an extended downtrend followed, lasting for over 500 days. </p>
<p>This downtrend was succeeded by a period of consolidation, marking the complexity of crypto market dynamics and the interplay between halving events and price trends.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/4CBkYyij/" width="2475" height="1179"/></p>

<strong>LTC&#8217;s Third Halving Event And Network Fundamentals</strong>
<p>Fast-forward to August 2, 2023, and Litecoin&#8217;s blockchain has just experienced its third halving event. Occurring at block 2,520,000, this event has effectively slashed mining rewards to 6.25 LTC per block. Despite the prevailing lull in price action, Litecoin&#8217;s network fundamentals remain robust. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Litecoin&#8217;s Hashrate is currently at getting close to hitting a new all time high. Currently at 933.2 TH/s, with difficultly just touching on a new ATH. <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24LTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$LTC</a> is stronger than ever!</p>
<p>Despite what you may read in the &#8216;press&#8217;. <a href="https://t.co/0hEgED09kd" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/0hEgED09kd</a></p>
<p>— Litecoin (@litecoin) <a href="https://twitter.com/litecoin/status/1688207330188693504?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 6, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Meanwhile, <a href="https://twitter.com/litecoin/status/1688207330188693504" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Litecoin&#8217;s hashrate</a> is poised to achieve an all-time high, exemplifying the network&#8217;s resilience and ongoing miner participation. </p>
<p>Presently boasting a difficulty level of 933.2 TH/s, Litecoin inches closer to establishing a new record, highlighting its secure and decentralized network infrastructure. </p>
<p>The strengthening hashrate and its associated positive network indicators underline Litecoin&#8217;s capacity to withstand market fluctuations and continue to evolve in the face of external pressures.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from The Currency Analytics</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-31.png?fit=460%2C271" width="460" height="271" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546154</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Bitcoin Mispriced? Lessons From Past Volatility Slumps</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/is-bitcoin-mispriced-lessons-past-volatility-slumps/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin on-chain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[glassnode]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546148</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Since its inception, Bitcoin has (almost) always been the poster child for volatility. Yet, the Bitcoin price is hardly moving in any direction at the moment. But the latest data suggests a surprising twist in the tale. As per a recent report by on-chain data provider Glassnode, &#8220;Bitcoin markets are experiencing an incredibly quiet patch, with several measures of volatility collapsing towards all-time lows.&#8221; This raises the question: Are we entering a new era of Bitcoin price stability, or is the market misreading the signs? Historical Context For The Volatility Of Bitcoin To truly understand the current state of the market, it&#8217;s essential to delve into the historical context. The Glassnode report notes, &#8220;It has been 842-days since the bull market peak was set in April 2021.&#8221; During this period, Bitcoin&#8217;s recovery has been more robust than in previous cycles, trading at -54% below its all-time high (ATH), compared to a historical average of -64%. Related Reading: Bitcoin Fate Hangs In The Balance, 50% Chance Of Falling Below $25,000 In September Drawing parallels with past cycles, the report highlights that both the 2015-16 and 2019-20 cycles underwent a &#8220;6-month period of sideways boredom before the market accelerated above the -54% drawdown level.&#8221; This could be indicative of a similar &#8220;boredom&#8221; phase in the current cycle. One of the most striking revelations from the Glassnode report is the extreme volatility compression Bitcoin is currently undergoing. &#8220;Bitcoin realized volatility ranging from 1-month to 1-year observation windows has fallen dramatically in 2023, reaching multi-year lows.&#8221; This is reminiscent of four distinct periods in Bitcoin&#8217;s history, including the late stage of the 2015 bear market and the post-March 2020 consolidation following the outbreak of COVID-19. Following the furious rally at the beginning to 2023, the price performance on both a quarterly and monthly basis has moderated. This mirrors Bitcoin’s previous cycles where the initial surge from the low is robust, but then transitions into a prolonged phase of uneven consolidation, a phase of re-accumulation. Furthermore, the report states, &#8220;The price range which separates the 7-day high and low is just 3.6%. Just 4.8% of all trading days have ever experienced a tighter weekly trade range.&#8221; The 30-day price range is even more extreme, constricting price to just a 9.8%, and with only 2.8% of all months in BTC&#8217;s history being tighter. Such levels of price compression are rare for Bitcoin, suggesting an anomaly or a potential precursor to a significant market move. Derivatives Market Insights The derivatives market, often seen as a barometer for underlying asset sentiment, is also echoing this quiet spell. &#8220;The combined Futures and Options trade volume for [BTC and ETH] are at, or approaching all-time-lows,&#8221; the report notes. This is further emphasized by the fact that &#8220;BTC is currently seeing $19.0B in aggregate derivatives trade volume, whilst ETH markets have just $9.2B/day.&#8221; Related Reading: Why Low Volatility Bitcoin Could Last A Lot Longer Interestingly, the options market is showing signs of a significant &#8220;volatility crush.&#8221; As per Glassnode, &#8220;Options are pricing in the smallest volatility premium in history, with IV between 24% and 52%, less than half of the long-term baseline.&#8221; This is further corroborated by the historically low Put/Call Ratio and the 25-delta skew metric, suggesting a net bullish sentiment in the market. The crux of the matter lies in interpreting these signs. The report aptly questions, &#8220;Given the context of Bitcoin&#8217;s infamous volatility, is a new era of BTC price stability upon us, or is volatility mispriced?&#8221; Historically, periods of low volatility in Bitcoin have often been followed by significant price movements. Whether this is a calm before a storm or a genuine shift towards a more stable Bitcoin remains to be seen. But as Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221;, the chief chart technician at NewsBTC, has pointed out yesterday, the technical indicators are also pointing to a prolonged period of re-accumulation, meaning that the phase of low volatility is likely to continue for some time to come. At press time, the BTC price was at $29,277. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Since its inception, Bitcoin has (almost) always been the poster child for volatility. Yet, the Bitcoin price is hardly moving in any direction at the moment. But the latest data suggests a surprising twist in the tale.</p>
<p>As per a recent <a href="https://insights.glassnode.com/the-week-onchain-week-32-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a> by on-chain data provider Glassnode, &#8220;Bitcoin markets are experiencing an incredibly quiet patch, with several measures of volatility collapsing towards all-time lows.&#8221; This raises the question: Are we entering a new era of Bitcoin price stability, or is the market misreading the signs?</p>
<h2>Historical Context For The Volatility Of Bitcoin</h2>
<p>To truly understand the current state of the market, it&#8217;s essential to delve into the historical context. The Glassnode report notes, &#8220;It has been 842-days since the bull market peak was set in April 2021.&#8221; During this period, Bitcoin&#8217;s recovery has been more robust than in previous cycles, trading at -54% below its all-time high (ATH), compared to a historical average of -64%.</p>

<p>Drawing parallels with past cycles, the report highlights that both the 2015-16 and 2019-20 cycles underwent a &#8220;6-month period of sideways boredom before the market accelerated above the -54% drawdown level.&#8221; This could be indicative of a similar &#8220;boredom&#8221; phase in the current cycle.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-546158 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/03_cycleath.png?resize=2400%2C1382" alt="Bitcoin cycles" width="2400" height="1382" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/03_cycleath.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=2400 2400w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/03_cycleath.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/03_cycleath.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/03_cycleath.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/03_cycleath.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/03_cycleath.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/03_cycleath.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/03_cycleath.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>One of the most striking revelations from the Glassnode report is the extreme volatility compression Bitcoin is currently undergoing. &#8220;Bitcoin realized volatility ranging from 1-month to 1-year observation windows has fallen dramatically in 2023, reaching multi-year lows.&#8221; This is reminiscent of four distinct periods in Bitcoin&#8217;s history, including the late stage of the 2015 bear market and the post-March 2020 consolidation following the outbreak of COVID-19.</p>
<p>Following the furious rally at the beginning to 2023, the price performance on both a quarterly and monthly basis has moderated. This mirrors Bitcoin’s previous cycles where the initial surge from the low is robust, but then transitions into a prolonged phase of uneven consolidation, a phase of re-accumulation.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-546157 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/04_quarterlyperformance.png?resize=2400%2C1382" alt="Bitcoin price performance" width="2400" height="1382" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/04_quarterlyperformance.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=2400 2400w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/04_quarterlyperformance.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/04_quarterlyperformance.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/04_quarterlyperformance.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/04_quarterlyperformance.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/04_quarterlyperformance.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/04_quarterlyperformance.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/04_quarterlyperformance.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>Furthermore, the report states, &#8220;The price range which separates the 7-day high and low is just 3.6%. Just 4.8% of all trading days have ever experienced a tighter weekly trade range.&#8221; The 30-day price range is even more extreme, constricting price to just a 9.8%, and with only 2.8% of all months in BTC&#8217;s history being tighter. Such levels of price compression are rare for Bitcoin, suggesting an anomaly or a potential precursor to a significant market move.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-546156 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/07_30dayrange.png?resize=2400%2C1382" alt="Bitcoin 30-day range" width="2400" height="1382" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/07_30dayrange.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=2400 2400w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/07_30dayrange.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/07_30dayrange.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/07_30dayrange.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/07_30dayrange.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/07_30dayrange.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/07_30dayrange.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/07_30dayrange.png?resize=2400%2C1382?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<h2>Derivatives Market Insights</h2>
<p>The derivatives market, often seen as a barometer for underlying asset sentiment, is also echoing this quiet spell. &#8220;The combined Futures and Options trade volume for [BTC and ETH] are at, or approaching all-time-lows,&#8221; the report notes. This is further emphasized by the fact that &#8220;BTC is currently seeing $19.0B in aggregate derivatives trade volume, whilst ETH markets have just $9.2B/day.&#8221;</p>

<p>Interestingly, the options market is showing signs of a significant &#8220;volatility crush.&#8221; As per Glassnode, &#8220;Options are pricing in the smallest volatility premium in history, with IV between 24% and 52%, less than half of the long-term baseline.&#8221; This is further corroborated by the historically low Put/Call Ratio and the 25-delta skew metric, suggesting a net bullish sentiment in the market.</p>
<p>The crux of the matter lies in interpreting these signs. The report aptly questions, &#8220;Given the context of Bitcoin&#8217;s infamous volatility, is a new era of BTC price stability upon us, or is volatility mispriced?&#8221; Historically, periods of low volatility in Bitcoin have often been followed by significant price movements. Whether this is a calm before a storm or a genuine shift towards a more stable Bitcoin remains to be seen.</p>
<p>But as Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221;, the chief chart technician at NewsBTC, has <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/why-low-volatility-bitcoin-could-last-a-lot-longer/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">pointed</a> out yesterday, the technical indicators are also pointing to a prolonged period of re-accumulation, meaning that the phase of low volatility is likely to continue for some time to come.</p>
<p>At press time, the BTC price was at $29,277.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-546161 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-08_08-30-15.png?resize=3628%2C1673" alt="Bitcoin price" width="3628" height="1673" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-08_08-30-15.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=3628 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-08_08-30-15.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-08_08-30-15.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-08_08-30-15.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-08_08-30-15.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-08_08-30-15.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-08_08-30-15.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-08_08-30-15.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=1140 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-08_08-30-15.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=3000 3000w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-501851154.jpg?fit=460%2C270" width="460" height="270" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546148</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Could Stage Steady Increase If It Clears This Hurdle</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-increase-29-5k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546151</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is still facing strong resistance near $29,500. BTC is slowly moving higher and might start a steady increase above $29,500. Bitcoin is moving higher toward the $29,500 pivot level. The price is trading above $29,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $29,080 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could start a steady increase if there is a close above the $29,500 resistance zone. Bitcoin Price Eyes Fresh Increase Bitcoin price extended its decline below the $28,800 support zone. However, the downsides were limited below the $28,600 level. A low is formed near $28,628 and the price is now attempting a fresh increase. There was a move above the $28,900 and $29,000 levels. Besides, there was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $29,080 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. The pair is now trading above $29,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. A high is formed near $29,280 and the price is now consolidating gains. Bitcoin is trading above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $28,628 swing low to the $29,280 high. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com Immediate resistance is near the $29,300 zone. The first major resistance is near the $29,400 level. The next major resistance is near the $29,500 level. A close above the $29,500 resistance might start a steady increase. In the stated case, the price could test $30,000. Any more gains might open the doors for a move toward $31,200. Fresh Decline In BTC? If Bitcoin fails to clear the $29,400 resistance, it could start a fresh decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $29,100 level the 100 hourly Simple moving average. The next major support is near the $28,800 level, below which the price could accelerate lower. The next support is near the $28,400 level. Any more losses might call for a move toward the $28,000 level in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $29,100, followed by $28,800. Major Resistance Levels – $29,300, $29,400, and $29,500.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is still facing strong resistance near $29,500. BTC is slowly moving higher and might start a steady increase above $29,500.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is moving higher toward the $29,500 pivot level.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $29,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $29,080 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a steady increase if there is a close above the $29,500 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Eyes Fresh Increase</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-muted-29k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">extended its decline below the $28,800 support zone</a>. However, the downsides were limited below the $28,600 level. A low is formed near $28,628 and the price is now attempting a fresh increase.</p>
<p>There was a move above the $28,900 and $29,000 levels. Besides, there was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $29,080 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. The pair is now trading above $29,000 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-stuck-in-range-but-heres-why-bulls-are-safe/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>.</p>
<p>A high is formed near $29,280 and the price is now consolidating gains. Bitcoin is trading above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $28,628 swing low to the $29,280 high.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-546152" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-2.png?resize=1024%2C465" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1024" height="465" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-2.png?resize=1024%2C465?w=1950 1950w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-2.png?resize=1024%2C465?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-2.png?resize=1024%2C465?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-2.png?resize=1024%2C465?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-2.png?resize=1024%2C465?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-2.png?resize=1024%2C465?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-2.png?resize=1024%2C465?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>Immediate resistance is near the $29,300 zone. The first major resistance is near the $29,400 level. The next major resistance is near the $29,500 level. A close above the $29,500 resistance might start a steady increase. In the stated case, the price could test $30,000. Any more gains might open the doors for a move toward $31,200.</p>
<h2>Fresh Decline In BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin fails to clear the $29,400 resistance, it could start a fresh decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $29,100 level the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $28,800 level, below which the price could accelerate lower. The next support is near the $28,400 level. Any more losses might call for a move toward the $28,000 level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $29,100, followed by $28,800.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $29,300, $29,400, and $29,500.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/shutterstock_555674926.jpg?fit=460%2C313" width="460" height="313" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546151</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Few Bitcoin Holders Withdrawing BTC From Exchanges, Is Fear Creeping In?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/few-bitcoin-holders-withdrawing-btc-exchanges-fear-creeping-in/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 03:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546113</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Recent data from CryptoQuant on August 7 shows that few Bitcoin holders are moving coins away from centralized cryptocurrency exchanges like Binance and Coinbase. Despite BTC prices increasing in recent weeks and teetering close to the $30,000 psychological level, this observation is accurate.  More Bitcoin Held in Exchanges As of July 28, there were 30,663 addresses withdrawing coins from exchanges though prices were relatively higher, trading around $28,000, up from around $25,000 registered on June 14 when 39,311 addresses moved coins. On April 14, when BTC changed hands at around $30,000, 132,237 addresses withdrew the coin from exchanges. The drop in the number of exchange addresses moving coins to external, often non-custodial wallets can be a concern, significantly if prices are rising.  The shift also raises important questions about why more Bitcoin holders opt to store coins in exchanges despite these ramps being targets by hackers. Usually, when fewer people transfer their Bitcoin to external, often non-custodial wallets, it might mean they&#8217;re unsure about the uptrend. As such, they keep their coins on exchanges to quickly sell for USDT or traditional currencies like USD or Euro if needed.  Optimism Abound Even with this change, the broader Bitcoin community remains positive about the coin&#8217;s potential in the coming months. This optimism comes partly from recent classifications from agencies like the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and Commodity Futures Trade Commission (CFTC) that expressly endorse Bitcoin as a commodity subject to capital gains tax.  Related Reading: Solana Products See Strong Inflows, Bitcoin And Crypto Lose $107 Million Other digital assets like ETH have not been categorized as such, sowing doubts among some Ethereum holders that US regulators can classify the second most valuable coin as a security. Because of this positive outlook on the world&#8217;s most valuable coin, advanced derivatives, like BlackRock&#8217;s planned launch (if approved) of a spot Bitcoin Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF), are being developed. Complex Bitcoin trading products are already live in Canada and other parts of the world. Bloomberg Intelligence analysts say that the odds of a Bitcoin ETF getting approved by the SEC are 65%. The increase is partly due to bullish progress, including SEC Chair Gary Gensler&#8217;s comments on Bitcoin, the regulator&#8217;s reportedly insisting that BTC is the only commodity before Coinbase was sued, and the agency accepting re-filing from BlackRock&#8217;s ETF. Related Reading: XRP Journey To $10: Unveiling The Forces That Could Trigger An Upward Momentum While the upcoming halving of Bitcoin in 2024 could be good news, Bloomberg analysts argue that the expected upswing appears to be &#8220;priced in&#8221; based on &#8220;previous cycles.&#8221; Subsequently, analysts think BTC may rally to $50,000 by April 2024, looking at how prices have been performing in the recent few months.  Feature image from Canva, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Recent data from CryptoQuant on August 7 <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptoquant.com/asset/btc/chart/exchange-flows/exchange-withdrawing-addresses?exchange=all_exchange&amp;window=DAY&amp;sma=0&amp;ema=0&amp;priceScale=log&amp;metricScale=linear&amp;chartStyle=line" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shows</a> that few Bitcoin holders are moving coins away from centralized cryptocurrency exchanges like Binance and Coinbase. Despite BTC prices increasing in recent weeks and teetering close to the $30,000 psychological level, this observation is accurate. </p>
<h2>More Bitcoin Held in Exchanges</h2>
<p>As of July 28, there were 30,663 addresses withdrawing coins from exchanges though prices were relatively higher, trading around $28,000, up from around $25,000 registered on June 14 when 39,311 addresses moved coins. On April 14, when BTC changed hands at around $30,000, 132,237 addresses withdrew the coin from exchanges. </p>
<p>The drop in the number of exchange addresses moving coins to external, often non-custodial wallets can be a concern, significantly if prices are rising. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-546114" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Withdrawing-Addresses-All-Exchanges.png?resize=1024%2C645" alt="Bitcoin Exchange Withdrawing Addresses - All Exchanges| CryptoQuant" width="1024" height="645" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Withdrawing-Addresses-All-Exchanges.png?resize=1024%2C645?w=4287 4287w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Withdrawing-Addresses-All-Exchanges.png?resize=1024%2C645?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Withdrawing-Addresses-All-Exchanges.png?resize=1024%2C645?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Withdrawing-Addresses-All-Exchanges.png?resize=1024%2C645?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Withdrawing-Addresses-All-Exchanges.png?resize=1024%2C645?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Withdrawing-Addresses-All-Exchanges.png?resize=1024%2C645?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Withdrawing-Addresses-All-Exchanges.png?resize=1024%2C645?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Withdrawing-Addresses-All-Exchanges.png?resize=1024%2C645?w=1140 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Withdrawing-Addresses-All-Exchanges.png?resize=1024%2C645?w=3000 3000w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>The shift also raises important questions about why more Bitcoin holders opt to store coins in exchanges despite these ramps being targets by hackers. Usually, when fewer people transfer their Bitcoin to external, often non-custodial wallets, it might mean they&#8217;re unsure about the uptrend. As such, they keep their coins on exchanges to quickly sell for USDT or traditional currencies like USD or Euro if needed. </p>
<h2>Optimism Abound</h2>
<p>Even with this change, the broader Bitcoin community remains positive about the coin&#8217;s potential in the coming months. This optimism comes partly from recent classifications from agencies like the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and Commodity Futures Trade Commission (CFTC) that expressly endorse Bitcoin as a commodity subject to capital gains tax. </p>

<p>Other digital assets like ETH have not been categorized as such, sowing doubts among some Ethereum holders that US regulators can classify the second most valuable coin as a security. </p>
<p>Because of this positive outlook on the world&#8217;s most valuable coin, advanced derivatives, like BlackRock&#8217;s planned launch (if approved) of a spot Bitcoin Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF), are being developed. Complex Bitcoin trading products are already live in Canada and other parts of the world.</p>
<p>Bloomberg Intelligence analysts say that the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-spot-etf-odds-65-bloomberg-analysts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">odds</a> of a Bitcoin ETF getting approved by the SEC are 65%. The increase is partly due to bullish progress, including SEC Chair Gary Gensler&#8217;s comments on Bitcoin, the regulator&#8217;s reportedly insisting that BTC is the only commodity before Coinbase was sued, and the agency accepting re-filing from BlackRock&#8217;s ETF.</p>

<p>While the upcoming halving of Bitcoin in 2024 could be good news, Bloomberg analysts argue that the expected upswing appears to be &#8220;priced in&#8221; <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-04-23/bitcoin-btc-halving-in-2024-spurs-predictions-of-rally-past-50-000" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">based</a> on &#8220;previous cycles.&#8221; Subsequently, analysts think BTC may rally to $50,000 by April 2024, looking at how prices have been performing in the recent few months. </p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/6W4R30Kp/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/6W4R30Kp/" alt="BTC price on August 7 as few Bitcoin holders move coins from exchanges| Source: BTCUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Few-BTC-Holders-Moving-Coins-From-Exchanges.jpg?fit=460%2C260" width="460" height="260" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546113</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Fate Hangs In The Balance, 50% Chance Of Falling Below $25,000 In September</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-fate-hangs-in-the-balance-50-chance-of-falling-below-25000-in-september/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 02:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=546120</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) has been no stranger to dramatic price swings in the volatile cryptocurrency world. As September approaches, market analysts closely monitor BTC&#8217;s possibility of plunging below the $25,000 mark.  However, history has shown that September&#8217;s struggles often pave the way for a resurgence in October, with massive rallies that rekindle investor optimism.  Potential For BTC To Drop Below $25,000 Before A Promising October When examining Bitcoin&#8217;s historical performance during September, it becomes evident that the month has posed challenges for the world&#8217;s most renowned cryptocurrency.  Related Reading: BREAKING: Did Solana Miss A Golden Opportunity To Collaborate With PayPal’s PYUSD Stablecoin? Previous September has witnessed BTC experiencing declines of up to 13%. This downward trend has undoubtedly concerned traders and investors, raising questions about the sustainability of Bitcoin&#8217;s bullish momentum. According to Timothy Peterson, market analyst and investment Manager, based on current market analysis, there is a 50% probability that Bitcoin&#8217;s price will dip below the $25,000 threshold before September concludes.  While a potential drop below $25,000 might cause temporary unease among Bitcoin enthusiasts, historical patterns suggest that October could be the month to look forward to.  In the past, September&#8217;s price declines have often catalyzed significant rallies in the subsequent month. Observing the heatmap above, Peterson identified instances where Bitcoin rebounded with gains as high as 48% following sharp declines in September. If Bitcoin does indeed experience a dip below $25,000 in September, it may mark the final significant correction before the commencement of a new bull run cycle.  On this note, Peterson believes that such a dip, coupled with the subsequent recovery and October&#8217;s potential rally, could set the stage for substantial gains in the coming months. Bitcoin Bullish Divergence As BTC experienced a drop from $32,000 to $29,000, trader Ali Martinez highlighted a significant trend; the number of new Bitcoin addresses continued to rise steadily.  Related Reading: Ripple Is Now A Member Of Trade Organization That Hosts The Likes Of BlackRock This intriguing divergence between price and network growth provides insights into BTC&#8217;s potentially stable long-term uptrend.  While Bitcoin&#8217;s price exhibited a downward trajectory, the number of newly created Bitcoin addresses has consistently grown.  This divergence is noteworthy, suggesting that despite short-term price fluctuations, the network&#8217;s expansion remains robust. It signifies a growing interest in Bitcoin adoption and usage, which, in turn, supports the notion of a stable and sustainable long-term uptrend. Conversely, Bitcoin remains trapped within a price range of $29,200 and $28,900, a pattern that has persisted since the start of August. As of the time of writing, BTC is trading at $28,960, reflecting a 0.5% decrease in the last 24 hours. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC) has been no stranger to dramatic price swings in the volatile cryptocurrency world. As September approaches, market analysts closely monitor BTC&#8217;s possibility of plunging below the $25,000 mark. </p>
<p>However, history has shown that September&#8217;s struggles often pave the way for a resurgence in October, with massive rallies that rekindle investor optimism. </p>
<h2>Potential For BTC To Drop Below $25,000 Before A Promising October</h2>
<p>When examining Bitcoin&#8217;s historical performance during September, it becomes evident that the month has posed challenges for the world&#8217;s most renowned cryptocurrency. </p>

<p>Previous September has witnessed BTC experiencing declines of up to 13%. This downward trend has undoubtedly concerned traders and investors, raising questions about the sustainability of Bitcoin&#8217;s bullish momentum.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-546125 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F24krh4X0AEBMJ4.jpg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C653" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="653" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F24krh4X0AEBMJ4.jpg?w=1195 1195w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F24krh4X0AEBMJ4.jpg?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F24krh4X0AEBMJ4.jpg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F24krh4X0AEBMJ4.jpg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C653 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F24krh4X0AEBMJ4.jpg?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F24krh4X0AEBMJ4.jpg?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/nsquaredcrypto/status/1688328067255840768?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to Timothy Peterson, market analyst and investment Manager, based on current market analysis, there is a 50% probability that Bitcoin&#8217;s price will dip below the $25,000 threshold before September concludes. </p>
<p>While a potential drop below $25,000 might cause temporary unease among Bitcoin enthusiasts, historical patterns suggest that October could be the month to look forward to. </p>
<p>In the past, September&#8217;s price declines have often catalyzed significant rallies in the subsequent month. Observing the heatmap above, Peterson identified instances where Bitcoin rebounded with gains as high as 48% following sharp declines in September.</p>
<p>If Bitcoin does indeed experience a dip below $25,000 in September, it may mark the final significant correction before the commencement of a new bull run cycle. </p>
<p>On this note, Peterson believes that such a dip, coupled with the subsequent recovery and October&#8217;s potential rally, could set the stage for substantial gains in the coming months.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Bullish Divergence</h2>
<p>As BTC experienced a drop from $32,000 to $29,000, trader Ali Martinez <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1688441865832386560?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">highlighted </a>a significant trend; the number of new Bitcoin addresses continued to rise steadily. </p>

<p>This intriguing divergence between price and network growth provides insights into BTC&#8217;s potentially stable long-term uptrend. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-546124 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F26LxOyWMAA6HX1.jpg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C484" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="484" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F26LxOyWMAA6HX1.jpg?w=1800 1800w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F26LxOyWMAA6HX1.jpg?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F26LxOyWMAA6HX1.jpg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F26LxOyWMAA6HX1.jpg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C484 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F26LxOyWMAA6HX1.jpg?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F26LxOyWMAA6HX1.jpg?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F26LxOyWMAA6HX1.jpg?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>While Bitcoin&#8217;s price exhibited a downward trajectory, the number of newly created Bitcoin addresses has consistently grown. </p>
<p>This divergence is noteworthy, suggesting that despite short-term price fluctuations, the network&#8217;s expansion remains robust. It signifies a growing interest in Bitcoin adoption and usage, which, in turn, supports the notion of a stable and sustainable long-term uptrend.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/07HUytHc/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Conversely, Bitcoin remains trapped within a price range of $29,200 and $28,900, a pattern that has persisted since the start of August. As of the time of writing, BTC is trading at $28,960, reflecting a 0.5% decrease in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1393470258.jpg?fit=460%2C164" width="460" height="164" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">546120</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
