<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 07:10:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>FLOKI Recovers From A Bad Fall, Climbs Back Up To The Green Zone</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/floki-recovers-from-a-bad-fall-climbs-back-up-to-the-green-zone/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 07:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Floki Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FLOKI Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537608</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the midst of a volatile cryptocurrency market, Floki Inu (FLOKI) has managed to defy expectations and become a symbol of optimism for investors. While altcoins face the challenges of a recession triggered by the Securities and Exchange Commission&#8217;s actions against major cryptocurrencies in the US, the meme coin sector is struggling with declining capitalization, sinking further into uncertainty. However, against all odds, FLOKI has kept its steady bearing and rise above the chaos, proudly glowing in green on today&#8217;s trading charts. As the cryptocurrency world grapples with regulatory hurdles and market volatility, FLOKI remains steadfast, capturing the attention of investors and defying the prevailing negative market sentiment.  Floki Inu (FLOKI) Surges Amidst Meme Coin Downturn In the midst of a recent collapse in meme coins, Floki Inu (FLOKI) has experienced a noteworthy 24-hour rally of 5.17%. This surge has propelled its price on CoinMarketCap to $0.00002218. Furthermore, the trading volume for FLOKI has reached an impressive $10,059,314 in the last 24 hours, catapulting it to the fifth position among the most traded meme coins. Related Reading: Coinbase Receives Hong Kong Legislator’s Support Amid Regulatory Storm Source: CoinMarketCap In stark contrast, its competitors, including popular coins such as Dogecoin (DOGE) and Shiba Inu (SHIB), have been experiencing declines, with their market caps diminishing by 0.5% to 1%. Amidst the current downturn in meme coins, FLOKI has emerged as a standout performer, attracting attention and trading activity while its counterparts falter. This unexpected surge showcases the resilience and potential of FLOKI, demonstrating its ability to rebound and generate renewed interest in an otherwise challenging market environment. FLOKI in an upward trajectory. Source: CoinMarketCap. Crypto Market Remains Volatile Amid Regulatory Uncertainty As the new week began, the crypto market showed signs of renewed activity, albeit with cautious optimism as regulatory crackdowns from the previous week continued to weigh on sentiment. The uncertainty surrounding the classification of crypto tokens added to investor jitters, further exacerbating the market&#8217;s volatility. Related Reading: Venture Firm Andreessen Horowitz To Open 1st UK Office Amid Crypto Scrutiny In US The index tracking the top 100 crypto tokens experienced a decline of 0.8%, reflecting the cautious mood prevailing among investors. Latest data indicated that the total market capitalization of cryptocurrencies slipped to $1.09 trillion on Monday, underscoring the ongoing challenges faced by the market. Bitcoin re-enters the $26K territory. BTCUSD chart: TradingView.com Regulatory ambiguity has become a significant point of concern, with differing views on the classification of various tokens. While Bitcoin (and apparently Ethereum and Litecoin) is not by definition a security by US regulators, SEC Chair Gary Gensler has emphasized that most other tokens fall under the agency&#8217;s investor-protection laws.  Furthermore, Gensler has stressed the importance of trading platforms registering with the SEC, adding another layer of complexity to the regulatory landscape. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from BlockchainReporter]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the midst of a volatile cryptocurrency market, Floki Inu (FLOKI) has managed to defy expectations and become a symbol of optimism for investors. While altcoins face the challenges of a recession triggered by the Securities and Exchange Commission&#8217;s actions against major cryptocurrencies in the US, the meme coin sector is struggling with declining capitalization, sinking further into uncertainty.</p>
<p>However, against all odds, FLOKI has kept its steady bearing and rise above the chaos, proudly glowing in green on today&#8217;s trading charts.</p>
<p>As the cryptocurrency world grapples with regulatory hurdles and market volatility, FLOKI remains steadfast, capturing the attention of investors and defying the prevailing negative market sentiment. </p>
<h2><strong>Floki Inu (FLOKI) Surges Amidst Meme Coin Downturn</strong></h2>
<p>In the midst of a recent collapse in meme coins, Floki Inu (FLOKI) has experienced a noteworthy 24-hour rally of 5.17%. This surge has propelled its price on <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/?page=2" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinMarketCap</a> to $0.00002218. Furthermore, the trading volume for FLOKI has reached an impressive $10,059,314 in the last 24 hours, catapulting it to the fifth position among the most traded meme coins.</p>

<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-537609" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-68.png" alt="" width="996" height="85" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-68.png 996w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-68-460x39.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-68-860x73.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-68-768x66.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-68-750x64.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 996px) 100vw, 996px"/></p>

<p>In stark contrast, its competitors, including popular coins such as Dogecoin (DOGE) and Shiba Inu (SHIB), have been experiencing declines, with their market caps diminishing by 0.5% to 1%.</p>
<p>Amidst the current downturn in meme coins, <a href="https://u.today/floki-surging-again-while-altcoins-keep-bleeding" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">FLOKI</a> has emerged as a standout performer, attracting attention and trading activity while its counterparts falter. This unexpected surge showcases the resilience and potential of FLOKI, demonstrating its ability to rebound and generate renewed interest in an otherwise challenging market environment.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-537610" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-69.png" alt="" width="1046" height="471" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-69.png 1046w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-69-460x207.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-69-860x387.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-69-768x346.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-69-750x338.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1046px) 100vw, 1046px"/></p>

<h2><strong>Crypto Market Remains Volatile Amid Regulatory Uncertainty</strong></h2>
<p>As the new week began, the crypto market showed signs of renewed activity, albeit with cautious optimism as regulatory crackdowns from the previous week continued to weigh on sentiment. The uncertainty surrounding the classification of crypto tokens added to investor jitters, further exacerbating the market&#8217;s volatility.</p>

<p>The index tracking the <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/tokens/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">top 100 crypto tokens</a> experienced a decline of 0.8%, reflecting the cautious mood prevailing among investors. Latest data indicated that the total market capitalization of cryptocurrencies slipped to $1.09 trillion on Monday, underscoring the ongoing challenges faced by the market.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/0Mp6wjhh/" width="2314" height="1109"/></p>

<p>Regulatory ambiguity has become a significant point of concern, with differing views on the classification of various tokens. While Bitcoin (and apparently<a href="https://fortune.com/crypto/2023/06/12/gensler-video-ethereum-litecoin-not-securities/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> Ethereum and Litecoin</a>) is not by definition a security by US regulators, SEC Chair Gary Gensler has emphasized that most other tokens fall under the agency&#8217;s investor-protection laws. </p>
<p>Furthermore, Gensler has stressed the importance of trading platforms registering with the SEC, adding another layer of complexity to the regulatory landscape.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from BlockchainReporter</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-70-460x227.png" width="460" height="227" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Price Targets Fresh Highs While Other Altcoins Bleed</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-price-targets-0-58/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 04:38:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537605</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ripple’s token price is rising above the $0.52 resistance against the US Dollar. XRP price is trading in a bullish zone while ADA, BNB, and other altcoins bleed. Ripple’s token price is holding gains above the $0.500 resistance against the US dollar. The price is now trading above $0.515 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.535 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Kraken). The pair might continue to rise if it clears the $0.545 and $0.550 resistance levels. Ripple’s Token Price Holds Ground In the past few days, Ripple’s XRP saw a downside correction from the $0.540 resistance against the US Dollar. It dipped below the $0.52 support zone and saw bearish moves, similar to Bitcoin and Ethereum. However, the bulls were active near the $0.475 zone. A low was formed near $0.4752 and the price is now rising. It trimmed most of its losses while ADA and BNB were tumbling. XRP surpassed the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.5411 swing high to the $0.4752 low. XRP price is now trading above $0.515 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). It is testing the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.5411 swing high to the $0.4752 low. Source: XRPUSD on TradingView.com Initial resistance on the upside is near the $0.535 zone. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.535 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair. The first major resistance is near the $0.545 level. A successful break above the $0.545 resistance level might send the price toward the $0.565 resistance. Any more gains might call for a test of the $0.580 resistance. Fresh Decline in XRP? If ripple fails to clear the $0.535 resistance zone, it could start a downside correction. Initial support on the downside is near the $0.515 zone. The next major support is near $0.501. If there is a downside break and a close below the $0.501 level, XRP’s price could extend losses. In the stated case, the price could retest the $0.480 support zone. Technical Indicators 4-Hours MACD – The MACD for XRP/USD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone. 4-Hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for XRP/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $0.515, $0.501, and $0.480. Major Resistance Levels – $0.535, $0.545, and $0.550.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ripple’s token price is rising above the $0.52 resistance against the US Dollar. XRP price is trading in a bullish zone while ADA, BNB, and other altcoins bleed.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ripple’s token price is holding gains above the $0.500 resistance against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $0.515 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.535 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair (data source from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair might continue to rise if it clears the $0.545 and $0.550 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ripple’s Token Price Holds Ground</h2>
<p>In the past few days, Ripple’s XRP saw a downside correction from the $0.540 resistance against the US Dollar. It dipped below the $0.52 support zone and saw bearish moves, similar to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-consolidates-26000/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a> and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-recovery-1800/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum</a>.</p>
<p>However, the bulls were active near the $0.475 zone. A low was formed near $0.4752 and the price is now rising. It trimmed most of its losses while ADA and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/bnb/bnb-price-prediction-200/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">BNB</a> were tumbling. XRP surpassed the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.5411 swing high to the $0.4752 low.</p>
<p>XRP price is now trading above $0.515 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). It is testing the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.5411 swing high to the $0.4752 low.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-537606" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRP_Price-1.png" alt="XRP Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRP_Price-1.png 1834w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRP_Price-1-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRP_Price-1-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRP_Price-1-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRP_Price-1-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRP_Price-1-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRP_Price-1-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">XRPUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>Initial resistance on the upside is near the $0.535 zone. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $0.535 on the 4-hour chart of the XRP/USD pair. The first major resistance is near the $0.545 level. A successful break above the $0.545 resistance level might send the price toward the $0.565 resistance. Any more gains might call for a test of the $0.580 resistance.</p>
<h2>Fresh Decline in XRP?</h2>
<p>If ripple fails to clear the $0.535 resistance zone, it could start a downside correction. Initial support on the downside is near the $0.515 zone.</p>
<p>The next major support is near $0.501. If there is a downside break and a close below the $0.501 level, XRP’s price could extend losses. In the stated case, the price could retest the $0.480 support zone.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>4-Hours MACD – The MACD for XRP/USD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4-Hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for XRP/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $0.515, $0.501, and $0.480.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $0.535, $0.545, and $0.550.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/shutterstock_786470158-460x288.jpg" width="460" height="288" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Could See Recovery If It’s Able to Clear $1,800</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-recovery-1800/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 04:06:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537602</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum price is attempting a recovery wave above the $1,740 level against the US Dollar. ETH could rise steadily if there is a move above the $1,780 resistance. Ethereum is still below the $1,780 and $1,800 resistance levels. The price is trading below $1,780 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $1,740 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could recover if there is a move above the $1,780 and $1,800 levels. Ethereum Price Forms Support Base Ethereum’s price settled below the $1,775 and $1,780 resistance levels. ETH tested the $1,720 zone and is currently forming a support base, similar to Bitcoin. A low is formed near $1,718 and the price is attempting a recovery wave. The price is slowly moving higher above the $1,740 level. There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $1,740 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. Ether is now testing the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the main drop from the $1,854 swing high to the $1,718 low. However, it is still trading below $1,780 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. Immediate resistance is near the $1,770 zone and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. The next major resistance is near the $1,785 level. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the main drop from the $1,854 swing high to the $1,718 low. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com A proper move above the $1,770 and $1,785 resistance levels might send Ether toward $1,820. The next resistance sits near $1,850, above which Ethereum could rise toward the $1,880 level. Any more gains above the $1,880 resistance zone might send the price toward the $1,920 resistance. Another Drop in ETH? If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,770 resistance, it could start another decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,730 level. The next major support is near the $1,720 level. If there is a break and close below the $1,720 support, the price could gain bearish momentum toward the $1,640 support. Any more losses may perhaps send the price toward the $1,600 zone. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is losing momentum in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,720 Major Resistance Level – $1,780]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum price is attempting a recovery wave above the $1,740 level against the US Dollar. ETH could rise steadily if there is a move above the $1,780 resistance.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum is still below the $1,780 and $1,800 resistance levels.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $1,780 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</li>
<li>There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $1,740 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could recover if there is a move above the $1,780 and $1,800 levels.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Forms Support Base</h2>
<p>Ethereum’s price settled below the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-downtrend-1800/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$1,775 and $1,780 resistance levels</a>. ETH tested the $1,720 zone and is currently forming a support base, similar to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-consolidates-26000/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p>A low is formed near $1,718 and the price is attempting a recovery wave. The price is slowly moving higher above the $1,740 level. There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $1,740 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD.</p>
<p>Ether is now testing the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the main drop from the $1,854 swing high to the $1,718 low. However, it is still trading below $1,780 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</p>
<p>Immediate resistance is near the $1,770 zone and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. The next major resistance is near the $1,785 level. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the main drop from the $1,854 swing high to the $1,718 low.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-537603" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-7.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-7.png 1834w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-7-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-7-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-7-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-7-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-7-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-7-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>A proper move above the $1,770 and $1,785 resistance levels might send Ether toward $1,820. The next resistance sits near $1,850, above which Ethereum could rise toward the $1,880 level. Any more gains above the $1,880 resistance zone might send the price toward the $1,920 resistance.</p>
<h2>Another Drop in ETH?</h2>
<p>If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,770 resistance, it could start another decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,730 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $1,720 level. If there is a break and close below the $1,720 support, the price could gain bearish momentum toward the $1,640 support. Any more losses may perhaps send the price toward the $1,600 zone.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,720</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,780</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/shutterstock_1100038610-460x272.jpg" width="460" height="272" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Consolidates, Why 100 SMA Is The Key To Fresh Increase</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-consolidates-26000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 03:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537599</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is consolidating above the $25,500 support. BTC could start a fresh increase if it settles above the 100 hourly SMA and $26,150. Bitcoin is slowly moving higher from the $25,500 support zone. The price is trading below $26,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $25,900 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could start a recovery wave if there is a move above the $26,150 resistance. Bitcoin Price Eyes Recovery Bitcoin price formed a base above the $25,400 support zone. BTC is now consolidating and slowly moving higher above the $25,650 level but it faces many hurdles. The bulls were able to push the price above the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $26,200 swing high to the $25,620 low. Besides, there was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $25,900 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Bitcoin price is now testing $26,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. It seems to be facing resistance near the $26,000 zone or the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $26,200 swing high to the $25,620 low. The first major resistance is near the $26,150 level. A clear move above the $26,150 resistance might start a fresh increase. The next major resistance is near the $26,500 level. A close above $26,500 might start a move toward the $26,500 resistance zone. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The next key resistance is near the $26,800 level, above which Bitcoin might rise toward the $27,000 resistance. Any more gains above the $27,000 resistance zone might send the price toward the $27,500 resistance zone. Another Rejection in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $26,150 resistance, it could start another decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $25,575 level. The next major support is near the $25,400 level, below which the price might gain bearish momentum. In the stated case, the price could drop toward the $25,000 support in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $25,575, followed by $25,500. Major Resistance Levels – $26,000, $26,150, and $26,500.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is consolidating above the $25,500 support. BTC could start a fresh increase if it settles above the 100 hourly SMA and $26,150.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is slowly moving higher from the $25,500 support zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $26,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $25,900 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a recovery wave if there is a move above the $26,150 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Eyes Recovery</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price formed a base above the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-at-significant-risk-25400/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$25,400 support zone</a>. BTC is now consolidating and slowly moving higher above the $25,650 level but it faces many hurdles.</p>
<p>The bulls were able to push the price above the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $26,200 swing high to the $25,620 low. Besides, there was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $25,900 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is now testing $26,000 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-defies-gravity-26k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>. It seems to be facing resistance near the $26,000 zone or the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $26,200 swing high to the $25,620 low.</p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $26,150 level. A clear move above the $26,150 resistance might start a fresh increase. The next major resistance is near the $26,500 level. A close above $26,500 might start a move toward the $26,500 resistance zone.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-537600" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-8.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-8.png 1834w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-8-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-8-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-8-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-8-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-8-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-8-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The next key resistance is near the $26,800 level, above which Bitcoin might rise toward the $27,000 resistance. Any more gains above the $27,000 resistance zone might send the price toward the $27,500 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Another Rejection in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $26,150 resistance, it could start another decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $25,575 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $25,400 level, below which the price might gain bearish momentum. In the stated case, the price could drop toward the $25,000 support in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $25,575, followed by $25,500.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $26,000, $26,150, and $26,500.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/shutterstock_1402375832-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#8217;s Vision Pro Launch Impacts Metaverse, Why This Token Recorded 160% In Profits</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/apple-vision-pro-launch-impacts-metaverse-why-this-token-recorded-160-in-profits/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 01:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Metaverse]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537546</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The crypto market has been flowing in a sea of red as major assets experienced a correction over the weekend, but tech giant Apple could offer relief. Every cryptocurrency, except for Bitcoin, trended to the downside, but some sectors have bloomed amidst the panic and selling pressure. Related Reading: Cardano Price Falls Below Key Support Levels, Will It Continue To Fall? In particular, some tokens in the Metaverse sector have seen important profits. The assets’ positive price action, defying the overall trend in the crypto market, seems related to Apple’s launch of its new product the Vision Pro. Metaverse Tokens Bloom As Hype For The Apple Vision Pro Growths Apple’s Vision Pro is the company’s first “spatial computer,” the headset will allow users to blend the physical with the digital world. In that sense, people will have the capacity to interact with applications, content, media across different formats, and more. The Metaverse and the projects using blockchain technology to support their platforms want to achieve the same objectives. Thus, there has been a growing correlation between Metaverse tokens and announcements from big tech companies related to the sector. According to a study from CoinGecko, the Apple Vision Pro highlighted the positive performance of Metaverse and Augmented Reality tokens. At its publication, the study showed that Ovr and its native Metaverse token (OVR) saw a 168.6% increase on the back of the announcement. By late May and early June, the token climbed from a low of around $0.28 to $0.74. Other small-cap tokens in the sector experienced similar gains. VFOX recorded a 62% profit between May 15 and June 7, and virtual reality token CUBE from the Metaverse project Somnium rose by around 40% over the same period. Metaverse tokens with larger market caps appreciated pre and after the Apple announcement, although they registered fewer profits. The Sandbox (SAND) saw an 18% increase between mid-May and June 5, and Decentraland (MANA) saw fewer gains, with an 11% profit mostly registered during the announcement. As seen in the chart below, SAND, OVR, and VFOX were just some of the tokens that benefited from the launch of the Vision Pro. Related Reading: Insights On ADA’s Security Concerns: Cardano Founder And Ripple CTO Exchange Views However, the Metaverse has been partially affected by the current trend in the overall crypto market. Some tokens retraced some of their gains on the back of the most recent downturn, but the current price dip could be favorable for long-term investors, as these tokens could continue to benefit from similar announcements.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>The crypto market has been flowing in a sea of red as major assets experienced a correction over the weekend, but tech giant Apple could offer relief. Every cryptocurrency, except for Bitcoin, trended to the downside, but some sectors have bloomed amidst the panic and selling pressure. </strong></p>

<p>In particular, some tokens in the Metaverse sector have seen important profits. The assets’ positive price action, defying the overall trend in the crypto market, seems related to Apple’s launch of its new product the Vision Pro.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-537571 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Apple-SAND-SANDUSDT-ETH-ETHUSDT-860x410.png" alt="Apple SAND SANDUSDT ETH ETHUSDT" width="860" height="410" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Apple-SAND-SANDUSDT-ETH-ETHUSDT-860x410.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Apple-SAND-SANDUSDT-ETH-ETHUSDT-460x219.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Apple-SAND-SANDUSDT-ETH-ETHUSDT-768x366.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Apple-SAND-SANDUSDT-ETH-ETHUSDT-1536x733.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Apple-SAND-SANDUSDT-ETH-ETHUSDT-750x358.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Apple-SAND-SANDUSDT-ETH-ETHUSDT-1140x544.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Apple-SAND-SANDUSDT-ETH-ETHUSDT.png 1757w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<h2>Metaverse Tokens Bloom As Hype For The Apple Vision Pro Growths</h2>
<p>Apple’s Vision Pro is the company’s first “spatial computer,” the headset will allow users to blend the physical with the digital world. In that sense, people will have the capacity to interact with applications, content, media across different formats, and more.</p>
<p>The Metaverse and the projects using blockchain technology to support their platforms want to achieve the same objectives. Thus, there has been a growing correlation between Metaverse tokens and announcements from big tech companies related to the sector.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/research/publications/apple-impact-metaverse-tokens" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">study</a> from CoinGecko, the Apple Vision Pro highlighted the positive performance of Metaverse and Augmented Reality tokens. At its publication, the study showed that Ovr and its native Metaverse token (OVR) saw a 168.6% increase on the back of the announcement.</p>
<p>By late May and early June, the token climbed from a low of around $0.28 to $0.74. Other small-cap tokens in the sector experienced similar gains. VFOX recorded a 62% profit between May 15 and June 7, and virtual reality token CUBE from the Metaverse project Somnium rose by around 40% over the same period.</p>
<p>Metaverse tokens with larger market caps appreciated pre and after the Apple announcement, although they registered fewer profits. The Sandbox (SAND) saw an 18% increase between mid-May and June 5, and Decentraland (MANA) saw fewer gains, with an 11% profit mostly registered during the announcement.</p>
<p>As seen in the chart below, SAND, OVR, and VFOX were just some of the tokens that benefited from the launch of the Vision Pro.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-537570 size-jnews-750x536" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Apple-Metaverse-ETH-ETHUSDT-750x536.jpg" alt="Apple Metaverse ETH ETHUSDT" width="750" height="536" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Apple-Metaverse-ETH-ETHUSDT-750x536.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Apple-Metaverse-ETH-ETHUSDT-120x86.jpg 120w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Apple-Metaverse-ETH-ETHUSDT-350x250.jpg 350w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px"/>

<p>However, the Metaverse has been partially affected by the current trend in the overall crypto market. Some tokens retraced some of their gains on the back of the most recent downturn, but the current price dip could be favorable for long-term investors, as these tokens could continue to benefit from similar announcements.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Apple-Crypto-ETH-ETHUSDT-Metaverse-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin&#8217;s (BTC) Key Indicator Points Bullish Continuation Despite Recent Dip</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoins-btc-key-indicator-points-bullish-continuation-despite-recent-dip/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 00:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537587</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Despite the recent downturn in the cryptocurrency market, there are positive signs for Bitcoin&#8217;s (BTC) future. One key indicator is the Puell Multiple, which suggests a bullish continuation for Bitcoin despite the recent dip. Crypto Con, a well-known cryptocurrency analyst, has closely monitored the Puell Multiple and identified two key factors that point to a positive outlook.  Related Reading: Cardano Price Falls Below Key Support Levels, Will It Continue To Fall? Bitcoin&#8217;s Bullish Potential According to Crypto Con’s analysis, the trend for Bitcoin remains intact, indicating that the market is still bullish on the cryptocurrency. Additionally, Bitcoin has not yet reached the mid-top line that every mid-top has reached without diminishing, as seen in the chart below, suggesting that there is still room for growth. The Puell Multiple is a cryptocurrency market indicator that measures the ratio between Bitcoin&#8217;s daily issuance value and its 365-day moving average (MA) The Puell Multiple is calculated by dividing the daily issuance value of Bitcoin (in USD) by its 365-day moving average. A high reading on the Puell Multiple suggests that BTC is overvalued and may be due for a correction. In contrast, a low reading suggests that Bitcoin is undervalued and may be a good buying opportunity. The Puell Multiple is considered a long-term indicator, providing insights into the macro trends of the Bitcoin market. It has been used to predict major market movements, including the bull run in 2011 and the subsequent bear market. These factors have been evident for Crypto Con since December 2022, when Bitcoin broke the downtrend macro bearish outlook and reached $21,000. At the time, Crypto Con made his first bullish calls on the Puell Multiple when Bitcoin traded at $16,500. Is BTC Facing A Bear Market? Doctor Crypto, a prominent analyst in the cryptocurrency space, has provided insights into what could be next for BTC. In a recent report, Doctor Crypto discussed the significance of key “price manipulations” that took place, which resulted in Bitcoin breaking above the 50-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA) and subsequently nuking afterward.  According to Doctor Crypto, losing the 200-week MA indicator can suggest that Bitcoin is entering a bear market.  Furthermore, the recent Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) uncertainty in the market played a role in breaking down this important indicator, suggesting a clear manipulation by market makers. However, the report notes that market makers may be awaiting the outcome of the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) decision this week before deciding on the next move. Related Reading: SBI CEO Predicts Massive XRP Price Surge, Expects Ripple Verdict In Few Weeks The report suggests that a worse-than-expected FOMC decision could lead to a massive drop toward the $24,000 region and potentially even lower. The fear of recession combined with SEC fear, uncertainty, and doubt (FUD) could lead to BTC’s “total collapse”, hunting down the liquidity pool at $24,000 and potentially even lower. At the time of writing, the primary cryptocurrency in the market, Bitcoin, is trading at $25,800. It has been maintaining a sideways price action, leaving investors uncertain about which direction the market will move in Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite the recent downturn in the cryptocurrency market, there are positive signs for Bitcoin&#8217;s (BTC) future. One key indicator is the Puell Multiple, which suggests a bullish continuation for Bitcoin despite the recent dip.</p>
<p>Crypto Con, a well-known cryptocurrency analyst, has closely monitored the Puell Multiple and <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoCon_/status/1667940442271526912?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">identified </a>two key factors that point to a positive outlook. </p>

<h2>Bitcoin&#8217;s Bullish Potential</h2>
<p>According to Crypto Con’s analysis, the trend for Bitcoin remains intact, indicating that the market is still bullish on the cryptocurrency. Additionally, Bitcoin has not yet reached the mid-top line that every mid-top has reached without diminishing, as seen in the chart below, suggesting that there is still room for growth.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-537589 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyW1czEaQAMpwwn-860x572.jpg" alt="BTC" width="860" height="572" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyW1czEaQAMpwwn-860x572.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyW1czEaQAMpwwn-460x306.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyW1czEaQAMpwwn-768x511.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyW1czEaQAMpwwn-750x499.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyW1czEaQAMpwwn-1140x758.jpg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FyW1czEaQAMpwwn.jpg 1394w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>The Puell Multiple is a cryptocurrency market indicator that measures the ratio between Bitcoin&#8217;s daily issuance value and its 365-day moving average (MA)</p>
<p>The Puell Multiple is calculated by dividing the daily issuance value of Bitcoin (in USD) by its 365-day moving average. A high reading on the Puell Multiple suggests that BTC is overvalued and may be due for a correction. In contrast, a low reading suggests that Bitcoin is undervalued and may be a good buying opportunity.</p>
<p>The Puell Multiple is considered a long-term indicator, providing insights into the macro trends of the Bitcoin market. It has been used to predict major market movements, including the bull run in 2011 and the subsequent bear market.</p>
<p>These factors have been evident for Crypto Con since December 2022, when Bitcoin broke the downtrend macro bearish outlook and reached $21,000. At the time, Crypto Con made his first bullish calls on the Puell Multiple when Bitcoin traded at $16,500.</p>
Is BTC Facing A Bear Market?
<p>Doctor Crypto, a prominent analyst in the cryptocurrency space, has provided <a href="https://twitter.com/DrProfitCrypto/status/1667914585586761733?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">insights </a>into what could be next for BTC. In a recent report, Doctor Crypto discussed the significance of key “price manipulations” that took place, which resulted in Bitcoin breaking above the 50-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA) and subsequently nuking afterward. </p>
<p>According to Doctor Crypto, losing the 200-week MA indicator can suggest that Bitcoin is entering a bear market. </p>
<p>Furthermore, the recent Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) uncertainty in the market played a role in breaking down this important indicator, suggesting a clear manipulation by market makers. However, the report notes that market makers may be awaiting the outcome of the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) decision this week before deciding on the next move.</p>

<p>The report suggests that a worse-than-expected FOMC decision could lead to a massive drop toward the $24,000 region and potentially even lower. The fear of recession combined with SEC fear, uncertainty, and doubt (FUD) could lead to BTC’s “total collapse”, hunting down the liquidity pool at $24,000 and potentially even lower.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/OsXrZrRf/" alt="BTC" width="1813" height="858"/>
<p>At the time of writing, the primary cryptocurrency in the market, Bitcoin, is trading at $25,800. It has been maintaining a sideways price action, leaving investors uncertain about which direction the market will move in</p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1321736875-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Miner Inflows To Exchanges Reach 2021 Levels As Bear Trend Persists</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-miner-inflows-to-exchanges-reach-2021-levels-as-bear-trend-persists/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 23:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin miners]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537535</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin miners are now taking advantage of the recent price increase as they have begun to send massive amounts of BTC to centralized exchanges. While this is not new as miners tend to sell BTC to fund their operations, the sheer volume that is being moved to exchanges is what is alarming. Bitcoin Miners Send Over $70 Million To Exchanges In a recent development reported by on-chain data aggregator Glassnode, Bitcoin miners are moving massive amounts of BTC to exchange. In the last week alone, these miners moved a reported $70.8 million worth of BTC to centralized exchanges. Related Reading: Crypto Investor Sentiment Refuses To Budge, But Can The Weekend Change This? The amount moved in the last week marks the third-largest single inflow for Bitcoin miners in terms of dollar value. It is just 30% below the highest figures which were recorded in 2021 when the price of BTC hit its all-time high of $69,000. BTC miners send over $70m to exchanges &#124; Source: Glassnode Interestingly, because of the current price of Bitcoin, it means that the miners are moving more in terms of the BTC count compared to the dollar count. So miners moved around twice the number of BTC they moved back in 2021 to get the current figure of $70.8 million, data from Glassnode shows. Despite the large selling volumes that seem to be coming from miners, Bitcoin holders continue to be steadfast in their belief in the digital asset. Glassnode reported that long-term holders, i.e. holders who have held their BTC for more than one year, continue to be the most dominant of the bunch with a total of 40.1% of BTC supply remaining unmoved in the last three years. BTC Price Still Shows Bearish Pressure Bitcoin bulls have continued to fight the bears but the effort has fallen short of expectations. As such, BTC prices continue to show intense bearish pressure. BTC falls below $26,000 support &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com Despite the digital asset trading above the $26,000 support, it is still sitting below its 50-day and 100-day moving averages, which could tell of more declines to come. It is also obvious in the fact that bulls are barely holding on to the $26,000 support as resistance mounts at $26,500. Related Reading: Here’s Why Ethereum Could Be At Risk Of Falling To $1,000 Again Nevertheless, the long-term outlook for the cryptocurrency is still very bullish with BTC well above its 200-day moving average. With the Bitcoin halving just around the corner, the digital asset could be headed into another bull market very soon. At the time of writing, BTC is changing hands at a price of $26,015, up 1.09% in the last 24 hours. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin miners are now taking advantage of the recent price increase as they have begun to send massive amounts of BTC to centralized exchanges. While this is not new as miners tend to sell BTC to fund their operations, the sheer volume that is being moved to exchanges is what is alarming.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Miners Send Over $70 Million To Exchanges</h2>
<p>In a recent development <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1667901731588517893?s=61" rel="nofollow">reported</a> by on-chain data aggregator Glassnode, Bitcoin miners are moving massive amounts of BTC to exchange. In the last week alone, these miners moved a reported $70.8 million worth of BTC to centralized exchanges.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/crypto-investor-sentiment-refuses-to-budge-but-can-the-weekend-change-this/?swcfpc=1">Crypto Investor Sentiment Refuses To Budge, But Can The Weekend Change This?</a></p>
<p>The amount moved in the last week marks the third-largest single inflow for Bitcoin miners in terms of dollar value. It is just 30% below the highest figures which were recorded in 2021 when the price of BTC hit its all-time high of $69,000.</p>


<p>Interestingly, because of the current price of Bitcoin, it means that the miners are moving more in terms of the BTC count compared to the dollar count. So miners moved around twice the number of BTC they moved back in 2021 to get the current figure of $70.8 million, data from Glassnode shows.</p>
<p>Despite the large selling volumes that seem to be coming from miners, Bitcoin holders continue to be steadfast in their belief in the digital asset. Glassnode <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1668200023811584003?s=61" rel="nofollow">reported</a> that long-term holders, i.e. holders who have held their BTC for more than one year, continue to be the most dominant of the bunch with a total of 40.1% of BTC supply remaining unmoved in the last three years.</p>
<h2>BTC Price Still Shows Bearish Pressure</h2>
<p>Bitcoin bulls have continued to fight the bears but the effort has fallen short of expectations. As such, BTC prices continue to show intense bearish pressure.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/J5RmbNc7/" alt="Bitcoin price chart from TradingView.com" width="2882" height="1724"/></p>

<p>Despite the digital asset trading above the $26,000 support, it is still sitting below its 50-day and 100-day moving averages, which could tell of more declines to come. It is also obvious in the fact that bulls are barely holding on to the $26,000 support as resistance mounts at $26,500.</p>

<p>Nevertheless, the long-term outlook for the cryptocurrency is still very bullish with BTC well above its 200-day moving average. With the Bitcoin halving just around the corner, the digital asset could be headed into another bull market very soon.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, BTC is changing hands at a price of $26,015, up 1.09% in the last 24 hours.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-502544320-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Changes Terms of Service As BNB Reverses 2023 Gains</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/binance-coin/binance-changes-terms-of-service-as-bnb-reverses-2023-gains/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 22:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537580</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Binance, the largest global cryptocurrency exchange, has quietly changed its terms of service after the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filed a complaint at the District Court for the District of Columbia on June 5. Meanwhile, BNB prices continue to crash, dropping to register new 2023 lows as when writing on June 12. Binance Changes Terms Of Service News of the exchange quietly changing its terms of service was shared on Twitter. Under these new terms, Binance can, at their volition, swap delisted assets held in a user&#8217;s dormant account without consent. Moreover, the exchange can swap the token or coin for any asset they wish. Related Reading: SBI CEO Predicts Massive XRP Price Surge, Expects Ripple Verdict In Few Weeks Observers on Twitter say this update represents an additional tool in the ramp&#8217;s arsenal, as it can affect users based on listing and delisting assets, identifying dormant accounts, and the precedents it establishes for other cryptocurrency exchanges. Under the new terms, Binance has exclusive authority to determine which assets are listed, allowing it to list or delist an asset at will. Such a delisted asset can then be converted into a different coin and modified to its order size. Binance can absolve itself and its operatives, of any liabilities or accountability to the asset&#8217;s owner, for any fees or losses, or damages incurred in the process. While most of the above interpretation is speculative, as there have been no official announcements or operational evidence of such activities, concerns have been raised about the possibility of Binance absolving itself of any need to be transparent. BNB Crashing After SEC&#8217;s Lawsuit The changes come after the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Binance, which accuses the exchange of allegedly illegally operating an unauthorized exchange in the United States. Changpeng Zhao, the CEO of Binance, claims that, from 2019, all US-based citizens were restricted from transacting on Binance Global. Zhao also reiterated that its US-based exchange is an independent entity. However, the SEC claims that the exchange&#8221; subverted their controls to secretly allow high-value United States customers to continue trading on the Binance Global platform.&#8221; Moreover, while Binance publicly claimed that Binance US is independent, the SEC alleges that Zhao secretly controls the company behind the scenes. Related Reading: Data Reveals Short-Term Bitcoin Holders Refuse To Sell Despite SEC Crackdown In the wake of this lawsuit, BNB has been free-falling, according to trackers on June 12. The coin is trading at $230 and down 35% from its April high. At this level, BNB has reversed all gains posted in 2023 and is trading in December 2022 territory. With the SEC cracking the whip, laying down allegations against cryptocurrency exchanges and individual protocols, their respective tokens would likely be under pressure as holders exit.   Feature Image From Canva, Chart From TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance, the largest global cryptocurrency exchange, has quietly changed its terms of service after the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2023-101" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">filed</a> a complaint at the District Court for the District of Columbia on June 5. Meanwhile, BNB prices continue to crash, dropping to register new 2023 lows as when writing on June 12.</p>
<h2>Binance Changes Terms Of Service</h2>
<p>News of the exchange quietly changing its terms of service was <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/jaypinho/status/1667485001359802369" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shared</a> on Twitter. Under these new terms, Binance can, at their volition, swap delisted assets held in a user&#8217;s dormant account without consent. Moreover, the exchange can swap the token or coin for any asset they wish.</p>

<p>Observers on Twitter say this update represents an additional tool in the ramp&#8217;s arsenal, as it can affect users based on listing and delisting assets, identifying dormant accounts, and the precedents it establishes for other cryptocurrency exchanges.</p>
<p>Under the new terms, Binance has exclusive authority to determine which assets are listed, allowing it to list or delist an asset at will. Such a delisted asset can then be converted into a different coin and modified to its order size. Binance can absolve itself and its operatives, of any liabilities or accountability to the asset&#8217;s owner, for any fees or losses, or damages incurred in the process.</p>
<p>While most of the above interpretation is speculative, as there have been no official announcements or operational evidence of such activities, concerns have been raised about the possibility of Binance absolving itself of any need to be transparent.</p>
<h2>BNB Crashing After SEC&#8217;s Lawsuit
</h2>
<p>The changes come after the SEC&#8217;s <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2023/jun/06/sec-crypto-crackdown-us-regulator-sues-binance-and-coinbase" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">lawsuit</a> against Binance, which accuses the exchange of allegedly illegally operating an unauthorized exchange in the United States.</p>
<p>Changpeng Zhao, the CEO of Binance, claims that, from 2019, all US-based citizens were restricted from transacting on Binance Global. Zhao also reiterated that its US-based exchange is an independent entity.</p>
<p>However, the SEC claims that the exchange&#8221; subverted their controls to secretly allow high-value United States customers to continue trading on the Binance Global platform.&#8221; Moreover, while Binance publicly claimed that Binance US is independent, the SEC alleges that Zhao secretly controls the company behind the scenes.</p>

<p>In the wake of this lawsuit, BNB has been free-falling, according to trackers on June 12. The coin is trading at $230 and down 35% from its April high. At this level, BNB has reversed all gains posted in 2023 and is trading in December 2022 territory.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/pU8dvUbm/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/pU8dvUbm/" alt="BNB Price On June 12| Source: BNBUSDT On Binance, TradingView" width="1225" height="595"/></a>
<p>With the SEC cracking the whip, laying down allegations against cryptocurrency exchanges and individual protocols, their respective tokens would likely be under pressure as holders exit.  </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Binance-Terms-of-Service-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>MATIC Price Displays Recovery But Can Bulls Sustain The $0.50 Support?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/matic/matic-price-displays-recovery-but-can-bulls-sustain-the-0-50-support/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 21:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATICUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[maticusdt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537529</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Over the past 24 hours, the Polygon (MATIC) price has shown attempts to reverse its downward movement. The altcoin has regained more than 4% of its value during this time. However, on the weekly chart, MATIC has experienced a decline of over 27%, causing it to breach important support levels. The technical analysis of MATIC indicates a prevailing bearish sentiment in the market, with low levels of demand and accumulation. The volatility of Bitcoin has influenced the price action of altcoins, including MATIC, which have struggled to maintain support levels. Related Reading: Cardano Price Falls Below Key Support Levels, Will It Continue To Fall? A significant return of buying strength is needed for MATIC to surpass immediate resistance. Additionally, the overall strength of the broader market, particularly Bitcoin, will impact MATIC and other altcoins. The decrease in market capitalization for MATIC indicates lower buying activity for the coin. MATIC Price Analysis: One-Day Chart At the time of writing, the altcoin price was $0.64. The bulls have managed to defend the support level at $0.60 but sustained low demand could pose challenges for them to maintain it. The immediate resistance level is at $0.67; if surpassed, another resistance may be encountered at $0.73. On the other hand, if the price falls from $0.64, the bears could gain control, causing the altcoin to trade below $0.60. Failure to stay above the $0.60 level in upcoming trading sessions could push MATIC below $0.50. The trading volume for the altcoin in the previous session has declined, indicating stronger selling pressure in the market. Technical Analysis Investor confidence in MATIC has waned since June following its rejection at the $0.76 level. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) indicates that the coin is currently oversold and undervalued, with the RSI falling below both the half-line and the 30-mark. Moreover, the price has dipped below the 20-Simple Moving Average line, indicating low demand and the dominance of sellers in driving the price momentum. To see a resurgence in demand, MATIC must trade above the $0.70 price. This level becomes crucial for the coin to attract buyers and potentially reverse the current bearish sentiment. Aligning with the bearish sentiments observed in other technical indicators, the Directional Movement Index (DMI) confirms the negative price direction of an altcoin. The -DI line (orange) was positioned above the +DI line (blue), indicating a prevailing downward trend. Related Reading: Bitcoin Bearish Signal: Miners Sell At 3rd Largest Scale Ever Additionally, the Chaikin Money Flow (CMF), which tracks capital inflows and outflows, was below the half-line. This signifies that capital outflows outweighed inflows at the time, indicating a decrease in buying pressure. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Over the past 24 hours, the Polygon (MATIC) price has shown attempts to reverse its downward movement. The altcoin has regained more than 4% of its value during this time. However, on the weekly chart, MATIC has experienced a decline of over 27%, causing it to breach important support levels.</p>
<p>The technical analysis of MATIC indicates a prevailing bearish sentiment in the market, with low levels of demand and accumulation. The volatility of Bitcoin has influenced the price action of altcoins, including MATIC, which have struggled to maintain support levels.</p>

<p>A significant return of buying strength is needed for MATIC to surpass immediate resistance. Additionally, the overall strength of the broader market, particularly Bitcoin, will impact MATIC and other altcoins. The decrease in market capitalization for MATIC indicates lower buying activity for the coin.</p>
<h2>MATIC Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-537542 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-12_19-57-40.png" alt="MATIC" width="1816" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-12_19-57-40.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-12_19-57-40-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-12_19-57-40-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-12_19-57-40-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-12_19-57-40-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-12_19-57-40-750x343.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-12_19-57-40-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>
<p>At the time of writing, the altcoin price was $0.64. The bulls have managed to defend the support level at $0.60 but sustained low demand could pose challenges for them to maintain it. The immediate resistance level is at $0.67; if surpassed, another resistance may be encountered at $0.73.</p>
<p>On the other hand, if the price falls from $0.64, the bears could gain control, causing the altcoin to trade below $0.60. Failure to stay above the $0.60 level in upcoming trading sessions could push MATIC below $0.50. The trading volume for the altcoin in the previous session has declined, indicating stronger selling pressure in the market.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-537551 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-12_19-58-49.png" alt="MATIC" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-12_19-58-49.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-12_19-58-49-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-12_19-58-49-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-12_19-58-49-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-12_19-58-49-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-12_19-58-49-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-12_19-58-49-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>
<p>Investor confidence in MATIC has waned since June following its rejection at the $0.76 level. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) indicates that the coin is currently oversold and undervalued, with the RSI falling below both the half-line and the 30-mark.</p>
<p>Moreover, the price has dipped below the 20-Simple Moving Average line, indicating low demand and the dominance of sellers in driving the price momentum.</p>
<p>To see a resurgence in demand, MATIC must trade above the $0.70 price. This level becomes crucial for the coin to attract buyers and potentially reverse the current bearish sentiment.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-537552 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-12_19-59-16.png" alt="MATIC" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-12_19-59-16.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-12_19-59-16-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-12_19-59-16-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-12_19-59-16-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-12_19-59-16-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-12_19-59-16-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSD_2023-06-12_19-59-16-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>
<p>Aligning with the bearish sentiments observed in other technical indicators, the Directional Movement Index (DMI) confirms the negative price direction of an altcoin. The -DI line (orange) was positioned above the +DI line (blue), indicating a prevailing downward trend.</p>

<p>Additionally, the Chaikin Money Flow (CMF), which tracks capital inflows and outflows, was below the half-line. This signifies that capital outflows outweighed inflows at the time, indicating a decrease in buying pressure.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shubham-s-web3-D8lZhEXeWgM-unsplash-2-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Forms Weekly Golden Cross, But Is It Enough To Save Crypto?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-price-golden-cross-enough-save-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 19:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethbtc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusdc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[golden cross]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[moving averages]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=537593</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Despite the carnage and chaos all across the crypto market due to recent US SEC-related enforcement actions, Ethereum has just given a bullish buy signal. On weekly timeframes, ETHUSD has formed a golden cross, but will it be enough to give the asset class a glimmer of hope amidst such darkness? Let&#8217;s take a closer look. Ethereum Price Golden Cross Buy Signal Forms On Weekly Chart Ethereum prices are down roughly 20% off 2023 highs, but still down more than 60% from the record peak back in 2021. Hope for a recovery across the crypto market dwindled last week, when the United States SEC launched enforcement actions against an already weakened industry. Related Reading: Bitcoin Retests Moving Average That Marked All Major Market Bottoms Other coins have plummeted by 50% or more in just days, while Bitcoin and Ethereum have shown resilience as the two top cryptocurrencies by market cap. ETHUSD has done so well in the recently bearish environment, in fact, is has formed a golden cross of the 50-week moving average and the 200-week moving average. The golden cross comes almost immediately after a death cross, nullifying a long-term sell signal with a buy signal. When using a two-moving average system, a buy signal occurs when the shorter timeframe crosses the longer timeframe span. This is called a golden cross, while the opposite crossover is called a death cross. A golden cross appears &#124; ETHUSD on TradingView.com Will The Moving Averages Save Crypto From Further Collapse? When using moving averages as a trading signal, in addition to crossovers, price making it above or below the averages is another signal a trend is strengthening. ETHUSD is also well above both the 50- and 200-week MAs. Finally, the slope of the moving averages can be used similarly to a trend line. The 200-week moving average is still pointed in an upward trajectory. Meanwhile, the 50-week is just starting to turn direction upward. Related Reading: Rare Crypto Signal Emerges That Could Spark Another 2017-Style Boom The last time the golden cross appeared, Ethereum climbed another 680% before its peak. In contrast, the last time ETHUSD pushed above both moving averages in 2020, Ether rallied by more than 1,700%. Current price action has only brought Ethereum under 5% from the moment it made it above the two averages. Past performance is not a guarantee of future results. Plus, considering the macro and regulatory pressure on altcoins, another death cross could follow any day now. However, of ETHUSD can remain above the two averages, another impressive price increase could be around the corner. With all the noise in the market right now, everyone has entirely missed the fact #Ethereum has formed a weekly golden cross pic.twitter.com/ylNwp3DEUI — Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221; (@tonythebullBTC) June 12, 2023 Tony is the author of the CoinChartist (VIP) newsletter. Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter. Or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite the carnage and chaos all across the crypto market due to recent US SEC-related enforcement actions, Ethereum has just given a bullish buy signal.</p>
<p>On weekly timeframes, ETHUSD has formed a golden cross, but will it be enough to give the asset class a glimmer of hope amidst such darkness? Let&#8217;s take a closer look.</p>
<h2>Ethereum Price Golden Cross Buy Signal Forms On Weekly Chart</h2>
<p>Ethereum prices are down roughly 20% off 2023 highs, but still down more than 60% from the record peak back in 2021. Hope for a recovery across the crypto market dwindled last week, when the United States SEC launched enforcement actions against an already weakened industry.</p>

<p>Other coins have plummeted by 50% or more in just days, while Bitcoin and Ethereum have shown resilience as the two top cryptocurrencies by market cap. ETHUSD has done so well in the recently bearish environment, in fact, is has formed a golden cross of the 50-week moving average and the 200-week moving average.</p>
<p>The golden cross comes almost immediately after a death cross, nullifying a long-term sell signal with a buy signal. When using a two-moving average system, a buy signal occurs when the shorter timeframe crosses the longer timeframe span. This is called a golden cross, while the opposite crossover is called a death cross.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-537594 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSD_2023-06-12_14-52-50-860x408.png" alt="ETHUSD_2023-06-12_14-52-50" width="860" height="408" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSD_2023-06-12_14-52-50-860x408.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSD_2023-06-12_14-52-50-460x218.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSD_2023-06-12_14-52-50-768x364.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSD_2023-06-12_14-52-50-1536x729.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSD_2023-06-12_14-52-50-2048x972.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSD_2023-06-12_14-52-50-750x356.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSD_2023-06-12_14-52-50-1140x541.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<h2>Will The Moving Averages Save Crypto From Further Collapse?</h2>
<p>When using moving averages as a trading signal, in addition to crossovers, price making it above or below the averages is another signal a trend is strengthening. ETHUSD is also well above both the 50- and 200-week MAs.</p>
<p>Finally, the slope of the moving averages can be used similarly to a trend line. The 200-week moving average is still pointed in an upward trajectory. Meanwhile, the 50-week is just starting to turn direction upward.</p>

<p>The last time the golden cross appeared, Ethereum climbed another 680% before its peak. In contrast, the last time ETHUSD pushed above both moving averages in 2020, Ether rallied by more than 1,700%. Current price action has only brought Ethereum under 5% from the moment it made it above the two averages.</p>
<p>Past performance is not a guarantee of future results. Plus, considering the macro and regulatory pressure on altcoins, another death cross could follow any day now. However, of ETHUSD can remain above the two averages, another impressive price increase could be around the corner.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">With all the noise in the market right now, everyone has entirely missed the fact <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Ethereum?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Ethereum</a> has formed a weekly golden cross <a href="https://t.co/ylNwp3DEUI" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/ylNwp3DEUI</a></p>
<p>— Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221; (@tonythebullBTC) <a href="https://twitter.com/tonythebullBTC/status/1668332848011702272?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 12, 2023</a></p></blockquote>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1492895580-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
