<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 19:49:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Stablecoin TrueUSD To Be Fully Controlled By Asian Owner</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/stablecoin/stablecoin-trueusd-to-be-fully-controlled-by-asian-owner/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 02:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Archblock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trueusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542747</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Featured Image From Kraken, Chart From Tradingview. In today&#8217;s news, the prominent stablecoin TrueUSD &#8211; with the ticker TUSD &#8211; is now undergoing a management change.  According to a thread this morning by the project’s official Twitter handle, Archblock Inc., the current TUSD operator, has begun the transfer of total control of Token to its Asian-based owners, Techteryx Ltd.  Techteryx Finally Assumes Control Of TrueUSD Back in December 2020, Techteryx acquired ownership of TUSD but hired Archblock to keep maintaining the stablecoin’s operations. And for the last two years in which Archblock remained TUSD’s operator, Techteryx claims to have been focusing on expanding the token’s foreign use cases in the global markets.  Related Reading: BUSD Market Cap Plunge Of 80% Raises Concerns Of Impending Collapse However, Archblock has now commenced the transfer of control yesterday, July 13, marking the end phase of TUSD’s international transition. Upon completion, Techteryx will reportedly assume full management of all aspects of the stablecoin’s operation. These controls will include mining and redemptions, customer onboarding and compliance, conservation of fiat reserve, and maintenance of banking and fiduciary relationships. During the transition period, Archblock will continue to support the US-based TUSD users, with Techteryx stepping in with the necessary guidance and further updates.  Prior to today&#8217;s news, TUSD has attracted some interest especially following Binance&#8217;s recent moves with the stablecoin. On June 21, the cryptocurrency exchange announced the launch of a TUSD zero-maker fee promotion for spot and margin trading pairs beginning from June 30. Interestingly, Binance had minted $1 billion worth of TUSD on the Tron network a week before making that announcement becoming the largest holder of the token. Related Reading: Stablecoin Market Share Dwindles As USDC And BUSD Supply Deplete At the time of writing, Ethercscan data shows that Binance accounts for over 68% of TUSD&#8217;s circulating supply, estimated at $1.92 billion. With a market cap value of $2.8 billion, TrueUSD currently ranks as the 5th largest stablecoin and 27th largest cryptocurrency, according to data by Coingecko.  TUSD Valued At $0.99 On The 4-Hour Chart &#124; Source: TUSDUSD Chart On Tradingview.com The Stablecoin Market In 2023 Stablecoins are considered a vital part of the crypto space, especially due to their constant value, allowing traders and investors to avoid the volatility of the crypto market.  According to data from DeFi ilLama, the stablecoin market has been on the decline all year, with its total market cap shrinking from $137.79 billion on January 1 to its current value of $126.96 billion, accounting for 9.86% of the total crypto market.  Related Reading: Stablecoin Sharks &#38; Whales Show Strong Accumulation, Good Sign For Bitcoin? Unsurprisingly, Tether USDT (USDT) has remained the leader of the pack, with a market cap of $83.5 billion, with Circle’s USDCoin (USDC) following with a market cap of $27.08 billion. Following the regulatory embargo that halted its issuance in February, Binance USD (BUSD) &#8211; with a market cap of 3.99 billion &#8211; lost over 75% of its market share, slipping to fourth place behind the DAI stablecoin, which currently boasts a market cap of $4.28 billion.  Featured Image From Kraken, Chart From Tradingview.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In today&#8217;s news, the prominent stablecoin TrueUSD &#8211; with the ticker TUSD &#8211; is now undergoing a management change.  According to a <a href="https://twitter.com/tusdio/status/1679712914050289665?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">thread this morning</a> by the project’s official Twitter handle, Archblock Inc., the current TUSD operator, has begun the transfer of total control of Token to its Asian-based owners, Techteryx Ltd. </p>
<h2>Techteryx Finally Assumes Control Of TrueUSD</h2>
<p>Back in December 2020, Techteryx <a href="https://trueusd.medium.com/scaling-trust-announcing-tusds-next-stage-of-growth-f1fb58d62b" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">acquired</a> ownership of TUSD but hired Archblock to keep maintaining the stablecoin’s operations. And for the last two years in which Archblock remained TUSD’s operator, Techteryx claims to have been focusing on expanding the token’s foreign use cases in the global markets. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/busd-market-cap-plunge-of-80-in-2023-raises-concerns-of-impending-collapse/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">BUSD Market Cap Plunge Of 80% Raises Concerns Of Impending Collapse</a></p>
<p>However, Archblock has now commenced the transfer of control yesterday, July 13, marking the end phase of TUSD’s international transition. Upon completion, Techteryx will reportedly assume full management of all aspects of the stablecoin’s operation.</p>
<p>These controls will include mining and redemptions, customer onboarding and compliance, conservation of fiat reserve, and maintenance of banking and fiduciary relationships.</p>
<p>During the transition period, Archblock will continue to support the US-based TUSD users, with Techteryx stepping in with the necessary guidance and further updates. </p>
<p>Prior to today&#8217;s news, TUSD has attracted some interest especially following Binance&#8217;s recent moves with the stablecoin. On June 21, the cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/binance-launches-tusd-zero-maker-fee-promotion-and-updates-fee-promotions-for-busd-usd-stablecoin-pairs-a376bf14673044e0a1fae8fe60cb0700" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced</a> the launch of a TUSD zero-maker fee promotion for spot and margin trading pairs beginning from June 30.</p>
<p>Interestingly, Binance <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1669306467520851969?s=46&amp;t=JAUmthpFclo8jS4VJkm3DQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">had minted</a> $1 billion worth of TUSD on the Tron network a week before making that announcement becoming the largest holder of the token.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/stablecoin-market-share-dwindles-as-usdc-and-busd-supply-deplete/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Stablecoin Market Share Dwindles As USDC And BUSD Supply Deplete</a></p>
<p>At the time of writing, <a href="https://etherscan.io/token/0x0000000000085d4780B73119b644AE5ecd22b376#balances" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Ethercscan data</a> shows that Binance accounts for over 68% of TUSD&#8217;s circulating supply, estimated at $1.92 billion. With a market cap value of $2.8 billion, TrueUSD currently ranks as the 5th largest stablecoin and 27th largest cryptocurrency, according to data by Coingecko. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/VzSW05zF/" alt="Stablecoin" width="1480" height="913"/>

<h2>The Stablecoin Market In 2023</h2>
<p>Stablecoins are considered a vital part of the crypto space, especially due to their constant value, allowing traders and investors to avoid the volatility of the crypto market. </p>
<p>According to <a href="https://defillama.com/stablecoins" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from DeFi ilLama</a>, the stablecoin market has been on the decline all year, with its total market cap shrinking from $137.79 billion on January 1 to its current value of $126.96 billion, accounting for 9.86% of the total crypto market. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/stablecoin-shark-whales-strong-accumulation-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Stablecoin Sharks &amp; Whales Show Strong Accumulation, Good Sign For Bitcoin?</a></p>
<p>Unsurprisingly, Tether USDT (USDT) has remained the leader of the pack, with a market cap of $83.5 billion, with Circle’s USDCoin (USDC) following with a market cap of $27.08 billion.</p>
<p>Following the regulatory embargo that halted its issuance in February, Binance USD (BUSD) &#8211; with a market cap of 3.99 billion &#8211; lost over 75% of its market share, slipping to fourth place behind the DAI stablecoin, which currently boasts a market cap of $4.28 billion. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/NewNetwork_TUSD_TRON_BlogInner-460x210.png" width="460" height="210" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Ripple&#8217;s Victory Against The SEC May Be Short-Lived: Legal Expert</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/ripple-victory-against-the-sec-may-be-short-lived/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 22:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542840</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The news of Ripple&#8217;s recent partial victory against the SEC after a legal battle spanning almost three years sent a ripple of joy around the entire crypto industry. However, according to a legal expert on Twitter, Lawyer Bryan Jacoutot, the victory might be short-lived as SEC has enough grounds to appeal the decision and drag this thing out for a lot longer. The SEC&#8217;s Lawsuit Against Ripple Labs The SEC filed a lawsuit against Ripple Labs in December 2020, alleging that Ripple had conducted an unregistered securities offering worth over $1.3 billion through the sale of XRP. According to the SEC, XRP is a security under federal securities laws. But the court determined on June 13 that the random &#8220;programmatic sale&#8221; of XRP to regular investors does not constitute the sale of an unregistered security under Howey.  Related Reading: Large Exchanges Relist XRP Following Ripple Victory Over SEC However, sales to institutional investors fall under Howey, which is used in the United States to determine whether a transaction qualifies as an investment contract. In this case, the Court found that the buyers couldn&#8217;t know who was selling them the XRP, unlike the institutional investors who would expect Ripple Labs to use the capital for the betterment of the Ripple ecosystem. According to Jacoutot, the Court&#8217;s reasoning is weak and Howey was misapplied in the case. The Court reasoned that regular investors bought XRP fully knowing that it is subject to the general cryptocurrency market trends, especially secondary sales of XRP tokens. However, Jacoutot believes those buying XRP would have also expected to make a profit from the efforts of Ripple Labs. XRP price at $0.7254 &#124; Source: XRPUSD on Tradingview.com The attorney also made a case of the Ethereum Foundation, as everyone who took part in the pre-sale of ETH knew they were buying from Ethereum Foundation. When looking at the XRP ruling in a similar manner, this would mean institutional investors of the ETH presale also bought unregistered securities. What Does The Ruling Mean? According to Jacoutot, the ruling opens up a few loopholes that can be exploited. In a tweet by attorney Joe Carlasare on Twitter, it explains that the logic of the ruling leaves an opening that can be used to lawfully launch a pyramid scheme. In this case, profits from the &#8220;programmatic sales&#8221; to retail investors can be distributed to institutional investors. Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse has said the ruling provided relief and that the company could now promote the various use cases for Ripple and its technology without worrying about legal repercussions. Related Reading: XRP Kicks Out BNB To Become 4th-Largest Crypto After 65% Rally This is definitely a win for Ripple, but an appeal by the SEC could drag out the legal battle for years and create another round of major uncertainty in the crypto market.  The price of XRP skyrocketed after the ruling. It is now up by 50% this month and is currently trading at $0.7154. Featured image from Bit2Me Academy, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The news of Ripple&#8217;s recent partial victory against the SEC after a legal battle spanning almost three years sent a ripple of joy around the entire crypto industry. However, <a href="https://twitter.com/BryanJacoutot/status/1679539621724577809?s=20" rel="nofollow">according </a>to a legal expert on Twitter, Lawyer Bryan Jacoutot, the victory might be short-lived as SEC has enough grounds to appeal the decision and drag this thing out for a lot longer.</p>
<h2>The SEC&#8217;s Lawsuit Against Ripple Labs</h2>
<p>The SEC filed a lawsuit against Ripple Labs in December 2020, alleging that Ripple had conducted an unregistered securities offering worth over $1.3 billion through the sale of XRP. According to the SEC, XRP is a security under federal securities laws. But the court determined on June 13 that the random &#8220;programmatic sale&#8221; of XRP to regular investors does not constitute the sale of an unregistered security under Howey. </p>

<p>However, sales to institutional investors fall under Howey, which is used in the United States to determine whether a transaction qualifies as an investment contract. In this case, the Court found that the buyers couldn&#8217;t know who was selling them the XRP, unlike the institutional investors who would expect Ripple Labs to use the capital for the betterment of the Ripple ecosystem.</p>
<p>According to Jacoutot, the Court&#8217;s reasoning is weak and Howey was misapplied in the case. The Court reasoned that regular investors bought XRP fully knowing that it is subject to the general cryptocurrency market trends, especially secondary sales of XRP tokens. However, Jacoutot believes those buying XRP would have also expected to make a profit from the efforts of Ripple Labs.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/g2KmUHw5/" alt="Ripple (XRP) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>

<p>The attorney also made a <a href="https://twitter.com/BryanJacoutot/status/1679539633674149902?s=20" rel="nofollow">case </a>of the Ethereum Foundation, as everyone who took part in the pre-sale of ETH knew they were buying from Ethereum Foundation. When looking at the XRP ruling in a similar manner, this would mean institutional investors of the ETH presale also bought unregistered securities.</p>
<h2>What Does The Ruling Mean?</h2>
<p>According to Jacoutot, the ruling opens up a few loopholes that can be exploited. In a <a href="https://twitter.com/JoeCarlasare/status/1680244269519368193?s=20" rel="nofollow">tweet </a>by attorney Joe Carlasare on Twitter, it explains that the logic of the ruling leaves an opening that can be used to lawfully launch a pyramid scheme. In this case, profits from the &#8220;programmatic sales&#8221; to retail investors can be distributed to institutional investors.</p>
<p>Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse has <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-ceo-takes-on-sec-calls-them-a-bully/" rel="nofollow">said </a>the ruling provided relief and that the company could now promote the various use cases for Ripple and its technology without worrying about legal repercussions.</p>

<p>This is definitely a win for Ripple, but an appeal by the SEC could drag out the legal battle for years and create another round of major uncertainty in the crypto market. </p>
<p>The price of XRP skyrocketed after the ruling. It is now up by 50% this month and is currently trading at $0.7154.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ripple-XRP-460x250.jpeg" width="460" height="250" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ark Invest Sells Over $50 Million Worth of Coinbase Shares Amidst Stock Rally</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/ark-invest-sells-coinbase-shares/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 19:35:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ark invest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[COIN stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542838</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cathie Wood&#8217;s investment firm, Ark Invest, has made significant moves in its holdings of Coinbase shares, selling over $50 million worth of shares as the cryptocurrency exchange&#8217;s stock continues to surge.  This marked the second time in a week that Ark Invest reduced its stake in Coinbase, reflecting its active management approach amid a backdrop of regulatory developments and industry optimism. At the same time, Ark Invest has been actively investing in other notable companies, including Meta Platforms and Robinhood.  Ark Invest Cashes In on Coinbase Rally Ark Invest, led by Cathie Wood, sold a total of 478,356 shares of Coinbase on Friday, amounting to more than $50 million. The sales were spread across Ark&#8217;s flagship fund, Ark Innovation ETF, which sold 263,247 shares, Ark Next Generation Internet ETF, which sold 93,227 shares, and Ark Fintech Innovation ETF, which offloaded 121,882 shares.  Related Reading: XRP Kicks Out BNB To Become 4th-Largest Crypto After 65% Rally This decision comes on the heels of Coinbase&#8217;s role as a surveillance-sharing partner for several spot Bitcoin ETF applicants, including industry giants BlackRock and Fidelity. Furthermore, recent legal rulings surrounding the status of the cryptocurrency XRP have added to the overall industry optimism. However, despite the sales, Ark Invest remains the second-largest owner of Coinbase shares, holding a 6.30% stake.  Ark Invest offloads shares as price recovers &#124; Source: Coinbase Global, Inc., on Tradingview.com Looking To The Future With Meta Platforms and Robinhood While reducing its Coinbase holdings, Ark Invest has also been actively investing in other crypto-adjacent companies. The firm initiated purchases of shares in Meta Platforms (formerly Facebook) and Robinhood. In June, Ark Innovation ETF acquired 69,793 Meta shares, while Ark Fintech Innovation ETF purchased 111,843 shares of Robinhood.  Additionally, the Ark Next Generation Internet ETF increased its holdings with 12,559 Meta shares and 169,116 Robinhood shares. These strategic investments reflect Ark Invest&#8217;s ongoing strategy to navigate the evolving digital asset market. Ark Invest&#8217;s decision to trim its Coinbase holdings after significant acquisitions during market volatility and regulatory challenges demonstrates a calculated approach to secure profits amid the stock&#8217;s impressive rally this year and indicates a calculated effort to secure profits during the stock&#8217;s rally. Related Reading: Large Exchanges Relist XRP Following Ripple Victory Over SEC Also, it demonstrates the firm&#8217;s commitment to diversifying its portfolio for long-term growth potential, as evidenced by its investments in Meta Platforms and Robinhood.  As the crypto market continues to evolve, Ark Invest&#8217;s actions will be closely watched by market participants, looking for insights and guidance in navigating this dynamic landscape. Featured image from Crypto News, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cathie Wood&#8217;s investment firm, Ark Invest, has made significant moves in its holdings of Coinbase shares, selling over $50 million worth of shares as the cryptocurrency exchange&#8217;s stock continues to surge. </p>
<p>This marked the second time in a week that Ark Invest reduced its stake in Coinbase, reflecting its active management approach amid a backdrop of regulatory developments and industry optimism.</p>
<p>At the same time, Ark Invest has been actively investing in other notable companies, including Meta Platforms and Robinhood. </p>
<h2>Ark Invest Cashes In on Coinbase Rally</h2>
<p>Ark Invest, led by Cathie Wood, <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/239769/ark-invest-coinbase-sells-cathie-wood" rel="nofollow">sold</a> a total of 478,356 shares of Coinbase on Friday, amounting to more than $50 million. The sales were spread across Ark&#8217;s flagship fund, Ark Innovation ETF, which sold 263,247 shares, Ark Next Generation Internet ETF, which sold 93,227 shares, and Ark Fintech Innovation ETF, which offloaded 121,882 shares. </p>

<p>This decision comes on the heels of Coinbase&#8217;s role as a surveillance-sharing partner for several spot Bitcoin ETF applicants, including industry giants BlackRock and Fidelity. Furthermore, recent legal rulings surrounding the status of the cryptocurrency XRP have added to the overall industry optimism.</p>
<p>However, despite the sales, Ark Invest remains the second-largest owner of Coinbase shares, holding a 6.30% stake. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/8M0TU0cc/" alt="Coinbase (COIN) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>

<h2>Looking To The Future With Meta Platforms and Robinhood</h2>
<p>While reducing its Coinbase holdings, Ark Invest has also been actively investing in other crypto-adjacent companies. The firm initiated purchases of shares in Meta Platforms (formerly Facebook) and Robinhood. In June, Ark Innovation ETF acquired 69,793 Meta shares, while Ark Fintech Innovation ETF purchased 111,843 shares of Robinhood. </p>
<p>Additionally, the Ark Next Generation Internet ETF increased its holdings with 12,559 Meta shares and 169,116 Robinhood shares. These strategic investments reflect Ark Invest&#8217;s ongoing strategy to navigate the evolving digital asset market.</p>
<p>Ark Invest&#8217;s decision to trim its Coinbase holdings after significant acquisitions during market volatility and regulatory challenges demonstrates a calculated approach to secure profits amid the stock&#8217;s impressive rally this year and indicates a calculated effort to secure profits during the stock&#8217;s rally.</p>

<p>Also, it demonstrates the firm&#8217;s commitment to diversifying its portfolio for long-term growth potential, as evidenced by its investments in Meta Platforms and Robinhood. </p>
<p>As the crypto market continues to evolve, Ark Invest&#8217;s actions will be closely watched by market participants, looking for insights and guidance in navigating this dynamic landscape.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ark-Invest-Coinbase-460x309.jpeg" width="460" height="309" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Engagement Fails To Impress, Raising Concerns About Broader Interest</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin-engagement-fails-to-impress/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 11:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doge price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542819</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Is Dogecoin (DOGE losing its charm? Despite the impressive price rally in May, recent trends suggest a decline in engagement and investor interest. As the crypto market continues to evolve, concerns are mounting about the broader implications of Dogecoin&#8217;s waning appeal.  Dogecoin&#8217;s engagement metrics have faltered, leaving some experts wondering if the crypto&#8217;s allure is wearing off. Market indicators show a decline in trading volume, with fewer transactions taking place compared to previous months.  Will this once-beloved digital currency be able to regain its momentum, or is its star beginning to fade? Dogecoin New Addresses Stagnant The growth of new addresses joining the Dogecoin community has hit a roadblock since May, according to a recent DOGE price report. However, on-chain data analysis reveals that this stagnation in new holders has not adversely affected the weighted sentiment associated with the cryptocurrency. Related Reading: BNB Chain Inks New Record With Soaring User Activity – A Boost For Price? Source: Santiment As of the latest update, DOGE&#8217;s weighted sentiment stands at -0.645. This metric provides insights into the average sentiment attached to a particular cryptocurrency, taking into account the unique social volume surrounding it. Interestingly, despite the somewhat negative value, the weighted sentiment has shown improvement from its low point of -1.99 on June 9. This shift suggests that the prevailing defeatist perception during that period has gradually shifted towards a more optimistic outlook. DOGE market cap slightly above the $10 billion level. Chart: TradingView.com Social Volume And Holder Count: A Diverging Trend However, while the weighted sentiment demonstrates a positive trajectory, the coin&#8217;s social volume tells a different story. Instead of aligning with the stagnant number of holders, the social volume of Dogecoin has remained remarkably low since June 9, as per Santiment&#8217;s data. Social volume measures the number of mentions and discussions specifically related to a cryptocurrency across various platforms. In the case of Dogecoin, this metric indicates a significant decrease in overall online activity and conversations surrounding the coin. Related Reading: Cardano Development Activity Dropping – What Does It Mean For ADA Price? As of now, there have been no significant changes in the aforementioned trends. This suggests that the hype surrounding DOGE has diminished considerably. From a market perspective, this could potentially indicate that the coin is undervalued and has yet to reach its peak valuation. The road ahead for Dogecoin appears challenging, as the cryptocurrency grapples with stagnant new addresses and a decline in social volume. However, it would be premature to discount the resilience of this meme-based digital asset. Source: Coingecko As of the latest data from Coingecko, the price of DOGE stands at $0.068, reflecting a decline of 4.7% over the past 24 hours. However, despite this recent dip, Dogecoin has experienced a seven-day rally of 4.6%, showing signs of resilience in the face of short-term fluctuations. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Terminix]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is Dogecoin (DOGE losing its charm? Despite the impressive price rally in May, recent trends suggest a decline in engagement and investor interest. As the crypto market continues to evolve, concerns are mounting about the broader implications of Dogecoin&#8217;s waning appeal. </p>
<p>Dogecoin&#8217;s engagement metrics have faltered, leaving some experts wondering if the crypto&#8217;s allure is wearing off. Market indicators show a decline in trading volume, with fewer transactions taking place compared to previous months. </p>
<p>Will this once-beloved digital currency be able to regain its momentum, or is its star beginning to fade?</p>
<h2><strong>Dogecoin New Addresses Stagnant</strong></h2>
<p>The growth of new addresses joining the Dogecoin community has hit a roadblock since May, according to a recent <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/why-dogecoins-soaring-numbers-hit-a-snag/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">DOGE price report</a>. However, on-chain data analysis reveals that this stagnation in new holders has not adversely affected the weighted sentiment associated with the cryptocurrency.</p>

<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-542823 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-96-860x292.png" alt="" width="860" height="292" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-96-860x292.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-96-460x156.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-96-768x261.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-96-1536x522.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-96-750x255.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-96-1140x387.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-96.png 1543w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>As of the latest update, DOGE&#8217;s weighted sentiment stands at -0.645. This metric provides insights into the average sentiment attached to a particular cryptocurrency, taking into account the unique social volume surrounding it.</p>
<p>Interestingly, despite the somewhat negative value, the weighted sentiment has shown improvement from its low point of -1.99 on June 9. This shift suggests that the prevailing defeatist perception during that period has gradually shifted towards a more optimistic outlook.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/jByEe3iV/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>

<h2><strong>Social Volume And Holder Count: A Diverging Trend</strong></h2>
<p>However, while the weighted sentiment demonstrates a positive trajectory, the coin&#8217;s social volume tells a different story. Instead of aligning with the stagnant number of holders, the social volume of Dogecoin has remained remarkably low since June 9, as per Santiment&#8217;s data.</p>
<p>Social volume measures the number of mentions and discussions specifically related to a cryptocurrency across various platforms. In the case of Dogecoin, this metric indicates a significant decrease in overall online activity and conversations surrounding the coin.</p>

<p>As of now, there have been no significant changes in the aforementioned trends. This suggests that the hype surrounding DOGE has diminished considerably. From a market perspective, this could potentially indicate that the coin is undervalued and has yet to reach its peak valuation.</p>
<p>The road ahead for Dogecoin appears challenging, as the cryptocurrency grapples with stagnant new addresses and a decline in social volume. However, it would be premature to discount the resilience of this meme-based digital asset.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-542820" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-95.png" alt="" width="945" height="69" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-95.png 945w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-95-460x34.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-95-860x63.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-95-768x56.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-95-750x55.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 945px) 100vw, 945px"/></p>

<p>As of the latest data from <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/dogecoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Coingecko</a>, the price of DOGE stands at $0.068, reflecting a decline of 4.7% over the past 24 hours. However, despite this recent dip, Dogecoin has experienced a seven-day rally of 4.6%, showing signs of resilience in the face of short-term fluctuations.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Terminix</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-97-460x315.png" width="460" height="315" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polygon (MATIC) Flexes Muscles In The Last Week With 27% Gain &#8211; Details</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/matic/polygon-matic-flexes-muscles-in-the-last-week-with-27-gain-details/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olowoporoku Adeniyi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 11:34:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Matic Network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon (MATIC)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542795</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Polygon (MATIC) has demonstrated a significant price surge in the past week, rising by 27.39%. This bullish momentum has been further reinforced by a 9.38% increase in the last 24 hours. However, in the most recent hour, the price experienced a slight decline of 1.04%. Currently trading at $0.84 per MATIC, the cryptocurrency remains 71.11% below its all-time high of $2.92. Reasons For The Price Movement Multiple factors have contributed to the recent price movement of the crypto. Firstly, a favorable court ruling for XRP ripple effect on market sentiment, potentially influencing the performance of other cryptocurrencies like MATIC. The court&#8217;s determination that XRP is not a security has provided investors reassurance and positively impacted the overall cryptocurrency market. Related Reading: PEPE Sees Sharp 17% Surge, But Will This Whale Spoil The Party? Furthermore, the increased activity of decentralized applications (Dapps) on the Polygon Network has significantly driven up demand for MATIC. The network&#8217;s reputation as a scalable and efficient solution for the Ethereum network has attracted numerous developers and users to build and interact with Dapps on the platform. This heightened interest in the Polygon Network has increased demand for MATIC tokens. Additionally, the highly anticipated launch of Polygon 2.0 has generated excitement within the community. This proposed upgrade aims to enhance the functionality and scalability of the Polygon Network, allowing for the support of multiple chains without compromising security. If successfully implemented, Polygon 2.0 could further solidify MATIC&#8217;s position as a leading blockchain solution, potentially attracting more investors and driving higher prices. Expectations For Polygon Looking ahead, Polygon holds promising prospects for further growth and development. With a total value locked (TVL) of $1 billion on the Polygon Network, the platform has established itself as a prominent second-layer scaling solution for Ethereum. The increasing TVL, which has grown from $878 million in the previous month, indicates a rising demand for Polygon&#8217;s processing capabilities and underscores its potential for further adoption and expansion. The impending launch of Polygon 2.0 adds a layer of anticipation. This upgrade will introduce new features and improvements, enhancing the network&#8217;s efficiency and functionality. If successfully implemented, Polygon 2.0 could attract even more users, developers, and investors, ultimately driving up the price of MATIC. However, it is essential to exercise caution and closely monitor the market. While the current price movement suggests positive momentum, competition from other scaling solutions, such as Arbirtrum (ARB) and Optimism (OP), should be considered. Additionally, developments in privacy implementations utilizing zero-knowledge proofs could introduce new dynamics to the market. Related Reading: XRP Explodes With 1,300% Surge In Trading Volume As crypto Exchanges Jump On Board Investors and traders should remain attentive to updates regarding the Polygon 2.0 upgrade, ongoing market trends, and any significant announcements within the cryptocurrency ecosystem that may impact the future performance of MATIC. By staying informed and exercising due diligence, market participants can make more informed decisions regarding their investments in Polygon. (This site’s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured Image from istock, chart from TradingView.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Polygon (MATIC) has demonstrated a significant price surge in the past week, rising by 27.39%. This bullish momentum has been further reinforced by a 9.38% increase in the last 24 hours. However, in the most recent hour, the price experienced a slight decline of 1.04%. Currently trading at $0.84 per MATIC, the cryptocurrency remains 71.11% below its all-time high of $2.92.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-542796 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image1-3-860x474.png" alt="Polygon (MATIC) has experienced an uptick in value this week: Source " width="860" height="474" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image1-3-860x474.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image1-3-460x253.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image1-3-768x423.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image1-3-750x413.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image1-3.png 1080w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<h2><strong>Reasons For The Price Movement</strong></h2>
<p>Multiple factors have contributed to the recent price movement of the crypto. Firstly, a favorable court ruling for XRP ripple effect on market sentiment, potentially influencing the performance of other cryptocurrencies like MATIC. The court&#8217;s determination that XRP is not a security has provided investors reassurance and positively impacted the overall cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p><b>Related Reading</b>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/pepe-sees-sharp-17-surge-but-whale-spoil-party/?swcfpc=1">PEPE Sees Sharp 17% Surge, But Will This Whale Spoil The Party?</a></p>
<p>Furthermore, the increased activity of decentralized applications (Dapps) on the Polygon Network has significantly driven up demand for MATIC. The network&#8217;s reputation as a scalable and efficient solution for the Ethereum network has attracted numerous developers and users to build and interact with Dapps on the platform. This heightened interest in the Polygon Network has increased demand for MATIC tokens.</p>
<p>Additionally, the highly anticipated launch of Polygon 2.0 has generated excitement within the community. This proposed upgrade aims to enhance the functionality and scalability of the Polygon Network, allowing for the support of multiple chains without compromising security. If successfully implemented, Polygon 2.0 could further solidify MATIC&#8217;s position as a leading blockchain solution, potentially attracting more investors and driving higher prices.</p>
<h2><strong>Expectations For Polygon</strong></h2>
<p>Looking ahead, Polygon holds promising prospects for further growth and development. With a total value locked (TVL) of $1 billion on the Polygon Network, the platform has established itself as a prominent second-layer scaling solution for Ethereum. The increasing TVL, which has grown from $878 million in the previous month, indicates a rising demand for Polygon&#8217;s processing capabilities and underscores its potential for further adoption and expansion.</p>
<p>The impending launch of Polygon 2.0 adds a layer of anticipation. This upgrade will introduce new features and improvements, enhancing the network&#8217;s efficiency and functionality. If successfully implemented, Polygon 2.0 could attract even more users, developers, and investors, ultimately driving up the price of MATIC.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-542797" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image2-1-460x265.png" alt="Polygon ecosystem have also enjoyed a bullish rise: source @coinstats" width="460" height="265" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image2-1-460x265.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image2-1.png 684w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/>
<p>However, it is essential to exercise caution and closely monitor the market. While the current price movement suggests positive momentum, competition from other scaling solutions, such as Arbirtrum (ARB) and Optimism (OP), should be considered. Additionally, developments in privacy implementations utilizing zero-knowledge proofs could introduce new dynamics to the market.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading</strong>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-explodes-with-1300-surge-in-trading-volume-as-crypto-exchanges-jump-on-board/?swcfpc=1">XRP Explodes With 1,300% Surge In Trading Volume As crypto Exchanges Jump On Board</a></p>
<p>Investors and traders should remain attentive to updates regarding the Polygon 2.0 upgrade, ongoing market trends, and any significant announcements within the cryptocurrency ecosystem that may impact the future performance of MATIC. By staying informed and exercising due diligence, market participants can make more informed decisions regarding their investments in Polygon.</p>
<p><i>(This site’s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</i></p>
<p><i>Featured Image from istock, chart from TradingView.</i></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1291935777-460x263.jpg" width="460" height="263" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BNB Chain Inks New Record With Soaring User Activity &#8211; A Boost For Price?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bnb-chain-enjoys-soaring-user-activity/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 09:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnb chain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542782</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[BNB Chain, the blockchain platform powering the Binance ecosystem, has recently emerged as a formidable force in the crypto world, surpassing its competitors in terms of daily active users. This surge in user engagement has coincided with a surge in the value of the BNB token, which has experienced a steady increase of over 5% within a single week.  As BNB&#8217;s daily active users continue to soar, one can&#8217;t help but question the overall impact of this unprecedented growth. What lies behind BNB&#8217;s ability to outshine its rivals and attract a growing user base? Is there a hidden catalyst propelling its value upwards?  Moreover, as these metrics diverge from the norm, skeptics begin to raise valid concerns about the sustainability and potential risks associated with BNB&#8217;s rise. BNB Chain Surpasses BTC, ETH In Daily Active Users In the ever-evolving landscape of blockchain technology, BNB Chain has recently achieved a significant milestone, surpassing renowned chains such as Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) in terms of daily user activity. According to a BNB analysis, the chain secured the second position, solidifying its position as a formidable player in the crypto world. Related Reading: Cardano Development Activity Dropping – What Does It Mean For ADA Price? Token Terminal&#8217;s data also revealed that BNB Chain boasts an impressive count of over 1 million daily active users, a testament to the platform&#8217;s growing popularity and appeal. This notable achievement is even more remarkable considering the longstanding dominance of Bitcoin and Ethereum, which have traditionally held the top positions in the cryptocurrency market. Source: Token Terminal The BNB token has also made waves in the market. Currently priced at $248.78, it experienced a slight setback with a 3.5% slump in the past 24 hours. However, the token quickly bounced back with a decent 5.4% increase in the last week. Source: CoinMarketCap Mixed Signals While the BNB Chain has garnered widespread enthusiasm and positioned itself as a competitive player in the crypto market, recent data from Santiment reveals a nuanced picture. Despite the chain&#8217;s impressive user base, as measured by daily active addresses, the level of excitement appears to be relatively consistent without any notable spikes, according to Santiment&#8217;s analysis. &#160; Source: Santiment Related Reading: Optimism (OP) Rides The Wave Of Today’s Crypto Surge With 15% Rally When examining the Total Value Locked (TVL) metric, which indicates the amount of assets held within a blockchain protocol, BNB Chain falls behind Ethereum and Tron, occupying the third position. As of the latest data, the TVL for BNB Chain stands at approximately $3.4 billion, highlighting room for growth in this area. Total cryptocurrencies market cap at $1.18 trillion. Chart: TradingView.com Similarly, the stablecoin market cap on the BNB Chain has exceeded $5 billion. However, Santiment&#8217;s charts indicate that both the TVL and market cap metrics have yet to exhibit a significant upward trend, despite the chain&#8217;s growing user base. This suggests that while BNB Chain boasts a higher number of active users, the overall TVL and market cap have not fully reflected this growth. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Gadgets 360]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BNB Chain, the blockchain platform powering the Binance ecosystem, has recently emerged as a formidable force in the crypto world, surpassing its competitors in terms of daily active users. This surge in user engagement has coincided with a surge in the value of the BNB token, which has experienced a steady increase of over 5% within a single week. </p>
<p>As BNB&#8217;s daily active users continue to soar, one can&#8217;t help but question the overall impact of this unprecedented growth. What lies behind BNB&#8217;s ability to outshine its rivals and attract a growing user base? Is there a hidden catalyst propelling its value upwards? </p>
<p>Moreover, as these metrics diverge from the norm, skeptics begin to raise valid concerns about the sustainability and potential risks associated with BNB&#8217;s rise.</p>
<h2><strong>BNB Chain Surpasses BTC, ETH In Daily Active Users</strong></h2>
<p>In the ever-evolving landscape of blockchain technology, BNB Chain has recently achieved a significant milestone, surpassing renowned chains such as Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) in terms of daily user activity. According to a <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/bnb-chain-impresses-in-daily-active-users-but/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BNB analysis</a>, the chain secured the second position, solidifying its position as a formidable player in the crypto world.</p>

<p><a href="https://twitter.com/tokenterminal/status/1679517145053425669" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Token Terminal&#8217;s data</a> also revealed that BNB Chain boasts an impressive count of over 1 million daily active users, a testament to the platform&#8217;s growing popularity and appeal. This notable achievement is even more remarkable considering the longstanding dominance of Bitcoin and Ethereum, which have traditionally held the top positions in the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-542811 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-91-860x646.png" alt="" width="860" height="646" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-91-860x646.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-91-460x346.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-91-768x577.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-91-750x563.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-91-1140x856.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-91.png 1194w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>The <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bnb/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BNB token</a> has also made waves in the market. Currently priced at $248.78, it experienced a slight setback with a 3.5% slump in the past 24 hours. However, the token quickly bounced back with a decent 5.4% increase in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-542808" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-90.png" alt="" width="941" height="70" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-90.png 941w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-90-460x34.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-90-860x64.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-90-768x57.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-90-750x56.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 941px) 100vw, 941px"/></p>

<h2><strong>Mixed Signals</strong></h2>
<p>While the BNB Chain has garnered widespread enthusiasm and positioned itself as a competitive player in the crypto market, recent data from Santiment reveals a nuanced picture. Despite the chain&#8217;s impressive user base, as measured by daily active addresses, the level of excitement appears to be relatively consistent without any notable spikes, according to <a href="https://embed.santiment.net/chart?ps=binance-coin&amp;pt=BNB&amp;df=2023-03-04T00%3A00%3A00.000Z&amp;emcg=1&amp;wm=daily_active_addresses%3Bprice_usd&amp;wax=0%3B1&amp;wc=%23FFAD4D%3B%2326C953&amp;ws=%3B%7B%22interval%22%3A%221d%22%7D" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Santiment&#8217;s analysis</a>.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-542814 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-93-860x294.png" alt="" width="860" height="294" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-93-860x294.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-93-460x157.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-93-768x262.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-93-1536x524.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-93-750x256.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-93-1140x389.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-93.png 1541w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>


<p>When examining the Total Value Locked (TVL) metric, which indicates the amount of assets held within a blockchain protocol, BNB Chain falls behind Ethereum and Tron, occupying the third position. As of the latest data, the TVL for BNB Chain stands at approximately $3.4 billion, highlighting room for growth in this area.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/PQnzVqrp/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>

<p>Similarly, the stablecoin market cap on the BNB Chain has exceeded $5 billion. However, Santiment&#8217;s charts indicate that both the TVL and market cap metrics have yet to exhibit a significant upward trend, despite the chain&#8217;s growing user base. This suggests that while BNB Chain boasts a higher number of active users, the overall TVL and market cap have not fully reflected this growth.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Gadgets 360</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-94-460x212.png" width="460" height="212" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>AVAX Tallies 23% In The Past Week, Buyers Accumulate For Potential Breakout</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/avalanche/avax-tallies-23-in-past-week/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olowoporoku Adeniyi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 07:21:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Avalanche]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542792</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Avalanche (AVAX), the native token of the Avalanche blockchain, has witnessed a notable price surge of 27.39% over the past seven days, capturing the attention of traders and investors. Currently facing strong resistance at the EMA50 daily level, AVAX is showing promising signs of potential bullish momentum. As buyers accumulate AVAX anticipating a breakout, optimism grows within the market. As of the latest data, Avalanche is trading at $15.45 per AVAX, showcasing impressive price growth within the past week. With a circulating supply of 345,845,505.008 AVAX, the token&#8217;s total market capitalization stands at $5,294,894,681.68. Furthermore, AVAX has experienced a substantial surge in trading volume, which has increased by $2,091,996,941.63 in the last 24 hours, marking a significant 381.96% rise. In the past day, approximately $547,703,576.77 worth of AVAX has been traded. AVAX: Strong Resistance And Accumulation The EMA50 daily level has emerged as a formidable resistance point for the coin, presenting a considerable challenge for buyers to overcome. However, buyers&#8217; increasing accumulation of AVAX indicates a positive sentiment and a belief in the token&#8217;s potential to breach the resistance level. Traders have noticed similarities between AVAX and other successful cryptocurrencies, drawing comparisons that suggest a potentially significant price surge. Related Reading: XRP Explodes With 1,300% Surge In Trading Volume As crypto Exchanges Jump On Board Looking at the technical indicators, its relative strength index is at 65 in the neutral zone between the oversold region of 50 and the overbought region of 75. The Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) is currently in the buy zone which is a bullish signal. In addition, the histogram bars are green and signal that a bullish trend is ahead and if the bulls persist, the crypto is likely to have a sustained uptrend in the coming days Growing Investor Interest And Bullish Sentiment The ongoing accumulation of AVAX demonstrates a growing interest and confidence among investors in the token&#8217;s underlying technology and future growth potential. As buyers strategically position themselves at key support regions, they aim to capitalize on the anticipated breakout and potential price appreciation. This accumulation activity is a positive indicator for AVAX and reinforces the belief that the token&#8217;s price could experience a notable upward movement. Market participants closely monitoring Avalanche have identified similarities between its current price pattern and other successful cryptocurrencies. In particular, the comparison with SOL, which experienced a significant surge after successfully breaking through a crucial resistance level, adds to the overall bullish sentiment surrounding AVAX. These comparisons contribute to the growing optimism within the market. Related Reading: PEPE Sees Sharp 17% Surge, But Will This Whale Spoil The Party? While the accumulation of AVAX and the anticipation of a breakout are encouraging signs, it is essential to acknowledge the highly volatile nature of the cryptocurrency market and the potential influence of various market forces. Traders should exercise caution and consider other technical indicators and market factors that may impact AVAX&#8217;s price trajectory. (This site’s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured Image from iStock, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Avalanche (AVAX), the native token of the Avalanche blockchain, has witnessed a notable price surge of 27.39% over the past seven days, capturing the attention of traders and investors. Currently facing strong resistance at the EMA50 daily level, AVAX is showing promising signs of potential bullish momentum. As buyers accumulate AVAX anticipating a breakout, optimism grows within the market.</p>
<p>As of the latest data, Avalanche is trading at $15.45 per AVAX, showcasing impressive price growth within the past week. With a circulating supply of 345,845,505.008 AVAX, the token&#8217;s total market capitalization stands at $5,294,894,681.68. Furthermore, AVAX has experienced a substantial surge in trading volume, which has increased by $2,091,996,941.63 in the last 24 hours, marking a significant 381.96% rise. In the past day, approximately $547,703,576.77 worth of AVAX has been traded.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-542793 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image1-2-860x474.png" alt="Avax has experienced a bullish trend: source @tradingview" width="860" height="474" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image1-2-860x474.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image1-2-460x253.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image1-2-768x423.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image1-2-750x413.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image1-2.png 1080w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<h2><strong>AVAX: Strong Resistance And Accumulation</strong></h2>
<p>The EMA50 daily level has emerged as a formidable resistance point for the coin, presenting a considerable challenge for buyers to overcome. However, buyers&#8217; increasing accumulation of AVAX indicates a positive sentiment and a belief in the token&#8217;s potential to breach the resistance level. Traders have noticed similarities between AVAX and other successful cryptocurrencies, drawing comparisons that suggest a potentially significant price surge.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading</strong>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-explodes-with-1300-surge-in-trading-volume-as-crypto-exchanges-jump-on-board/?swcfpc=1">XRP Explodes With 1,300% Surge In Trading Volume As crypto Exchanges Jump On Board</a></p>
<p>Looking at the technical indicators, its relative strength index is at 65 in the neutral zone between the oversold region of 50 and the overbought region of 75. The Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) is currently in the buy zone which is a bullish signal. In addition, the histogram bars are green and signal that a bullish trend is ahead and if the bulls persist, the crypto is likely to have a sustained uptrend in the coming days</p>
<h2><strong>Growing Investor Interest And Bullish Sentiment</strong></h2>
<p>The ongoing accumulation of AVAX demonstrates a growing interest and confidence among investors in the token&#8217;s underlying technology and future growth potential. As buyers strategically position themselves at key support regions, they aim to capitalize on the anticipated breakout and potential price appreciation. This accumulation activity is a positive indicator for AVAX and reinforces the belief that the token&#8217;s price could experience a notable upward movement.</p>
<p>Market participants closely monitoring Avalanche have identified similarities between its current price pattern and other successful cryptocurrencies. In particular, the comparison with SOL, which experienced a significant surge after successfully breaking through a crucial resistance level, adds to the overall bullish sentiment surrounding AVAX. These comparisons contribute to the growing optimism within the market.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading: </strong><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/pepe-sees-sharp-17-surge-but-whale-spoil-party/?swcfpc=1">PEPE Sees Sharp 17% Surge, But Will This Whale Spoil The Party?</a></p>
<p>While the accumulation of AVAX and the anticipation of a breakout are encouraging signs, it is essential to acknowledge the highly volatile nature of the cryptocurrency market and the potential influence of various market forces. Traders should exercise caution and consider other technical indicators and market factors that may impact AVAX&#8217;s price trajectory.</p>
<p><i>(This site’s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</i></p>
<p><i>Featured Image from iStock, chart from TradingView</i></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-157559643-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Explodes With 1,300% Surge In Trading Volume As crypto Exchanges Jump On Board</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-explodes-with-1300-surge-in-trading-volume-as-crypto-exchanges-jump-on-board/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 21:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542775</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a long-awaited decision, Judge Torres ruled in favor of XRP in their case against the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) yesterday. The verdict is a positive development for the cryptocurrency industry, particularly with a focus on whether digital assets should be deemed securities in the US. The ruling is expected to set a precedent for the industry moving forward. It is positive for both altcoins and the wider industry, as the default expectation is that these assets are not deemed securities so long as they are made available to the public.  This event will likely have wider implications for ongoing legal cases and may help rebuild confidence in the industry for developers and attract more liquidity to the ecosystem. XRP Defies Expectations With Massive Price Surge And Trading Volume Spike Following the news, XRP saw a surge in price, reaching as high as $0.93, the highest price since May 2021, and closing at $0.82.  According to data compiled by the research company CCData, the news led to an influx of trading activity, with XRP trading pairs on centralized exchanges (CEX) recording a total volume of $6.05 billion on the day, an increase of 1351% from the previous day. Related Reading: Crypto Liquidations Cross $300 Million Amid Massive Market Recovery The relisting of the asset on other centralized exchanges, including Coinbase, Kraken, and Gemini has also contributed to the spike in volumes.  The news surrounding the ruling also led to almost 100% daily gains for XRP, with other tokens such as Solana (SOL) and Cardano (ADA), recently deemed securities, seeing significant gains of 35% and 28%, respectively. Despite the negative backdrop that XRP has faced due to the lawsuit, its market depth liquidity at the 1% level has remained resilient year-to-date (YTD). XRP’s 1% bid/ask side depth at Yearly Open was 26.5 million XRP, which saw a variance of 0.41% throughout the year and remained strong at 25.1 million XRP on the 12th of July. Derivatives Data Shows Positive Sentiment According to the report, Derivatives data indicate that XRP&#8217;s positive funding rate remained steady over the past few days, in line with the wider positive market sentiment.  The lawsuit news generated a significant rise in speculative interest on the bid side, with a $280 million increase in Open Interest, from $635 million to a high of $913 million across exchanges. Moreover, funding rates reached over 0.03% across exchanges, over three times higher than its baseline level of under 0.01% before the announcement. On the other hand, the funding rate history of XRP shows that speculators trading perpetual contracts have been favoring the upside, with minimal time spent this year in negative funding rate territory.  This underscores the positive sentiment of traders for XRP, which was recently rewarded with a large price rise due to the announcement. While it remains to be seen whether XRP will maintain its extremely positive funding rate, it is currently a good standard for gauging positive sentiment within altcoins, given the attention and volume it is generating. Considering the lawsuit&#8217;s success, the implications for the market are overwhelmingly positive, and the ruling provides clarity that did not exist before the judgment.  Related Reading: Here’s What On-Chain Data Reveals About XRP Rally According to CCData, the market could see a few trends emerge, such as coins deemed securities recovering well and potentially outperforming and the potential for Bitcoin dominance to drop as an overall percent of market cap, given renewed optimism in altcoins. Despite the recent surge in positive sentiment and renewed investor confidence, XRP has experienced a significant price drop. After coming close to reaching the $1 mark, which it has not seen since November 2021, XRP is currently trading at $0.7002, marking a decrease of over 11% in the last 24 hours. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a long-awaited decision, Judge Torres ruled in favor of XRP in their case against the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) yesterday. The verdict is a positive development for the cryptocurrency industry, particularly with a focus on whether digital assets should be deemed securities in the US.</p>
<p>The ruling is expected to set a precedent for the industry moving forward. It is positive for both altcoins and the wider industry, as the default expectation is that these assets are not deemed securities so long as they are made available to the public. </p>
<p>This event will likely have wider implications for ongoing legal cases and may help rebuild confidence in the industry for developers and attract more liquidity to the ecosystem.</p>
<h2>XRP Defies Expectations With Massive Price Surge And Trading Volume Spike</h2>
<p>Following the news, XRP saw a surge in price, reaching as high as $0.93, the highest price since May 2021, and closing at $0.82. </p>
<p><a href="https://blog.ccdata.io/analysing-xrp-following-judge-torres-ruling-682bd8f345af" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to data compiled by the research company CCData, the news led to an influx of trading activity, with XRP trading pairs on centralized exchanges (CEX) recording a total volume of $6.05 billion on the day, an increase of 1351% from the previous day.</p>

<p>The <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/crypto-giant-coinbase-reverses-course-relists-xrp-after-landmark-ruling/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">relisting of the asset</a> on other centralized exchanges, including Coinbase, Kraken, and Gemini has also contributed to the spike in volumes. </p>
<p>The news surrounding the ruling also led to almost 100% daily gains for XRP, with other tokens such as Solana (SOL) and Cardano (ADA), recently deemed securities, seeing significant gains of 35% and 28%, respectively.</p>
<p>Despite the negative backdrop that XRP has faced due to the lawsuit, its market depth liquidity at the 1% level has remained resilient year-to-date (YTD). XRP’s 1% bid/ask side depth at Yearly Open was 26.5 million XRP, which saw a variance of 0.41% throughout the year and remained strong at 25.1 million XRP on the 12th of July.</p>
Derivatives Data Shows Positive Sentiment
<p>According to the report, Derivatives data indicate that XRP&#8217;s positive funding rate remained steady over the past few days, in line with the wider positive market sentiment. </p>
<p>The lawsuit news generated a significant rise in speculative interest on the bid side, with a $280 million increase in Open Interest, from $635 million to a high of $913 million across exchanges. Moreover, funding rates reached over 0.03% across exchanges, over three times higher than its baseline level of under 0.01% before the announcement.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the funding rate history of XRP shows that speculators trading perpetual contracts have been favoring the upside, with minimal time spent this year in negative funding rate territory. </p>
<p>This underscores the positive sentiment of traders for XRP, which was recently rewarded with a large price rise due to the announcement. While it remains to be seen whether XRP will maintain its extremely positive funding rate, it is currently a good standard for gauging positive sentiment within altcoins, given the attention and volume it is generating.</p>
<p>Considering the lawsuit&#8217;s success, the implications for the market are overwhelmingly positive, and the ruling provides clarity that did not exist before the judgment. </p>

<p>According to CCData, the market could see a few trends emerge, such as coins deemed securities recovering well and potentially outperforming and the potential for Bitcoin dominance to drop as an overall percent of market cap, given renewed optimism in altcoins.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/mJAK60uV/" alt="XRP" width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>Despite the recent surge in positive sentiment and renewed investor confidence, XRP has experienced a significant price drop. After coming close to reaching the $1 mark, which it has not seen since November 2021, XRP is currently trading at $0.7002, marking a decrease of over 11% in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1349331161-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Large Exchanges Relist XRP Following Ripple Victory Over SEC</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/large-exchanges-relist-xrp/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 19:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitstamp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto exchanges]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP exchange listings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542755</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a significant turn of events, large cryptocurrency exchanges Coinbase, Kraken, Bitstamp, and Gemini announced their decision to relist XRP after a significant legal victory for Ripple against the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). This momentous decision comes as a result of the exchanges reevaluating their previous delisting of XRP, showcasing a renewed confidence in the token&#8217;s regulatory standing.  This was brought about by the recent landmark court ruling by Judge Analisa Torres. Coinbase, Kraken, And Bitstamp Reinstate XRP Trading Coinbase, a leading cryptocurrency exchange, wasted no time in announcing the resumption of XRP trading following the court ruling. Brian Armstrong, the CEO of Coinbase, expressed the exchange&#8217;s decision in a tweet, stating: “Coinbase will re-enable trading for XRP (XRP) on the XRP network. Do not send this asset over other networks or your funds may be lost. Transfers for this asset remain available on @Coinbase &#38;  @CoinbaseExch.“ Related Reading: Ripple Eyes Tokenized Assets Sector As It Expects Market Cap To Reach $30 Trillion The reinstatement of the digital asset on Coinbase&#8217;s platform marks a significant shift in their position after delisting the token in January 2021. Kraken, another prominent exchange, also confirmed its plans to reinstate trading for the cryptocurrency, as Marco Santori, Kraken’ Legal Officer tweeted stated: “1/ This morning, the Federal Court for the Southern District of New York ruled that XRP is not a security. As such, just a few minutes ago, Kraken re-enabled trading in XRP for US users.”  Bitstamp, an early adopter of XRP, joined the bandwagon, emphasizing its role as a leading liquidity venue for the asset globally as it confirms the return of the token on its exchange for US users.  Token holding majority of gains from Thursday &#124; Source: XRPUSD on TradingView.com Ripple&#8217;s Legal Battle And Market Impact The court ruling stems from the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Ripple, which accused the company of conducting an unregistered securities offering through the sale and distribution of XRP. Ripple chose to fight the lawsuit, investing substantial resources into the legal proceedings. The outcome of this case carries significant weight for the cryptocurrency industry, as it determines the regulatory oversight faced by digital asset firms. Although Judge Torres&#8217; recent summary judgment concluded that while Ripple&#8217;s initial sale of XRP to institutional investors could be classified as a securities offering, the subsequent trading of the tokens on crypto exchanges did not fall under the same classification.  Related Reading: Fund Manager Vanguard Increases Stake In Bitcoin Mining Stocks To $600 Million This ruling provides a level of clarity regarding the regulatory status of the token and sets a precedent for similar cases involving other cryptocurrencies. The market responded with enthusiasm to the court ruling as XRP experienced a surge in value, rising by over 75% compared to its price at the beginning of Thursday. Coinbase&#8217;s share prices also witnessed a significant jump of more than 24% following the ruling. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a significant turn of events, large cryptocurrency exchanges Coinbase, Kraken, Bitstamp, and Gemini announced their decision to relist XRP after a significant legal victory for Ripple against the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<p>This momentous decision comes as a result of the exchanges reevaluating their previous delisting of XRP, showcasing a renewed confidence in the token&#8217;s regulatory standing.  This was brought about by the recent landmark court ruling by Judge Analisa Torres.</p>
<h2>Coinbase, Kraken, And Bitstamp Reinstate XRP Trading</h2>
<p>Coinbase, a leading cryptocurrency exchange, wasted no time in announcing the resumption of XRP trading following the court ruling. Brian Armstrong, the CEO of Coinbase, expressed the exchange&#8217;s decision in a <a href="https://twitter.com/CoinbaseAssets/status/1679575239657758721" rel="nofollow">tweet</a>, stating:</p>
<p>“Coinbase will re-enable trading for XRP (XRP) on the XRP network. Do not send this asset over other networks or your funds may be lost. Transfers for this asset remain available on @Coinbase &amp;  @CoinbaseExch.“</p>

<p>The reinstatement of the digital asset on Coinbase&#8217;s platform marks a significant shift in their position after delisting the token in January 2021. Kraken, another prominent exchange, also confirmed its plans to reinstate trading for the cryptocurrency, as Marco Santori, Kraken’ Legal Officer <a href="https://twitter.com/msantoriESQ/status/1679590081072594952" rel="nofollow">tweeted</a> stated:</p>
<p>“1/ This morning, the Federal Court for the Southern District of New York ruled that XRP is not a security. As such, just a few minutes ago, Kraken re-enabled trading in XRP for US users.” </p>
<p>Bitstamp, an early adopter of XRP, joined the bandwagon, emphasizing its role as a leading liquidity venue for the asset globally as it confirms the <a href="https://blog.bitstamp.net/post/xrp-is-back-in-the-us-start-trading-today/" rel="nofollow">return </a>of the token on its exchange for US users. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/T8EebvN5/" alt="Ripple (XRP) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>

<h2>Ripple&#8217;s Legal Battle And Market Impact</h2>
<p>The court ruling stems from the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Ripple, which accused the company of conducting an unregistered securities offering through the sale and distribution of XRP.</p>
<p>Ripple chose to fight the lawsuit, investing substantial resources into the legal proceedings. The outcome of this case carries significant weight for the cryptocurrency industry, as it determines the regulatory oversight faced by digital asset firms.</p>
<p>Although Judge Torres&#8217; recent summary judgment concluded that while Ripple&#8217;s initial sale of XRP to institutional investors could be classified as a securities offering, the subsequent trading of the tokens on crypto exchanges did not fall under the same classification. </p>

<p>This ruling provides a level of clarity regarding the regulatory status of the token and sets a precedent for similar cases involving other cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>The market responded with enthusiasm to the court ruling as XRP experienced a surge in value, rising by over 75% compared to its price at the beginning of Thursday. Coinbase&#8217;s share prices also witnessed a significant jump of more than 24% following the ruling.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1436037805-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>PEPE Sees Sharp 17% Surge, But Will This Whale Spoil The Party?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/pepe-sees-sharp-17-surge-but-whale-spoil-party/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 18:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE Rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE Whale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pepeusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542728</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows a PEPE whale has made a large deposit to Binance, something that could provide an impedance to the meme coin&#8217;s rally. PEPE Whale Has Deposited $7.2 Million To Binance According to data from the cryptocurrency transaction tracker service Whale Alert, a massive PEPE transfer has occurred on the Ethereum blockchain during the past day. The transaction in question involved the movement of 3.94 trillion PEPE, which was worth almost $7.2 million at the time the transfer went through on the network. Generally, only the whale entities are capable of making such large moves, so it&#8217;s reasonable to assume that a whale investor would have been behind this transfer. Due to the massive amount of capital involved in transactions of these humongous investors, they can sometimes cause noticeable fluctuations in the price of the asset. As such, the movements of the whales can be something to watch out for. How such transfers may affect the market, though, depends on the exact intent the investor had behind it. Related Reading: Perfect Storm: Why Bitcoin &#38; Crypto Are Poised For A Dramatic Recovery Here are some additional details regarding the relevant PEPE whale transfer, which may shed some light on what the whale wanted to achieve with the move: Looks like this large transfer on the Ethereum blockchain only cost a fee of about $2.5 to go through &#124; Source: Whale Alert As you can see above, the sending address in the case of this PEPE transfer is an unknown wallet, meaning that it&#8217;s an address unattached to any known centralized platform, making it likely that it&#8217;s the personal wallet of an investor. The receiving address, on the other hand, looks to be a wallet affiliated with a centralized platform. More specifically, this address is connected to the cryptocurrency exchange Binance. Transfers like these, where coins move from self-custodial wallets to exchanges are called &#8220;exchange inflows.&#8221; As one of the main reasons why investors may deposit their coins to these platforms is for selling-related purposes, exchange inflows can provide hints about the selling pressure in the market. In the current case, as the whale has made a rather large inflow to these platforms, it&#8217;s possible that the price of the meme coin may suffer bearish consequences from it. Naturally, this would only be so if the PEPE whale in question truly made these deposits with selling in mind, and not for using any of the other services the Binance platform offers. Though, considering that the exchange inflow has occurred following a rapid 17% rise in the meme coin&#8217;s value, there is probably a fair chance that the whale is indeed looking to sell and take advantage of this profitable exit opportunity. Related Reading: XRP Price Retreats After Massive 80% Rally, Buy The Dips? So far, however, the PEPE price has only moved mostly sideways since the whale made the transfer, implying that, if the whale indeed sold the coins, the market currently has enough buying pressure that the selling has simply been absorbed. Another possibility, though, may be that the whale has only made the deposit in advance and is yet to actually the pull trigger on selling the stack, perhaps to see if the price goes up further. Naturally, if this is the case, the price would feel a bearish effect from this later down the line. PEPE Price At the time of writing, PEPE is trading around $0.000001736, up 11% in the last week. PEPE has shot up during the past day &#124; Source: PEPEUSD on TradingView Featured image from iStock.com, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows a PEPE whale has made a large deposit to Binance, something that could provide an impedance to the meme coin&#8217;s rally.</p>
<h2>PEPE Whale Has Deposited $7.2 Million To Binance</h2>
<p>According to data from the cryptocurrency transaction tracker service <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1679674107145625601" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Whale Alert</a>, a massive PEPE transfer has occurred on the Ethereum blockchain during the past day.</p>
<p>The transaction in question involved the movement of 3.94 trillion PEPE, which was worth almost $7.2 million at the time the transfer went through on the network.</p>
<p>Generally, only the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-whale-10-total-shib-supply-shocks-market/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">whale</a> entities are capable of making such large moves, so it&#8217;s reasonable to assume that a whale investor would have been behind this transfer.</p>
<p>Due to the massive amount of capital involved in transactions of these humongous investors, they can sometimes cause noticeable fluctuations in the price of the asset.</p>
<p>As such, the movements of the whales can be something to watch out for. How such transfers may affect the market, though, depends on the exact intent the investor had behind it.</p>

<p>Here are some additional details regarding the relevant PEPE whale transfer, which may shed some light on what the whale wanted to achieve with the move:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-542733 size-large aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/details-860x445.png" alt="PEPE Whale" width="860" height="445" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/details-860x445.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/details-460x238.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/details-768x398.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/details-750x388.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/details-1140x590.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/details.png 1170w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>As you can see above, the sending address in the case of this PEPE transfer is an unknown wallet, meaning that it&#8217;s an address unattached to any known centralized platform, making it likely that it&#8217;s the personal wallet of an investor.</p>
<p>The receiving address, on the other hand, looks to be a wallet affiliated with a centralized platform. More specifically, this address is connected to the cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/nft/cristiano-ronaldo-goes-crypto-again-drops-second-nft-collection-on-binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Binance</a>.</p>
<p>Transfers like these, where coins move from self-custodial wallets to exchanges are called &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-short-term-holders-exchange-inflows-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">exchange inflows</a>.&#8221; As one of the main reasons why investors may deposit their coins to these platforms is for selling-related purposes, exchange inflows can provide hints about the selling pressure in the market.</p>
<p>In the current case, as the whale has made a rather large inflow to these platforms, it&#8217;s possible that the price of the meme coin may suffer bearish consequences from it.</p>
<p>Naturally, this would only be so if the PEPE whale in question truly made these deposits with selling in mind, and not for using any of the other services the Binance platform offers.</p>
<p>Though, considering that the exchange inflow has occurred following a rapid 17% rise in the meme coin&#8217;s value, there is probably a fair chance that the whale is indeed looking to sell and take advantage of this profitable exit opportunity.</p>

<p>So far, however, the PEPE price has only moved mostly sideways since the whale made the transfer, implying that, if the whale indeed sold the coins, the market currently has enough buying pressure that the selling has simply been absorbed.</p>
<p>Another possibility, though, may be that the whale has only made the deposit in advance and is yet to actually the pull trigger on selling the stack, perhaps to see if the price goes up further. Naturally, if this is the case, the price would feel a bearish effect from this later down the line.</p>
<h2>PEPE Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, PEPE is trading around $0.000001736, up 11% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Xf9TL9oY/" alt="PEPE Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1429119108-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
