<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:51:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>80% Of Uniswap Holders Support BNB PoS Chain For Deploying V3 Protocol</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/uni/uniswap-support-bnb-deploying-v3-protocol/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli Dambell]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[UNI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uniswap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UNIUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517335</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Uniswap (UNI), a decentralized protocol, is ready to roll out the third version of its platform. The protocol aims to provide a suitable platform where users can seamlessly swap ERC-20 tokens without using an order book. For the v3 launch, the protocol carried out a &#8216;temperature test&#8217; for a possible blockchain to use. The proposal was for deploying Uniswap v3 on the Binance Smart Chain (BNB) instead of the Ethereum blockchain. The proposal got the UNI community voting on its government forum using their UNI tokens. Related Reading: Bullish Indicator: Bitcoin Shakes Off Genesis Bankruptcy Filing Surprisingly, about 80% of the UNI holders supported the Uniswap v3 deployment on the BNB Chain, Ethereum&#8217;s rival. Unfortunately, this left a smaller percentage of votes for the Ethereum blockchain, making it lose the temperature check proposal. 🦄 We’re excited to share that our @0xPlasma proposal to deploy @Uniswap v3 on @BNBCHAIN has passed the &#34;Temperature Check&#34; with 20M votes &#34;YES&#34; and 6,495 $UNI voters (the biggest number for the whole Uniswap Governance History). Moving forward to the final &#34;Governance Proposal&#34; pic.twitter.com/HoIJgY8mX1 &#8212; 0xPlasma Labs: DeFi &#38; NFT Metaverse 🦇 🔊 (@0xPlasma) January 22, 2023 0xPlasma Labs, a decentralized finance protocol, contributes to the proposal. According to the post on Twitter, the firm noted that the &#8220;Temperature Check&#8221; on the proposal got 20 million votes for &#8216;YES.&#8217; In addition, the supporting votes came from 6,495 $UNI voters, the most significant voting numbers in the history of Uniswap&#8217;s Governance system. 0xPlasma Labs&#8217; CEO Lists Benefits of Deploying Uniswap V3 on BNB Chain Recently, the CEO of 0xPlasma Labs, Ilia Maksimenka, wrote a proposal for deploying the Uniswap v3 protocol. The CEO lined his argument on the benefits of deploying the new v3 protocol on the BNB Chain. Maksimenka cited the License expiration of Uniswap as one of the reasons for choosing BNB Chain. Also, he mentioned that the chain has many packages that would help boost Uniswap&#8217;s popularity in the DeFi space. Some include high transactions, low fees, staking opportunities, cross-chain support, etc. Related Reading: Crypto Analyst Says Bitcoin Price Could See Another 30% Rally Also, the CEO acknowledged that Binance had acquired a global presence, being rated as the largest crypto exchange in the world. Hence, as a strong brand, using the BNB Chain will fast-forward the awareness and adoption of the v3 version globally for Uniswap. The Proposal Gets Support The proposal has received support from other firms and crypto participants. For example, ConsenSys, a blockchain software company behind one of Ethereum&#8217;s most important clients, is optimistic about the deployment move. The DAO governance strategist at ConsenSys, Cameron O&#8217;Donnell, revealed the company&#8217;s stance. First, the firm noted the need for Uniswap to be agnostic in its service to users, especially in the Web3 space, even with its license expiration in April.  Hence, O&#8217;Donnell maintained that existing and future platform users would enjoy a secured and robust platform for decentralized exchange through the BSC market. Other supporting comments came from Brian-Armstrong, CEO at Coinbase, and Modong also optimistic about the deployment of Uniswap v3 on BNB Chain. The Plasma Finance team started its operation after the Uniswap governance community approved the proposal. The team noted that it could take five to eight weeks to deploy all the relevant Uniswap smart contracts to the BNB Chain. The price performance of UNI was entirely on the positive lane over the past 30 days. The token gained over 28% in the past month and has shown a slight increase of 0.38% in the past seven days. But at the time of writing, UNI is trading at $6.60, indicating a drop within the past 24 hours. Featured Image From CityAM, Charts From Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Uniswap (UNI), a decentralized protocol, is ready to roll out the third version of its platform. The protocol aims to provide a suitable platform where users can seamlessly swap ERC-20 tokens without using an order book.</p>
<p>For the v3 launch, the protocol carried out a &#8216;temperature test&#8217; for a possible blockchain to use. The proposal was for deploying Uniswap v3 on the Binance Smart Chain (BNB) instead of the Ethereum blockchain. The proposal got the UNI community voting on its government forum using their UNI tokens.</p>

<p>Surprisingly, about 80% of the UNI holders supported the Uniswap v3 deployment on the BNB Chain, Ethereum&#8217;s rival. Unfortunately, this left a smaller percentage of votes for the Ethereum blockchain, making it lose the temperature check proposal.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f984.png" alt="🦄" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> We’re excited to share that our <a href="https://twitter.com/0xPlasma?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@0xPlasma</a> proposal to deploy <a href="https://twitter.com/Uniswap?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@Uniswap</a> v3 on <a href="https://twitter.com/BNBCHAIN?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@BNBCHAIN</a> has passed the &quot;Temperature Check&quot; with 20M votes &quot;YES&quot; and 6,495 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24UNI&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$UNI</a> voters (the biggest number for the whole Uniswap Governance History). Moving forward to the final &quot;Governance Proposal&quot; <a href="https://t.co/HoIJgY8mX1" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/HoIJgY8mX1</a></p>
<p>&mdash; 0xPlasma Labs: DeFi &amp; NFT Metaverse <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f987.png" alt="🦇" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f50a.png" alt="🔊" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@0xPlasma) <a href="https://twitter.com/0xPlasma/status/1617022128414687232?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 22, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>0xPlasma Labs, a decentralized finance protocol, contributes to the proposal. According to the post on Twitter, the firm <a href="https://twitter.com/0xPlasma/status/1617022128414687232?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1617022128414687232%7Ctwgr%5E39309c7670616234142b25928821d4b1f7ce85d0%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.bsc.news%2Fpost%2Flandslide-victory-for-proposal-to-deploy-uniswap-v3-on-bnb-chain" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">noted</a> that the &#8220;Temperature Check&#8221; on the proposal got 20 million votes for &#8216;YES.&#8217; In addition, the supporting votes came from 6,495 $UNI voters, the most significant voting numbers in the history of Uniswap&#8217;s Governance system.</p>
<h2>0xPlasma Labs&#8217; CEO Lists Benefits of Deploying Uniswap V3 on BNB Chain</h2>
<p>Recently, the CEO of 0xPlasma Labs, Ilia Maksimenka, <a href="https://gov.uniswap.org/t/temperature-check-should-uniswap-v3-be-deployed-to-bnb-chain/20046" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">wrote</a> a proposal for deploying the Uniswap v3 protocol. The CEO lined his argument on the benefits of deploying the new v3 protocol on the BNB Chain.</p>
<p>Maksimenka cited the License expiration of Uniswap as one of the reasons for choosing BNB Chain. Also, he mentioned that the chain has many packages that would help boost Uniswap&#8217;s popularity in the DeFi space. Some include high transactions, low fees, staking opportunities, cross-chain support, etc.</p>

<p>Also, the CEO acknowledged that Binance had acquired a global presence, being rated as the largest crypto exchange in the world. Hence, as a strong brand, using the BNB Chain will fast-forward the awareness and adoption of the v3 version globally for Uniswap.</p>
<h2>The Proposal Gets Support</h2>
<p>The proposal has received support from other firms and crypto participants. For example, ConsenSys, a blockchain software company behind one of Ethereum&#8217;s most important clients, is optimistic about the deployment move. </p>
<p>The DAO governance strategist at ConsenSys, Cameron O&#8217;Donnell, <a href="https://gov.uniswap.org/t/temperature-check-should-uniswap-v3-be-deployed-to-bnb-chain/20046/6" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">revealed</a> the company&#8217;s stance. First, the firm noted the need for Uniswap to be agnostic in its service to users, especially in the Web3 space, even with its license expiration in April. </p>
<p>Hence, O&#8217;Donnell maintained that existing and future platform users would enjoy a secured and robust platform for decentralized exchange through the BSC market. Other supporting comments came from Brian-Armstrong, CEO at Coinbase, and Modong also optimistic about the deployment of Uniswap v3 on BNB Chain.</p>
<p>The Plasma Finance team started its operation after the Uniswap governance community approved the proposal. The team noted that it could take five to eight weeks to deploy all the relevant Uniswap smart contracts to the BNB Chain.</p>
<p>The price performance of UNI was entirely on the positive lane over the past 30 days. The token gained over 28% in the past month and has shown a slight increase of 0.38% in the past seven days.</p>
<img class="wp-image-517347 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/UNIUSDT_2023-01-24_23-04-27-860x499.png" alt="80% Of Uniswap Holders Support BNB PoS Chain For Deploying V3 protocol " width="860" height="499" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/UNIUSDT_2023-01-24_23-04-27-860x499.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/UNIUSDT_2023-01-24_23-04-27-460x267.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/UNIUSDT_2023-01-24_23-04-27-768x446.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/UNIUSDT_2023-01-24_23-04-27-750x435.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/UNIUSDT_2023-01-24_23-04-27.png 1116w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>But at the time of writing, UNI is trading at $6.60, indicating a drop within the past 24 hours.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Screenshot-2023-01-24-230104-460x254.png" width="460" height="254" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SushiSwap To Redirect 100% Trading Fees To Treasury</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/defi/sushiswap-redirect-trading-fees-to-treasury/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 23:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sushi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SushiSwap]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517360</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[While the DeFi market has continued to mirror the crypto market rally, more innovations have been introduced to the ecosystem. In today’s news, SushiSwap, the sixth-largest decentralized exchange (DEX) by 24 hours trading volume, has passed a proposal to relocate 100% of its trading fees to the SushiSwap treasury for maintenance and expenses. Related Reading: SushiSwap Head Chef Suggests Cooking Up New Token Model – Will The DEX Survive 2023? SushiSwap Introduces New Update This new update comes after CEO Jared Grey voiced warnings that the exchange treasury stability is numbered as it has &#8220;only 1.5 years of treasury runway left,&#8221; despite having cut down the annual operating expenses from $9 million to $5 million during the ongoing crypto winter. According to a presented governance proposal by the developers of the SushiSwap decentralized exchange, which was passed on January 23, the SushiSwap exchange will now extend the usage of trading fees by redirecting them to the exchange’s treasury to enhance the operation and maintenance of the exchange over the next one year.  The proposal noted, “Revenue to the treasury will be 50% ETH and 50% USDC, with a projection of ~$6m being earned over the next year if this proposal were to pass.” In another proposal passed the same day, approximately 99.85% of voters voted in favor of “clawing back” 10,936,284 unclaimed SUSHI ($14.8 million) tokens to be rewarded to early liquidity providers during the DEX&#8217;s launch in 2020. SushiSwap Painful Loss And Recovery  Undoubtedly the crypto winter hit most projects in the industry, including DeFi platforms such as SushiSwap. Last December, SushiSwap CEO Jared Grey revealed that the DEX experienced a $30 million loss over the past 12 months on incentives for liquidity providers (LPs).  To counter that loss and initiate recovery, Grey revealed plans to refine SushiSwap’s tokenomics so that LPs are no longer bankrolled with emissions and redesign the complete model of bootstrapping liquidity on the exchange.  The “Kanpai” governance proposal, which aims to relocate trading protocol fees to the treasury, was also referred to by Grey when illustrating the plans to update the SushiSwap exchange.  “Put simply, it (Kanpai) allows the protocol to rebuild its cash reserves to continue to pay competitive wages, pay for critical infrastructure, &#38; to diversify its Treasury with funds collected in the base pairs of assets, like ETH, stablecoins, etc. Kanpai is a temporary solution,” Grey stated. Related Reading: SushiSwap: Deciphering How SUSHI Is Posting Unparalleled Price Growth Speaking of SushiSwap, the protocol’s native token, SUSHI, has been in a rally, following the rest of the DeFi sector.  SUSHI has surged by over 40% in the last 30 days; meanwhile, at the time of writing, SUSHI trades at $1.34, down by 1.4% in the previous 24 hours and with a trading volume of $58.6 million in the same period. Featured image from BlockchainReporter, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While the DeFi market has continued to mirror the crypto market rally, more innovations have been introduced to the ecosystem. In today’s news, <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/sushiswap-how-sushi-posts-unparalleled-growth/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SushiSwap</a>, the sixth-largest decentralized exchange (DEX) by 24 hours trading volume, has passed a proposal to relocate 100% of its trading fees to the SushiSwap treasury for maintenance and expenses.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/sushiswap-new-token-model/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SushiSwap Head Chef Suggests Cooking Up New Token Model – Will The DEX Survive 2023?</a></p>
<h2>SushiSwap Introduces New Update</h2>
<p>This new update comes after CEO Jared Grey voiced warnings that the exchange treasury stability is numbered as it has &#8220;only 1.5 years of treasury runway left,&#8221; despite having cut down the annual operating expenses from $9 million to $5 million during the ongoing crypto winter.</p>
<p>According to a presented governance <a href="https://snapshot.org/#/sushigov.eth/proposal/0x64c5c6cdb74a1ebafe8e808ba69bd51ff70938b7db791ca8a05b37736541d147" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">proposal</a> by the developers of the SushiSwap decentralized exchange, which was passed on January 23, the SushiSwap exchange will now extend the usage of trading fees by redirecting them to the exchange’s treasury to enhance the operation and maintenance of the exchange over the next one year. </p>
<p>The proposal noted, “Revenue to the treasury will be 50% ETH and 50% USDC, with a projection of ~$6m being earned over the next year if this proposal were to pass.” In <a href="https://snapshot.org/#/sushigov.eth/proposal/0xf0353dcc69b766e96e2d1f65f76be2f13c03c1df7ed5ef483e9352e0da59a821" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">another proposal</a> passed the same day, approximately 99.85% of voters voted in favor of “clawing back” 10,936,284 unclaimed SUSHI ($14.8 million) tokens to be rewarded to early liquidity providers during the DEX&#8217;s launch in 2020.</p>
<h2>SushiSwap Painful Loss And Recovery </h2>
<p>Undoubtedly the crypto winter hit most projects in the industry, including <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a> platforms such as SushiSwap. Last December, SushiSwap CEO Jared Grey revealed that the DEX experienced a $30 million loss over the past 12 months on incentives for liquidity providers (LPs). </p>
<p>To counter that loss and initiate recovery, Grey revealed<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/sushiswap-new-token-model/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> plans</a> to refine SushiSwap’s tokenomics so that LPs are no longer bankrolled with emissions and redesign the complete model of bootstrapping liquidity on the exchange. </p>
<p>The “Kanpai” governance proposal, which aims to relocate trading protocol fees to the treasury, was also referred to by Grey when illustrating the plans to update the SushiSwap exchange. </p>
<p>“Put simply, it (Kanpai) allows the protocol to rebuild its cash reserves to continue to pay competitive wages, pay for critical infrastructure, &amp; to diversify its Treasury with funds collected in the base pairs of assets, like ETH, stablecoins, etc. Kanpai is a temporary solution,” Grey stated.</p>

<p>Speaking of SushiSwap, the protocol’s native token, SUSHI, has been in a rally, following the rest of the DeFi sector. </p>
<img loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/8Ng7S6Ea/" alt="SUSHI price chart on TradingView" width="1575" height="880" />
<p>SUSHI has surged by over 40% in the last 30 days; meanwhile, at the time of writing, <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/sushiswap-cracks-24-gains-as-market-rebounds-is-this-a-fakeout/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SUSHI</a> trades at $1.34, down by 1.4% in the previous 24 hours and with a trading volume of $58.6 million in the same period.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SushiSwap-460x230.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chiliz (CHZ) Continues To Record Significant Gains, Moves Over 5% In The Last Day</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/chiliz-chz/chiliz-chz-continues-to-record-significant/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jammy Hunts]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 21:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Chiliz (CHZ)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chiliZ]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chiliz price analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CHZ]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CHZ Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517340</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The global cryptocurrency market cap stands at $1.05 trillion, representing a 0.19% increase in the last day. As the cryptocurrency market continues to rally, altcoins are posting incredible gains. For instance, Chiliz&#8217;s price is gaining today, reflecting the positive moves of the general market. CHZ&#8217;s trading volume has also increased by 82.02% in 24 hours, showing rising interest among investors. CHZ is among the top gainers today, recording an almost 6% increase in value. The asset has outperformed market leader Bitcoin today, which recorded a 0.02% increase in 24 hours. This price increase might support a bull run in the coming weeks. Related Reading: Money Leaves ADA, SOL To Small Cap Altcoins, Here’s Where It’s Headed Some experts have predicted 2023 to be bullish, and the price performance of cryptos so far is leaning toward this prediction. What Is Behind The Chiliz (CHZ) Rally? CHZ acts as a fan token and has always been a community-driven project that relies on voting power from members. The Chiliz project has many lucrative partnerships with soccer giants such as Juventus, Manchester City, FC Barcelona, and Paris Saint-Germain. It equips the club supporters with limited editions of fan tokens. Sports is a lucrative sector worldwide, with fans investing heavily in merchandise and fan tokens to support their favorite teams. The platform&#8217;s native token CHZ is the currency for purchasing these fan tokens through smart contracts. These fan tokens are offered in limited supply to preserve their scarcity and uniqueness. The Chiliz development team posted the progressive strides the network has made in 2022 and early 2023 on Twitter. It has formed new partnerships with notable partners such as Italian Serie A teams, MLS teams, and SL Benfica. Also, the Scoville Testnet upgrade launched in 2022 has recorded success in stages 1-5. According to the development team, Stage 6 will launch in 2023. CHZ Price Prediction Where Is it Headed? Chiliz (CHZ) is trading at 0.1461, a 5.29% increase in the token&#8217;s value. The Chiliz token is in an uptrend, as the formation of consecutive green candles with higher highs indicates. CHZ is trading above its 50-day Simple Moving Average (SMA) and below its 200-day (SMA). It implies a short-term rally as the bulls seize control of the market. The support levels are $0.130459, $0.133246, and $0.136924, while the resistance levels are $0.143388, $0.146176, and $0.146176.   Chiliz has broken its first resistance level of $0.133246 and turned it to support, leading to a positive movement on the charts. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) is at 64.85, showing that Chiliz is close to the buy zone but not in the overbought region. If the bullish pressure sustains,  Chiliz will likely surpass its next resistance level soon. The MACD (Moving Average Convergence Divergence) is now above the signal line. It also indicates slight bullish pressure. However, the MACD is still tentative and reflects a possible reversal if the bears seize control. Related Reading: Solana (SOL) Network On Hyperdrive As TVL And NFT Trade Volume Soars Expect CHZ to sustain its gains in the coming days. The asset will likely surpass the $0.14676 level soon. However, if the resistance prevails, it will retrace to the $0.133246 support. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">global cryptocurrency market cap</a> stands at $1.05 trillion, representing a 0.19% increase in the last day. As the cryptocurrency market continues to rally, <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/gainers-losers/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">altcoins</a> are posting incredible gains. </p>
<p>For instance, Chiliz&#8217;s price is gaining today, reflecting the positive moves of the general market. CHZ&#8217;s trading volume has also increased by 82.02% in 24 hours, showing rising interest among investors.</p>
<p>CHZ is among the top gainers today, recording an almost 6% increase in value. The asset has outperformed market leader Bitcoin today, which recorded a 0.02% increase in 24 hours. This price increase might support a bull run in the coming weeks.</p>

<p>Some <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mvr4RW2HICM" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">experts</a> have predicted 2023 to be bullish, and the price performance of cryptos so far is leaning toward this prediction.</p>
<h2><b>What Is Behind The Chiliz (CHZ) Rally?</b></h2>
<p>CHZ acts as a fan token and has always been a community-driven project that relies on voting power from members. The Chiliz project has many <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/chiliz/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">lucrative partnerships</a> with soccer giants such as Juventus, Manchester City, FC Barcelona, and Paris Saint-Germain. It equips the club supporters with limited editions of fan tokens.</p>
<p>Sports is a lucrative sector worldwide, with fans investing heavily in merchandise and fan tokens to support their favorite teams. The platform&#8217;s native token CHZ is the currency for purchasing these fan tokens through smart contracts. These fan tokens are offered in limited supply to preserve their scarcity and uniqueness.</p>
<p>The Chiliz development team posted the progressive strides the network has made in 2022 and early 2023 on <a href="https://twitter.com/Chiliz/status/1612389947339640833" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Twitter</a>. It has formed new partnerships with notable partners such as Italian Serie A teams, MLS teams, and SL Benfica. Also, the Scoville Testnet upgrade launched in 2022 has recorded success in stages 1-5. According to the <a href="https://twitter.com/Chiliz/status/1612389934265950209" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">development team</a>, Stage 6 will launch in 2023.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-517343" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CHZUSD_2023-01-24_22-53-24.png" alt="CHZUSD" width="856" height="538" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CHZUSD_2023-01-24_22-53-24.png 856w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CHZUSD_2023-01-24_22-53-24-460x289.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CHZUSD_2023-01-24_22-53-24-768x483.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CHZUSD_2023-01-24_22-53-24-750x471.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 856px) 100vw, 856px" />
<b>CHZ Price Prediction Where Is it Headed?</b>
<p>Chiliz (CHZ) is trading at 0.1461, a 5.29% increase in the token&#8217;s value. The Chiliz token is in an uptrend, as the formation of consecutive green candles with higher highs indicates. </p>
<p>CHZ is trading above its 50-day <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-cDkE8NURUE" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Simple Moving Average (</a><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-cDkE8NURUE" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">SMA</a><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-cDkE8NURUE" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">)</a> and below its 200-day (SMA). It implies a short-term rally as the bulls seize control of the market. The support levels are $0.130459, $0.133246, and $0.136924, while the resistance levels are $0.143388, $0.146176, and $0.146176.  </p>
<p>Chiliz has broken its first resistance level of $0.133246 and turned it to support, leading to a positive movement on the charts. The <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cjoEGsB7ph4" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Relative Strength Index (</a><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cjoEGsB7ph4" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">RSI</a><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cjoEGsB7ph4" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">)</a> is at 64.85, showing that Chiliz is close to the buy zone but not in the overbought region. If the bullish pressure sustains,  Chiliz will likely surpass its next resistance level soon.</p>
<p>The MACD (Moving Average Convergence Divergence) is now above the signal line. It also indicates slight bullish pressure. However, the MACD is still tentative and reflects a possible reversal if the bears seize control.</p>

<p>Expect CHZ to sustain its gains in the coming days. The asset will likely surpass the $0.14676 level soon. However, if the resistance prevails, it will retrace to the $0.133246 support.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Chiliz-1-460x324.png" width="460" height="324" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Surges To 23,000 As Miners Sales Sees Multi-Year Low</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-surges-23k-miners-sales-sees-low/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 19:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517324</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin has continued with its bullishness as it surged its price above the USD$23,000 level, a positive signal amid miners reduced the sales of their mined coins. On-chain flows flagged by Bitifinex analysts indicate that the amount of Bitcoin moved from Bitcoin mining addresses to wallets owned by cryptocurrency exchanges has declined to multi-year lows. Selling Power Low, Favorable For A BTC Rally                       As per a Bitfinex analyst, Bitcoin miner sales are at a three-year low. The report claims that the selling could be a sign that Bitcoin miners are in the mood to accumulate coins as they expect the surge of prices of the flagship cryptocurrency. The declined Bitcoin sales from mining companies mean low selling pressure from these market actors. Therefore, it signals bullishness for the broader market. Related Reading: Bitcoin Reaches One-Month High As Mini Bull Run Continues The analysts, however, stated that the recent uptick in Bitcoin price might witness a correction as investors try to recoup their profits amid the current price surges. The analysts identified large wallet sizes (&#62;$1M) as the majorly responsible for accumulating Bitcoin. They further said such wallets, as well as major market actors, are the ones creating the buying pressure that comes after the FTX saga and a series of bearish events generally witnessed last year. The analysts mentioned that since the second week of January, the numbers of wallets with $1,000 and $10,000 worth of Bitcoin have increased. The analyst further acknowledged that the trading activities of retail investors had accompanied the uptrend. According to the figure above, the current low Bitcoin selling pressure coincided with the lowest sales in November last year. The current low level signals a green (bullish) indicator for the cryptocurrency. When miners sell more BTC, it implies a bearish for the coin value. Conversely, when mining firms don’t have the selling urge, this suggests a bullish trend for the crypto market. Related Reading: Bitcoin Mining Stocks In Solid Gains As Crypto Market Rallies Today&#8217;s Bitcoin Price Bitcoin has surged its value by almost 40% this month, trading at $22,909, up 1.48% on Tuesday. The crypto is trading at levels not witnessed since the downfall of the FTX exchange. BTC volume stands at about $26.82 billion, an increase of 12.78% in the past 24 hours, as per Coinmarketcap. As highlighted above, the rise in Bitcoin value could be attributed to whales committed to accumulating coins amid surging prices. The bullish trend is also seen in the global crypto market capitalization, which is trading at a higher level, around $1.06 trillion, up 1.27% in the last 24 hours, according to Tradingview. Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has continued with its bullishness as it surged its price above the USD$23,000 level, a positive signal amid miners reduced the sales of their mined coins.<a href="https://twitter.com/BTC_Archive/status/1617839204670803968" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> On-chain flows</a> flagged by Bitifinex analysts indicate that the amount of Bitcoin moved from Bitcoin mining addresses to wallets owned by cryptocurrency exchanges has declined to multi-year lows.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-517331 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-3.jpg" alt="Bitcoin transfer volume from miners to exchanges" width="680" height="374" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-3.jpg 680w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-3-460x253.jpg 460w" sizes="(max-width: 680px) 100vw, 680px" />
<h2>Selling Power Low, Favorable For A BTC Rally                      </h2>
<p>As per a <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-shorts-decline-on-bitfinex-players-brace-for-upward-trend/">Bitfinex</a> analyst, Bitcoin miner sales are at a three-year low. The report claims that the selling could be a sign that Bitcoin miners are in the mood to accumulate coins as they expect the surge of prices of the flagship cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>The declined <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin-mining-stocks-in-solid-gains/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> sales from mining companies mean low selling pressure from these market actors. Therefore, it signals bullishness for the broader market.</p>

<p>The analysts, however, stated that the recent uptick in Bitcoin price might witness a correction as investors try to recoup their profits amid the current price surges.</p>
<p>The analysts identified large wallet sizes (&gt;$1M) as the majorly responsible for accumulating Bitcoin. They further said such wallets, as well as major market actors, are the ones creating the buying pressure that comes after the FTX saga and a series of bearish events generally witnessed last year.</p>
<p>The analysts mentioned that since the second week of January, the numbers of wallets with $1,000 and $10,000 worth of Bitcoin have increased. The analyst further acknowledged that the trading activities of retail investors had accompanied the uptrend.</p>
<p>According to the figure above, the current low Bitcoin selling pressure coincided with the lowest sales in November last year. The current low level signals a green (bullish) indicator for the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>When miners sell more BTC, it implies a bearish for the coin value. Conversely, when mining firms don’t have the selling urge, this suggests a <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/sell-pressure-mounts-on-bitcoin/">bullish trend</a> for the crypto market.</p>

<h2>Today&#8217;s Bitcoin Price</h2>
<p>Bitcoin has surged its value by almost 40% this month, trading at $22,909, up 1.48% on Tuesday. The crypto is trading at levels not witnessed since the downfall of the FTX exchange. <a href="https://newsbtc.com/press-releases/bitcoin-btc-ethereum-eth-bullrun-toon-finance-presale-ends-in-less-than-2-days/">BTC</a> volume stands at about $26.82 billion, an increase of 12.78% in the past 24 hours, as per Coinmarketcap.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/NObeA1fj/" alt="BTCUSDT price chart on TradingView" width="1575" height="808" />
<p>As highlighted above, the rise in Bitcoin value could be attributed to whales committed to accumulating coins amid surging prices. The bullish trend is also seen in the global crypto market capitalization, which is trading at a higher level, around $1.06 trillion, up 1.27% in the last 24 hours, according to Tradingview.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-1.jpg" width="350" height="250" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Repeat Of April 2019? Bitcoin Rally Shows Similar Break Above These Key Levels</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/repeat-april-2019-bitcoin-rally-levels/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 18:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin long-term holders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Realized Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin short-term holders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517291</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows Bitcoin has broken above these three key levels in a manner reminiscent of the rally in April 2019. Bitcoin Breakout Shows Initial Similarities To April 2019 Rally According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Glassnode, BTC has broken above the three investor cost-basis levels for the first time since the COVID-19 crash and the 2018-2019 bear market. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;realized price,&#8221; to understand the concept of the &#8220;realized cap&#8221; it needs to be looked at first. The realized cap is a capitalization model for Bitcoin that assumes that each coin in the circulating supply has its real value as the price at which it was last moved rather than the current BTC price (which the normal market cap uses for its calculation). Now, from the realized cap, a &#8220;realized price&#8221; can be obtained by dividing the metric by the total number of coins in circulation. Since the realized cap accounted for the prices at which investors bought their coins (which is to say, their cost basis), the realized price can be thought of as the average acquisition price in the market. This means that if the normal price of Bitcoin dips below this indicator, the average holder can be assumed to have entered a state of loss. While this realized price is the average cost basis for the entire market, the metric can also be defined for only specific groups of investors. The BTC market can be divided into two primary cohorts: short-term holders (STHs) and long-term holders (LTHs). Investors who bought their coins within the last 155 days fall into the STHs, while those holding them since before that threshold are included in the LTHs. Related Reading: Dogecoin Whale Transfers $5M In DOGE To Coinbase, Bearish Signal? Here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin realized price for the entire market, as well as for these two holder groups separately, over the last few years: BTC seems to have broken above all these levels recently &#124; Source: Glassnode on Twitter As the above graph shows, Bitcoin had broken above the STH cost basis and the entire market&#8217;s realized price earlier in the latest rally, suggesting that the average STH and the overall average investor was back in profit. In the most recent continuation to the rally, the crypto has now surged above the LTH cost basis of $22,400. This means that the average investor in every segment is now in the green. Related Reading: Bitcoin Puell Multiple Starts To Leave Bear Market Zone, Bull Rally Here? The last time Bitcoin displayed a breakout above all these levels was following the black swan COVID-19 crash, which had briefly taken the coin below these prices. A similar trend also formed in April 2019, when the bear market of that cycle ended, and a bullish transition took place. Though it&#8217;s early to tell right now, this similarity between the two rallies could hint about the path that the current one might also end up following. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $22,900, up 8% in the last week. Looks like BTC has been moving sideways in the last few days &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Glassnode.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows Bitcoin has broken above these three key levels in a manner reminiscent of the rally in April 2019.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Breakout Shows Initial Similarities To April 2019 Rally</h2>
<p>According to data from the on-chain analytics firm <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1617865019508539392" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Glassnode</a>, BTC has broken above the three investor cost-basis levels for the first time since the COVID-19 crash and the 2018-2019 bear market. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;realized price,&#8221; to understand the concept of the &#8220;<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-long-term-holders-own-80-realized-cap/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">realized cap</a>&#8221; it needs to be looked at first.</p>
<p>The realized cap is a capitalization model for Bitcoin that assumes that each coin in the circulating supply has its real value as the price at which it was last moved rather than the current BTC price (which the normal market cap uses for its calculation).</p>
<p>Now, from the realized cap, a &#8220;<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-under-realized-price-163-days/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">realized price</a>&#8221; can be obtained by dividing the metric by the total number of coins in circulation. Since the realized cap accounted for the prices at which investors bought their coins (which is to say, their cost basis), the realized price can be thought of as the average acquisition price in the market.</p>
<p>This means that if the normal price of Bitcoin dips below this indicator, the average holder can be assumed to have entered a state of loss. While this realized price is the average cost basis for the entire market, the metric can also be defined for only specific groups of investors.</p>
<p>The BTC market can be divided into two primary cohorts: short-term holders (STHs) and <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin-holders-losing-faith-in-btc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">long-term holders</a> (LTHs). Investors who bought their coins within the last 155 days fall into the STHs, while those holding them since before that threshold are included in the LTHs.</p>

<p>Here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin realized price for the entire market, as well as for these two holder groups separately, over the last few years:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FnPPpcNXEAEUuPc?format=png&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Bitcoin Realized Price" width="4096" height="2359" /></p>

<p>As the above graph shows, Bitcoin had broken above the STH cost basis and the entire market&#8217;s realized price earlier in the latest rally, suggesting that the average STH and the overall average investor was back in profit.</p>
<p>In the most recent continuation to the rally, the crypto has now surged above the LTH cost basis of $22,400. This means that the average investor in every segment is now in the green.</p>

<p>The last time Bitcoin displayed a breakout above all these levels was following the black swan COVID-19 crash, which had briefly taken the coin below these prices.</p>
<p>A similar trend also formed in April 2019, when the bear market of that cycle ended, and a bullish transition took place. Though it&#8217;s early to tell right now, this similarity between the two rallies could hint about the path that the current one might also end up following.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $22,900, up 8% in the last week.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-517317 size-large aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-36-860x315.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="860" height="315" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-36-860x315.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-36-460x168.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-36-768x281.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-36-750x274.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-36.png 987w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/kanchanara-rhm7H8X5J98-unsplash-1-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Money Leaves ADA, SOL To Small Cap Altcoins, Here’s Where It’s Headed</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/altcoin/money-leaves-to-small-cap-altcoins/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 17:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[small-cap altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sol]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517270</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[With the crypto market rally, altcoins have benefitted just as much as bitcoin. Digital assets across the space have been able to return to their pre-FTX collapse levels, signaling the start of a bull run. However, as the market begins to settle into this new normal, investors are moving gains around from larger cap assets to take advantage of possible price movement in smaller altcoins. Cycling Out Money To Small Cap Altcoins A recent report from on-chain data aggregation website Santiment shows that investors may be moving money out of larger cap coins such as Cardano and Solana and moving to small cap coins. This paints a picture of a rotation of funds rather than outright pulling money out of the crypto sector. Related Reading: Bullish Indicator: Bitcoin Shakes Off Genesis Bankruptcy Filing Santiment notes that the large gains recorded by the likes of Solana, Cardano, and Polkadot are now being moved into smaller altcoins. Most of these coins are top 200 and below tokens with market caps lower than $300 million. The cycling of funds into these smaller altcoins is shown by their address activity. The image shared by Santiment shows a significant uptick in the address activities of these coins. Most notably, the uptick was seen from last week as a lot of these larger cap coins hit new local peaks. Money flows out from large cap to small cap altcoins &#124; Source: Santiment The small cap coins mentioned in the report are TRADE, RBN, SLP, PLSPAD, POND, MITX, MTH, and CBG. Most of these are coins flying under the radar. Ribbon Finance (RBN) which is the most prominent on the list is only at a $139.7 million market cap but has risen 24% in the last seven days. What Happens To These Tokens? The tokens mentioned by Santiment are still small enough that they can see prominent movement with just a fraction of the amount needed to move the prices of the likes of SOL and ADA. This means that if this rotation of gains from large caps to small cap altcoins continues, then these tokens could see positive movement in the coming days. Related Reading: Crypto Analyst Says Bitcoin Price Could See Another 30% Rally However, for coins with such low market caps, just as it is easy to pump their prices, it is also just as easy to drag their prices down with sell-offs from a few large holders. It becomes a double-edged sword for investors who follow the movement. On one hand, it could mean very large gains in a short time, but on the other hand, could see them lose money fast. A good thing about this though is that attention is being spread out instead of just focusing on a handful of coins. As wallet activity rises for these altcoins, it could trigger exploration into similarly priced altcoins which could benefit from new interest. Crypto market cap crosses $1 trillion as investors move money around &#124; Source: Crypto Total Market Cap on TradingView.com Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from MARCA, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">With the crypto market rally, altcoins have benefitted just as much as bitcoin. Digital assets across the space have been able to return to their pre-FTX collapse levels, signaling the start of a bull run. However, as the market begins to settle into this new normal, investors are moving gains around from larger cap assets to take advantage of possible price movement in smaller altcoins.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Cycling Out Money To Small Cap Altcoins</h2>
<p class="p2">A recent report from on-chain data aggregation website Santiment <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1617682191600996353?s=20&amp;t=ZnD6wURbfJjk8V1lX-hoig" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">shows</a> that investors may be moving money out of larger cap coins such as Cardano and Solana and moving to small cap coins. This paints a picture of a rotation of funds rather than outright pulling money out of the crypto sector.</p>

<p class="p2">Santiment notes that the large gains recorded by the likes of Solana, Cardano, and Polkadot are now being moved into smaller altcoins. Most of these coins are top 200 and below tokens with market caps lower than $300 million.</p>
<p class="p2">The cycling of funds into these smaller altcoins is shown by their address activity. The image shared by Santiment shows a significant uptick in the address activities of these coins. Most notably, the uptick was seen from last week as a lot of these larger cap coins hit new local peaks.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-517271 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Santiment-ADA-SOL-small-cap-altcoins-460x295.jpeg" alt="Santiment ADA SOL small cap altcoins" width="460" height="295" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Santiment-ADA-SOL-small-cap-altcoins-460x295.jpeg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Santiment-ADA-SOL-small-cap-altcoins-860x551.jpeg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Santiment-ADA-SOL-small-cap-altcoins-768x492.jpeg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Santiment-ADA-SOL-small-cap-altcoins-1536x984.jpeg 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Santiment-ADA-SOL-small-cap-altcoins-2048x1312.jpeg 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Santiment-ADA-SOL-small-cap-altcoins-750x480.jpeg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Santiment-ADA-SOL-small-cap-altcoins-1140x730.jpeg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p class="p2">The small cap coins mentioned in the report are TRADE, RBN, SLP, PLSPAD, POND, MITX, MTH, and CBG. Most of these are coins flying under the radar. Ribbon Finance (RBN) which is the most prominent on the list is only at a $139.7 million market cap but has risen 24% in the last seven days.</p>
<h2 class="p2">What Happens To These Tokens?</h2>
<p class="p2">The tokens mentioned by Santiment are still small enough that they can see prominent movement with just a fraction of the amount needed to move the prices of the likes of SOL and ADA. This means that if this rotation of gains from large caps to small cap altcoins continues, then these tokens could see positive movement in the coming days.</p>

<p class="p2">However, for coins with such low market caps, just as it is easy to pump their prices, it is also just as easy to drag their prices down with sell-offs from a few large holders. It becomes a double-edged sword for investors who follow the movement. On one hand, it could mean very large gains in a short time, but on the other hand, could see them lose money fast.</p>
<p class="p2">A good thing about this though is that attention is being spread out instead of just focusing on a handful of coins. As wallet activity rises for these altcoins, it could trigger exploration into similarly priced altcoins which could benefit from new interest.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/IGYgj83G/" alt="Crypto total market cap chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1610" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Small-cap-altcoins-460x259.jpeg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana (SOL) Network On Hyperdrive As TVL And NFT Trade Volume Soars</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/solana-network-on-hyperdrive/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 15:38:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Saga Pass Cards]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL NFT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517304</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) is on hyperdrive as the network quickly gains momentum in terms of liquidity which are seen at more than 300% as of press time. Following a sweeping price decline, Solana has turned the tide with metrics with flying colors. Here&#8217;s a quick glance at SOL performance of late: SOL metrics and trustworthiness score looking positive Solana’s TVL seen to jump higher Solana rolls out Saga Pass Cards There is sizeable growth seen both in terms of NFT with the rollout of the Saga Pass Cards and market cap. Solana was seen to nosedive the past couple of weeks, but it’s now back on the top 10 cryptocurrencies list that is stacked at the green lane. Related Reading: Aptos Climbs 75% – What Keeps APT In The Green In Last 7 Days SOL Price Gaining Traction According to price monitoring by Coingecko, SOL price is currently trading at $24.28, up 3.0% in the last seven days. Evidently, following the FTX crash, short-term traders and the bulls were fixated on SOL which unlocked roughly 100 million coins from different contacts which could have punched a hole in the market, driving the price of SOL to null or $0. But, that didn’t happen as SOL holders chose to hold out their coins waiting for better days and not panic and sell their SOL holdings. True enough, the market gained traction and recovered with most assets moving north, including SOL which made the investors extremely happy with the gains. SOL total market cap at $8.9 billion on the daily chart &#124; Chart: TradingView.com With this hypergrowth happening with Solana, the investors decided to accumulate longs which triggered SOL’s open interest to accelerate higher. As a matter of fact, around $460 million worth of orders is currently open at crypto derivative exchanges. Could this be bad news for SOL? Now, the open interest really isn’t the culprit here as it can’t really pull SOL price down but it’s the increased number of longs that could trigger a squeeze brought about by SOL holders rapidly selling their holdings to counterpunch future risks. On the brighter side, nothing is set in stone and SOL holders and investors need not panic right now as SOL has not gained much momentum yet to trigger millions in the liquidation of assets. SOL Currently In No. 2 Spot On Top Chains List SOL is performing so well that it managed to jump to the second spot on the top chains list in terms of NFT trade volume seen in the past month. SOL’s NFT trade volume is seen to spike and gain momentum in the past couple of weeks. Top chains by NFT volume (30 days) 🥇@ethereum 🥈@solana 🥉@0xPolygon 4️⃣@Immutable 5️⃣@Cardano 6️⃣@flow_blockchain 7️⃣@BNBCHAIN pic.twitter.com/trNHUxk1fB — Delphi Digital (@Delphi_Digital) January 21, 2023 Solana Mobile has announced that they would be rolling out new cards on rotation. Basically, the first card is exclusive only to holders of the OG Saga Pass, and then a random card will be introduced every week. Additionally, the Saga Pass Card Collection is set to be verified via MagicEden real soon. SOL TVL. Image: Defillama Related Reading: ApeCoin Buckles As News Of Stolen BAYC NFT Hits The Market Meanwhile, according to DeFiLlama&#8217;s numbers, the total value locked in the network has been on the rise since the start of the year, which is encouraging. Featured image by Manula.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Solana (SOL) is on hyperdrive as the network quickly gains momentum in terms of liquidity which are seen at more than <a href="https://u.today/solana-sol-hits-4x-in-open-interest-heres-why-it-might-end-ugly?amp" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">300%</a> as of press time. Following a sweeping price decline, Solana has turned the tide with metrics with flying colors.</p>
<p>Here&#8217;s a quick glance at SOL performance of late:</p>
<ul>
<li>SOL metrics and trustworthiness score looking positive</li>
<li>Solana’s TVL seen to jump higher</li>
<li>Solana rolls out Saga Pass Cards</li>
</ul>
<p>There is sizeable growth seen both in terms of NFT with the rollout of the Saga Pass Cards and market cap.</p>
<p>Solana was seen to nosedive the past couple of weeks, but it’s now back on the top 10 cryptocurrencies list that is stacked at the green lane.</p>

<h2><b>SOL Price Gaining Traction</b></h2>
<p>According to<a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/solana/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> price monitoring</a> by Coingecko, SOL price is currently trading at $24.28, up 3.0% in the last seven days.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-517305 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-71.png" alt="" width="789" height="95" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-71.png 789w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-71-460x55.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-71-768x92.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-71-750x90.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 789px) 100vw, 789px" /></p>
<p>Evidently, following the<a href="https://www.investopedia.com/what-went-wrong-with-ftx-6828447" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> FTX crash,</a> short-term traders and the bulls were fixated on SOL which unlocked roughly 100 million coins from different contacts which could have punched a hole in the market, driving the price of SOL to null or $0.</p>
<p> But, that didn’t happen as SOL holders chose to hold out their coins waiting for better days and not panic and sell their SOL holdings.</p>
<p>True enough, the market gained traction and recovered with most assets moving north, including SOL which made the investors extremely happy with the gains.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/PcgQHqen/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>

<p>With this hypergrowth happening with Solana, the investors decided to accumulate longs which triggered <a href="https://u.today/solana-sol-hits-4x-in-open-interest-heres-why-it-might-end-ugly" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">SOL’s open interest</a> to accelerate higher. As a matter of fact, around $460 million worth of orders is currently open at crypto derivative exchanges. Could this be bad news for SOL?</p>
<p>Now, the open interest really isn’t the culprit here as it can’t really pull SOL price down but it’s the increased number of longs that could trigger a squeeze brought about by SOL holders rapidly selling their holdings to counterpunch future risks.</p>
<p>On the brighter side, nothing is set in stone and SOL holders and investors need not panic right now as SOL has not gained much momentum yet to trigger millions in the liquidation of assets.</p>
<h2><b>SOL Currently In No. 2 Spot On Top Chains List</b></h2>
<p>SOL is performing so well that it managed to jump to the second spot on the top chains list in terms of NFT trade volume seen in the past month. SOL’s NFT trade volume is seen to spike and gain momentum in the past couple of weeks.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Top chains by NFT volume (30 days)</p>
<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f947.png" alt="🥇" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><a href="https://twitter.com/ethereum?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@ethereum</a>
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f948.png" alt="🥈" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><a href="https://twitter.com/solana?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@solana</a>
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f949.png" alt="🥉" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><a href="https://twitter.com/0xPolygon?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@0xPolygon</a>
4&#x20e3;<a href="https://twitter.com/Immutable?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@Immutable</a>
5&#x20e3;<a href="https://twitter.com/Cardano?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@Cardano</a>
6&#x20e3;<a href="https://twitter.com/flow_blockchain?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@flow_blockchain</a>
7&#x20e3;<a href="https://twitter.com/BNBCHAIN?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@BNBCHAIN</a> <a href="https://t.co/trNHUxk1fB" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/trNHUxk1fB</a></p>
<p>— Delphi Digital (@Delphi_Digital) <a href="https://twitter.com/Delphi_Digital/status/1616842728838414337?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 21, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Solana Mobile has announced that they would be rolling out new cards on rotation. Basically, the first card is exclusive only to holders of the OG Saga Pass, and then a random card will be introduced every week.</p>
<p>Additionally, the Saga Pass Card Collection is set to be verified via MagicEden real soon.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-517306 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-72-860x283.png" alt="" width="860" height="283" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-72-860x283.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-72-460x151.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-72-768x253.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-72-750x247.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-72-1140x375.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-72.png 1385w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>


<p>Meanwhile, according to DeFiLlama&#8217;s numbers, the total value locked in the network has been on the rise since the start of the year, which is encouraging.</p>
<p><em>Featured image by Manula.com</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Solana-7-460x259.png" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>ApeCoin Buckles As News Of Stolen BAYC NFT Hits The Market </title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/apecoin-buckles-on-stolen-bayc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 14:03:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[APE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ApeCoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bored Ape Yacht Club]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517295</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Bored Ape Yacht Club NFT collection has been the target of an exploit this January 20th. FranklinIsbored, one of the biggest holders of BAYC NFTs, is targeted with an exploit of OpenSea’s stolen ApeCoin policy which allowed the attacker to sell a marked Bored Ape.  This Bored Ape was marked  as “under review for suspicious activity” which supposedly locks the NFT from being sold. Franklin has been the target of this exploit for the second time this week with the first one being January 20.  Hey @opensea can you PLEASE fix your stolen ape policy? This ape with a yellow caution mark sold to my OpenSea WETH offer for 65 WETH. You collected 1.625 WETH in fees, and I cannot resell this ape. It was already marked before the sale happened. You have failed with this policy. pic.twitter.com/jGO9sClKbi — Franklin (@franklinisbored) January 20, 2023 Since then, ApeCoin, the native token of the Bored Ape Yacht Club ecosystem, has fallen 1.3% in value in the past 24 hours. APE is currently trading at $5.80, up 16.6% in the last seven days, data from Coingecko show.  The Gist Of The Situation The two exploits happened within three days of each other. According to Franklin’s tweets, the flagged apes can’t be sold since they are subjected for review. These stolen assets shouldn’t have been sold in the open market according to OpenSea’s stolen item policy.  The exploit works as the attacker uses OpenSea’s “Match Advance Order” system to “Mint” and sell it to Franklin. According to recent news, the total amount of Bored Ape and Mutant Ape NFTs being stolen has now reached nearly $20 million.  It happened again &#8211; second time in a week someone has exploited OpenSea&#8217;s stolen ape policy to sell to my collection offer after it was already marked as &#8220;under review for suspicious activity&#8221; (yellow mark). They used a &#8220;Match Advanced Order&#8221; function to &#8220;Mint&#8221; and sell to me. pic.twitter.com/21hijgtUse — Franklin (@franklinisbored) January 22, 2023 OpenSea has not been transparent with the amount of stolen NFTs on the platform. Beetle, a self-described on-chain sleuth, has recently released charts of the platform’s number of stolen NFTs. In total, 1,278 NFTs have fallen in the hands of cyber-thieves within the platform. The NFT marketplace has not responded since the news hit the market.  Bored Ape. Image: Forbes ApeCoin Still Showing Potential Even with the negative news surrounding BAYC, the token is still poised to see gains in the coming days. At the time of writing, the charts show that ApeCoin bulls are able to break through the $5.867 resistance.  For the bullish momentum to continue, the token should close today above its current resistance which would give the bulls a chance to move upwards. However, if the resistance holds, a retest of the $5.063 support could occur in the coming days.  Related Reading: THETA Breaches $1 Level Courtesy Of Solid On-Chain Developments Crypto total market cap now showing signs of strength and reclaims the $1 trillion territory &#124; Chart: TradingView.com Related Reading: Aptos Climbs 75% – What Keeps APT In The Green In Last 7 Days The token also has a strong correlation with Bitcoin which is retesting the $23,000 resistance. If Bitcoin closes above this crucial $23k resistance, ApeCoin will have the boost needed to grab its September 2022 price levels.  For now, investors and traders should focus on breaking through ApeCoin current resistance as a breakthrough on this level would mean more gains in the medium and long term.  -Featured image from African Wildlife Foundation]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Bored Ape Yacht Club NFT collection has been the target of an exploit this January 20th. <a href="https://twitter.com/franklinisbored" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">FranklinIsbored</a>, one of the biggest holders of BAYC NFTs, is targeted with an exploit of OpenSea’s stolen ApeCoin policy which allowed the attacker to sell a marked Bored Ape. </p>
<p>This Bored Ape was marked  as “under review for suspicious activity” which supposedly locks the NFT from being sold. Franklin has been the target of this exploit for the second time this week with the first one being <a href="https://twitter.com/franklinisbored/status/1616315985857810433" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">January 20</a>. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Hey <a href="https://twitter.com/opensea?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@opensea</a> can you PLEASE fix your stolen ape policy? This ape with a yellow caution mark sold to my OpenSea WETH offer for 65 WETH. You collected 1.625 WETH in fees, and I cannot resell this ape. It was already marked before the sale happened. You have failed with this policy. <a href="https://t.co/jGO9sClKbi" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/jGO9sClKbi</a></p>
<p>— Franklin (@franklinisbored) <a href="https://twitter.com/franklinisbored/status/1616315985857810433?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 20, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Since then, ApeCoin, the native token of the Bored Ape Yacht Club ecosystem, has fallen 1.3% in value in the past 24 hours. <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">APE</a> is currently trading at $5.80, up 16.6% in the last seven days, data from Coingecko show. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-517297 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-69.png" alt="" width="789" height="94" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-69.png 789w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-69-460x55.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-69-768x91.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-69-750x89.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 789px) 100vw, 789px" /></p>
<h2><strong>The Gist Of The Situation</strong></h2>
<p>The two exploits happened within three days of each other. According to Franklin’s tweets, the flagged apes can’t be sold since they are subjected for review. These stolen assets shouldn’t have been sold in the open market according to <a href="https://support.opensea.io/hc/en-us/articles/4815371492499-What-is-OpenSea-s-stolen-item-policy-" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">OpenSea’s stolen item policy</a>. </p>
<p>The exploit works as the attacker <a href="https://twitter.com/franklinisbored/status/1617239670391459840?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1617239670391459840%7Ctwgr%5E2d1c96546208eac3f11a1d640819ccc578d5a4b5%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fambcrypto.com%2Fapecoin-ape-breaks-even-as-bayc-robbery-cases-persists%2F" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">uses</a> OpenSea’s “Match Advance Order” system to “Mint” and sell it to Franklin. According to recent news, the total amount of Bored Ape and Mutant Ape NFTs being stolen has now <a href="https://decrypt.co/104656/bored-ape-ethereum-nfts-stolen-opensea-18-million" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">reached</a> nearly $20 million. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">It happened again &#8211; second time in a week someone has exploited OpenSea&#8217;s stolen ape policy to sell to my collection offer after it was already marked as &#8220;under review for suspicious activity&#8221; (yellow mark). They used a &#8220;Match Advanced Order&#8221; function to &#8220;Mint&#8221; and sell to me. <a href="https://t.co/21hijgtUse" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/21hijgtUse</a></p>
<p>— Franklin (@franklinisbored) <a href="https://twitter.com/franklinisbored/status/1617239670391459840?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 22, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>OpenSea has not been transparent with the amount of stolen NFTs on the platform. <a href="https://twitter.com/1kbeetlejuice" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Beetle</a>, a self-described on-chain sleuth, has recently released <a href="https://dune.com/beetle/opensea-stolen-assets-top-pfp-collections" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">charts</a> of the platform’s number of stolen NFTs. In total, 1,278 NFTs have fallen in the hands of cyber-thieves within the platform.</p>
<p>The NFT marketplace has not responded since the news hit the market. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-517300 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-70.png" alt="" width="768" height="384" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-70.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-70-460x230.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-70-360x180.png 360w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-70-750x375.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /></p>

<h2><strong>ApeCoin Still Showing Potential</strong></h2>
<p>Even with the negative news surrounding BAYC, the token is still poised to see gains in the coming days. At the time of writing, the charts show that ApeCoin bulls are able to break through the $5.867 resistance. </p>
<p>For the bullish momentum to continue, the token should close today above its current resistance which would give the bulls a chance to move upwards. However, if the resistance holds, a retest of the $5.063 support could occur in the coming days. </p>

<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/N17DtUwg/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>


<p>The token also has a strong correlation with Bitcoin which is retesting the $23,000 resistance. If Bitcoin closes above this crucial $23k resistance, ApeCoin will have the boost needed to grab its September 2022 price levels. </p>
<p>For now, investors and traders should focus on breaking through ApeCoin current resistance as a breakthrough on this level would mean more gains in the medium and long term. </p>
<p><em>-Featured image from African Wildlife Foundation</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ape-460x306.png" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Whale Transfers $5M In DOGE To Coinbase, Bearish Signal?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/dogecoin-whale-5m-doge-coinbase-bearish/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 13:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin Bearish Signal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin Whale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Whale]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517278</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Data shows a Dogecoin whale has deposited more than $5 million in the crypto to Coinbase. Here&#8217;s what it may mean for DOGE&#8217;s price. Dogecoin Whale Sends 57 Million DOGE To Crypto Exchange Coinbase As per data from the crypto transaction tracker service Whale Alert, a massive Dogecoin transaction has taken place on the blockchain today. In total, this transfer involved the movement of 57,056,400 DOGE, worth upwards of $5 million at the time the transaction was sent. Since the amount here is so large, the entity behind the transfer is likely to be a whale, or at least a group made up of multiple large investors. Due to the sheer volume of tokens involved in transactions like these, they can sometimes cause noticeable ripples in the price of the asset. But what change may potentially be produced in the crypto&#8217;s value from such a movement of coins depends on several factors, with the exact intent behind the transaction being the main one. Related Reading: Bitcoin Puell Multiple Starts To Leave Bear Market Zone, Bull Rally Here? Here are some specifics surrounding the latest Dogecoin whale transaction, which may shed some light on why the investor decided to make this move: Looks like the holder only had to pay a small fee of $0.21 for this massive transfer to be possible &#124; Source: Whale Alert As can be seen above, the sending address for this Dogecoin transaction was an unknown address, which is a type of address that&#8217;s unattached to any known centralized platform, and thus is likely a personal wallet. The receiver in this case was an address affiliated with the crypto exchange Coinbase. Note that the transaction details show there being another receiver present for this transaction, with the total amount of the transfer being almost $10.5 million. But on closer inspection, it&#8217;s clear that it&#8217;s just the same address as the sender, meaning that this output is only showing the amount still remaining in the original wallet (that is, a bit more than $5.3 million, as $5.1 million went towards Coinbase). Related Reading: Bitcoin Bullish Signal: Whales Go On $1.4B Buying Spree A transaction like this where coins move from a personal wallet to an exchange is called an exchange inflow. Investors usually deposit to exchanges for selling purposes, so inflows can have bearish implications for the price of the meme coin. If this Dogecoin whale truly made this transfer with the intent to sell on Coinbase, then DOGE may feel a negative effect from it. Data from WhaleStats, however, shows that the crypto was in the top 10 most bought tokens by the largest BNB Smart Chain (BSC) whales just yesterday. JUST IN: $DOGE @dogecoin now on top 10 purchased tokens among 100 biggest #BSC whales in the last 24hrs 🐳 Check the top 100 whales here: https://t.co/0SYnjw0xQs (and hodl $BBW to see data for the top 4000!)#DOGE #whalestats #babywhale #BBW pic.twitter.com/G6RCR4INnt &#8212; WhaleStats &#8211; the top 1000 BSC richlist (@WhaleStatsBSC) January 23, 2023 Such accumulation from whales can generally be bullish for the price, so depending on the scale of these purchases, they can make up for any possible selling pressure today&#8217;s whale may cause. In such a scenario, Dogecoin would likely not feel any impact from the exchange inflow. DOGE Price At the time of writing, Dogecoin is trading around $0.0889, up 5% in the last week. The value of the crypto seems to have climbed up in recent days &#124; Source: DOGEUSD on TradingView Featured image from Richard Sagredo on Unsplash.com, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Data shows a Dogecoin whale has deposited more than $5 million in the crypto to Coinbase. Here&#8217;s what it may mean for DOGE&#8217;s price.</p>
<h2>Dogecoin Whale Sends 57 Million DOGE To Crypto Exchange Coinbase</h2>
<p>As per data from the crypto transaction tracker service <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1617780623292203009" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Whale Alert</a>, a massive Dogecoin transaction has taken place on the blockchain today. In total, this transfer involved the movement of 57,056,400 DOGE, worth upwards of $5 million at the time the transaction was sent.</p>
<p>Since the amount here is so large, the entity behind the transfer is likely to be a <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/whales-bag-500m-dogecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">whale</a>, or at least a group made up of multiple large investors. Due to the sheer volume of tokens involved in transactions like these, they can sometimes cause noticeable ripples in the price of the asset.</p>
<p>But what change may potentially be produced in the crypto&#8217;s value from such a movement of coins depends on several factors, with the exact intent behind the transaction being the main one.</p>

<p>Here are some specifics surrounding the latest Dogecoin whale transaction, which may shed some light on why the investor decided to make this move:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-517279 size-large aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-34-860x474.png" alt="Dogecoin Whale Inflow" width="860" height="474" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-34-860x474.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-34-460x253.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-34-768x423.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-34-750x413.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-34.png 1009w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>

<p>As can be seen above, the sending address for this Dogecoin transaction was an unknown address, which is a type of address that&#8217;s unattached to any known centralized platform, and thus is likely a personal wallet. The receiver in this case was an address affiliated with the crypto exchange <a href="https://newsbtc.com/crypto/coinbase-binance-crypto-price-manipulation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a>.</p>
<p>Note that the transaction details show there being another receiver present for this transaction, with the total amount of the transfer being almost $10.5 million. But on closer inspection, it&#8217;s clear that it&#8217;s just the same address as the sender, meaning that this output is only showing the amount still remaining in the original wallet (that is, a bit more than $5.3 million, as $5.1 million went towards Coinbase).</p>

<p>A transaction like this where coins move from a personal wallet to an exchange is called an exchange inflow. Investors usually deposit to exchanges for selling purposes, so inflows can have bearish implications for the price of the meme coin.</p>
<p>If this Dogecoin whale truly made this transfer with the intent to sell on Coinbase, then DOGE may feel a negative effect from it. Data from WhaleStats, however, shows that the crypto was in the top 10 most bought tokens by the largest <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/ripple/preference-for-ripple-xrp-surges-among-bsc-whales/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BNB Smart Chain (BSC) whales</a> just yesterday.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">JUST IN: <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24DOGE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$DOGE</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/dogecoin?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@dogecoin</a> now on top 10 purchased tokens among 100 biggest <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BSC?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#BSC</a> whales in the last 24hrs <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f433.png" alt="🐳" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>Check the top 100 whales here: <a href="https://t.co/0SYnjw0xQs" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">https://t.co/0SYnjw0xQs</a></p>
<p>(and hodl <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BBW&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$BBW</a> to see data for the top 4000!)<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/DOGE?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#DOGE</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/whalestats?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#whalestats</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/babywhale?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#babywhale</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BBW?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#BBW</a> <a href="https://t.co/G6RCR4INnt" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/G6RCR4INnt</a></p>
<p>&mdash; WhaleStats &#8211; the top 1000 BSC richlist (@WhaleStatsBSC) <a href="https://twitter.com/WhaleStatsBSC/status/1617318775988129794?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 23, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>Such accumulation from whales can generally be bullish for the price, so depending on the scale of these purchases, they can make up for any possible selling pressure today&#8217;s whale may cause. In such a scenario, Dogecoin would likely not feel any impact from the exchange inflow.</p>
<h2>DOGE Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Dogecoin is trading around $0.0889, up 5% in the last week.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-517283 size-large aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-35-860x318.png" alt="Dogecoin Price CHart" width="860" height="318" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-35-860x318.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-35-460x170.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-35-768x284.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-35-750x277.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-35.png 976w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/richard-sagredo-ZC2PWF4jTHc-unsplash-460x329.jpg" width="460" height="329" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Bull Trap Or Bull Run? This Is What Glassnode Says</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-bull-trap-or-bull-run-glassnode/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 09:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[glassnode]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517238</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin price is up 40% year-to-date (YTD) and has recaptured the $23,000 level. However, with ongoing concerns around DCG and Grayscale as well as macroeconomic uncertainties, many investors doubt the sustainability of the recent price rally. With higher prices, motivation among investors may be increasing to use the current price level to exit and gain liquidity, especially after the long and painful bear market in 2022, as Glassnode discusses in its report. The renowned on-chain analysis firm examines in its newest research whether Bitcoin&#8217;s recent bounce above the price it has last seen before the FTX collapse is a bull trap or if indeed a new bull run is on the horizon. Bitcoin On-Chain-Data Suggests Glassnode notes in its report that the recent price spike in the $21,000-$23,000 region has resulted in the reclamation of several on-chain price models, which has historically meant a &#8220;psychological shift in holder behavior patterns.&#8221; Related Reading: Bitcoin Weekly RSI Reaches Line Between Bear &#38; Bull Market The company takes a look at the Investor Price and Delta Price, noting that in the 2018-2019 bear market, prices stayed within the confines of the Investor-Delta price band for a similar amount of time (78 days) as they currently do (76 days). &#8220;This suggests an equivalency in durational pain across the darkest phase of both bear markets,&#8221; Glassnodes states. In addition to the duration component of the bottoming phase, Glassnode also points to the compression of the investor delta price range as an indicator of the intensity of market undervaluation. &#8220;Considering the current price and compression value, a similar confirmation signal will be triggered when the market price reclaims $28.3k.&#8221; Regarding the sustainability of the current move, the analysis notes that the recent rally has been accompanied by a sudden increase in the percentage of supply in profit, rising from 55% to over 67%. This sudden increase in 14 days was one of the strongest swings in profitability compared to previous bear markets (+10.6% in 2015 and 8.3% in 2019), which is a bullish signal for Bitcoin. Following last year&#8217;s capitulation events, when a majority of investors were pushed into a loss, the market has now transitioned to a &#8220;regime of profit dominance,&#8221; which Glassnode says is &#8220;a promising sign of healing after the strong deleveraging pressure in the second half of 2022.&#8221; Less bullish, however, is the selling pressure from Bitcoin short-term holders (STHs), traditionally &#8220;an influential factor in the formation of local recovery (or correction) pivots.&#8221; The recent surge has pushed this metric above 97.5% in profit for the first time since its November 2021 all-time high, massively increasing the likelihood of selling pressure from STHs. Long-term Bitcoin holders (LTHs) have risen back above the cost basis at current prices after 6.5 months, which is at $22,600. This means that the average LTH is now just above its breakeven base. Indeed, the current trend indicates that the bottom could be in: Considering the time length of LTH-MVRV traded below 1 and the lowest printed value, the ongoing bear market has been very comparable with 2018-2019 so far. Glassnode also states that the volume of coins older than 6 months has increased by 301,000 BTC since the beginning of December, proving the strength of the HODLing conviction. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Gearing For Another Lift-Off and Might Surge To $25K On the other hand, miners have used the recent price spike to boost their balance sheets. Miners have spent about 5,600 BTC more than they have received since January 8. In conclusion, the research firm says that it is not yet possible to make a final judgment on whether the next bull market is imminent or whether the bulls are heading into a trap: [H]igher prices and the lure of gains after a prolonged bear market tend to motivate supply to become liquid again. [&#8230;] On the contrary, supply held by long-term holders continues to increase, which can be taken as a signal of strength and conviction [&#8230;]. At press time, the Bitcoin price stood at $23.085, remaining relatively calm after the recent spike. Featured image from iStock, Charts from Glassnode and TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin price is up 40% year-to-date (YTD) and has recaptured the $23,000 level. However, with ongoing <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/firm-warns-bitcoin-eth-investors-over-dcg/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">concerns</a> around DCG and Grayscale as well as macroeconomic uncertainties, many investors doubt the sustainability of the recent price rally.</p>
<p>With higher prices, motivation among investors may be increasing to use the current price level to exit and gain liquidity, especially after the long and painful bear market in 2022, as Glassnode discusses in its report.</p>
<p>The renowned on-chain analysis firm examines in its newest research whether Bitcoin&#8217;s recent bounce above the price it has last seen before the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/scaramucci-ftx-cannot-be-saved-sam-betrayed-me/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX collapse</a> is a bull trap or if indeed a new bull run is on the horizon.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin On-Chain-Data Suggests</h2>
<p>Glassnode notes in its <a href="https://insights.glassnode.com/the-week-onchain-week-04-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a> that the recent price spike in the $21,000-$23,000 region has resulted in the reclamation of several on-chain price models, which has historically meant a &#8220;psychological shift in holder behavior patterns.&#8221;</p>

<p>The company takes a look at the Investor Price and Delta Price, noting that in the 2018-2019 bear market, prices stayed within the confines of the Investor-Delta price band for a similar amount of time (78 days) as they currently do (76 days).</p>
<p>&#8220;This suggests an equivalency in durational pain across the darkest phase of both bear markets,&#8221; Glassnodes states.</p>
<p>In addition to the duration component of the bottoming phase, Glassnode also points to the compression of the investor delta price range as an indicator of the intensity of market undervaluation. &#8220;Considering the current price and compression value, a similar confirmation signal will be triggered when the market price reclaims $28.3k.&#8221;</p>
<p>Regarding the sustainability of the current move, the analysis notes that the recent rally has been accompanied by a sudden increase in the percentage of supply in profit, rising from 55% to over 67%.</p>
<p>This sudden increase in 14 days was one of the strongest swings in profitability compared to previous bear markets (+10.6% in 2015 and 8.3% in 2019), which is a bullish signal for Bitcoin.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-517245 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-supply-profitability.png" alt="Bitcoin supply profitability" width="2000" height="1152" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-supply-profitability.png 2000w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-supply-profitability-460x265.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-supply-profitability-860x495.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-supply-profitability-768x442.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-supply-profitability-1536x885.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-supply-profitability-750x432.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-supply-profitability-1140x657.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2000px) 100vw, 2000px" />
<p>Following last year&#8217;s capitulation events, when a majority of investors were pushed into a loss, the market has now transitioned to a &#8220;regime of profit dominance,&#8221; which Glassnode says is &#8220;a promising sign of healing after the strong deleveraging pressure in the second half of 2022.&#8221;</p>
<p>Less bullish, however, is the selling pressure from Bitcoin short-term holders (STHs), traditionally &#8220;an influential factor in the formation of local recovery (or correction) pivots.&#8221; The recent surge has pushed this metric above 97.5% in profit for the first time since its November 2021 all-time high, massively increasing the likelihood of selling pressure from STHs.</p>
<p>Long-term Bitcoin holders (LTHs) have risen back above the cost basis at current prices after 6.5 months, which is at $22,600. This means that the average LTH is now just above its breakeven base. Indeed, the current trend indicates that the bottom could be in:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>Considering the time length of LTH-MVRV traded below 1 and the lowest printed value, the ongoing bear market has been very comparable with 2018-2019 so far.</strong></p></blockquote>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-517247 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-long-Term-Holder.png" alt="Bitcoin long-Term Holder" width="2400" height="1382" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-long-Term-Holder.png 2400w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-long-Term-Holder-460x265.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-long-Term-Holder-860x495.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-long-Term-Holder-768x442.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-long-Term-Holder-1536x884.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-long-Term-Holder-2048x1179.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-long-Term-Holder-750x432.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-long-Term-Holder-1140x656.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2400px) 100vw, 2400px" />
<p>Glassnode also states that the volume of coins older than 6 months has increased by 301,000 BTC since the beginning of December, proving the strength of the HODLing conviction.</p>

<p>On the other hand, miners have used the recent price spike to boost their balance sheets. Miners have spent about 5,600 BTC more than they have received since January 8.</p>
<p>In conclusion, the research firm says that it is not yet possible to make a final judgment on whether the next bull market is imminent or whether the bulls are heading into a trap:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>[H]igher prices and the lure of gains after a prolonged bear market tend to motivate supply to become liquid again. [&#8230;] On the contrary, supply held by long-term holders continues to increase, which can be taken as a signal of strength and conviction [&#8230;].</strong></p></blockquote>
<p>At press time, the Bitcoin price stood at $23.085, remaining relatively calm after the recent spike.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-517249 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-24_09-01-13.png" alt="BTC USD" width="2954" height="1616" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-24_09-01-13.png 2954w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-24_09-01-13-460x252.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-24_09-01-13-860x470.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-24_09-01-13-768x420.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-24_09-01-13-1536x840.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-24_09-01-13-2048x1120.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-24_09-01-13-750x410.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-24_09-01-13-1140x624.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2954px) 100vw, 2954px" />

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/iStock-1255216496-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/

Object Caching 228/231 objects using apc
Page Caching using disk: enhanced (Page is feed) 
Database Caching 34/43 queries in 0.009 seconds using memcached

Served from: newsbtc.com @ 2023-01-24 22:31:55 by W3 Total Cache
-->