<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 05:46:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Price Weakens Below $100 As Bears Extend Their Grip</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin-weakens-below-100/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 05:46:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541927</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Litecoin (LTC) has recently faced a significant decline in its price, with bears gaining momentum as it slumps below the crucial $100 mark. LTC, often referred to as the &#8220;silver to Bitcoin&#8217;s gold,&#8221; has been a favorite among investors seeking an alternative to the pioneer cryptocurrency. The bearish momentum behind Litecoin&#8217;s decline raises questions about the factors driving this price slump and the potential implications for the broader cryptocurrency market.  Will Litecoin be able to regain its strength and recover from this setback, or is there more downside ahead? Related Reading: PEPE Bulls Losing Steam? Fatigue Appears To Undermine Price Rally Bears Pull LTC Price Down Litecoin is currently experiencing a downturn in its price, with CoinGecko reporting it at $93.52. This marks a significant decline of 4.5% within the last 24 hours and a substantial seven-day slump of 17.2%. Source: Coingecko As the price slips below the crucial $100 mark, traders and investors are closely monitoring the situation and assessing the potential factors that could influence LTC&#8217;s rebound. The recent dip below $100 has sparked concerns among market participants, indicating that sellers might be gaining the upper hand. Traders and investors are now paying close attention to the $90-$92 price range as a critical zone that could determine the outcome of the ongoing battle between the bulls and the bears.  LTC market cap currently at $6.8 billion on the daily chart: TradingView.com According to an LTC price report, if the price manages to hold above this level and the bulls can regain control, it could indicate a potential recovery for LTC. However, a breach of this support zone may further fuel the bearish sentiment and lead to additional downward pressure on Litecoin&#8217;s price. Insights And Technical Factors To Consider To anticipate how Litecoin will rebound from this slump, traders and investors should closely examine various insights and technical factors. Factors such as trading volume, price patterns, and support/resistance levels should be considered to gauge the strength of a potential rebound. Related Reading: XRP Next Step: Here’s Why An Upward Move Could Be Likely Apart from technical considerations, market sentiment and external factors also play a crucial role in Litecoin&#8217;s price movement. As the broader cryptocurrency market often influences individual assets, monitoring industry-wide trends becomes vital. LTC seven-day price action. Source: Coingecko Traders and investors should keep a close eye on Bitcoin, the leading cryptocurrency, as Litecoin has often displayed a strong correlation with its price movements. If Bitcoin experiences a significant recovery, it could potentially boost sentiment across the cryptocurrency market and provide support for Litecoin&#8217;s rebound. Any positive developments in terms of regulatory clarity or major adoption announcements may also generate renewed interest in Litecoin and drive its price higher. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Pexels]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin (LTC) has recently faced a significant decline in its price, with bears gaining momentum as it slumps below the crucial $100 mark. LTC, often referred to as the &#8220;silver to Bitcoin&#8217;s gold,&#8221; has been a favorite among investors seeking an alternative to the pioneer cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>The bearish momentum behind Litecoin&#8217;s decline raises questions about the factors driving this price slump and the potential implications for the broader cryptocurrency market. </p>
<p>Will Litecoin be able to regain its strength and recover from this setback, or is there more downside ahead?</p>

<h2><strong>Bears Pull LTC Price Down</strong></h2>
<p>Litecoin is currently experiencing a downturn in its price, with <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/litecoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a> reporting it at $93.52. This marks a significant decline of 4.5% within the last 24 hours and a substantial seven-day slump of 17.2%.<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-541931" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-51.png" alt="" width="1038" height="76" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-51.png 1038w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-51-460x34.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-51-860x63.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-51-768x56.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-51-750x55.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1038px) 100vw, 1038px"/></p>

<p>As the price slips below the crucial $100 mark, traders and investors are closely monitoring the situation and assessing the potential factors that could influence LTC&#8217;s rebound.</p>
<p>The recent dip below $100 has sparked concerns among market participants, indicating that sellers might be gaining the upper hand. </p>
<p>Traders and investors are now paying close attention to the $90-$92 price range as a critical zone that could determine the outcome of the ongoing battle between the bulls and the bears. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/CdfomfG0/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>

<p>According to an <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/should-litecoin-bulls-be-worried-as-the-price-drops-below-100/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">LTC price report</a>, if the price manages to hold above this level and the bulls can regain control, it could indicate a potential recovery for LTC. </p>
<p>However, a breach of this support zone may further fuel the bearish sentiment and lead to additional downward pressure on Litecoin&#8217;s price.</p>
<h2><strong>Insights And Technical Factors To Consider</strong></h2>
<p>To anticipate how Litecoin will rebound from this slump, traders and investors should closely examine various insights and technical factors. Factors such as trading volume, price patterns, and support/resistance levels should be considered to gauge the strength of a potential rebound.</p>

<p>Apart from technical considerations, market sentiment and external factors also play a crucial role in Litecoin&#8217;s price movement. As the broader cryptocurrency market often influences individual assets, monitoring industry-wide trends becomes vital.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-541932" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-52.png" alt="" width="752" height="460" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-52.png 752w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-52-460x281.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-52-750x459.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 752px) 100vw, 752px"/></p>

<p>Traders and investors should <a href="https://forkast.news/bitcoin-above-us30000-ether-dips/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">keep a close eye on Bitcoin</a>, the leading cryptocurrency, as Litecoin has often displayed a strong correlation with its price movements. </p>
<p>If Bitcoin experiences a significant recovery, it could potentially boost sentiment across the cryptocurrency market and provide support for Litecoin&#8217;s rebound. </p>
<p>Any positive developments in terms of regulatory clarity or major adoption announcements may also generate renewed interest in Litecoin and drive its price higher.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Pexels</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-53-460x303.png" width="460" height="303" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>ADA Price Consolidates Below $0.30 &#8211; What Could Trigger A Sharp Decline?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/ada/ada-price-consolidates-0-30/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 04:38:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[adausd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541924</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cardano’s price is struggling below the $0.30 zone. ADA could start a sharp decline if it breaks the $0.2765 support zone in the near term. ADA price is moving lower below the $0.292 support against the US dollar. The price is trading below $0.290 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.2815 on the 4-hour chart of the ADA/USD pair (data source from Kraken). The pair could decline heavily if the bulls fail to protect the $0.2765 support zone. Cardano’s ADA Price Faces Uphill Task This past week, Cardano’s price attempted a fresh increase above the $0.285 zone. The price climbed above the $0.295 resistance zone but the bears were active near the $0.30 zone. A high was formed near $0.3015 before there was a fresh decline. The price declined below the $0.285 level and tested the $0.2765 support. It is now consolidating losses below $0.292, similar to Bitcoin and Ethereum. There was a minor recovery wave above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3013 swing high to the $0.2754 low. However, the bears were active above the $0.290 level. ADA is now trading below $0.290 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.2815 on the 4-hour chart of the ADA/USD pair. On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $0.288 zone and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). Source: ADAUSD on TradingView.com The first major resistance is forming near the $0.292 zone or the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3013 swing high to the $0.2754 low. The next key resistance might be $0.30. If there is a close above the $0.30 resistance, the price could start a decent increase. In the stated case, the price could rise toward the $0.320 resistance zone. More Losses in ADA? If Cardano’s price fails to climb above the $0.292 resistance level, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $0.2815 level and the trend line. The next major support is near the $0.2765 level. A downside break below the $0.2765 level could open the doors for a sharp fresh decline toward $0.255. The next major support is near the $0.232 level. Technical Indicators 4 hours MACD – The MACD for ADA/USD is gaining momentum in the bearish zone. 4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for ADA/USD is now below the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $0.2815, $0.2765, and $0.255. Major Resistance Levels – $0.288, $0.292, and $0.300.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Cardano’s price is struggling below the $0.30 zone. ADA could start a sharp decline if it breaks the $0.2765 support zone in the near term.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>ADA price is moving lower below the $0.292 support against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $0.290 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.2815 on the 4-hour chart of the ADA/USD pair (data source from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could decline heavily if the bulls fail to protect the $0.2765 support zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Cardano’s ADA Price Faces Uphill Task</h2>
<p>This past week, Cardano’s price attempted a fresh increase above the $0.285 zone. The price climbed above the $0.295 resistance zone but the bears were active near the $0.30 zone.</p>
<p>A high was formed near $0.3015 before there was a fresh decline. The price declined below the $0.285 level and tested the $0.2765 support. It is now consolidating losses below $0.292, similar to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-could-nosedive-30k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a> and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-bearish-revisit-1800/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum</a>.</p>
<p>There was a minor recovery wave above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3013 swing high to the $0.2754 low. However, the bears were active above the $0.290 level. ADA is now trading below $0.290 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.2815 on the 4-hour chart of the ADA/USD pair. On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $0.288 zone and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-541925" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Cardano-ADA-1.png" alt="Cardano’s ADA Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Cardano-ADA-1.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Cardano-ADA-1-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Cardano-ADA-1-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Cardano-ADA-1-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Cardano-ADA-1-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Cardano-ADA-1-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Cardano-ADA-1-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ADAUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ADAUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The first major resistance is forming near the $0.292 zone or the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $0.3013 swing high to the $0.2754 low. The next key resistance might be $0.30. If there is a close above the $0.30 resistance, the price could start a decent increase. In the stated case, the price could rise toward the $0.320 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>More Losses in ADA?</h2>
<p>If Cardano’s price fails to climb above the $0.292 resistance level, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $0.2815 level and the trend line.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $0.2765 level. A downside break below the $0.2765 level could open the doors for a sharp fresh decline toward $0.255. The next major support is near the $0.232 level.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for ADA/USD is gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for ADA/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $0.2815, $0.2765, and $0.255.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $0.288, $0.292, and $0.300.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/Crypto_Market_Bitcoin_Declining-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Prints Bearish Technical Pattern, Why It Could Revisit $1,800</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-bearish-revisit-1800/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 04:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541920</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum price extended its decline below $1,880 against the US Dollar. ETH is showing bearish signs and might decline further toward $1,800. Ethereum is currently attempting a recovery wave from the $1,825 zone. The price is trading below $1,880 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,905 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could attempt a fresh increase but upsides might be capped near $1,900. Ethereum Price Faces Resistance Ethereum’s price failed to continue higher above the $1,925 resistance and started a fresh decline. ETH declined below the $1,900 and $1,880 levels to move into a short-term bearish zone, similar to Bitcoin. The price even tested the $1,825 support. A low is formed near $1,825 and the price is now attempting a recovery wave. There was a break above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $1,956 swing high to the $1,825 low. Ether price is still trading below $1,880 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,905 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. Immediate resistance is near the $1,880 level or the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. The first major resistance is near the $1,890 zone. The next major resistance is near the $1,900 level and the trend line. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $1,956 swing high to the $1,825 low. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com A clear move above the $1,905 resistance could start a decent increase toward $1,955. The next major resistance is near the $1,975 level. Any more gains could send Ether toward the $2,050 resistance. More Losses in ETH? If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,890 resistance or $1,900, it could continue to move down. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,840 level. The first major support is near the $1,825 level, below which there is a risk of a larger decline. The next major support is near the $1,770 level. Any more losses could send Ether toward the $1,720 support level. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is losing momentum in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is now below the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,825 Major Resistance Level – $1,890]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum price extended its decline below $1,880 against the US Dollar. ETH is showing bearish signs and might decline further toward $1,800.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum is currently attempting a recovery wave from the $1,825 zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $1,880 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,905 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could attempt a fresh increase but upsides might be capped near $1,900.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Faces Resistance</h2>
<p>Ethereum’s price failed to continue higher above the $1,925 resistance and started a fresh decline. ETH declined below the $1,900 and $1,880 levels to move into a short-term bearish zone, similar to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-could-nosedive-30k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p>The price even tested the $1,825 support. A low is formed near $1,825 and the price is now attempting a recovery wave. There was a break above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $1,956 swing high to the $1,825 low.</p>
<p>Ether price is still trading below $1,880 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-is-plunging-1825/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100-hourly Simple Moving Average</a>. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,905 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD.</p>
<p>Immediate resistance is near the $1,880 level or the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. The first major resistance is near the $1,890 zone. The next major resistance is near the $1,900 level and the trend line. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $1,956 swing high to the $1,825 low.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-541921" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-5.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-5.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-5-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-5-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-5-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-5-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-5-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-5-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>A clear move above the $1,905 resistance could start a decent increase toward $1,955. The next major resistance is near the $1,975 level. Any more gains could send Ether toward the $2,050 resistance.</p>
<h2>More Losses in ETH?</h2>
<p>If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,890 resistance or $1,900, it could continue to move down. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,840 level.</p>
<p>The first major support is near the $1,825 level, below which there is a risk of a larger decline. The next major support is near the $1,770 level. Any more losses could send Ether toward the $1,720 support level.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,825</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,890</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1353098829-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Could Nosedive If It Continues To Struggle Below $31K</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-could-nosedive-30k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 03:10:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541917</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is moving lower below the $30,500 pivot level. BTC could decline heavily if there is a close below the $29,800 support zone in the near term. Bitcoin is moving lower below the $30,500 support zone. The price is trading below $30,500 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There was a break below a contracting triangle with support near $30,200 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could extend its decline if it stays below $31,200 for a long time. Bitcoin Price Shows Bearish Signs Bitcoin price moved into the red zone after it broke the $30,500 support zone. BTC traded below the $30,000 level but the downsides were limited. The price seems to be trading in a range above the $29,850 support zone. There was a move above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $31,630 swing high to the $29,868 low. The price even attempted a fresh increase above the $30,500 resistance but failed. Bitcoin is now trading below $30,500 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There was also a break below a contracting triangle with support near $30,200 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. If there is another increase, the price might face resistance near the $30,300 level and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. The next resistance is near the $30,500 zone, above which the price might retest $30,750. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $31,630 swing high to the $29,868 low. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com If the bulls push the price above the $30,750 level, there could be a drift toward $31,000. The next major resistance is near the $31,400 level. Any more gains could open the doors for a move toward the $32,000 resistance zone. More Losses in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $30,300 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $30,000 level. The next major support is near the $29,850 level, below which there could be a drop toward $29,400. Any more losses might send the price toward the $28,800 level. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now below the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $29,850, followed by $29,400. Major Resistance Levels – $30,300, $30,500, and $30,750.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is moving lower below the $30,500 pivot level. BTC could decline heavily if there is a close below the $29,800 support zone in the near term.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is moving lower below the $30,500 support zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $30,500 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There was a break below a contracting triangle with support near $30,200 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could extend its decline if it stays below $31,200 for a long time.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Shows Bearish Signs</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price moved into the red zone after it broke the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-takes-hit-30k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$30,500 support zone</a>. BTC traded below the $30,000 level but the downsides were limited.</p>
<p>The price seems to be trading in a range above the $29,850 support zone. There was a move above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $31,630 swing high to the $29,868 low. The price even attempted a fresh increase above the $30,500 resistance but failed.</p>
<p>Bitcoin is now trading below $30,500 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-rejects-31k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>. There was also a break below a contracting triangle with support near $30,200 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>If there is another increase, the price might face resistance near the $30,300 level and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. The next resistance is near the $30,500 zone, above which the price might retest $30,750. It is close to the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $31,630 swing high to the $29,868 low.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-541918" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-5.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-5.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-5-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-5-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-5-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-5-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-5-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-5-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>If the bulls push the price above the $30,750 level, there could be a drift toward $31,000. The next major resistance is near the $31,400 level. Any more gains could open the doors for a move toward the $32,000 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>More Losses in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $30,300 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $30,000 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $29,850 level, below which there could be a drop toward $29,400. Any more losses might send the price toward the $28,800 level.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $29,850, followed by $29,400.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $30,300, $30,500, and $30,750.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/shutterstock_1334283245-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana (SOL) Tallies 10% Gains On Weekly Chart &#8211; Will It Cross $25?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/solana/solana-sol-tallies-10-gains-on-weekly-chart-will-it-cross-25/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olowoporoku Adeniyi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 07:33:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana Rally]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541891</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) has witnessed a remarkable recovery in the past week, showcasing a string of steady gains. Presently, SOL has increased by 10% and is actively traded at $21.80, reflecting a slight uptick in the crypto&#8217;s price. While it&#8217;s important to note that SOL remains significantly distant from its all-time high of $260, the recent upward motion has lifted its value beyond the $20 mark, indicating promising signs of an extended bullish sentiment What&#8217;s Behind SOL Rise?  There are several factors right now that could have influenced the rise in SOL’s price. These include macroeconomic factors such as inflation and crypto regulation in different areas. In addition, Solana has experienced some success in adoption with some ecosystems adopting the token and launching cross-chain bridges.  Related Reading: XRP Next Step: Here’s Why An Upward Move Could Be Likely However, the most likely factor is the increase in DEX volume recorded this week. Blockchain analysis platform DefiLlama revealed in a report earlier in the week that Solana had experienced a spike in DEX volume. According to the report, SOL’s DEX volume surged by over 80% and is ranked fifth within the crypto market. This development is likely to have boosted its price action in the past week.  Nonetheless, the Total Value Locked (TVL) has not reacted to this uptrend and has been stagnant since its decline last November following the FTX collapse. Currently, the TVL sits at around $275 million with no noticeable increase in value despite the gains of SOL in recent days.  Solana (SOL) Price Outlook And Prediction  SOL is currently trending upward and has continued its positive price action towards the weekend. However, the intermittent red candles on its weekly chart show that the bears are active this week.  Looking at the technical indicators, its relative strength index is at 50 in the neutral zone between the oversold region of 35 and the overbought region of 75. The Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) is currently in the buy zone which is a bullish signal. In addition, the histogram bars are green and signal that a bullish trend is ahead and if the bulls persist, SOL is likely to have a sustained uptrend in the coming days.  SOL is trading at $21.83 after it found critical support at the $15.43 price level weeks ago. This puts the altcoin close to the $22.50 resistance level. Related Reading: PEPE Bulls Losing Steam? Fatigue Appears To Undermine Price Rally A break above the $22.50 resistance level will help to boost its price to reclaim the $25 psychological resistance level. If this happens, SOL will likely rally to the $23.00 resistance level after breaking above $22. However, a price decline below $20 in the short term remains possible due to external market conditions that are bearish.  (This site’s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured Image from iStock, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Solana (SOL) has witnessed a remarkable recovery in the past week, showcasing a string of steady gains. Presently, SOL has increased by 10% and is actively traded at $21.80, reflecting a slight uptick in the crypto&#8217;s price.</p>
<p>While it&#8217;s important to note that SOL remains significantly distant from its all-time high of $260, the recent upward motion has lifted its value beyond the $20 mark, indicating promising signs of an extended bullish sentiment</p>
<h2><strong>What&#8217;s Behind SOL Rise? </strong></h2>
<p>There are several factors right now that could have influenced the rise in SOL’s price. These include macroeconomic factors such as inflation and crypto regulation in different areas. In addition, Solana has experienced some success in adoption with some ecosystems adopting the token and launching cross-chain bridges. </p>
<p><strong>Related Reading: </strong><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/xrp-next-step-heres-why-an-upward-move-could-be-likely/?swcfpc=1">XRP Next Step: Here’s Why An Upward Move Could Be Likely</a></p>
<p>However, the most likely factor is the increase in DEX volume recorded this week. Blockchain analysis platform DefiLlama revealed in a report earlier in the week that Solana had experienced a spike in DEX volume. According to the report, SOL’s DEX volume surged by over 80% and is ranked fifth within the crypto market. This development is likely to have boosted its price action in the past week. </p>
<p>Nonetheless, the Total Value Locked (TVL) has not reacted to this uptrend and has been stagnant since its decline last November following the FTX collapse. Currently, the TVL sits at around $275 million with no noticeable increase in value despite the gains of SOL in recent days. </p>
<h2><strong>Solana (SOL) Price Outlook And Prediction </strong></h2>
<p>SOL is currently trending upward and has continued its positive price action towards the weekend. However, the intermittent red candles on its weekly chart show that the bears are active this week. </p>
<p>Looking at the technical indicators, its relative strength index is at 50 in the neutral zone between the oversold region of 35 and the overbought region of 75. The Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) is currently in the buy zone which is a bullish signal. In addition, the histogram bars are green and signal that a bullish trend is ahead and if the bulls persist, SOL is likely to have a sustained uptrend in the coming days. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-541893" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SOLUSD_2023-07-09_07-59-45-460x231.png" alt="SOL 7-day chart shows upward trend Source @Tradingview" width="460" height="231" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SOLUSD_2023-07-09_07-59-45-460x231.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SOLUSD_2023-07-09_07-59-45-860x432.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SOLUSD_2023-07-09_07-59-45-768x386.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SOLUSD_2023-07-09_07-59-45-360x180.png 360w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SOLUSD_2023-07-09_07-59-45-750x377.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SOLUSD_2023-07-09_07-59-45-1140x572.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SOLUSD_2023-07-09_07-59-45.png 1480w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/>
<p>SOL is trading at $21.83 after it found critical support at the $15.43 price level weeks ago. This puts the altcoin close to the $22.50 resistance level.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading: </strong><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/pepe-bulls-losing-steam/?swcfpc=1">PEPE Bulls Losing Steam? Fatigue Appears To Undermine Price Rally</a></p>
<p>A break above the $22.50 resistance level will help to boost its price to reclaim the $25 psychological resistance level. If this happens, SOL will likely rally to the $23.00 resistance level after breaking above $22. However, a price decline below $20 in the short term remains possible due to external market conditions that are bearish. </p>
<p><i>(This site’s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</i></p>
<p><i>Featured Image from iStock, chart from TradingView</i></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1291935777-460x263.jpg" width="460" height="263" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bone ShibaSwap (BONE) Spikes 43% In A Week – Here’s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/bone-shibaswap-bone-spikes-43-in-a-week-heres-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olowoporoku Adeniyi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 07:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BONE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bone Shibaswap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu BONE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541880</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[BONE, the governance token of Shiba Inu, has experienced a significant uptick in the past week with its price surging by double digits during this period. At the time of writing, BONE has seen an increase of 0.5% in the past 24 hours reaching $1.20. Additionally, the token has witnessed a weekly rise of more than 40% making it the best performer among the top 100 tokens.  This spike holds major significance as BONE has managed to be bullish despite the recent market sell-off, which has left the crypto market in a bearish state. The recent growth of BONE could be attributed to the statement of Shitoshi Kusama, the lead developer of Shiba Inu.  Kusama Provides Tentative Date For Shibarium Launch  Kusama had earlier in the week disclosed a potential date for the launch of Shibarium, the highly anticipated Layer-2 blockchain that would power the Shiba Inu ecosystem. According to a blog post on July 6, Kusama stated that the mainnet launch of Shibarium could be discussed and unveiled at the Blockchain Futurists Conference scheduled to take place in Toronto in August.  Related Reading:  Stellar (XLM) Sheds 13% As Bearish Sentiment Takes Over Kusama further defined the role of the multiple token systems that would be supported by Shibarium. According to him, the Shiba Inu ecosystem would be divided into four sections with each section utilizing a unique token. SHIB would be used to govern the community, while BONE governs and support community technology (such as Shibarium gas fees), LEASH would cater to community security and provides exclusivity, and TREAT moderates and enhances community projects.  Following this disclosure, the price of BONE experienced a major uptrend due to the positive sentiments from the community. BONE’s unique role in relation to Shibarium gas fees makes it a vital token within the Shiba Inu ecosystem.  Related Reading: PEPE Bulls Losing Steam? Fatigue Appears To Undermine Price Rally Shibarium is also seen as a significant development and has attracted the attention of many within the crypto community. Since its launch on March 11, PuppyNet, the testnet for Shibarium has displayed remarkable activities. The testnet has witnessed more than 27.5 million transactions from over $17 million wallets. This high level of activity on the Shibarium testnet is a major indicator of the potential of the network and BONE is central to this.  BONE Price Prediction   BONE has experienced a consistent upward trend since June 11, after it bottomed at $0.665. Since then, its price has increased by 100% in today’s trading reaching a high of $1.35.  This positive trend is likely to continue in the coming weeks with more developments expected to be deployed on Shibarium.  This will invariably trickle down to BONE providing more thrust for the memecoin to break new resistance limits. At the moment the current resistance mark is $1.5 and if there’s a major correction, the next support levels are $1.30 and $1.25, respectively. (This site’s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured Image from unSplash, chart from TradingView and Coingecko]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BONE, the governance token of Shiba Inu, has experienced a significant uptick in the past week with its price surging by double digits during this period. At the time of writing, BONE has seen an increase of 0.5% in the past 24 hours reaching $1.20. Additionally, the token has witnessed a weekly rise of more than 40% making it the best performer among the top 100 tokens. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-541881" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-09-065254-460x63.png" alt="BONE upp by 43% in the past week: Source @coingecko" width="460" height="63" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-09-065254-460x63.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-09-065254.png 682w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/>
<p>This spike holds major significance as BONE has managed to be bullish despite the recent market sell-off, which has left the crypto market in a bearish state. The recent growth of BONE could be attributed to the statement of Shitoshi Kusama, the lead developer of Shiba Inu. </p>
<h2><strong>Kusama Provides Tentative Date For Shibarium Launch </strong></h2>
<p>Kusama had earlier in the week disclosed a potential date for the launch of Shibarium, the highly anticipated Layer-2 blockchain that would power the Shiba Inu ecosystem. According to a blog post on July 6, Kusama stated that the mainnet launch of Shibarium could be discussed and unveiled at the Blockchain Futurists Conference scheduled to take place in Toronto in August. </p>
<p><strong>Related Reading:</strong>  <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/stellar/stellar-xlm-sheds-13-as-bearish-sentiments-take-over/">Stellar (XLM) Sheds 13% As Bearish Sentiment Takes Over</a></p>
<p>Kusama further defined the role of the multiple token systems that would be supported by Shibarium. According to him, the Shiba Inu ecosystem would be divided into four sections with each section utilizing a unique token. SHIB would be used to govern the community, while BONE governs and support community technology (such as Shibarium gas fees), LEASH would cater to community security and provides exclusivity, and TREAT moderates and enhances community projects. </p>
<p>Following this disclosure, the price of BONE experienced a major uptrend due to the positive sentiments from the community. BONE’s unique role in relation to Shibarium gas fees makes it a vital token within the Shiba Inu ecosystem. </p>
<p><strong>Related Reading</strong>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/pepe-bulls-losing-steam/">PEPE Bulls Losing Steam? Fatigue Appears To Undermine Price Rally</a></p>
<p>Shibarium is also seen as a significant development and has attracted the attention of many within the crypto community. Since its launch on March 11, PuppyNet, the testnet for Shibarium has displayed remarkable activities. The testnet has witnessed more than 27.5 million transactions from over $17 million wallets. This high level of activity on the Shibarium testnet is a major indicator of the potential of the network and BONE is central to this. </p>
<h2><strong>BONE Price Prediction </strong></h2>
<p> BONE has experienced a consistent upward trend since June 11, after it bottomed at $0.665. Since then, its price has increased by 100% in today’s trading reaching a high of $1.35.  This positive trend is likely to continue in the coming weeks with more developments expected to be deployed on Shibarium. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-541882" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BONEUSDT_2023-07-09_06-56-01-460x231.png" alt="BONE 7-day chart shows significant uptrend in price: Source @Tradingview" width="460" height="231" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BONEUSDT_2023-07-09_06-56-01-460x231.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BONEUSDT_2023-07-09_06-56-01-860x432.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BONEUSDT_2023-07-09_06-56-01-768x386.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BONEUSDT_2023-07-09_06-56-01-360x180.png 360w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BONEUSDT_2023-07-09_06-56-01-750x377.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BONEUSDT_2023-07-09_06-56-01-1140x573.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BONEUSDT_2023-07-09_06-56-01.png 1479w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/>
<p>This will invariably trickle down to BONE providing more thrust for the memecoin to break new resistance limits. At the moment the current resistance mark is $1.5 and if there’s a major correction, the next support levels are $1.30 and $1.25, respectively.</p>
<p><i>(This site’s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</i></p>
<p><i>Featured Image from unSplash, chart from TradingView and Coingecko</i></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/chris-jarvis-NOLrgL3hUJg-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar (XLM) Sheds 13% As Bearish Sentiment Takes Over</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/stellar/stellar-xlm-sheds-13-as-bearish-sentiments-take-over/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olowoporoku Adeniyi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 11:11:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar Lumen Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar Lumens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541843</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the past week, Stellar (XLM) experienced a decline in price, moving from $0.1 to $0.096. This represents a decrease of -13.42% in value. Furthermore, in the past 24 hours, XLM recorded a minor drop of -0.61%. These price movements indicate a slight bearish sentiment prevailing in the crypto market, with XLM being influenced by the broader market conditions. The recent downtrend in XLM&#8217;s price suggests that bears currently have the upper hand, while the scope for bullish activity appears limited. What Could Be Responsible For The Recent Price Dip? The Stellar ecosystem has been rife with developments in recent months, with the biggest being the launch of the Spacewalk bridge that connects the blockchain to Polkadot. The bridge was meant to enable smooth transfer of the USDC stablecoin between the two blockchains fostering increased utility and potential demand within Stellar&#8217;s ecosystem.  However, this has not gone to plan, as Stellar&#8217;s price has failed to match the positive advancements in its ecosystem. Instead, bearish sentiment has engulfed XLM, which has contributed to the recent downward price movement. Related Reading: XRP Next Step: Here’s Why An Upward Move Could Be Likely The bearish sentiment indicates that market participants are cautious about XLM, leading to selling pressure and a lack of significant buying interest. It is important to consider the impact of market sentiment on short-term price fluctuations, as it can create challenges for price recovery and limit the potential for bullish momentum in the near term. What&#8217;s Next For Stellar (XLM)? Although XLM is currently experiencing a bearish sentiment, the long-term prospects for the cryptocurrency remain positive. Stellar&#8217;s roadmap for 2023 focuses on enhancing network utility through strategic initiatives. This includes making innovation easy and scalable through Soroban development, scaling and decentralization endeavors, and improving developer wallet tools. Stellar aims to win over builders by accelerating the growth of widely-used assets, promoting accessibility and user-friendly apps, and leveraging smart contracts for sustainable use cases in the DeFi ecosystem. Related Reading: Circle Intervenes, Freezes $63 Million From Multichain Hack Furthermore, Stellar&#8217;s focus on utility and building trust involves engaging in public policy, raising platform awareness, and maintaining high-quality wallet products. These initiatives are designed to strengthen Stellar&#8217;s position in the market and drive future growth. While short-term price movements may be influenced by market sentiment, the long-term success of Stellar relies on the execution of its strategic initiatives and the adoption of its network utility. As a result, XLM&#8217;s value could potentially increase in the future, with projections indicating the possibility of reaching $0.11 by 2024. Investors and traders should closely monitor the progress of Stellar&#8217;s roadmap and evaluate market conditions when considering the future prospects of XLM. At press time, XLM was trading at $0.09691 per coin with a 1-hour price increase of 1.1%. (This site’s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured Image from iStock, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the past week, Stellar (XLM) experienced a decline in price, moving from $0.1 to $0.096. This represents a decrease of -13.42% in value. Furthermore, in the past 24 hours, XLM recorded a minor drop of -0.61%. These price movements indicate a slight bearish sentiment prevailing in the crypto market, with XLM being influenced by the broader market conditions. The recent downtrend in XLM&#8217;s price suggests that bears currently have the upper hand, while the scope for bullish activity appears limited.</p>
<h2>What Could Be Responsible For The Recent Price Dip?</h2>
<p>The Stellar ecosystem has been rife with developments in recent months, with the biggest being the launch of the Spacewalk bridge that connects the blockchain to Polkadot. The bridge was meant to enable smooth transfer of the USDC stablecoin between the two blockchains fostering increased utility and potential demand within Stellar&#8217;s ecosystem. </p>
<p>However, this has not gone to plan, as Stellar&#8217;s price has failed to match the positive advancements in its ecosystem. Instead, bearish sentiment has engulfed XLM, which has contributed to the recent downward price movement.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading: </strong><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/xrp-next-step-heres-why-an-upward-move-could-be-likely/">XRP Next Step: Here’s Why An Upward Move Could Be Likely</a></p>
<p>The bearish sentiment indicates that market participants are cautious about XLM, leading to selling pressure and a lack of significant buying interest. It is important to consider the impact of market sentiment on short-term price fluctuations, as it can create challenges for price recovery and limit the potential for bullish momentum in the near term.</p>
<h2>What&#8217;s Next For Stellar (XLM)?</h2>
<p>Although XLM is currently experiencing a bearish sentiment, the long-term prospects for the cryptocurrency remain positive. Stellar&#8217;s roadmap for 2023 focuses on enhancing network utility through strategic initiatives. This includes making innovation easy and scalable through Soroban development, scaling and decentralization endeavors, and improving developer wallet tools. Stellar aims to win over builders by accelerating the growth of widely-used assets, promoting accessibility and user-friendly apps, and leveraging smart contracts for sustainable use cases in the DeFi ecosystem.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading</strong>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/circle-intervenes-freezes-63-million-from-multichain-hack/?swcfpc=1">Circle Intervenes, Freezes $63 Million From Multichain Hack</a></p>
<p>Furthermore, Stellar&#8217;s focus on utility and building trust involves engaging in public policy, raising platform awareness, and maintaining high-quality wallet products. These initiatives are designed to strengthen Stellar&#8217;s position in the market and drive future growth. While short-term price movements may be influenced by market sentiment, the long-term success of Stellar relies on the execution of its strategic initiatives and the adoption of its network utility.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-541849" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XLMUSD_2023-07-08_08-16-47-460x231.png" alt="XLM Price Movement: Source @Tradingview" width="460" height="231" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XLMUSD_2023-07-08_08-16-47-460x231.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XLMUSD_2023-07-08_08-16-47-860x432.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XLMUSD_2023-07-08_08-16-47-768x386.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XLMUSD_2023-07-08_08-16-47-360x180.png 360w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XLMUSD_2023-07-08_08-16-47-750x377.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XLMUSD_2023-07-08_08-16-47-1140x573.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XLMUSD_2023-07-08_08-16-47.png 1479w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/>
<p>As a result, XLM&#8217;s value could potentially increase in the future, with projections indicating the possibility of reaching $0.11 by 2024. Investors and traders should closely monitor the progress of Stellar&#8217;s roadmap and evaluate market conditions when considering the future prospects of XLM. At press time, XLM was trading at $0.09691 per coin with a 1-hour price increase of 1.1%.</p>
<p><i>(This site’s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</i></p>
<p><i>Featured Image from iStock, chart from TradingView</i></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1385861326-1-460x248.jpg" width="460" height="248" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>PEPE Bulls Losing Steam? Fatigue Appears To Undermine Price Rally</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/pepe-bulls-losing-steam/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 07:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541830</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[PEPE, once riding the waves of a bullish surge, finds itself in a precarious position as the price correction of Bitcoin (BTC)] reverberates across the market. Over the past 24 hours, the signs of exhaustion have become increasingly apparent, casting a shadow of doubt on PEPE&#8217;s recent gains.  The critical resistance hurdle at $0.00000172 looms large, presenting an insurmountable challenge for the bullish forces that once propelled PEPE&#8217;s ascent.  As the crypto realm holds its breath, all eyes are fixed on the fate of this whimsical digital asset, wondering if it can break free from the grip of resistance and soar to new heights. Related Reading: XRP Next Step: Here’s Why An Upward Move Could Be Likely PEPE Faces Bearish Pressure As Prices Experience A Slump PEPE&#8217;s price on CoinGecko currently stands at $0.00000157. Over the course of the past seven days, PEPE has experienced a slight decline of 2.5%. These recent figures have raised concerns among investors and analysts alike, as PEPE&#8217;s bullish momentum appears to be waning. Source: Coingecko For the past three weeks, PEPE had been enjoying a bullish fervor, displaying impressive price surges. The trend even persisted through the first week of July, as PEPE managed to break past the critical resistance level at $0.00000172. Source: PEPE/USDT on TradingView However, this triumph proved to be short-lived as declining trading volumes paved the way for bearish forces to seize control, putting a halt to the buying pressure. A PEPE price report further confirmed the recent weakening in PEPE&#8217;s performance. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) recently displayed a bearish crossover, with a series of red bars appearing below the zero level. This signal indicates a potential shift in momentum towards the bearish side.  Seeking A Rebound: PEPE&#8217;s Future Prospects While Bitcoin&#8217;s current correction has undoubtedly influenced PEPE&#8217;s recent performance, it is important to remember that the cryptocurrency market is highly dynamic and subject to rapid changes. As Bitcoin stabilizes or regains momentum, it can inject renewed optimism and buying pressure into the market, potentially benefiting tokens like PEPE. PEPE seven-day price performance. Source: Coingecko. Related Reading: Recent 800 Billion Shiba Inu Dump Has Short Traders Worried – Here’s Why Furthermore, PEPE&#8217;s fate also depends on its own fundamentals and developments within its ecosystem. Positive news, partnerships, or adoption initiatives specific to PEPE can have a considerable impact on its price trajectory, even in the face of a broader influence of Bitcoin. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from The Guardian]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>PEPE, once riding the waves of a bullish surge, finds itself in a precarious position as the price correction of Bitcoin (BTC)] reverberates across the market. </p>
<p>Over the past 24 hours, the signs of exhaustion have become increasingly apparent, casting a shadow of doubt on PEPE&#8217;s recent gains. </p>
<p>The critical resistance hurdle at $0.00000172 looms large, presenting an insurmountable challenge for the bullish forces that once propelled PEPE&#8217;s ascent. </p>
<p>As the crypto realm holds its breath, all eyes are fixed on the fate of this whimsical digital asset, wondering if it can break free from the grip of resistance and soar to new heights.</p>

<h2><strong>PEPE Faces Bearish Pressure As Prices Experience A Slump</strong></h2>
<p><a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/pepe" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">PEPE&#8217;s price on CoinGecko</a> currently stands at $0.00000157. Over the course of the past seven days, PEPE has experienced a slight decline of 2.5%. These recent figures have raised concerns among investors and analysts alike, as PEPE&#8217;s bullish momentum appears to be waning.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-541835" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-45.png" alt="" width="1035" height="75" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-45.png 1035w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-45-460x33.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-45-860x62.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-45-768x56.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-45-750x54.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1035px) 100vw, 1035px"/></p>

<p>For the past three weeks, PEPE had been enjoying a bullish fervor, displaying impressive price surges. The trend even persisted through the first week of July, as PEPE managed to break past the critical resistance level at $0.00000172. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-541836" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-46.png" alt="" width="1336" height="709" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-46.png 1336w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-46-460x244.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-46-860x456.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-46-768x408.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-46-750x398.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-46-1140x605.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1336px) 100vw, 1336px"/></p>

<p>However, this triumph proved to be short-lived as declining trading volumes paved the way for bearish forces to seize control, putting a halt to the buying pressure.</p>
<p>A <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/pepe-exhaustion-creeps-up-on-bulls/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">PEPE price report</a> further confirmed the recent weakening in PEPE&#8217;s performance. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) recently displayed a bearish crossover, with a series of red bars appearing below the zero level. This signal indicates a potential shift in momentum towards the bearish side. </p>
<h2><strong>Seeking A Rebound: PEPE&#8217;s Future Prospects</strong></h2>
<p>While <a href="https://watcher.guru/news/bitcoin-investors-should-remain-flat-this-weekend-heres-why" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Bitcoin&#8217;s current correction</a> has undoubtedly influenced PEPE&#8217;s recent performance, it is important to remember that the cryptocurrency market is highly dynamic and subject to rapid changes. As Bitcoin stabilizes or regains momentum, it can inject renewed optimism and buying pressure into the market, potentially benefiting tokens like PEPE.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-541841" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-47.png" alt="" width="762" height="499" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-47.png 762w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-47-460x301.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-47-750x491.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 762px) 100vw, 762px"/></p>


<p>Furthermore, PEPE&#8217;s fate also depends on its own fundamentals and developments within its ecosystem. Positive news, partnerships, or adoption initiatives specific to PEPE can have a considerable impact on its price trajectory, even in the face of a broader influence of Bitcoin.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from The Guardian</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-48-460x332.png" width="460" height="332" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Next Step: Here&#8217;s Why An Upward Move Could Be Likely</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/xrp-next-step-heres-why-an-upward-move-could-be-likely/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 05:34:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541824</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[XRP&#8217;s price performance has been underwhelming recently, with a notable decline from its previous highs. Regulatory uncertainties surrounding Ripple Labs, the company behind XRP, have played a significant role in dampening investor sentiment.  The ongoing legal battle between Ripple and the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) regarding the classification of XRP as a security has raised concerns about the asset&#8217;s long-term viability. However, despite these challenges, there are reasons to remain cautiously optimistic about XRP&#8217;s future. Related Reading: Recent 800 Billion Shiba Inu Dump Has Short Traders Worried – Here’s Why XRP Shows Potential For A Reversal Despite Recent Declines XRP, currently priced at $0.467053 according to CoinGecko, has experienced a marginal decline of 0.5% over the past 24 hours and a slight drop of 0.3% over the past seven days. However, despite dropping toward the $0.46 level, which serves as the lower border of a descending price channel, there are indications that a likely upward shift may be on the horizon. Up until a breakout to the upper border, which denotes a potential trend reversal, descending price channels are often bearish patterns. In line with this downward trend, XRP has been trading at regularly lower highs and lows. The currency is currently experiencing a significant decline in its value, and it is approaching the lower limit of a trading channel. This decline has created an environment that holds the potential for a potential recovery to take place. When a currency approaches the bottom border of a trading channel, it suggests that it has reached a support level, a point at which there is increased demand for the currency, which could lead to a reversal in its downward trend. XRP market cap currently at $24.3 billion. Chart: TradingView.com According to an XRP price report, when a cryptocurrency reaches the lower border of a descending channel, it often signifies a critical juncture where buying pressure may overcome selling pressure, leading to a reversal in the price direction. While past performance is not indicative of future results, this development suggests that XRP may be poised for an upward movement in the foreseeable future. Ripple Labs&#8217; UBRI Thrives With Global Expansion Meanwhile, Ripple has achieved significant milestones in its University Blockchain Research Initiative (UBRI), a key operational initiative. With a philanthropic commitment of $50 million, the program has successfully onboarded 50 partners from various sectors, Ripple announced on Twitter. 1/ In 2018, Ripple’s UBRI program launched with a $50M philanthropic commitment to leading universities around the world to support academic research, technical development, and innovation in blockchain and crypto. https://t.co/B1DBYNiSdV — Ripple (@Ripple) July 7, 2023 The UBRI program, focused on academic research related to blockchain technology, has made remarkable progress. It has awarded 590 fellowships and scholarships, providing support to aspiring researchers and students. Additionally, the initiative has played a vital role in facilitating the publication of over 1,000 research articles and presentations, contributing to the advancement of knowledge in the field. Related Reading: Compound (COMP) Token Rallies Over 100% After CEO Quits – Details The success of the UBRI program is further highlighted by its global reach, as it is now active on six continents across the world.  (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Shutterstock]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>XRP&#8217;s price performance has been underwhelming recently, with a notable decline from its previous highs. Regulatory uncertainties surrounding Ripple Labs, the company behind XRP, have played a significant role in dampening investor sentiment. </p>
<p>The ongoing legal battle between Ripple and the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) regarding the classification of XRP as a security has raised concerns about the asset&#8217;s long-term viability.</p>
<p>However, despite these challenges, there are reasons to remain cautiously optimistic about XRP&#8217;s future.</p>

<h2><strong>XRP Shows Potential For A Reversal Despite Recent Declines</strong></h2>
<p>XRP, currently priced at $0.467053 according to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/xrp" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a>, has experienced a marginal decline of 0.5% over the past 24 hours and a slight drop of 0.3% over the past seven days. </p>
<p>However, despite dropping toward the $0.46 level, which serves as the lower border of a descending price channel, there are indications that a likely upward shift may be on the horizon.</p>
<p>Up until a breakout to the upper border, which denotes a potential trend reversal, descending price channels are often bearish patterns. In line with this downward trend, XRP has been trading at regularly lower highs and lows.</p>
<p>The currency is currently experiencing a significant decline in its value, and it is approaching the lower limit of a trading channel. This decline has created an environment that holds the potential for a potential recovery to take place.</p>
<p>When a currency approaches the bottom border of a trading channel, it suggests that it has reached a support level, a point at which there is increased demand for the currency, which could lead to a reversal in its downward trend.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/jJZrt6De/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>

<p>According to an <a href="https://u.today/xrps-next-move-should-aim-upward-heres-why" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">XRP price report</a>, when a cryptocurrency reaches the lower border of a descending channel, it often signifies a critical juncture where buying pressure may overcome selling pressure, leading to a reversal in the price direction. </p>
<p>While past performance is not indicative of future results, this development suggests that XRP may be poised for an upward movement in the foreseeable future.</p>
<h2><strong>Ripple Labs&#8217; UBRI Thrives With Global Expansion</strong></h2>
<p>Meanwhile, Ripple has achieved significant milestones in its University Blockchain Research Initiative (UBRI), a key operational initiative. With a philanthropic commitment of $50 million, the program has successfully onboarded 50 partners from various sectors, <a href="https://twitter.com/Ripple/status/1677302826375204867" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Ripple announced on Twitter</a>.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">1/ In 2018, Ripple’s UBRI program launched with a $50M philanthropic commitment to leading universities around the world to support academic research, technical development, and innovation in blockchain and crypto. <a href="https://t.co/B1DBYNiSdV" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/B1DBYNiSdV</a></p>
<p>— Ripple (@Ripple) <a href="https://twitter.com/Ripple/status/1677302826375204867?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 7, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>The UBRI program, focused on academic research related to blockchain technology, has made remarkable progress. It has awarded 590 fellowships and scholarships, providing support to aspiring researchers and students. </p>
<p>Additionally, the initiative has played a vital role in facilitating the publication of over 1,000 research articles and presentations, contributing to the advancement of knowledge in the field.</p>

<p>The success of the UBRI program is further highlighted by its global reach, as it is now active on six continents across the world. </p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Shutterstock</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-44-460x255.png" width="460" height="255" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Circle Intervenes, Freezes $63 Million From Multichain Hack</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/circle-intervenes-freezes-63-million-from-multichain-hack/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 02:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fantom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[multichain]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541817</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Circle, the official issuer of USDC, the second largest stablecoin by circulating supply, has frozen $63 million from the Multichain hack. Compiled Etherscan data on July 7 shows that the stablecoin issuer froze $27.65 million, $30.1 million, and $5.5 million in three transactions, hampering the hacker&#8217;s cash-out efforts. Multichain Hacked, Circle Intervenes Multichain, a cross-chain protocol router, was hacked on July 7, resulting in the loss of over $126 million worth of various tokens. The exploit came after the attacker illegally accessed Multichain&#8217;s Multi-Party Computation (MPC) address, which stores funds locked between blockchains. Subsequently, the hacker withdrew funds from the address and moved them to an externally controlled wallet. The Fantom Bridge was adversely affected by this outflow as the hacker withdrew various tokens, including wBTC, USDC, and USDT. There were a handful of other altcoins that the hacker stole.  Related Reading: Arbitrum DAO Locks $770 Million In ARB Tokens Into Vesting Contract: Implications For ARB Funds were also stripped from the Moonriver Bridge, with observers noting that at least $6.8 million worth of various coins, including USDC, were moved to an external address. It is also reported that an address associated with Multichain connecting with Dogecoin also lost over $600,000. The stolen USDC has now been frozen and cannot be moved, a relief for the community. However, it is not clear whether Circle will reverse funds to Multichain. In the past, Tether Holdings and Circle, the centralized issuers of the world&#8217;s most liquid stablecoins, have intervened to prevent bad actors from cashing out. Hack Compounding Multichain&#8217;s Woes, Bitcoin Firm Peckshield, a blockchain security firm, was the first to pick out the unusual transfers of over $118 million worth of assets from Multichain&#8217;s Fantom and Moonriver bridges. The firm went on to tag the team behind the cross-chain protocol, who immediately acted. In response to the hack, Multichain said the outflow was &#8220;abnormal&#8221; and halted all activity while recommending users pause their protocol and revoke all contracts approval.  Related Reading: Hackers Have Stolen $30 Billion In Crypto Since 2012, SlowMist Report Finds Although the Multichain team had assured the community that the private keys controlling asset movements through the bridge are secure and stored on-chain, their technology appears to have flaws, resulting in the hack. The hack marks what has also been a tumultuous past few weeks. Besides delayed transactions and what the team described as &#8220;multiple issues,&#8221; the founder is missing. Despite the attack, Bitcoin prices are firm when writing. The coin is above the $30,000 psychological support, rejecting bear pressure from July 6. However, FTM, the native currency of Fantom, is free-falling, dumping 20% from July highs. Feature image from Canva, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Circle, the official issuer of USDC, the second largest stablecoin by circulating supply, has frozen $63 million from the Multichain hack. Compiled Etherscan data on July 7 <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/14tdtbp/circle_freezes_three_addresses_linked_to_the/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shows</a> that the stablecoin issuer froze $27.65 million, $30.1 million, and $5.5 million in three transactions, hampering the hacker&#8217;s cash-out efforts.</p>
<h2>Multichain Hacked, Circle Intervenes</h2>
<p>Multichain, a cross-chain protocol router, was hacked on July 7, resulting in the loss of over $126 million worth of various tokens. The exploit came after the attacker illegally accessed Multichain&#8217;s Multi-Party Computation (MPC) address, which stores funds locked between blockchains.</p>
<p>Subsequently, the hacker withdrew funds from the address and moved them to an externally controlled wallet. The Fantom Bridge was adversely affected by this outflow as the hacker withdrew various tokens, including wBTC, USDC, and USDT. There were a handful of other altcoins that the hacker stole. </p>

<p>Funds were also stripped from the Moonriver Bridge, with observers noting that at least $6.8 million worth of various coins, including USDC, were moved to an external address. It is also reported that an address associated with Multichain connecting with Dogecoin also lost over $600,000.</p>
<p>The stolen USDC has now been frozen and cannot be moved, a relief for the community. However, it is not clear whether Circle will reverse funds to Multichain. In the past, Tether Holdings and Circle, the centralized issuers of the world&#8217;s most liquid stablecoins, have intervened to prevent bad actors from cashing out.</p>
<h2>Hack Compounding Multichain&#8217;s Woes, Bitcoin Firm</h2>
<p>Peckshield, a blockchain security firm, was the first to <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/peckshield/status/1677031203772289030" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">pick out</a> the unusual transfers of over $118 million worth of assets from Multichain&#8217;s Fantom and Moonriver bridges. The firm went on to tag the team behind the cross-chain protocol, who immediately acted.</p>
<p>In response to the hack, Multichain <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/MultichainOrg/status/1677096839731097600" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">said</a> the outflow was &#8220;abnormal&#8221; and halted all activity while recommending users pause their protocol and revoke all contracts approval. </p>

<p>Although the Multichain team had assured the community that the private keys controlling asset movements through the bridge are secure and stored on-chain, their technology appears to have flaws, resulting in the hack. The hack marks what has also been a tumultuous past few weeks. Besides delayed transactions and what the team described as &#8220;multiple issues,&#8221; the founder is missing.</p>
<p>Despite the attack, Bitcoin prices are firm when writing. The coin is above the $30,000 psychological support, rejecting bear pressure from July 6. However, FTM, the native currency of Fantom, is free-falling, dumping 20% from July highs.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/AjLjXJJQ/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/AjLjXJJQ/" alt="FTM price on July 7| Source: FTMUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Crypto-news-Template4-460x260.png" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
