<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 02:56:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Just Saw Technical Correction, Can Bulls Save The Day?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-correction-27500/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 02:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535597</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is correcting gains from $28,400. BTC must stay above the $27,500 support to start a fresh increase in the near term. Bitcoin is correcting gains below the $28,000 support zone. The price is trading above $27,500 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There was a break below a major bullish trend line with support near $27,720 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could start a fresh increase if the bulls manage to protect the $27,500 support. Bitcoin Price Corrects Lower Bitcoin price started a decent increase above the $28,000 resistance zone. However, BTC struggled to clear the $28,400 and $28,500 resistance levels. A high was formed near $28,450 and the price started a downside correction. There was a move below the $28,000 support zone. The price declined below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $27,142 swing low to the $28,450 high. Besides, there was a break below a major bullish trend line with support near $27,720 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Bitcoin price is still trading above $27,500 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. It is finding bids near the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $27,142 swing low to the $28,450 high. Immediate resistance on the upside is near the $27,800 level. The next major resistance is near the $28,000 level. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com An upside break above $28,000 might send the price toward the main resistance at $28,500. A close above the $28,500 resistance zone might start a strong increase toward the $29,200 resistance zone. The next key resistance is near $29,400, above which the price might rise toward the $30,000 resistance. More Losses in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $28,000 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $27,580 level. The next major support is near the $27,500 zone, below which the price might gain bearish momentum. In the stated case, the price could decline toward the $27,150 support and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $27,580, followed by $27,500. Major Resistance Levels – $28,000, $28,400, and $28,500.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is correcting gains from $28,400. BTC must stay above the $27,500 support to start a fresh increase in the near term.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is correcting gains below the $28,000 support zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $27,500 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There was a break below a major bullish trend line with support near $27,720 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a fresh increase if the bulls manage to protect the $27,500 support.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Corrects Lower</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price started a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-bullish-28500-critical/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">decent increase above the $28,000 resistance zone</a>. However, BTC struggled to clear the $28,400 and $28,500 resistance levels.</p>
<p>A high was formed near $28,450 and the price started a downside correction. There was a move below the $28,000 support zone. The price declined below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $27,142 swing low to the $28,450 high.</p>
<p>Besides, there was a break below a major bullish trend line with support near $27,720 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Bitcoin price is still trading above $27,500 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-struggles-26650/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>.</p>
<p>It is finding bids near the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $27,142 swing low to the $28,450 high. Immediate resistance on the upside is near the $27,800 level. The next major resistance is near the $28,000 level.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-535598" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-21.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-21.png 1834w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-21-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-21-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-21-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-21-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-21-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-21-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>An upside break above $28,000 might send the price toward the main resistance at $28,500. A close above the $28,500 resistance zone might start a strong increase toward the $29,200 resistance zone. The next key resistance is near $29,400, above which the price might rise toward the $30,000 resistance.</p>
<h2>More Losses in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $28,000 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $27,580 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $27,500 zone, below which the price might gain bearish momentum. In the stated case, the price could decline toward the $27,150 support and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $27,580, followed by $27,500.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $28,000, $28,400, and $28,500.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/shutterstock_638895124-460x264.jpg" width="460" height="264" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here Are The Top 3 Chinese Coins To Buy As China Leads The Bull Run</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/here-are-the-top-3-chinese-coins-to-buy-as-china-leads-the-bull-run/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 23:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CFX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[China coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chinese coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hong kong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[neo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VET]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535536</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As June 1 draws closer and the Hong Kong and Chinese investors look forward to legally trading cryptocurrencies once more, the market has already turned bullish. So far, Chinese coins have led the pack when it comes to gains, so here are three of the most popular Chinese tokens likely to rally if the bullish trend continues. Neo (NEO) Neo (NEO) has long been a favorite of Chinese investors and is often fondly referred to as the “Chinese Ethereum.” The cryptocurrency is one of the leading coins from the region so it is no surprise to see that it has moved back into the spotlight as retail traders are set to begin trading cryptocurrencies in Hong Kong on June 1. Related Reading: Bullish Case For Litecoin Grows Stronger As LTC Halving Draws Close The past week has already been profitable for its investors with 13.95% gains already recorded on the weekly chart. In the past day as well, the digital asset has seen gains of 3.34%, but there is still a lot of ground to cover before trading goes live. So NEO could present as a good choice for investors looking to take advantage of the new bull rally being led by Chinese investors. NEO price recovers above $11 &#124; Source: NEOUSD on TradingView.com Conflux (CFX) Conflux (CFX) is one of the top Chinese coins for investors to keep an eye on during this time. Conflux is a blockchain company based in China and its native token CFX has seen much success this year. However, the drawdown in the price of the coin in the last month has not deterred investors and as the Chinese narrative gains ground, the token has grown as well. Just like NEO, the last week has been a good one for CFX whose price has risen 9.96% to bring its price above $0.32 once more. The coin’s trading volume also crossed $117 million in a 24-hour period, indicating that investors are always investing in this token ahead of the anticipated June 1 date. VeChain (VET) VeChain (VET) is one of the oldest blockchains in the space which was founded in 2015, the same year as Ethereum. And although VeChain hasn’t grown as much as Ethereum, it hasn’t been stagnant either and has become one of the foremost Chinese coins, making it a perfect candidate for those looking to take advantage of the present narrative. Related Reading: Elon Musk Reveals Reason Behind Dogecoin Investment, But Why Is DOGE Down? Although VET hasn’t performed as well as the others on this list, it is up nonetheless with 5.58% gains in the last week. It is also seeing a modest upside of 1.67% on the 24-hour chart, but the promise of more gains remains vast as the last two days leading up to June 1 could see these coins heat up very fast. If the trend continues, then VET could be looking at breaking the $0.03 resistance before the week is over. China And Crypto China banned cryptocurrencies in 2021 when the price of Bitcoin had rallied to $60,000. This move triggered a crash in the market, from which Bitcoin recovered not too long after, but it left Chinese investors unable to adequately participate in a market that they had previously dominated. That is, until now that Hong Kong has made a move. Related Reading: When Is A Token Coming For Coinbase’s Base L2? Here’s What The Roadmap Says The country passed a new law that would allow crypto exchanges to offer services to investors, making it possible for them to participate in the market once more. This gives investors in China an avenue to trade cryptocurrencies without being worried about breaking the law. It is set to go into effect on June 1, less than three days from now. As this date draws closer, a study by Forex Suggest has shown that Hong Kong is the most crypto-ready country in the world. However, it remains to see how this event will play out in the crypto market. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from Blokt, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">As June 1 draws closer and the Hong Kong and Chinese investors look forward to legally trading cryptocurrencies once more, the market has already turned bullish. So far, Chinese coins have led the pack when it comes to gains, so here are three of the most popular Chinese tokens likely to rally if the bullish trend continues.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Neo (NEO)</h2>
<p class="p2"><a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/neo/" rel="nofollow">Neo (NEO)</a> has long been a favorite of Chinese investors and is often fondly referred to as the “Chinese Ethereum.” The cryptocurrency is one of the leading coins from the region so it is no surprise to see that it has moved back into the spotlight as retail traders are set to begin trading cryptocurrencies in Hong Kong on June 1.</p>

<p class="p2">The past week has already been profitable for its investors with 13.95% gains already recorded on the weekly chart. In the past day as well, the digital asset has seen gains of 3.34%, but there is still a lot of ground to cover before trading goes live. So NEO could present as a good choice for investors looking to take advantage of the new bull rally being led by Chinese investors.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/iymg3I39/" alt="NEO price chart from TradingView.com (China Chinese coins)" width="2882" height="1724"/></p>

<h2 class="p2">Conflux (CFX)</h2>
<p class="p2"><a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/conflux-network/" rel="nofollow">Conflux (CFX)</a> is one of the top Chinese coins for investors to keep an eye on during this time. Conflux is a blockchain company based in China and its native token CFX has seen much success this year. However, the drawdown in the price of the coin in the last month has not deterred investors and as the Chinese narrative gains ground, the token has grown as well.</p>
<p class="p2">Just like NEO, the last week has been a good one for CFX whose price has risen 9.96% to bring its price above $0.32 once more. The coin’s trading volume also crossed $117 million in a 24-hour period, indicating that investors are always investing in this token ahead of the anticipated June 1 date.</p>
<h2 class="p2">VeChain (VET)</h2>
<p class="p2">VeChain (VET) is one of the oldest blockchains in the space which was founded in 2015, the same year as Ethereum. And although VeChain hasn’t grown as much as Ethereum, it hasn’t been stagnant either and has become one of the foremost Chinese coins, making it a perfect candidate for those looking to take advantage of the present narrative.</p>

<p class="p2">Although VET hasn’t performed as well as the others on this list, it is up nonetheless with 5.58% gains in the last week. It is also seeing a modest upside of 1.67% on the 24-hour chart, but the promise of more gains remains vast as the last two days leading up to June 1 could see these coins heat up very fast. If the trend continues, then VET could be looking at breaking the $0.03 resistance before the week is over.</p>
China And Crypto
<p class="p2">China banned cryptocurrencies in 2021 when the price of Bitcoin had rallied to $60,000. This move triggered a crash in the market, from which Bitcoin recovered not too long after, but it left Chinese investors unable to adequately participate in a market that they had previously dominated. That is, until now that Hong Kong has made a move.</p>

<p class="p2">The <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/hong-kong-crypto-exchanges-but-with-restrictions/" rel="nofollow">country passed a new law that would allow crypto exchanges to offer services to investors</a>, making it possible for them to participate in the market once more. This gives investors in China an avenue to trade cryptocurrencies without being worried about breaking the law.</p>
<p class="p2">It is set to go into effect on June 1, less than three days from now. As this date draws closer, a <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-hk-proclaimed-leader-in-global-market/" rel="nofollow">study</a> by Forex Suggest has shown that Hong Kong is the most crypto-ready country in the world. However, it remains to see how this event will play out in the crypto market.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/China-coins-460x230.jpeg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Bitcoin Headed For $34,000? Large Buyer&#8217;s Purchase May Signal Yes</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/is-bitcoin-headed-for-34000-large-buyers-purchase-may-signal-yes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 22:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535543</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin is finally seeing some green after trading at a loss over the past two weeks. The cryptocurrency continues to trade within a tight range, but activity in the options market could hint at a potential run toward new highs. Related Reading: No All-Time High For Bitcoin In 2023, Former BitMEX Head Arthur Hayes Predicts As of this writing, Bitcoin (BTC) trades at $27,900 with a 2.5% profit in the last 24 hours. Over the last week, the cryptocurrency has seen twice the profits recording a 4.4% performance. Other cryptocurrencies in the top 10 by market cap are experiencing similar momentum. Bitcoin Options Hint At Fresh Rally? Data from crypto options trading platform Deribit indicates a drop in Implied Volatility (IV). This metric measures the expectation of future price movements by market participants. IV has been trading sideways over the past month, with a tendency to the downside. Deribit claims that growing uncertainty in the crypto market and the macroeconomic landscape is fueling the current dynamic on this metric, which translates into slow price action for BTC and crypto. As the price of Bitcoin retraces, option buyers have been selling their contracts. When the opposite happens, and BTC sees an uptick, options sellers dump their contracts. This dynamic has put “constant selling pressure” on the IV and contributed to suppressing the BTC spot sector. However, the upcoming U.S. debt ceiling, the date this country could default on its national financial commitments, could change the status quo. The narrative around this event hints at a further appreciation for BTC and risk-on assets. Today, equities and crypto rallied as key political factions in the North American country reached a tentative agreement that could avert a crisis across the financial world. Over the weekend and into today’s development, Deribit noted that maturity for BTC options turned profitable. The exchange also saw aggressive calls buying as the landscape signals profits for the cryptocurrency and prices return north of $27,000. This large player bought calls (buy orders), betting that BTC could hit $34,000 somewhere in July/August 2023, as seen on the chart below. Related Reading: Polkadot Experiences Correction After Reaching $5.54: What’s Next In Store? Deribit stated in a market update: Sub 7day ATM-28k Calls + July 31k Calls bought bravely ahead of the long weekend Theta turned profitable as Debt-ceiling talks progressed and a large DSOB buyer of July+Aug 34k Calls aggressively accumulated at higher prices just prior to Spot slicing through 27.3k and now 28k Cover image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Bitcoin is finally seeing some green after trading at a loss over the past two weeks. The cryptocurrency continues to trade within a tight range, but activity in the options market could hint at a potential run toward new highs. </strong></p>

<p>As of this writing, Bitcoin (BTC) trades at $27,900 with a 2.5% profit in the last 24 hours. Over the last week, the cryptocurrency has seen twice the profits recording a 4.4% performance. Other cryptocurrencies in the top 10 by market cap are experiencing similar momentum.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-535565 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-2-860x394.png" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT" width="860" height="394" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-2-860x394.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-2-460x211.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-2-768x352.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-2-1536x704.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-2-750x344.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-2-1140x523.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-2.png 1813w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<h2>Bitcoin Options Hint At Fresh Rally?</h2>
<p>Data from crypto options trading platform Deribit <a href="https://twitter.com/DeribitInsights/status/1663154877751517187" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">indicates</a> a drop in Implied Volatility (IV). This metric measures the expectation of future price movements by market participants.</p>
<p>IV has been trading sideways over the past month, with a tendency to the downside. Deribit <a href="https://insights.deribit.com/industry/vol-commentary-mixed-week/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">claims</a> that growing uncertainty in the crypto market and the macroeconomic landscape is fueling the current dynamic on this metric, which translates into slow price action for BTC and crypto.</p>
<p>As the price of Bitcoin retraces, option buyers have been selling their contracts. When the opposite happens, and BTC sees an uptick, options sellers dump their contracts.</p>
<p>This dynamic has put “constant selling pressure” on the IV and contributed to suppressing the BTC spot sector. However, the upcoming U.S. debt ceiling, the date this country could default on its national financial commitments, could change the status quo.</p>
<p>The narrative around this event hints at a further appreciation for BTC and risk-on assets. Today, equities and crypto rallied as key political factions in the North American country <a href="https://www.financialexpress.com/business/investing-abroad-us-debt-ceiling-crisis-implications-for-the-financial-markets-till-june-5-and-beyond-3106436/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reached a tentative agreement</a> that could avert a crisis across the financial world.</p>
<p>Over the weekend and into today’s development, Deribit noted that maturity for BTC options turned profitable. The exchange also saw aggressive calls buying as the landscape signals profits for the cryptocurrency and prices return north of $27,000.</p>
<p>This large player bought calls (buy orders), betting that BTC could hit $34,000 somewhere in July/August 2023, as seen on the chart below.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-535567 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2.png" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT Chart 2" width="704" height="450" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2.png 704w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-460x294.png 460w" sizes="(max-width: 704px) 100vw, 704px"/>

<p>Deribit stated in a market update:</p>
<blockquote><p>Sub 7day ATM-28k Calls + July 31k Calls bought bravely ahead of the long weekend Theta turned profitable as Debt-ceiling talks progressed and a large DSOB buyer of July+Aug 34k Calls aggressively accumulated at higher prices just prior to Spot slicing through 27.3k and now 28k</p></blockquote>
<p>Cover image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1-460x295.jpg" width="460" height="295" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>The End of Tether? Why A Structural Shift In The Market Spells Trouble For USDT</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/stablecoin/the-end-of-tether-why-a-structural-shift-in-the-market-spells-trouble-for-usdt/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 20:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535589</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tether (USDT) is the largest stablecoin in the market, with a market capitalization of over $86 billion as of May 2023. Despite the concerns about the current state of the cryptocurrency market, Tether has continued to dominate the stablecoin space, with its supply growing significantly since the beginning of 2023. However, there are signs that new competitors may challenge its dominance in the future. Related Reading: Bitcoin Rally Hopes Still Alive, If This Metric Is To Go By USDT&#8217;s Reign Over? According to the researcher and founder of DeFiance Capital, ArthurOx, one factor that may limit Tether&#8217;s growth is the emergence of new stablecoins. As investors become more concerned about the risks associated with Tether, they are likely to seek alternatives that offer greater transparency and accountability.  For example, USDC (USD Coin) is a stablecoin fully backed by US dollars held in reserve by regulated financial institutions, and its supply has been growing rapidly in recent years. Another factor that may limit Tether&#8217;s growth is the emergence of decentralized stablecoins. These stablecoins are built on blockchain platforms, offering a decentralized alternative to centralized stablecoins like Tether.  Decentralized stablecoins eliminate the need for a central authority to manage the reserves, as the reserves are held in smart contracts on the blockchain. This offers high transparency and security and eliminates the risk of a central authority mismanaging the reserves or engaging in fraudulent activities. One example of a decentralized stablecoin is DAI, built on the Ethereum blockchain. DAI is backed by a basket of cryptocurrencies held in smart contracts on the blockchain. This ensures that the value of DAI remains stable while offering high transparency and security. In addition to these factors, there are also regulatory risks associated with Tether. The stablecoin has come under scrutiny from regulators in the US and other countries, with some calling for greater transparency and oversight. If regulators impose stricter regulations on Tether, this could limit its growth and open up opportunities for other stablecoins to gain market share. Tether And USDC Show Resilience Amid US Debt Ceiling Drama According to a recent report by Kaiko, USDT and USDC have shown little volatility amid the ongoing drama surrounding the US debt ceiling. Despite concerns over a potential US default, USDT and USDC saw little to no price movement over the past two weeks. This suggests that the markets did not view default as the base case scenario and that investors remained confident in the stability of these stablecoins. Interestingly, USDT and USDC have increasingly been trading in tandem during periods of market stress. For example, when Binance temporarily halted withdrawals for Bitcoin (BTC) earlier this month due to network congestion issues, both stablecoins rose above $1, as seen in the chart above. This suggests that USDC may have gained some safe-haven appeal as U.S. banking troubles eased. The resilience of USDT and USDC during the debt ceiling drama reflects a wider trend in the cryptocurrency market, where stablecoins have become an increasingly popular way for investors to hedge against volatility. Related Reading: Bearish Sentiment Hits EOS As Bulls Lose Control, What Lies Ahead? These developments underscore the growing importance of stablecoins in the cryptocurrency ecosystem. As more investors seek to hedge against market volatility and regulatory uncertainty, the demand for stablecoins will likely grow. Moreover, the emergence of new decentralized finance (DeFi) applications that require stablecoins as a means of exchange and collateral is also fueling demand. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tether (USDT) is the largest stablecoin in the market, with a market capitalization of over $86 billion as of May 2023. Despite the concerns about the current state of the cryptocurrency market, Tether has continued to dominate the stablecoin space, with its supply growing significantly since the beginning of 2023. However, there are signs that new competitors may challenge its dominance in the future.</p>

<h2>USDT&#8217;s Reign Over?</h2>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/Arthur_0x/status/1663237605444702208?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to the researcher and founder of DeFiance Capital, ArthurOx, one factor that may limit Tether&#8217;s growth is the emergence of new stablecoins. As investors become more concerned about the risks associated with Tether, they are likely to seek alternatives that offer greater transparency and accountability. </p>
<p>For example, USDC (USD Coin) is a stablecoin fully backed by US dollars held in reserve by regulated financial institutions, and its supply has been growing rapidly in recent years.</p>
<p>Another factor that may limit Tether&#8217;s growth is the emergence of decentralized stablecoins. These stablecoins are built on blockchain platforms, offering a decentralized alternative to centralized stablecoins like Tether. </p>
<p>Decentralized stablecoins eliminate the need for a central authority to manage the reserves, as the reserves are held in smart contracts on the blockchain. This offers high transparency and security and eliminates the risk of a central authority mismanaging the reserves or engaging in fraudulent activities.</p>
<p>One example of a decentralized stablecoin is DAI, built on the Ethereum blockchain. DAI is backed by a basket of cryptocurrencies held in smart contracts on the blockchain. This ensures that the value of DAI remains stable while offering high transparency and security.</p>
<p>In addition to these factors, there are also regulatory risks associated with Tether. The stablecoin has come under scrutiny from regulators in the US and other countries, with some calling for greater transparency and oversight. If regulators impose stricter regulations on Tether, this could limit its growth and open up opportunities for other stablecoins to gain market share.</p>
Tether And USDC Show Resilience Amid US Debt Ceiling Drama
<p>According to a recent <a href="https://research.kaiko.com/insights/72-of-eth-liquidity-is-concentrated-on-5-exchanges" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report </a>by Kaiko, USDT and USDC have shown little volatility amid the ongoing drama surrounding the US debt ceiling. Despite concerns over a potential US default, USDT and USDC saw little to no price movement over the past two weeks. This suggests that the markets did not view default as the base case scenario and that investors remained confident in the stability of these stablecoins.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-535590" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_45.jpg" alt="Tether" width="718" height="339" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_45.jpg 718w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_45-460x217.jpg 460w" sizes="(max-width: 718px) 100vw, 718px"/>
<p>Interestingly, USDT and USDC have increasingly been trading in tandem during periods of market stress. For example, when Binance temporarily halted withdrawals for Bitcoin (BTC) earlier this month due to network congestion issues, both stablecoins rose above $1, as seen in the chart above. This suggests that USDC may have gained some safe-haven appeal as U.S. banking troubles eased.</p>
<p>The resilience of USDT and USDC during the debt ceiling drama reflects a wider trend in the cryptocurrency market, where stablecoins have become an increasingly popular way for investors to hedge against volatility.</p>

<p>These developments underscore the growing importance of stablecoins in the cryptocurrency ecosystem. As more investors seek to hedge against market volatility and regulatory uncertainty, the demand for stablecoins will likely grow. Moreover, the emergence of new decentralized finance (DeFi) applications that require stablecoins as a means of exchange and collateral is also fueling demand.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/EiTQXCn5/" alt="Tether" width="1813" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/drawkit-illustrations-5xlHjrzQO54-unsplash-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bearish Sentiment Hits EOS As Bulls Lose Control, What Lies Ahead?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/eos/bearish-sentiment-hits-eos-as-bulls-lose-control-what-lies-ahead/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli Dambel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 19:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[EOS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bears]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eosusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535573</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[EOS Network, a popular open-source blockchain platform prioritizing high performance and security, has recently witnessed a sharp price decline. The asset exhibits bearish sentiment in the 30-Day timeframe.  Related Reading: The Best Decision Is To ‘Buy Bitcoin (BTC),’ Robert Kiyosaki Urges The EOS price is down by 14.19% in its one-month data from CoinMarketCap. This suggests that the bears have controlled the market since the last 30 days trading session. This shift in market sentiment raises questions about what lies ahead for EOS.   EOS Faces High Bearish Momentum, Further Price Decline, or Potential Reversal? The bearish sentiment and the loss of control by the bulls have had a noticeable effect on EOS&#8217;s price. The cryptocurrency has experienced a downward trend, with declining trading volumes and increased selling pressure.  Notably, the 24-hour trading volume is declining by 13.29% today, May 29, 2023, and its market cap is down by 1.32%. As of the time of writing, the price of EOS is down by 1.28%, at $0.89. This trend reflects a shift in market dynamics as investors become more cautious and start to sell their EOS holdings. Despite the prevailing bearish sentiment, potential catalysts could alter the trajectory for EOS. On May 26, the EOS network shared potential bullish news about its partnership with Hypha DAO and an initiative dubbed Beta Program.  EOS network claims that the Beta program will offer a range of pre-configured templates designed to meet different firms&#8217; needs and objectives. Generally, this news may lead to a positive market impact on the EOS price and market sentiment. EOS&#8217;s positive development and partnership can attract new buyers and increase demand, increasing prices. Also, Fear of Missing Out (FOMO), a psychological phenomenon, can create a buying frenzy and drive the price even higher quickly. EOS Price Formed Double Bottom Pattern In that sense, the EOS/USDT has formed a double-bottom chart pattern, suggesting a potential uptrend movement soon. The double bottom pattern is a bullish reversal pattern that typically forms after a prolonged asset price decline. Confirming the double bottom pattern occurs when the asset&#8217;s price breaks above the resistance level formed by the peak between the two bottoms. This breakout confirms the reversal signal and suggests a higher probability of an upcoming uptrend. Related Reading: JPMorgan Predicts Bitcoin (BTC) To Revisit $45,000, Here’s Why EOS has an important resistance level at $0.931, which represents a significant blockage for possible bullish movement. Bollinger Bands and MACD Signal Potential Trend Reversal The asset is currently oscillating between the upper band and middle band of the Bollinger Band indicator. This suggests an increase in the buying pressure and a rising bullish momentum. In addition, the Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) is currently above its signal line, suggesting bullish momentum. This indicates that the buyers are gradually taking over the market, and there might be a potential trend reversal soon. As seen in the chart above, the histogram is above zero and has strong green bars, further confirming the bullish sentiment in the market. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>EOS Network, a popular open-source blockchain platform prioritizing high performance and security, has recently witnessed a sharp price decline. The asset exhibits bearish sentiment in the 30-Day timeframe. </p>

<p>The EOS price is down by 14.19% in its one-month data from <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/eos/" rel="nofollow">CoinMarketCap</a>. This suggests that the bears have controlled the market since the last 30 days trading session. This shift in market sentiment raises questions about what lies ahead for EOS.  </p>
<h2>EOS Faces High Bearish Momentum, Further Price Decline, or Potential Reversal?</h2>
<p>The bearish sentiment and the loss of control by the bulls have had a noticeable effect on EOS&#8217;s price. The cryptocurrency has experienced a downward trend, with declining trading volumes and increased selling pressure. </p>
<p>Notably, the 24-hour trading volume is declining by 13.29% today, May 29, 2023, and its market cap is down by 1.32%. As of the time of writing, the price of EOS is down by 1.28%, at $0.89.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-535576 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/EOSUSDT_2023-05-29_20-44-30-860x471.png" alt=" Bearish Sentiment Hits EOS As Bulls Lose Control, What Lies Ahead?" width="860" height="471" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/EOSUSDT_2023-05-29_20-44-30-860x471.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/EOSUSDT_2023-05-29_20-44-30-460x252.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/EOSUSDT_2023-05-29_20-44-30-768x420.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/EOSUSDT_2023-05-29_20-44-30-750x411.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/EOSUSDT_2023-05-29_20-44-30-1140x624.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/EOSUSDT_2023-05-29_20-44-30.png 1529w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>This trend reflects a shift in market dynamics as investors become more cautious and start to sell their EOS holdings.</p>
<p>Despite the prevailing bearish sentiment, potential catalysts could alter the trajectory for EOS. On May 26, the EOS network shared potential <a href="https://twitter.com/EOSnFoundation/status/1662112323371167745" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">bullish news</a> about its partnership with Hypha DAO and an initiative dubbed Beta Program. </p>
<p>EOS network claims that the <a href="https://eosnetwork.com/blog/hypha-dao-new-beta-program-features/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Beta program</a> will offer a range of pre-configured templates designed to meet different firms&#8217; needs and objectives. Generally, this news may lead to a positive market impact on the EOS price and market sentiment.</p>
<p>EOS&#8217;s positive development and partnership can attract new buyers and increase demand, increasing prices. Also, Fear of Missing Out (FOMO), a psychological phenomenon, can create a buying frenzy and drive the price even higher quickly.</p>
<h2>EOS Price Formed Double Bottom Pattern</h2>
<p>In that sense, the EOS/USDT has formed a double-bottom chart pattern, suggesting a potential uptrend movement soon. The double bottom pattern is a bullish reversal pattern that typically forms after a prolonged asset price decline.</p>
<p>Confirming the double bottom pattern occurs when the asset&#8217;s price breaks above the resistance level formed by the peak between the two bottoms. This breakout confirms the reversal signal and suggests a higher probability of an upcoming uptrend.</p>

<p>EOS has an important resistance level at $0.931, which represents a significant blockage for possible bullish movement.</p>
Bollinger Bands and MACD Signal Potential Trend Reversal
<p>The asset is currently oscillating between the upper band and middle band of the Bollinger Band indicator. This suggests an increase in the buying pressure and a rising bullish momentum.</p>
<p>In addition, the Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) is currently above its signal line, suggesting bullish momentum. This indicates that the buyers are gradually taking over the market, and there might be a potential trend reversal soon.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-535575 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-29-204248-860x377.png" alt=" Bearish Sentiment Hits EOS As Bulls Lose Control, What Lies Ahead?" width="860" height="377" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-29-204248-860x377.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-29-204248-460x202.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-29-204248-768x336.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-29-204248-750x329.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-29-204248.png 1075w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>As seen in the chart above, the histogram is above zero and has strong green bars, further confirming the bullish sentiment in the market.</p>
<p>Featured image from Pixabay and chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/pexels-gregory-rogers-1328414-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Rally Hopes Still Alive, If This Metric Is To Go By</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-rally-hopes-still-alive-this-metric-go-by/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 18:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin SOPR Ratio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535510</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[If the historical pattern in this on-chain indicator is anything to go by, hopes for the continuation of the Bitcoin rally may still be alive. Bitcoin SOPR Ratio Has Been Going Up In Recent Weeks As an analyst in a CryptoQuant post pointed out, the SOPR ratio has been above 1 recently. The &#8220;Spent Output Profit Ratio&#8221; (SOPR) indicates whether the investors in the Bitcoin market are selling their coins at a profit or a loss right now. When the value of this metric is above 1, it means the average holder in the sector is currently moving their coins at a loss. On the other hand, values below this threshold imply the market is realizing a net profit at the moment. The BTC sector is generally divided into two main holder groups: the &#8220;short-term holders&#8221; (STHs) and the &#8220;long-term holders&#8221; (LTHs). The former cohort includes all investors that acquired their coins within the last 155 days, while the latter group includes those who bought before this cutoff. In the context of the current discussion, the relevant indicator is not the SOPR itself but the &#8220;SOPR ratio.&#8221; This indicator measures the ratio between the SOPR, specifically for the LTHs and the STHs. Related Reading: Will This Political Deal In The US Save Bitcoin and Crypto? Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the 30-day simple moving average (SMA) Bitcoin SOPR ratio throughout the history of the asset: Looks like the value of the metric has been going up in recent days &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As you can see in the above graph, the quant has marked the pattern that the 30-day SMA Bitcoin SOPR ratio seems to have followed during the past cycles of the cryptocurrency. Whenever the SOPR ratio is below 1, the LTHs realize lower profits relative to the STHs. Historically, this has usually been observed inside bear markets. The bear market bottom formations in the asset price have always occurred when the indicator has plunged deep below this mark and hit a value of about 0.5. Bullish periods followed with a surge in the metric back above the 1 level. Such a breakout implies a shift in the market dynamics, as the LTHs are harvesting a higher profit than the STHs during periods like these. During the rally in the last few months, the 30-day SMA Bitcoin SOPR ratio has again managed to break above the 1 mark, suggesting that the shift towards a bull market may have occurred. Related Reading: Bitcoin Shows Recovery: Did This Historical Line Act As Support Again? The metric is still firmly above this level, despite the recent struggle that the coin has seen. The analyst believes this is a sign that the bulls continue to dominate the market. From the chart, it&#8217;s also visible that the present values of the SOPR ratio are nowhere near as high as what was observed during past rallies, including the April 2019 rally, which may hint that the rally has some potential to go before the top. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $27,900, up 4% in the last week. BTC has gone up during the past day &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from iStock.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If the historical pattern in this on-chain indicator is anything to go by, hopes for the continuation of the Bitcoin rally may still be alive.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin SOPR Ratio Has Been Going Up In Recent Weeks</h2>
<p>As an analyst in a CryptoQuant post pointed out, the SOPR ratio has been above 1 recently. The &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-decision-point-asopr-retests-crucial-level/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Spent Output Profit Ratio</a>&#8221; (SOPR) indicates whether the investors in the Bitcoin market are selling their coins at a profit or a loss right now.</p>
<p>When the value of this metric is above 1, it means the average holder in the sector is currently moving their coins at a loss. On the other hand, values below this threshold imply the market is realizing a net profit at the moment.</p>
<p>The BTC sector is generally divided into two main holder groups: the &#8220;short-term holders&#8221; (STHs) and the &#8220;long-term holders&#8221; (LTHs). The former cohort includes all investors that acquired their coins within the last 155 days, while the latter group includes those who bought before this cutoff.</p>
<p>In the context of the current discussion, the relevant indicator is not the SOPR itself but the &#8220;SOPR ratio.&#8221; This indicator measures the ratio between the SOPR, specifically for the LTHs and the STHs.</p>

<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the 30-day simple moving average (SMA) Bitcoin SOPR ratio throughout the history of the asset:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/333235/quicktake/pLfkq_9461eefa9b19f0a23b166f412d5d0825ea819237eca6f034e2b7bde43aa2b246.png" alt="Bitcoin SOPR Ratio" width="1280" height="806"/></p>

<p>As you can see in the above graph, the quant has marked the pattern that the 30-day SMA Bitcoin SOPR ratio seems to have followed during the past cycles of the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>Whenever the SOPR ratio is below 1, the LTHs realize lower profits relative to the STHs. Historically, this has usually been observed inside bear markets.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/does-the-bitcoin-price-dump-signal-the-start-of-another-bear-market/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">bear market</a> bottom formations in the asset price have always occurred when the indicator has plunged deep below this mark and hit a value of about 0.5.</p>
<p>Bullish periods followed with a surge in the metric back above the 1 level. Such a breakout implies a shift in the market dynamics, as the LTHs are harvesting a higher profit than the STHs during periods like these.</p>
<p>During the rally in the last few months, the 30-day SMA Bitcoin SOPR ratio has again managed to break above the 1 mark, suggesting that the shift towards a bull market may have occurred.</p>

<p>The metric is still firmly above this level, despite the recent struggle that the coin has seen. The analyst believes this is a sign that the bulls continue to dominate the market.</p>
<p>From the chart, it&#8217;s also visible that the present values of the SOPR ratio are nowhere near as high as what was observed during past rallies, including the<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/repeat-april-2019-bitcoin-rally-levels/" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> April 2019 rally</a>, which may hint that the rally has some potential to go before the top.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $27,900, up 4% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/OV7q4o2C/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1533" height="911"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1385861333-460x248.jpg" width="460" height="248" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Get Rich Or Get Rugged? RUGME&#8217;s Unique Liquidity Mechanism Sparks Controversy</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/get-rich-or-get-rugged-rugme-unique-liquidity-mechanism-sparks-controversy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 17:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pepe Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rug Me]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[RUGME]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535564</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A new token has emerged in the cryptocurrency world, causing a stir among investors. Rug Me (RUGME) has a unique liquidity mechanism that is daring investors to try to “rug” the contract. According to the DeFi researcher Tsubasa, this high-stakes competition has a big brain game that challenges the most intelligent investors to solve a complex puzzle, promising high rewards. However, there is a catch. If someone is smart enough to solve the puzzle, they can rug the liquidity and take 20% of the pool. &#8220;Rugging&#8221; the liquidity means that someone can pull out a significant amount of funds from the pool and cause the token&#8217;s value to drop rapidly. This can result in significant losses for investors who hold the token. Related Reading: Polkadot Experiences Correction After Reaching $5.54: What’s Next In Store? RUGME, Big Brain Game, Or Big Risk? RUGME has a 1 trillion supply, with 100% used as liquidity. The token has a 10% transfer and buy fee, with no selling fee. All fees are disbursed to holders, who can claim them from the contract. When the liquidity is rug-pulled, 20% goes to the rugger, and 80% is refunded to the holders. Furthermore, Tsubasa believes investing in Rug Me is not for the faint. The token is high-risk and high-reward, with the potential for significant loss. But Rug Me (RUGME) offers a unique and exciting investment opportunity for investors willing to take risks. Investors are flocking to RUGME, with 15 ETH already in the liquidity pool. The token has a 100e curve, meaning that any buy below 100e will get the same price, with no first-comer advantage. The token has a 10% transfer and buy fee, with all fees disbursed to holders who can claim from the contract. This mechanism incentivizes holding the token, as holders can earn fees every time the token is transferred or bought. Investors can enter the market at the same price point as others below 100e, eliminating the issue of joining later to this market. The earlier investors are, the more fees they earn from buys. However, after 100e, the price will start moving, and if people keep buying, the price could skyrocket. But the risk of rug-pulling is ever-present, and investors need to know the potential for loss. Is The Memecoin Craze Losing Steam? Signs Point To A Slowdown Despite the launch of this new project, the meme coin sector is declining. he Pepe (PEPE) token, a meme-inspired cryptocurrency, recently experienced a surge in popularity that saw its price skyrocket from $0.00000002764 on April 17 to a high of $0.000004354 on May 5. However, the frenzy has cooled considerably, leaving many investors wondering if the Pepe (PEPE) craze is over. Currently, the token is trading at $0.0000014390, Down by 1% in the last 24 hours and more than 7% in the seven-day time frame.  According to data from CoinGecko, the price of Pepe (PEPE) has fallen by more than 63% from its all-time high on May 5. Additionally, the daily transaction volume, which peaked at over $1 billion, has dropped to $270 million over the last 24 hours. Onchain data reveals a significant decline in interest in PEPE as the frenzy appears to end. Related Reading: No All-Time High For Bitcoin In 2023, Former BitMEX Head Arthur Hayes Predicts While the recent surge in popularity of meme-inspired cryptocurrencies like Pepe has captured the attention of investors, there are concerns about the sustainability of these coins. Many of them are highly speculative investments, and the recent drop-off in interest in Pepe (PEPE) seems to indicate that the hype may have been short-lived. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new token has emerged in the cryptocurrency world, causing a stir among investors. Rug Me (RUGME) has a unique liquidity mechanism that is daring investors to try to “rug” the contract.</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/0x8i11i0n/status/1663169667052220417?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to the DeFi researcher Tsubasa, this high-stakes competition has a big brain game that challenges the most intelligent investors to solve a complex puzzle, promising high rewards. However, there is a catch. If someone is smart enough to solve the puzzle, they can rug the liquidity and take 20% of the pool.</p>
<p>&#8220;Rugging&#8221; the liquidity means that someone can pull out a significant amount of funds from the pool and cause the token&#8217;s value to drop rapidly. This can result in significant losses for investors who hold the token.</p>

<h2>RUGME, Big Brain Game, Or Big Risk?</h2>
<p>RUGME has a 1 trillion supply, with 100% used as liquidity. The token has a 10% transfer and buy fee, with no selling fee. All fees are disbursed to holders, who can claim them from the contract. When the liquidity is rug-pulled, 20% goes to the rugger, and 80% is refunded to the holders.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-535569" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FxTD-ssaIAE-b7u-860x360.jpg" alt="RUGME" width="860" height="360" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FxTD-ssaIAE-b7u-860x360.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FxTD-ssaIAE-b7u-460x192.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FxTD-ssaIAE-b7u-768x321.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FxTD-ssaIAE-b7u-750x314.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FxTD-ssaIAE-b7u-1140x477.jpg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FxTD-ssaIAE-b7u.jpg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>Furthermore, Tsubasa believes investing in Rug Me is not for the faint. The token is high-risk and high-reward, with the potential for significant loss. But Rug Me (RUGME) offers a unique and exciting investment opportunity for investors willing to take risks.</p>
<p>Investors are flocking to RUGME, with 15 ETH already in the<a href="https://etherscan.io/token/0x00ff33802cb62bf8fa7ee8c5ba61e6d8f5477382#code" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> liquidity pool</a>. The token has a 100e curve, meaning that any buy below 100e will get the same price, with no first-comer advantage. The token has a 10% transfer and buy fee, with all fees disbursed to holders who can claim from the contract.</p>
<p>This mechanism incentivizes holding the token, as holders can earn fees every time the token is transferred or bought. Investors can enter the market at the same price point as others below 100e, eliminating the issue of joining later to this market.</p>
<p>The earlier investors are, the more fees they earn from buys. However, after 100e, the price will start moving, and if people keep buying, the price could skyrocket. But the risk of rug-pulling is ever-present, and investors need to know the potential for loss.</p>
Is The Memecoin Craze Losing Steam? Signs Point To A Slowdown
<p>Despite the launch of this new project, the meme coin sector is declining. he Pepe (PEPE) token, a meme-inspired cryptocurrency, recently experienced a surge in popularity that saw its price skyrocket from $0.00000002764 on April 17 to a high of $0.000004354 on May 5. </p>
<p>However, the frenzy has cooled considerably, leaving many investors wondering if the Pepe (PEPE) craze is over. Currently, the token is trading at $0.0000014390, Down by 1% in the last 24 hours and more than 7% in the seven-day time frame. </p>
<p>According to data from <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/es/monedas/pepe" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a>, the price of Pepe (PEPE) has fallen by more than 63% from its all-time high on May 5. Additionally, the daily transaction volume, which peaked at over $1 billion, has dropped to $270 million over the last 24 hours. Onchain data reveals a significant decline in interest in PEPE as the frenzy appears to end.</p>

<p>While the recent surge in popularity of meme-inspired cryptocurrencies like Pepe has captured the attention of investors, there are concerns about the sustainability of these coins. Many of them are highly speculative investments, and the recent drop-off in interest in Pepe (PEPE) seems to indicate that the hype may have been short-lived.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ykjeAn0e/" alt="RUGME" width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/sander-sammy-53bht9urH1A-unsplash-307x460.jpg" width="307" height="460" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bullish Run for Injective (INJ): Will the Momentum Continue?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bullish-run-for-injective-inj-will-the-momentum-continue/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli Dambel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 16:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bulls]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Injective (INJ)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[INJUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535556</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Injective (INJ) price has experienced an uptrend, resulting in price increases since yesterday, May 28. This trend indicates a positive sentiment among investors, with more buyers entering the market and increasing prices. Meanwhile, the uncertainty around the price of the general crypto market has caused speculations about whether this momentum will continue. Assessing The Potential For Sustained Momentum The bullish sentiment in the INJ market has affected its price positively, resulting in an increase of 8.78% in the last 24 hours. Also, the buyers have maintained this momentum, resulting in a surge of 8.56% in the 7-day trading period.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Exchange Inflows Mostly Coming From Loss Holders, Weak Hands Exiting? The asset&#8217;s current price sits at $7.41 as of the time of writing based on CoinMarketCap data. The assets’ 24-hour trading volume and total market cap show positive market participation with an increase of 200.36% and 9%, respectively. INJ has maintained the uptrend movement by forming higher highs and lows. This formation indicates that INJ&#8217;s price is under bullish control, and the demand is growing rapidly. Also, the asset trades above the trendline, which may be considered a trendline support for investors and traders. This positive sentiment may attract more investors and increase prices. Recent Bullish Fundamentals Recently, there have been many partnerships and initiatives around the Injective ecosystem. This has resulted in bullish sentiment and price gains for INJ. On May 24, Injective announced the launch of the first IBN-enabled SVM Rollup with their partnership, Eclipse, on their page. This initiative will enable Solana developers seamlessly interact and build with Injective and the broader Cosmos universe. The INJ team made this announcement on May 13, 2023, stating that anyone interacting with dApps built on INJ or L1 Chain may receive an NFT. The surprise NFT announcement boosted the bullish momentum in the market.  Bollinger Bands &#38; MACD Signals Bullish Momentum The asset is currently trading above the upper band of the Bollinger Bands Indicator. This suggests a bullish movement and a potential buy signal for investors and traders. It is important to note that an asset above the upper band implies that the price has moved to an extreme or overbought level. In addition, the Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) is currently above the signal line suggesting a bullish sentiment. This indicates that the buying pressure outweighs the selling pressure. The INJ price trades above the 50-day and 200-day Simple Moving Averages (SMA), indicating bullish sentiment. The price above both SMAs implies that the asset is under bullish pressure and a potential long-term bullish trend. Related Reading: Bitcoin Bulls Push BTC Back Up To $28K Amid Surging Address Activity Also, a Demand Index reading of 0.170 suggests positive buying pressure in the market. This indicates that the buying pressure is relatively stronger than the selling pressure. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Injective (INJ) price has experienced an uptrend, resulting in price increases since yesterday, May 28. This trend indicates a positive sentiment among investors, with more buyers entering the market and increasing prices.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the uncertainty around the price of the general crypto market has caused speculations about whether this momentum will continue.</p>
<h2>Assessing The Potential For Sustained Momentum</h2>
<p>The bullish sentiment in the INJ market has affected its price positively, resulting in an increase of 8.78% in the last 24 hours. Also, the buyers have maintained this momentum, resulting in a surge of 8.56% in the 7-day trading period. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-exchange-inflows-loss-weak-hands-exiting/">Bitcoin Exchange Inflows Mostly Coming From Loss Holders, Weak Hands Exiting?</a></p>
<p>The asset&#8217;s current price sits at <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/injective/" rel="nofollow">$7.41</a> as of the time of writing based on CoinMarketCap data. The assets’ 24-hour trading volume and total market cap show positive market participation with an increase of <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/injective/" rel="nofollow">200.36% and 9%</a>, respectively.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-535562 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/INJUSDT_2023-05-29_19-56-43-860x471.png" alt="Bearish Sentiment Hits EOS As Bulls Lose Control, What Lies Ahead?" width="860" height="471" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/INJUSDT_2023-05-29_19-56-43-860x471.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/INJUSDT_2023-05-29_19-56-43-460x252.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/INJUSDT_2023-05-29_19-56-43-768x420.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/INJUSDT_2023-05-29_19-56-43-750x411.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/INJUSDT_2023-05-29_19-56-43-1140x624.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/INJUSDT_2023-05-29_19-56-43.png 1529w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>INJ has maintained the uptrend movement by forming higher highs and lows. This formation indicates that INJ&#8217;s price is under bullish control, and the demand is growing rapidly.</p>
<p>Also, the asset trades above the trendline, which may be considered a trendline support for investors and traders. This positive sentiment may attract more investors and increase prices.</p>
<h2>Recent Bullish Fundamentals</h2>
<p>Recently, there have been many partnerships and initiatives around the Injective ecosystem. This has resulted in bullish sentiment and price gains for INJ.</p>
<p>On May 24, Injective <a href="https://twitter.com/Injective_/status/1661366171067723780" rel="nofollow">announced</a> the launch of the first IBN-enabled SVM Rollup with their partnership, Eclipse, on their page. This initiative will enable Solana developers seamlessly interact and build with Injective and the broader Cosmos universe.</p>
<p>The INJ team made this <a href="https://twitter.com/injective_/status/1657394070996615170?s=46&amp;t=JAUmthpFclo8jS4VJkm3DQ" rel="nofollow">announcement</a> on May 13, 2023, stating that anyone interacting with dApps built on INJ or L1 Chain may receive an NFT. The surprise NFT announcement boosted the bullish momentum in the market. </p>
Bollinger Bands &amp; MACD Signals Bullish Momentum
<p>The asset is currently trading above the upper band of the Bollinger Bands Indicator. This suggests a bullish movement and a potential buy signal for investors and traders.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-535561 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/INJ-860x300.png" alt="Bearish Sentiment Hits EOS As Bulls Lose Control, What Lies Ahead?" width="860" height="300" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/INJ-860x300.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/INJ-460x161.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/INJ-768x268.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/INJ-750x262.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/INJ-1140x398.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/INJ.png 1212w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>It is important to note that an asset above the upper band implies that the price has moved to an extreme or overbought level.</p>
<p>In addition, the Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) is currently above the signal line suggesting a bullish sentiment. This indicates that the buying pressure outweighs the selling pressure.</p>
<p>The INJ price trades above the 50-day and 200-day Simple Moving Averages (SMA), indicating bullish sentiment. The price above both SMAs implies that the asset is under bullish pressure and a potential long-term bullish trend.</p>

<p>Also, a Demand Index reading of 0.170 suggests positive buying pressure in the market. This indicates that the buying pressure is relatively stronger than the selling pressure.</p>
<p>Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/highland-cow-g58a557d37_1280-460x305.jpg" width="460" height="305" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>No All-Time High For Bitcoin In 2023, Former BitMEX Head Arthur Hayes Predicts</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/no-all-time-high-for-bitcoin-in-2023-former-bitmex-head-arthur-hayes-predicts/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 15:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535529</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a recent podcast appearance, Arthur Hayes, the former head of BitMEX, delivered a sobering prediction about the largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization, Bitcoin (BTC). Hayes believes that Bitcoin&#8217;s anticipated climb to an all-time high of $70,000 is unlikely to materialize this year, dampening the hopes of investors and traders. However, he points to a potentially bullish turn in 2024, driven by a significant event that could shape the market&#8217;s trajectory. Bitcoin Rise To $70,000 To Be Delayed During an episode of the &#8216;What Bitcoin Did&#8217; podcast, Hayes shared his perspective on Bitcoin&#8217;s price trajectory. He indicated that breaching the $70,000 milestone is not expected to occur in 2023. Related Reading: The Best Decision Is To ‘Buy Bitcoin (BTC),’ Robert Kiyosaki Urges Instead, Hayes suggests that next year&#8217;s anticipated halving event will play a crucial role in determining the market&#8217;s direction. While the delay may disappoint some, he remains optimistic about a potential breakthrough in the near future. The former head of BitMEX believes that the upcoming 2024 halving, an event that slashes Bitcoin&#8217;s block reward in half, will be a pivotal moment for the market. He suggests that crossing the $70,000 barrier will likely happen during that time. However, his long-term forecast raises concerns about an impending &#8220;blow-off top&#8221; in 2025 or 2026, potentially signaling a significant societal event or turmoil which he calls &#8220;Armageddon.&#8221; Hayes attributes this potential turmoil to factors such as excessive money printing and growing global discontent. Hayes noted: We have got this halving next year, 2024. I think that’s gonna be a good year. I don’t think we get up to $70,000 this year. Next year is when we cross that barrier and then we get the blow-off top 2025, 2026. And then it’s Armageddon. BTC Latest Price Action Meanwhile, Bitcoin has shown a possible brewing uptick in the past week. The largest crypto asset by market capitalization has surged 4.3% in the past week. Over the past 24 hours, BTC has seen a 2.8% gain. At the time of writing, Bitcoin currently trades at $27,925 after slightly trading above $28,000 on Sunday. Bitcoin&#8217;s trading volume has surged from $5 billion last Monday to $12 billion in the past 24 hours indicating a possible upward momentum.  In addition, the asset&#8217;s market capitalization has also seen a more than $20 billion gain in the past 7 days. However, according to Hayes, the increased practice of quantitative easing, which involves injecting more money into the economy, has created a volatile situation that could explode in the third and fourth quarters of this year. Related Reading: JPMorgan Predicts Bitcoin (BTC) To Revisit $45,000, Here’s Why He warns of mounting geopolitical tensions and a lack of trust, asserting that these factors form a &#8220;tinderbox&#8221; that could trigger a period of immense volatility for Bitcoin. Hayes emphasizes the importance of navigating these uncertain times, both for individuals seeking financial stability and for the cryptocurrency market as a whole. Featured image from Shutterstock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a recent podcast appearance, Arthur Hayes, the former head of BitMEX, delivered a sobering prediction about the largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization, Bitcoin (BTC). </p>
<p>Hayes believes that Bitcoin&#8217;s anticipated climb to an all-time high of $70,000 is unlikely to materialize this year, dampening the hopes of investors and traders. However, he points to a potentially bullish turn in 2024, driven by a significant event that could shape the market&#8217;s trajectory.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Rise To $70,000 To Be Delayed</h2>
<p>During an episode of the &#8216;What Bitcoin Did&#8217; <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yV-zwcFnR3Q" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">podcast</a>, Hayes shared his perspective on Bitcoin&#8217;s price trajectory. He indicated that breaching the $70,000 milestone is not expected to occur in 2023.</p>

<p>Instead, Hayes suggests that next year&#8217;s anticipated halving event will play a crucial role in determining the market&#8217;s direction. While the delay may disappoint some, he remains optimistic about a potential breakthrough in the near future. </p>
<p>The former head of BitMEX believes that the upcoming <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/best-decision-is-to-buy-bitcoin-btc-robert-kiyosaki-urges/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">2024 halving</a>, an event that slashes Bitcoin&#8217;s block reward in half, will be a pivotal moment for the market. He suggests that crossing the $70,000 barrier will likely happen during that time. </p>
<p>However, his long-term forecast raises concerns about an impending &#8220;blow-off top&#8221; in 2025 or 2026, potentially signaling a significant societal event or turmoil which he calls &#8220;Armageddon.&#8221; Hayes attributes this potential turmoil to factors such as excessive money printing and growing global discontent.</p>
<p>Hayes noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>We have got this halving next year, 2024. I think that’s gonna be a good year. I don’t think we get up to $70,000 this year. Next year is when we cross that barrier and then we get the blow-off top 2025, 2026. And then it’s Armageddon.</p></blockquote>
<h2>BTC Latest Price Action</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, Bitcoin has shown a possible brewing uptick in the past week. The largest crypto asset by market capitalization has surged 4.3% in the past week. Over the past 24 hours, BTC has seen a 2.8% gain.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/mqrI4rgb/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC)’s price chart on TradingView" width="2768" height="1556"/>
<p>At the time of writing, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/jpmorgan-predicts-bitcoin-btc-to-revisit-45000-heres-why/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a> currently trades at $27,925 after slightly trading above $28,000 on Sunday. Bitcoin&#8217;s trading volume has surged from $5 billion last Monday to $12 billion in the past 24 hours indicating a possible upward momentum.  In addition, the<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-shows-recovery-did-historical-line-act-support/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> asset&#8217;s market capitalization</a> has also seen a more than $20 billion gain in the past 7 days.</p>
<p>However, according to Hayes, the increased practice of quantitative easing, which involves injecting more money into the economy, has created a volatile situation that could explode in the third and fourth quarters of this year.</p>

<p>He warns of mounting geopolitical tensions and a lack of trust, asserting that these factors form a &#8220;tinderbox&#8221; that could trigger a period of immense volatility for Bitcoin. Hayes emphasizes the importance of navigating these uncertain times, both for individuals seeking financial stability and for the cryptocurrency market as a whole.</p>
<p>Featured image from Shutterstock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-460x282.jpg" width="460" height="282" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polkadot Experiences Correction After Reaching $5.54: What&#8217;s Next In Store?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/dot/polkadot-experiences-correction-after-reaching-5-54-whats-next-in-store/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 14:04:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[DOT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOTUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOTUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polkadot]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535518</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Yesterday, Polkadot (DOT) reached its weekly high at $5.54 but subsequently started a corrective phase. In the past 24 hours, DOT has managed to retain 1.8% of its overall gains during that period. On the weekly chart, DOT exhibited a 3% price increase. However, the technical analysis suggests that bears currently have the upper hand, with buying strength and demand remaining low. Despite this, if Bitcoin continues its upward movement toward the $28,000 level, several altcoins, including DOT, may also experience positive price action. Related Reading: Dogecoin Bounces Off $0.070 Mark, Awaits Breakthrough of Crucial Hurdle On the flip side, if sellers dominate, DOT could break below its crucial support level, strengthening the bearish sentiment in the upcoming trading sessions. The decline in the DOT market capitalization further indicates the prevailing low buying strength at the present moment. Polkadot Price Analysis: One-Day Chart At the time of writing, DOT was trading at $5.47. Following a rejection at the $5.54 level, the altcoin has experienced a retracement on its chart. The overhead resistance for DOT is currently positioned at $5.58. If the altcoin manages to surpass this resistance level, it could potentially reach $5.80. Despite the price correction, DOT has thus far maintained a position above the crucial support level of $5.40. However, if sellers gain momentum, the price may drop below the vital support level of $5.40 and trade around $5.30. The trading volume of DOT in the previous session was bearish, indicating a decline in demand driven by the bears on the daily chart. Technical Analysis Throughout the month of May, DOT has experienced minimal demand on its chart. Although the Relative Strength Index (RSI) displayed signs of recovery initially, the depreciation of DOT led to a decrease in demand. This suggests that buying strength did not enter the positive zone. Furthermore, the DOT price moved below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, indicating that sellers have been driving the price momentum in the market. If there is a slight increase in demand in the upcoming trading sessions, DOT may attempt to trade above the 20-SMA line, providing an opportunity for the bulls to regain control over the price. Although demand for Polkadot has declined, the chart still displays buy signals, suggesting the potential for a price increase. These buy signals are accompanied by an increase in demand, indicating a positive outlook. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicator, which reflects price momentum and trend changes, shows green histograms tied to buy signals. Related Reading: Floki Inu: Does Meme Coin Have What It Takes To Re-Enter Top 100 Spot? Additionally, the Bollinger Bands, which measure price volatility and fluctuation, are constricted, suggesting that Polkadot may experience significant volatility in the upcoming trading sessions. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[









<p>Yesterday, Polkadot (DOT) reached its weekly high at $5.54 but subsequently started a corrective phase. In the past 24 hours, DOT has managed to retain 1.8% of its overall gains during that period. On the weekly chart, DOT exhibited a 3% price increase.</p>
<p>However, the technical analysis suggests that bears currently have the upper hand, with buying strength and demand remaining low. Despite this, if Bitcoin continues its upward movement toward the $28,000 level, several altcoins, including DOT, may also experience positive price action.</p>

<p>On the flip side, if sellers dominate, DOT could break below its crucial support level, strengthening the bearish sentiment in the upcoming trading sessions. The decline in the DOT market capitalization further indicates the prevailing low buying strength at the present moment.</p>
<h2>Polkadot Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-535535 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOTUSD_2023-05-29_18-14-44.png" alt="Polkadot" width="1816" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOTUSD_2023-05-29_18-14-44.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOTUSD_2023-05-29_18-14-44-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOTUSD_2023-05-29_18-14-44-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOTUSD_2023-05-29_18-14-44-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOTUSD_2023-05-29_18-14-44-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOTUSD_2023-05-29_18-14-44-750x343.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOTUSD_2023-05-29_18-14-44-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>
<p>At the time of writing, DOT was trading at $5.47. Following a rejection at the $5.54 level, the altcoin has experienced a retracement on its chart.</p>
<p>The overhead resistance for DOT is currently positioned at $5.58. If the altcoin manages to surpass this resistance level, it could potentially reach $5.80. Despite the price correction, DOT has thus far maintained a position above the crucial support level of $5.40.</p>
<p>However, if sellers gain momentum, the price may drop below the vital support level of $5.40 and trade around $5.30. The trading volume of DOT in the previous session was bearish, indicating a decline in demand driven by the bears on the daily chart.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-535541 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOTUSD_2023-05-29_18-15-14.png" alt="Polkadot" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOTUSD_2023-05-29_18-15-14.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOTUSD_2023-05-29_18-15-14-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOTUSD_2023-05-29_18-15-14-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOTUSD_2023-05-29_18-15-14-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOTUSD_2023-05-29_18-15-14-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOTUSD_2023-05-29_18-15-14-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOTUSD_2023-05-29_18-15-14-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>
<p>Throughout the month of May, DOT has experienced minimal demand on its chart. Although the Relative Strength Index (RSI) displayed signs of recovery initially, the depreciation of DOT led to a decrease in demand.</p>
<p>This suggests that buying strength did not enter the positive zone. Furthermore, the DOT price moved below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, indicating that sellers have been driving the price momentum in the market.</p>
<p>If there is a slight increase in demand in the upcoming trading sessions, DOT may attempt to trade above the 20-SMA line, providing an opportunity for the bulls to regain control over the price.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-535542 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOTUSD_2023-05-29_18-15-33.png" alt="Polkadot" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOTUSD_2023-05-29_18-15-33.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOTUSD_2023-05-29_18-15-33-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOTUSD_2023-05-29_18-15-33-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOTUSD_2023-05-29_18-15-33-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOTUSD_2023-05-29_18-15-33-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOTUSD_2023-05-29_18-15-33-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOTUSD_2023-05-29_18-15-33-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>
<p>Although demand for Polkadot has declined, the chart still displays buy signals, suggesting the potential for a price increase. These buy signals are accompanied by an increase in demand, indicating a positive outlook.</p>
<p>The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicator, which reflects price momentum and trend changes, shows green histograms tied to buy signals.</p>

<p>Additionally, the Bollinger Bands, which measure price volatility and fluctuation, are constricted, suggesting that Polkadot may experience significant volatility in the upcoming trading sessions.</p>











]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/guerrillabuzz-m18EUUI8pSI-unsplash-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
