<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 17:39:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Craziest Bitcoin Price Predictions For 2023, 1,400% Rally Possible?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-price-predictions-2023-1400-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 00:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514470</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The start of a new year kicked off Bitcoin price and crypto market forecasts across social media and mainstream media platforms. Experts are debating whether bulls or bears will drive 2023’s price action. Last year, bears took over and sent the benchmark crypto back to its 2020 levels.  Related Reading: Cardano Enters 2023 With A Bang, But ADA Still Bearish In The Short Term As of this writing, the Bitcoin price trades at $16,700, recording a small profit during today’s trading session. On higher timeframes, the cryptocurrency continues to record sideways price action. The latter could operate as the dominant price action for 2023.  The Best Is Yet To Come For The Bitcoin Price Per a report from CNBC, the Bitcoin price is bound for an extreme shift in its trajectory. Optimistic experts, such as BTC bull Tim Draper, believe the cryptocurrency will trend higher from its current levels.  Draper believes the benchmark crypto will experience a 1,400% rally, reclaim previously lost territory, and break above $250,000 by mid-2023. The BTC bulls believe macroeconomic conditions will push adoption much higher.  One demographic will lead this potential new wave of adoption that will coincide with the upcoming Bitcoin halving. This event is scheduled for 2024, but in the past, the market has priced its impact much earlier. Draper said: My assumption is that since women control 80% of retail spending, and only 1 in 7 bitcoin wallets are currently held by women that the dam is about to break. Professor of finance at Sussex University, Carol Alexander, believes Bitcoin could see two short-term rallies. The first could take the Bitcoin price back to $30,000, and the second to $50,000 on the back of less trading volume and prominent players. As FTX and Three Arrows Capital collapse, Alexander expects less competition in the market, which could provide other prominent players with room to push BTC upwards. The professor explained: There will be a managed bull market in 2023, not a bubble — so we won’t see the price overshooting as before. We’ll see a month or two of stable trending prices interspersed with range-bounded periods and probably a couple of short-lived crashes. Exploring Less Favorable Scenarios, How Low Can BTC Go? Better macroeconomic landscape, adoption, halving and supply squeeze, and less competition. These are the factors that could work in favor of the cryptocurrency.  On the other hand, Eric Robertsen from Standard Charted claims the Bitcoin price could return to its 2020 levels and touch $5,000. A lack of trust from investors and more capitulation from crypto companies could prompt this scenario.  The low liquidity levels in the sector make things worse. The current state of the market could experience another leg lower if the U.S. Federal Reserve (Fed) doubles down on its hawkish monetary policy.  Related Reading: SOL Jumps 15% In 24 Hours As Solana Receives Support From Ethereum Founder According to Mark Mobius, who successfully predicted the BTC crash from $30,000 to $20,000 in 2022, if the Fed continues to tighten, the cryptocurrency could drop to around $10,000. Mobius said: With higher interest rates, holding or buying Bitcoin or other cryptocurrencies becomes less attractive since just holding the coin does not pay interest.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>The start of a new year kicked off Bitcoin price and crypto market forecasts across social media and mainstream media platforms. Experts are debating whether bulls or bears will drive 2023’s price action. Last year, bears took over and sent the benchmark crypto back to its 2020 levels. </strong></p>

<p>As of this writing, the Bitcoin price trades at $16,700, recording a small profit during today’s trading session. On higher timeframes, the cryptocurrency continues to record sideways price action. The latter could operate as the dominant price action for 2023. </p>
<img class="wp-image-514454 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-Holiday-860x376.png" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT Crypto Holiday" width="860" height="376" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-Holiday-860x376.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-Holiday-460x201.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-Holiday-768x336.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-Holiday-1536x672.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-Holiday-750x328.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-Holiday-1140x499.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-Holiday.png 1813w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<h2>The Best Is Yet To Come For The Bitcoin Price</h2>
<p>Per a <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/02/the-boldest-bitcoin-price-predictions-for-2023.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a> from CNBC, the Bitcoin price is bound for an extreme shift in its trajectory. Optimistic experts, such as BTC bull Tim Draper, believe the cryptocurrency will trend higher from its current levels. </p>
<p>Draper believes the benchmark crypto will experience a 1,400% rally, reclaim previously lost territory, and break above $250,000 by mid-2023. The BTC bulls believe macroeconomic conditions will push adoption much higher. </p>
<p>One demographic will lead this potential new wave of adoption that will coincide with the upcoming Bitcoin halving. This event is scheduled for 2024, but in the past, the market has priced its impact much earlier. Draper said:</p>
<blockquote><p>My assumption is that since women control 80% of retail spending, and only 1 in 7 bitcoin wallets are currently held by women that the dam is about to break.</p></blockquote>
<p>Professor of finance at Sussex University, Carol Alexander, believes Bitcoin could see two short-term rallies. The first could take the Bitcoin price back to $30,000, and the second to $50,000 on the back of less trading volume and prominent players.</p>
<p>As FTX and Three Arrows Capital collapse, Alexander expects less competition in the market, which could provide other prominent players with room to push BTC upwards. The professor explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>There will be a managed bull market in 2023, not a bubble — so we won’t see the price overshooting as before. We’ll see a month or two of stable trending prices interspersed with range-bounded periods and probably a couple of short-lived crashes.</p></blockquote>
Exploring Less Favorable Scenarios, How Low Can BTC Go?
<p>Better macroeconomic landscape, adoption, halving and supply squeeze, and less competition. These are the factors that could work in favor of the cryptocurrency. </p>
<p>On the other hand, Eric Robertsen from Standard Charted claims the Bitcoin price could return to its 2020 levels and touch $5,000. A lack of trust from investors and more capitulation from crypto companies could prompt this scenario. </p>
<p>The low liquidity levels in the sector make things worse. The current state of the market could experience another leg lower if the U.S. Federal Reserve (Fed) doubles down on its hawkish monetary policy. </p>

<p>According to Mark Mobius, who successfully predicted the BTC crash from $30,000 to $20,000 in 2022, if the Fed continues to tighten, the cryptocurrency could drop to around $10,000. Mobius said:</p>
<blockquote><p>With higher interest rates, holding or buying Bitcoin or other cryptocurrencies becomes less attractive since just holding the coin does not pay interest.</p></blockquote>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/iStock-1356849427-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Valkyrie Investments Wants To Take Over Grayscale Bitcoin Trust, Reveals Plans</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/valkyrie-wants-grayscale-bitcoin-trust/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 23:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin trust]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gbtc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grayscale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grayscale bitcoin trust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514430</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The state of the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC), the largest BTC trust in the world, has sparked concerns among investors in the space. With such a large discount to net asset value (NAV), there have been discussions on where the fund goes from here and if it is in trouble. Valkyrie Investments has now joined the conversation but is taking an entirely unexpected route. Valkyrie Wants The Grayscale Bitcoin TRUST In a statement that was released on Dec. 28, co-founder and CIO of Valkyrie Investments Steven McClurg revealed the company’s interest in taking over the management of Grayscale Bitcoin Trust. The statement highlights the unique challenges that are being faced by the GBTC and present the Valkyrie team as the best to manage the fund. Related Reading: Bitcoin Investor Sentiment Remains Steady As BTC Stalls At $16,000 It points to its experience in managing its own bitcoin fund, which it says has been operating with daily liquidity since it was launched a year ago. In addition, it also puts forward its experience with its multiple publicly traded BTC ETFs that were launched in 2021 as a good reason for why it would be a good fit. “We understand that Grayscale has played an important role in the development and growth of the bitcoin ecosystem with the launch of GBTC, and we respect the team and the work that they have done,” the statement said. However, in light of recent events involving Grayscale and its family of affiliated companies, it is time for a change. Valkyrie is the best company to manage GBTC to ensure its investors are treated fairly.” The company also announced a brand new fund called the “Valkyrie Opportunistic Fund, LP” which it says was created to help investors take advantage of the GBTC discount to NAV. “we are very interested in realizing the true value of the underlying bitcoin for our investors and will actively pursue this goal on their behalf,” McClurg said. GBTC sells trading at $8.11 &#124; Source: Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (BTC) on TradingView.com The Roadmap To Success Valkyrie’s statement also included its plan to actually improve the management of the Grayscale bitcoin trust if it were to take over. These were divided into three points. The first was that it plans to facilitate orderly redemptions for investors at NAV when they want it through a Regulation M filing. According to the statement, this would allow the investors to redeem shares without delays and at a fair price. Next was the plan to lower the fees associated with the fund. Valkyrie wants an over 50% reduction in the fee to fit in with best industry practices. As such, it plans to reduce the fee from 200 basis points to 75 basis points. Related Reading: Santiment: Bitcoin Will Trend Lower Because Whales Are Still Selling Last but not is the fact that Valkyrie wants to honor investor share redemptions in both BTC and cash. Its reasoning behind this was that it believes that it gives investors “greater flexibility and choice when it comes to redeeming their shares.” McClurg closes out the statement with a call for the statement to be considered. “We are committed to putting the interests of GBTC shareholders first, and we have the experience and expertise to do so effectively,” the co-founder said. The GBTC discount to NAV remains high despite some recovery recorded as 2022 drew to a close. It had reached a high of 48.57% on Dec. 16 but by the end of the day on Friday, Dec. 30, the GBTC discount had fallen to 45.17%. Featured image from Bloomberg, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">The state of the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC), the largest BTC trust in the world, has sparked concerns among investors in the space. With such a large discount to net asset value (NAV), there have been discussions on where the fund goes from here and if it is in trouble. Valkyrie Investments has now joined the conversation but is taking an entirely unexpected route.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Valkyrie Wants The Grayscale Bitcoin TRUST</h2>
<p class="p2">In a <a href="https://valkyrieinvest.com/press/opportunities-around-gbtc/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">statement</a> that was released on Dec. 28, co-founder and CIO of Valkyrie Investments Steven McClurg revealed the company’s interest in taking over the management of Grayscale Bitcoin Trust. The statement highlights the unique challenges that are being faced by the GBTC and present the Valkyrie team as the best to manage the fund.</p>

<p class="p2">It points to its experience in managing its own bitcoin fund, which it says has been operating with daily liquidity since it was launched a year ago. In addition, it also puts forward its experience with its multiple publicly traded BTC ETFs that were launched in 2021 as a good reason for why it would be a good fit.</p>
<p class="p2">“We understand that Grayscale has played an important role in the development and growth of the bitcoin ecosystem with the launch of GBTC, and we respect the team and the work that they have done,” the statement said. However, in light of recent events involving Grayscale and its family of affiliated companies, it is time for a change. Valkyrie is the best company to manage GBTC to ensure its investors are treated fairly.”</p>
<p class="p2">The company also announced a brand new fund called the “Valkyrie Opportunistic Fund, LP” which it says was created to help investors take advantage of the GBTC discount to NAV. “we are very interested in realizing the true value of the underlying bitcoin for our investors and will actively pursue this goal on their behalf,” McClurg said.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/sWShCSqo/" alt="Grayscale bitcoin trust (GBTC) price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1760" /></p>

<h2 class="p2">The Roadmap To Success</h2>
<p class="p2">Valkyrie’s statement also included its plan to actually improve the management of the Grayscale bitcoin trust if it were to take over. These were divided into three points.</p>
<p class="p2">The first was that it plans to facilitate orderly redemptions for investors at NAV when they want it through a Regulation M filing. According to the statement, this would allow the investors to redeem shares without delays and at a fair price.</p>
<p class="p2">Next was the plan to lower the fees associated with the fund. Valkyrie wants an over 50% reduction in the fee to fit in with best industry practices. As such, it plans to reduce the fee from 200 basis points to 75 basis points.</p>

<p class="p2">Last but not is the fact that Valkyrie wants to honor investor share redemptions in both BTC and cash. Its reasoning behind this was that it believes that it gives investors “greater flexibility and choice when it comes to redeeming their shares.”</p>
<p class="p2">McClurg closes out the statement with a call for the statement to be considered. “We are committed to putting the interests of GBTC shareholders first, and we have the experience and expertise to do so effectively,” the co-founder said.</p>
<p class="p2">The <a href="https://ycharts.com/companies/GBTC/discount_or_premium_to_nav" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">GBTC discount to NAV remains high</a> despite some recovery recorded as 2022 drew to a close. It had reached a high of 48.57% on Dec. 16 but by the end of the day on Friday, Dec. 30, the GBTC discount had fallen to 45.17%.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Grayscale-bitcoin-trust-460x306.jpeg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Crypto Holiday Special: Past, Present, And Future With Ben Lilly</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/interview/crypto-holiday-past-future-with-ben-lilly/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 23:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Holiday]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514445</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[2022 is coming to an end, and our staff at NewsBTC decided to launch this Crypto Holiday Special to provide some perspective on the crypto industry. We will talk with multiple guests to understand this year’s highs and lows for crypto. Related Reading: A Crypto Holiday Special: Past, Present, And Future With Blofin In the spirit of Charles Dicken’s classic, “A Christmas Carol,” we’ll look into crypto from different angles, look at its possible trajectory for 2023 and find common ground amongst these different views of an industry that might support the future of finances. Ben Lilly: “ (…) for fundamentals… Nothing has changed. If anything, builders are building faster than ever before. All of us veterans know that right now are the most productive weeks you can have in crypto. It is a blessing to those that can weather such bearish times.” And now, for a bonus round, we spoke with Ben Lilly, Co-Founder at Jarvis Labs, the on-chain analytics and token design firm tracking the crypto market. Lilly offered his views on the industry’s current state, why the Bear Market must be used as a time for building, and why the nascent class has matured. This is what he told us: Q: What’s the most significant difference for the crypto market today compared to Christmas 2021? Beyond the price of Bitcoin, Ethereum, and others, what changed from that moment of euphoria to today’s perpetual fear? Has there been a decline in adoption and liquidity? Are fundamentals still valid? A: In December 2021 we were discussing whether or not the U.S. Federal Reserve would follow through on rate hikes in the face of bubbling inflation. A year later, what we’ve seen is a strategic push on saying they will take two steps, and instead take three in a hawkish/bearish manner. It has not only hurt markets, but ensured markets could not find any solid footing to build momentum on. This mentality led to a rapid hiking regime. The down wind effects were dollars as a currency were the asset to hold. And most everything else lost value to the dollar. A lot of people like to say Bitcoin, Ethereum, and other assets “lost value”. This is a misnomer. We price things in U.S. dollars, and relative to the dollar, these assets lost considerable value. What a lot of people are also slowly realizing is that most participants in crypto markets are and were speculators. This is rather unfortunate, in my opinion. And something I look to track better with data. The drop in speculators (and many market makers closing up shops) has left a significant hole in liquidity. We are well aware of this. It is very difficult for market makers to run smoothly on some second tier exchanges as the books are pretty dry. We understand this well as we began to explore market making since our team has run autonomous trading systems for half a decade now. Clients are asking us more now than ever to do market making, so our team has begun ramping up these operations for 2023. As for fundamentals… Nothing has changed. If anything, builders are building faster than ever before. All of us veterans know that right now are the most productive weeks you can have in crypto. It is a blessing to those that can weather such bearish times. I’m seeing some really impressive tech solutions coming to fruition right now. Our team is testing some of them currently and look to broaden our functionality onchain in the coming months – something we’ve been exploring for years now. To us, it’s a testament to the fundamentals of the industry only getting better. Q: What are the dominant narratives driving this change in market conditions? And what should be the narrative today? What are most people overlooking? We saw a major crypto exchange blowing up, a hedge fund thought to be untouchable, and an ecosystem that promised a financial utopia. Is Crypto still the future of finance, or should the community pursue a new vision? A: Operations that take place onchain are becoming more desirable than before. Our clients are pushing us in this direction, which tells us the don’t trust, verify mentality is becoming more prominent. I love hearing this and hope to push everything we do to be fully onchain in the years to come. I’ll put it this way, never would I have imagined our team would be looking into zero knowledge technology to run part of our operations. To put it simply, the vision is the same, just more crystallized – a process that will keep happening as years pass. Q: If you must choose one, what do you think was a significant moment for crypto in 2022? And will the industry feel its consequences across 2023? Where do you see the industry next Christmas? Will it survive this winter? Mainstream is once again declaring the death of the industry. Will they finally get it right? A: The significant moment was GBTC sliding into negative NAV. As the tide was pulled out in 2022, we learned what was really happening in the waters of crypto, and we see many blowups having origins with the Grayscale Trust product. Three Arrows Capital, Genesis, DCG, BlockFi, Voyager, and others were all associated with the Trust and as the value of the Trust was more than the worth of all the shares outstanding (negative NAV), market dynamics caused spot demand to wane around April 2021. The timing with this and what the U.S. Federal Reserve did with rate hikes was like a double edge sword where both edges were pointed in the same direction. Higher rates and lower spot demand due to a toxic Grayscale product meant the bear market sword cut twice as much. As for 2023, I still think some of the worst is yet to come. I’m not necessarily referring to price here. I’m talking about operations not having enough cash to weather the winter. Revenues are down, new entrants to crypto are down. While I think this is good in a way because it rids the industry of poorly run businesses, it’ll cause some headline fears for the industry as companies close their doors. It won’t be the end of the industry from my vantage point. Those that have capital have plenty of runway. And even those that don’t have multi-year runways are staffed by very passionate builders. By the end of 2023 we will see the market coming back to life with lots of excitement. I don’t believe it’ll be a full blown bull market by any means… It’ll be more about projects rolling out the things that they’ve been busy building for the year. You give a bunch of crypto devs a year to build, the results are jaw dropping. Q: And, of course, we have to ask; many claim that the FTX collapse is setting the industry back to the 2018 bear market. Back to the Initial Coin Offering (ICO) era, to the so-called &#8220;Wild Wild West&#8221; days of crypto, what do you think about this idea, and where do you think the industry stands now? More importantly, what is Jarvis&#8217; role in this context, and where do you aim to be in 2023 and beyond? A: Crypto is maturing just like all of us do as we age. You ask anybody who has had ups and downs if they were set back to when they were a younger version of themselves… Most will say they are much wiser, and often the setbacks is how we truly realize our potential. Crypto is the same. Related Reading: A Crypto Holiday Special: Past, Present, And Future With Tony Spilotro We discussed earlier about how onchain solutions are more in demand than ever… Well the industry had a bad go at centralized entities like FTX, which had one goal of making money, and not contributing to the space. The space will be wiser moving forward. And we hope Jarvis Labs can help push this mindset. Our team has been busy in many verticals. We have teams building software solutions, new metrics, dashboards, token designs, algorithms, and a few other things that we will unveil soon. But if I had to keep it to one role, it’s to help empower everybody to hold crypto to a higher standard. We can be better. Let’s be better.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>2022 is coming to an end, and our staff at NewsBTC decided to launch this Crypto Holiday Special to provide some perspective on the crypto industry. We will talk with multiple guests to understand this year’s highs and lows for crypto.</strong></p>

<p><strong>In the spirit of Charles Dicken’s classic, “A Christmas Carol,” we’ll look into crypto from different angles, look at its possible trajectory for 2023 and find common ground amongst these different views of an industry that might support the future of finances.</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: center"><strong>Ben Lilly: “ (…) for fundamentals… Nothing has changed. If anything, builders are building faster than ever before. All of us veterans know that right now are the most productive weeks you can have in crypto. It is a blessing to those that can weather such bearish times.”</strong></p>
<p>And now, for a bonus round, we spoke with Ben Lilly, Co-Founder at <a href="https://twitter.com/Jarvis_Labs_LLC" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Jarvis Labs,</a> the on-chain analytics and token design firm tracking the crypto market. Lilly offered his views on the industry’s current state, why the Bear Market must be used as a time for building, and why the nascent class has matured. This is what he told us:</p>
<p><strong>Q: What’s the most significant difference for the crypto market today compared to Christmas 2021? Beyond the price of Bitcoin, Ethereum, and others, what changed from that moment of euphoria to today’s perpetual fear? Has there been a decline in adoption and liquidity? Are fundamentals still valid? </strong></p>
<p>A: In December 2021 we were discussing whether or not the U.S. Federal Reserve would follow through on rate hikes in the face of bubbling inflation. A year later, what we’ve seen is a strategic push on saying they will take two steps, and instead take three in a hawkish/bearish manner. It has not only hurt markets, but ensured markets could not find any solid footing to build momentum on.</p>
<p>This mentality led to a rapid hiking regime. The down wind effects were dollars as a currency were the asset to hold. And most everything else lost value to the dollar.</p>
<p>A lot of people like to say Bitcoin, Ethereum, and other assets “lost value”. This is a misnomer. We price things in U.S. dollars, and relative to the dollar, these assets lost considerable value.</p>
<p>What a lot of people are also slowly realizing is that most participants in crypto markets are and were speculators. This is rather unfortunate, in my opinion. And something I look to track better with data.</p>
<p>The drop in speculators (and many market makers closing up shops) has left a significant hole in liquidity. We are well aware of this. It is very difficult for market makers to run smoothly on some second tier exchanges as the books are pretty dry. We understand this well as we began to explore market making since our team has run autonomous trading systems for half a decade now. Clients are asking us more now than ever to do market making, so our team has begun ramping up these operations for 2023.</p>
<p>As for fundamentals… Nothing has changed. If anything, builders are building faster than ever before. All of us veterans know that right now are the most productive weeks you can have in crypto. It is a blessing to those that can weather such bearish times. I’m seeing some really impressive tech solutions coming to fruition right now. Our team is testing some of them currently and look to broaden our functionality onchain in the coming months – something we’ve been exploring for years now. To us, it’s a testament to the fundamentals of the industry only getting better.</p>
<p><strong>Q: What are the dominant narratives driving this change in market conditions? And what should be the narrative today? What are most people overlooking? We saw a major crypto exchange blowing up, a hedge fund thought to be untouchable, and an ecosystem that promised a financial utopia. Is Crypto still the future of finance, or should the community pursue a new vision?</strong></p>
<p>A: Operations that take place onchain are becoming more desirable than before. Our clients are pushing us in this direction, which tells us the don’t trust, verify mentality is becoming more prominent. I love hearing this and hope to push everything we do to be fully onchain in the years to come.</p>
<p>I’ll put it this way, never would I have imagined our team would be looking into zero knowledge technology to run part of our operations. To put it simply, the vision is the same, just more crystallized – a process that will keep happening as years pass.</p>
<p><strong>Q: If you must choose one, what do you think was a significant moment for crypto in 2022? And will the industry feel its consequences across 2023? Where do you see the industry next Christmas? Will it survive this winter? Mainstream is once again declaring the death of the industry. Will they finally get it right? </strong></p>
<p>A: The significant moment was GBTC sliding into negative NAV.</p>
<p>As the tide was pulled out in 2022, we learned what was really happening in the waters of crypto, and we see many blowups having origins with the Grayscale Trust product.</p>
<p>Three Arrows Capital, Genesis, DCG, BlockFi, Voyager, and others were all associated with the Trust and as the value of the Trust was more than the worth of all the shares outstanding (negative NAV), market dynamics caused spot demand to wane around April 2021.</p>
<p>The timing with this and what the U.S. Federal Reserve did with rate hikes was like a double edge sword where both edges were pointed in the same direction. Higher rates and lower spot demand due to a toxic Grayscale product meant the bear market sword cut twice as much.</p>
<p>As for 2023, I still think some of the worst is yet to come. I’m not necessarily referring to price here. I’m talking about operations not having enough cash to weather the winter. Revenues are down, new entrants to crypto are down. While I think this is good in a way because it rids the industry of poorly run businesses, it’ll cause some headline fears for the industry as companies close their doors.</p>
<p>It won’t be the end of the industry from my vantage point. Those that have capital have plenty of runway. And even those that don’t have multi-year runways are staffed by very passionate builders. By the end of 2023 we will see the market coming back to life with lots of excitement. I don’t believe it’ll be a full blown bull market by any means… It’ll be more about projects rolling out the things that they’ve been busy building for the year. You give a bunch of crypto devs a year to build, the results are jaw dropping.</p>
<p><strong>Q: And, of course, we have to ask; many claim that the FTX collapse is setting the industry back to the 2018 bear market. Back to the Initial Coin Offering (ICO) era, to the so-called &#8220;Wild Wild West&#8221; days of crypto, what do you think about this idea, and where do you think the industry stands now? More importantly, what is Jarvis&#8217; role in this context, and where do you aim to be in 2023 and beyond?</strong></p>
<p>A: Crypto is maturing just like all of us do as we age. You ask anybody who has had ups and downs if they were set back to when they were a younger version of themselves… Most will say they are much wiser, and often the setbacks is how we truly realize our potential. Crypto is the same.</p>

<p>We discussed earlier about how onchain solutions are more in demand than ever… Well the industry had a bad go at centralized entities like FTX, which had one goal of making money, and not contributing to the space.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514454 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-Holiday-860x376.png" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT Crypto Holiday" width="860" height="376" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-Holiday-860x376.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-Holiday-460x201.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-Holiday-768x336.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-Holiday-1536x672.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-Holiday-750x328.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-Holiday-1140x499.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Crypto-Holiday.png 1813w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>The space will be wiser moving forward. And we hope Jarvis Labs can help push this mindset. Our team has been busy in many verticals. We have teams building software solutions, new metrics, dashboards, token designs, algorithms, and a few other things that we will unveil soon. But if I had to keep it to one role, it’s to help empower everybody to hold crypto to a higher standard. We can be better. Let’s be better.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto-Holiday-Special-cover-image-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Still Stuck At $16,700, Why This Indicator Points To New Trajectory</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/bitcoin-stuck-indicator-points-to-new-trajectory/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Breaking News Ticker]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514428</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin has seen little to no action in its first two days of 2023; the cryptocurrency is bound for a spike in volatility, but in which direction? After experiencing months of downside pressure, there seems to be no room for further losses. Related Reading: Billion-Dollar Hedge Fund Is Betting Against Bitcoin And Grayscale, Not Just USDT As of this writing, Bitcoin trades at $16,700 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. On higher timeframes, BTC’s price records similar price action. Other cryptocurrencies in the top 10 by market capitalization follow this trajectory. Will History Repeat For Bitcoin? Pain Levels Max Out According to analyst Will Clement from Reflexivity Research, the price of Bitcoin is approaching critical levels on its Net Realized Profit and Loss Over Market Cap. This indicator measures the capital gain or loss for the cryptocurrency. As seen in the chart below, the metric is nearing levels of absolute capitulation when the crypto market and its participants are at their lowest. The industry approached a similar level in 2018 when BTC crashed from $20,000 and Ethereum from $1,400. In 2014 and 2015, the metric dropped into this territory following the collapse of the biggest Bitcoin exchange in the world, Mt. Gox. Today, with the collapse of prominent crypto companies, such as FTX and Three Arrows Capital, the market is close to previous cycle bottoms. Clemente said the following about this metric and its implication for the price of Bitcoin: Capitulation, represented by net realized losses adjusted for market cap, is on-par with any prior macro Bitcoin bottom. Major pain is being felt in this market. January Is The Worst Month To Expect Profits? Despite the metrics and indicators pointing towards extreme market sentiment and capitulation levels, the timing might remain unfavorable for Bitcoin. The cryptocurrency might see further sideways price action and additional losses until there is a change in macroeconomic conditions. Additional data from a pseudonym analyst indicates that January is historically a red month for the cryptocurrency. In the past two years, the returns for BTC in January were a historical exception. Since 2015, the cryptocurrency has been trading in the red during January, recording some of its worst losses. 2023 could see BTC return to that dynamic, but this period of losses might precede two months of gains. Related Reading: Litecoin Surges 7% In Strong 2023 Start, Jumps To 12th On Market Cap List In February and March, Bitcoin saw its best performance, as seen in the chart. These historical gains might finally align with the extreme sentiment in the market and macroconditions.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Bitcoin has seen little to no action in its first two days of 2023; the cryptocurrency is bound for a spike in volatility, but in which direction? After experiencing months of downside pressure, there seems to be no room for further losses. </strong></p>

<p>As of this writing, Bitcoin trades at $16,700 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. On higher timeframes, BTC’s price records similar price action. Other cryptocurrencies in the top 10 by market capitalization follow this trajectory.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514440 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-860x376.png" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT" width="860" height="376" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-860x376.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-460x201.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-768x336.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1536x672.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-750x328.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1140x499.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT.png 1813w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<h2>Will History Repeat For Bitcoin? Pain Levels Max Out</h2>
<p>According to analyst Will Clement from Reflexivity Research, the <a href="https://twitter.com/WClementeIII/status/1609747636302626816" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">price of Bitcoin is approaching critical levels</a> on its Net Realized Profit and Loss Over Market Cap. This indicator measures the capital gain or loss for the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>As seen in the chart below, the metric is nearing levels of absolute capitulation when the crypto market and its participants are at their lowest. The industry approached a similar level in 2018 when BTC crashed from $20,000 and Ethereum from $1,400.</p>
<p>In 2014 and 2015, the metric dropped into this territory following the collapse of the biggest Bitcoin exchange in the world, Mt. Gox. Today, with the collapse of prominent crypto companies, such as FTX and Three Arrows Capital, the market is close to previous cycle bottoms.</p>
<p>Clemente said the following about this metric and its implication for the price of Bitcoin:</p>
<blockquote><p>Capitulation, represented by net realized losses adjusted for market cap, is on-par with any prior macro Bitcoin bottom. Major pain is being felt in this market.</p></blockquote>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514433 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-860x484.jpeg" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT Chart 2" width="860" height="484" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-860x484.jpeg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-460x259.jpeg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-768x432.jpeg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-1536x864.jpeg 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-750x422.jpeg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-1140x641.jpeg 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2.jpeg 1920w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
January Is The Worst Month To Expect Profits?
<p>Despite the metrics and indicators pointing towards extreme market sentiment and capitulation levels, the timing might remain unfavorable for Bitcoin. The cryptocurrency might see further sideways price action and additional losses until there is a change in macroeconomic conditions.</p>
<p>Additional data <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-price-could-kick-2023-wrong-foot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">from a pseudonym analyst indicates that January is historically a red month</a> for the cryptocurrency. In the past two years, the returns for BTC in January were a historical exception.</p>
<p>Since 2015, the cryptocurrency has been trading in the red during January, recording some of its worst losses. 2023 could see BTC return to that dynamic, but this period of losses might precede two months of gains.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514439 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-860x347.png" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT Chart 3" width="860" height="347" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-860x347.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-460x186.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-768x310.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-750x303.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-1140x460.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3.png 1377w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />

<p>In February and March, Bitcoin saw its best performance, as seen in the chart. These historical gains might finally align with the extreme sentiment in the market and macroconditions.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-2-460x259.jpeg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Closes 2022 With A Year-Low &#8211; Will 2023 Be Better?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/all/bitcoin-cash-2022-year-low/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 19:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tags: Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514447</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It is no surprise for Bitcoin Cash to perform this poorly when the entire crypto market fell deeper in the bear market due to various negative factors, including the much-publicized collapse of crypto exchange FTX. According to CoinGecko, the token is down a further 1.4% in the past 24 hours. This doesn’t bode well as major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum have started 2023 very weakly as well. Bitcoin Cash And Bitcoin Connections Since Bitcoin Cash is a fork of Bitcoin, BCH will have a strong correlation to BTC most of the  time. To have a glimpse of where BCH will go, a look at what crypto analysts think of Bitcoin will provide strong insights on what the future for BCH will look like.  CryptoQuant analyst Dan Lim recently released his take on the current state of affairs in Bitcoin. He noticed that the top crypto is being dictated by a small number of whales. However, his analysis is contradicted by recent news that BTC is actually being accumulated by whales.  Image: Zipmex This might mean that Dan Lim’s analysis points to retail investor activity or a mix of both retail and whale activity.  What if this is the beginning of 3 bullish years for #BTC?$BTC #Crypto #Bitcoin pic.twitter.com/OtuOFLUftE — Rekt Capital (@rektcapital) January 1, 2023 2023: Year Of Reversals? With institutional investors slowly edging their way to the market, an uptick in Bitcoin will translate to gains in BCH as the two are closely correlated. However, some major financial institutions have been lost on the idea of cryptocurrency as a portfolio diversifier due to the many controversies that plagued the crypto market.  If Rekt Capital’s hypothesis, which essentially says that 2023 will be the accumulation period before the potential 2024 crypto bull market, is true, gains will be up for the entire crypto market, especially Bitcoin Cash.  Related Reading: Decentraland (MANA) Sheds 90% In 2022 Despite Solid NFT Volume Performance Related Reading: Avalanche Exits 2022 With 10% Decline – Will AVAX Recoup That Loss This Week? However, with the broader financial market having its worst year since the 2008 crisis, we can set 2023 to be a slow but steady phase of loss and gradual gain in the next few months.  In the short term, potential BCH investors and traders could hope that the current support at $96.18 will hold. But with potential downturns caused by further interest rate increases, we might see BCH bears test the $89.17 in the coming weeks.  With the start of another fiscal year, BCH investors and traders should watch out for macroeconomic developments as it also holds sway on the crypto market. Caution should still be exercised as the future is still uncertain for Bitcoin Cash and crypto as a whole.  -Featured image: Binance Academy]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It is no surprise for Bitcoin Cash to perform this poorly when the entire crypto market fell deeper in the bear market due to various negative factors, including the much-publicized collapse of crypto exchange <a href="https://www.businessinsider.in/investment/news/sam-bankman-frieds-ftx-collapse-is-a-nightmare-of-shady-finances-and-these-bizarre-schemes-emerged-recently/articleshow/96649659.cms" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">FTX</a>. </p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/bitcoin-cash" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a>, the token is down a further 1.4% in the past 24 hours. This doesn’t bode well as major cryptocurrencies like <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/bitcoin-cash" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Bitcoin</a> and <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/ethereum" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Ethereum</a> have started 2023 very weakly as well.</p>
<h2><strong>Bitcoin Cash And Bitcoin Connections</strong></h2>
<p>Since Bitcoin Cash is a <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/news/all-about-bitcoin-cash-hard-fork/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">fork</a> of Bitcoin, BCH will have a strong correlation to BTC most of the  time. To have a glimpse of where BCH will go, a look at what crypto analysts think of Bitcoin will provide strong insights on what the future for BCH will look like. </p>
<p>CryptoQuant analyst Dan Lim recently <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/quicktake/63ac0852f307a42a00cd6b4f-BTC-Market-Led-by-Whales" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">released</a> his take on the current state of affairs in Bitcoin. He noticed that the top crypto is being dictated by a small number of whales. However, his analysis is contradicted by recent news that BTC is actually being accumulated by whales. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-514466 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BCH-460x275.png" alt="Bitcoin Cash" width="460" height="275" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BCH-460x275.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BCH-860x515.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BCH-768x460.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BCH-750x449.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BCH.png 1019w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p>This might mean that Dan Lim’s analysis points to retail investor activity or a mix of both retail and whale activity. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">What if this is the beginning of 3 bullish years for <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BTC?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#BTC</a>?<a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$BTC</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Crypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#Crypto</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#Bitcoin</a> <a href="https://t.co/OtuOFLUftE" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/OtuOFLUftE</a></p>
<p>— Rekt Capital (@rektcapital) <a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1609351720143814658?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 1, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<h2><strong>2023: Year Of Reversals?</strong></h2>
<p>With institutional investors slowly edging their way to the market, an uptick in Bitcoin will translate to gains in BCH as the two are closely correlated. However, some major financial institutions have been <a href="https://sg.finance.yahoo.com/news/big-investors-giving-crypto-markets-063907872.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">lost</a> on the idea of cryptocurrency as a portfolio diversifier due to the many controversies that plagued the crypto market. </p>
<p>If <a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1609351720143814658" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Rekt Capital’s</a> hypothesis, which essentially says that 2023 will be the accumulation period before the potential 2024 crypto bull market, is true, gains will be up for the entire crypto market, especially Bitcoin Cash. </p>

<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Pxohn1OR/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>

<p>However, with the broader financial market having its <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/s-p-500-caps-off-dismal-year-with-worst-loss-since-2008-crash/ar-AA15OUUD" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">worst</a> year since the 2008 crisis, we can set 2023 to be a slow but steady phase of loss and gradual gain in the next few months. </p>
<p>In the short term, potential BCH investors and traders could hope that the current support at $96.18 will hold. But with potential downturns caused by further interest rate <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/billconerly/2022/11/10/interest-rates-going-up-even-more-in-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">increases</a>, we might see BCH bears test the $89.17 in the coming weeks. </p>
<p>With the start of another fiscal year, BCH investors and traders should watch out for macroeconomic developments as it also holds sway on the crypto market. Caution should still be exercised as the future is still uncertain for Bitcoin Cash and crypto as a whole. </p>
<p><em>-Featured image: Binance Academy</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bitcoin-1-460x262.png" width="460" height="262" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano Enters 2023 With A Bang, But ADA Still Bearish In The Short Term </title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/cardano-enters-2023-with-a-bang/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 17:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[federal reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tags: Cardano]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514453</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) started 2023 with an upward trend that retested the $0.2522 resistance level but has since failed to gather any meaningful momentum to sustain the run. As of writing, Coingecko notes an increase of a measly 0.2%. This might be small gains, but is a great indicator that investor sentiment has reversed by the start of this fiscal year.  Related Reading: Can Polygon (MATIC) Break 2022 Sideways Momentum? Can ADA Bounce Back? Cardano in 2022 has been very bearish in terms of its native token ADA. Even after its Vasil hard fork, an event likened to the Ethereum Merge, the token still continued its downward spiral to its current price of $0.2491.  One reason that pushed ADA’s price down is the current macroeconomic situation. During the first quarter of 2022, the U.S. Federal Reserve raised rates until last month which is the seventh rate increase in 2022.  This in turn had adverse effects on the market, pushing the price of both traditional finance instruments and digital assets down. But 2023 seems to have a new effect on the struggling ecosystem.  Image: Coinmama Cardano Fared Better Vs. Competitors The recent FTX debacle dealt a blow to any protocol or ecosystem affiliated with the failed exchange. Solana, a touted “Sam coin”, fell in value tremendously. According to recent news, Solana’s native token SOL has fallen so much that some are saying they are nearing collapse.  According to Santiment, ADA is undervalued at the moment, showing extreme exhaustion of the bears. Twitter users who are very bullish on Cardano share metrics that are increasing. With the upcoming on-chain upgrade bringing more features on the platform, investors on ADA might see more bullish action in the coming weeks.  Check the #Cardano on-chain stats. Everything goes up. pic.twitter.com/Q7pw44WTkA — Cardano YODA (@JaromirTesar) January 1, 2023 With Solana down, the NFT market is shifting from Solana to Cardano. However, Cardano still has a long way to go to be even on par with Solana’s trade volume and value. ADA investors and traders could see the token break through the $0.2522 price resistance.  ADA total market cap at $8.7 billion on the daily chart &#124; Chart: TradingView.com Related Reading: Can Polygon (MATIC) Break 2022 Sideways Momentum? A break on this price resistance level could be a new sign of life to the struggling ecosystem. In the long term, investors and traders should watch for macroeconomic developments as this has a strong effect on the crypto markets.  As markets recover, ADA’s current price movement could be a catalyst to a stronger bullish movement. However, ADA’s volatility is increasing which, if the $0.2522 resistance holds, can lead to drops as low as $0.2397. -Featured image: The Independent]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cardano (ADA) started 2023 with an upward trend that retested the $0.2522 resistance level but has since failed to gather any meaningful momentum to sustain the run. </p>
<p>As of writing, <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/cardano" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Coingecko</a> notes an increase of a measly 0.2%. This might be small gains, but is a great indicator that investor sentiment has reversed by the start of this fiscal year. </p>

<h2><strong>Can ADA Bounce Back?</strong></h2>
<p>Cardano in 2022 has been very bearish in terms of its native token ADA. Even after its <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/stocks/cardano-s-ada-upcoming-vasil-hard-fork-what-to-know-1031735403#:~:text=After%20a%20long%20wait%20from%20fans%20and%20investors%2C,which%20is%20set%20to%20occur%20on%20September%2016." target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Vasil hard fork</a>, an event likened to the Ethereum Merge, the token still continued its downward spiral to its current price of $0.2491. </p>
<p>One reason that pushed ADA’s price down is the current macroeconomic situation. During the first quarter of 2022, the U.S. Federal Reserve <a href="https://www.nerdwallet.com/article/finance/fed-rate-look-back-look-ahead#:~:text=The%20Federal%20Reserve%20raised%20the%20federal%20funds%20rate,2022%2C%20with%20more%20on%20the%20way%20in%202023." target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">raised rates</a> until last month which is the seventh rate increase in 2022. </p>
<p>This in turn had adverse effects on the market, pushing the price of both traditional finance instruments and digital assets down. But 2023 seems to have a new effect on the struggling ecosystem. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-514464 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CC-860x359.png" alt="" width="860" height="359" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CC-860x359.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CC-460x192.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CC-768x321.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CC-750x313.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CC.png 962w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>

<h2><strong>Cardano Fared Better Vs. Competitors</strong></h2>
<p>The recent FTX <a href="https://www.crowdfundinsider.com/2023/01/200474-thomas-kralow-financial-markets-professional-compares-ftx-collapse-with-mt-gox/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">debacle</a> dealt a blow to any protocol or ecosystem affiliated with the failed exchange. Solana, a touted <a href="https://a.msn.com/00/en-us/AA14Nbc8" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">“Sam coin”</a>, fell in value tremendously. According to recent news, Solana’s native token SOL has fallen so much that some are saying they are nearing <a href="https://www.weeklyblitz.net/economy/crypto-venture-solana-on-the-verge-of-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">collapse</a>. </p>
<p>According to <a href="https://insights.santiment.net/read/ada-is-undervalued-7152?utm_source=twitter&amp;utm_medium=post&amp;utm_campaign=twitter_ada_is_undervalued_insight_sanr_king_122722/&amp;fpr=twitter" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Santiment</a>, ADA is undervalued at the moment, showing extreme exhaustion of the bears. Twitter users who are very bullish on Cardano share metrics that are <a href="https://twitter.com/JaromirTesar/status/1609574603281633280?s=20" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">increasing</a>. With the <a href="https://twitter.com/thepizzaknight_/status/1609373418759012353?s=20" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">upcoming</a> on-chain upgrade bringing more features on the platform, investors on ADA might see more bullish action in the coming weeks. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Check the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Cardano?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#Cardano</a> on-chain stats. Everything goes up. <a href="https://t.co/Q7pw44WTkA" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/Q7pw44WTkA</a></p>
<p>— Cardano YODA (@JaromirTesar) <a href="https://twitter.com/JaromirTesar/status/1609574603281633280?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 1, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>With Solana down, the NFT market is <a href="https://twitter.com/marcosantiagoNY/status/1607889060609273857?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shifting</a> from Solana to Cardano. However, <a href="https://www.cryptoslam.io/blockchains/cardano" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Cardano</a> still has a long way to go to be even on par with <a href="https://www.cryptoslam.io/blockchains/solana" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Solana’s</a> trade volume and value. ADA investors and traders could see the token break through the $0.2522 price resistance. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ZMKPLa7N/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>


<p>A break on this price resistance level could be a new sign of life to the struggling ecosystem. In the long term, investors and traders should watch for macroeconomic developments as this has a strong effect on the crypto markets. </p>
<p>As markets recover, ADA’s current price movement could be a catalyst to a stronger bullish movement. However, ADA’s <a href="https://messari.io/asset/cardano/chart/daily-vol" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">volatility</a> is increasing which, if the $0.2522 resistance holds, can lead to drops as low as $0.2397.</p>
<p><em>-Featured image: The Independent</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-460x318.png" width="460" height="318" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SOL Jumps 15% In 24 Hours As Solana Receives Support From Ethereum Founder</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/solana/solana-support-from-ethereum-founder/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 17:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum founder]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514431</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) has been completely engulfed in FUD since the FTX crash. This invariably resulted in the price of the token declining much faster than the rest of the market, and last week, SOL touched single-digit values for the first time in almost two years. However, there seems to be a turn in the tide for the digital asset as it receives support from Vitalik Buterin. Vitalik Buterin Offers Support To Solana  Taking to Twitter, Ethereum founder Vitalik Buterin expressed support for Solana for the first time. Solana which had been the fiercest competitor of Ethereum had been unable to keep up given its ties to FTX crypto exchange, its sister company Alameda Research, and its disgraced founder Sam Bankman-Fried, but Buterin is not pleased that the competitor is essentially crumbling. Related Reading: Santiment: Bitcoin Will Trend Lower Because Whales Are Still Selling In the tweet, the Ethereum founder explained that “some smart people” had told it that there was still a good developer community on the blockchain who are earnest and smart. Furthermore, they added that since the opportunistic people trying to make a quick buck had now been pushed out, they expect the network to have a bright future. Buterin himself explains that he couldn’t tell if this was true looking in from the outside but said that he hoped that “the community gets its fair chance to thrive. This tweet was made about four days ago and it had an incredibly positive impact on Solana. SOL Price Rallies On Buterin Comments The price of SOL saw an upward trend following the tweets from the Ethereum founder. Although Solana remains a long way from its glory days, Buterin’s tweets had given the bulls just the morale boost they needed and by Monday, SOL’s price had surged as high as $12 before correcting back down. SOL recovers above $11 &#124; Source: SOLUSD on TradingView.com Presently, the price of the digital asset is sitting above $11, rising over 15% in the last 24 hours. This recovery has also helped to wipe out most of the losses recorded over the last week, and now, it is down only 1.81% in the last 7 days compared to over 20% losses being recorded last week. Related Reading: Bitcoin Investor Sentiment Remains Steady As BTC Stalls At $16,000 This recovery also puts the digital asset close to the top of the list of gainers for the day. It sits only behind Lido DAO which is up over 16% in the last hours. As for whether SOL will be able to maintain current prices and go higher, it depends on the momentum in the market. The cryptocurrency is still subject to intense FUD and community morale remains low but the $13 level remains within sights as long as buy pressure keeps up. Featured image from Coin Culture, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Solana (SOL) has been completely engulfed in FUD since the FTX crash. This invariably resulted in the price of the token declining much faster than the rest of the market, and last week, SOL touched single-digit values for the first time in almost two years. However, there seems to be a turn in the tide for the digital asset as it receives support from Vitalik Buterin.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Vitalik Buterin Offers Support To Solana </h2>
<p class="p2">Taking to Twitter, Ethereum founder Vitalik Buterin expressed support for Solana for the first time. Solana which had been the fiercest competitor of Ethereum had been unable to keep up given its ties to FTX crypto exchange, its sister company Alameda Research, and its disgraced founder Sam Bankman-Fried, but Buterin is not pleased that the competitor is essentially crumbling.</p>

<p class="p2">In the <a href="https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin/status/1608591727316684804?s=20&amp;t=4b23WhmA6rpOfFpmU-LOeQ" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">tweet</a>, the Ethereum founder explained that “some smart people” had told it that there was still a good developer community on the blockchain who are earnest and smart. Furthermore, they added that since the opportunistic people trying to make a quick buck had now been pushed out, they expect the network to have a bright future.</p>
<p class="p2">Buterin himself explains that he couldn’t tell if this was true looking in from the outside but said that he hoped that “the community gets its fair chance to thrive. This tweet was made about four days ago and it had an incredibly positive impact on Solana.</p>
<h2 class="p2">SOL Price Rallies On Buterin Comments</h2>
<p class="p2">The price of SOL saw an upward trend following the tweets from the Ethereum founder. Although Solana remains a long way from its glory days, Buterin’s tweets had given the bulls just the morale boost they needed and by Monday, SOL’s price had surged as high as $12 before correcting back down.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/F2C6wd3w/" alt="Solana (SOL) price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1760" /></p>

<p class="p2">Presently, the price of the digital asset is sitting above $11, rising over 15% in the last 24 hours. This recovery has also helped to wipe out most of the losses recorded over the last week, and now, it is down only 1.81% in the last 7 days compared to over 20% losses being recorded last week.</p>

<p class="p2">This recovery also puts the digital asset <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/gainers-losers/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">close to the top of the list of gainers for the day</a>. It sits only behind Lido DAO which is up over 16% in the last hours.</p>
<p class="p2">As for whether SOL will be able to maintain current prices and go higher, it depends on the momentum in the market. The cryptocurrency is still subject to intense FUD and community morale remains low but the $13 level remains within sights as long as buy pressure keeps up.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Solana--460x259.jpeg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Can Polygon (MATIC) Break 2022 Sideways Momentum? </title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/can-polygon-stop-2022-misery/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 15:22:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tags: MATIC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514458</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Polygon has been stuck in its current sideways movement since the later half of 2022. Since then, the ecosystem’s native token MATIC has not left its current support of $0.7550. This spot has left MATIC in a very delicate situation even as Polygon itself is setting itself apart from competitors.  Related Reading: Avalanche Exits 2022 With 10% Decline – Will AVAX Recoup That Loss This Week? Polygon Going Strong The ecosystem has ended 2022 on a beautiful note, though. Although the year&#8217;s bear market clawed through MATIC’s gains, the ecosystem is thriving with partnerships.  As of writing, the Ethereum L2 has over 20 partnerships with major brands like Nike, StarBucks, and Reddit. They mostly dealt with being the ideal NFT platform for their respective NFT collections or marketplace. Year to date, the NFT market of Polygon reached $305 million in trade value. This isn’t the only bullish development on the platform.  Bhavish Finance, a newly built prediction market platform, has reached new highs. According to the most recent tweet of Bhavish regarding its key metrics, the market platform breached 1,100 weekly active users with over $1.287 million predictions made on the platform.  According to Bhavish’s own website, the platform is handling over $90-$100 million in predictions and gains an average of $2.5 million to $3.5 million.  Major Headwinds Expected The ecosystem certainly is bullish, but the token is far from it. As of press time, MATIC is up by only 0.1%, showing signs of possible weakness.  MATIC has certainly suffered along with the entire crypto market following the collapse of crypto exchange FTX. Showing strong correlation to both Bitcoin and Ethereum, MATIC is set to have a bumpy 2023.  If ever BTC and ETH continue to suffer in the midst of possible hikes in interest by the U.S. Federal Reserve, we might see MATIC experiencing more pain. However, this is offset by eye-catching developments on-chain. MATIC total market cap at $6.8 billion on the daily chart &#124; Chart: TradingView.com Related Reading: Decentraland (MANA) Sheds 90% In 2022 Despite Solid NFT Volume Performance Most notable of these is the migration of y00ts and DeGods NFT collection to Polygon. This is a massive win for both Polygon and Ethereum against the touted “Ethereum killer” Solana. But with MATIC stuck on an oscillating path until now, the token’s holders can’t capitalize on the growth of the ecosystem just yet.  For investors and traders, the current support being this strong can support any upward growth. However, any bullish momentum that can be gained can only be attained above the current resistance at $0.8157. With the year only starting out, investors and traders should exercise caution as this sideways motion can always break down towards $0.7163.  -Featured image: Karate by Jesses]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Polygon has been stuck in its current sideways movement since the later half of 2022. Since then, the ecosystem’s native token MATIC has not left its current support of $0.7550. This spot has left MATIC in a very delicate situation even as Polygon itself is setting itself apart from competitors. </p>

<h2><strong>Polygon Going Strong</strong></h2>
<p>The ecosystem has ended 2022 on a beautiful note, though. Although the year&#8217;s bear market clawed through MATIC’s gains, the ecosystem is thriving with partnerships. </p>
<p>As of writing, the Ethereum L2 has over 20 <a href="https://twitter.com/RedCryptoKeeper/status/1609605974486138881/photo/1" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">partnerships</a> with major brands like Nike, StarBucks, and Reddit. They mostly dealt with being the ideal NFT platform for their respective NFT collections or marketplace. <a href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/polygon-nft-market-demonstrates-signs-223928811.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Year to date</a>, the NFT market of Polygon reached $305 million in trade value.</p>
<p>This isn’t the only bullish development on the platform. </p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/BhavishFinance" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Bhavish Finance</a>, a newly built prediction market platform, has reached new highs. According to the most recent tweet of Bhavish regarding its key metrics, the market platform breached 1,100 weekly active users with over $1.287 million predictions made on the platform. </p>
<p>According to Bhavish’s own website, the platform is handling over $90-$100 million in predictions and gains an average of $2.5 million to $3.5 million. </p>
<h2><strong>Major Headwinds Expected</strong></h2>
<p>The ecosystem certainly is bullish, but the token is far from it. As of press time, MATIC is up by only 0.1%, showing signs of possible weakness. </p>
<p>MATIC has certainly suffered along with the entire crypto market following the collapse of crypto exchange FTX. Showing strong correlation to both Bitcoin and Ethereum, MATIC is set to have a bumpy 2023. </p>
<p>If ever BTC and ETH continue to suffer in the midst of <a href="https://insurancenewsnet.com/oarticle/why-is-the-fed-looking-to-raise-interest-rates-in-23" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">possible hikes</a> in interest by the U.S. Federal Reserve, we might see MATIC experiencing more pain. However, this is offset by eye-catching developments on-chain.</p>


<p>Most notable of these is the <a href="https://www.investingcube.com/degods-and-y00ts-to-branch-off-to-ethereum-and-polygon-in-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">migration </a>of y00ts and DeGods NFT collection to Polygon. This is a massive win for both Polygon and Ethereum against the touted “Ethereum killer” Solana. But with MATIC stuck on an oscillating path until now, the token’s holders can’t capitalize on the growth of the ecosystem just yet. </p>
<p>For investors and traders, the current support being this strong can support any upward growth. However, any bullish momentum that can be gained can only be attained above the current resistance at $0.8157. With the year only starting out, investors and traders should exercise caution as this sideways motion can always break down towards $0.7163. </p>
<p><em>-Featured image: Karate by Jesses</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Polygon-460x261.png" width="460" height="261" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Taker Buy/Sell Ratio Can&#8217;t Give Any Clear Signals As Demand Remains Low</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-taker-buy-sell-ratio-demand-low/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 15:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Taker Buy Volume]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Taker Buy/Sell Ratio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Taker Sell Volume]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514424</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Bitcoin taker buy/sell ratio has been unable to give any real signal recently as the demand has remained low in the market. Bitcoin Taker Buy/Sell Ratio Hasn&#8217;t Been Able To Catch Any Momentum Recently As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, the taker buy/sell ratio hasn&#8217;t moved much above or below 1 since August 2022. The &#8220;Bitcoin taker buy/sell ratio&#8221; is an indicator that measures the ratio between the taker buy volume and the taker sell volume. When the value of this metric is greater than one, it means the buy or the &#8220;long&#8221; volume is higher in the market right now. Basically, this means that there are more buyers willing to purchase BTC at a higher price currently, and thus the buying pressure is stronger. On the other hand, values of the indicator under the threshold suggest the taker sell volume is more dominant at the moment. Such values imply a bearish sentiment is shared by the majority of the investors currently. Naturally, the ratio being exactly equal to one indicates the taker buy and taker sell volumes are exactly equal right now, and therefore the market is evenly split between bullish and bearish mentalities. Related Reading: Ethereum Finishes 2022 With ATH Correlation To Bitcoin, Despite The Merge Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the 14-day simple moving average (SMA) Bitcoin taker buy/sell ratio over the last few years: The 14-day SMA value of the metric seems to be close to 1 at the moment &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As you can see in the above graph, the quant has marked the relevant points of the trend for the 14-day SMA Bitcoin taker buy/sell ratio. It looks like whenever the indicator has crossed the 1.03 level, BTC has observed some bullish momentum shortly after. On the contrary, whenever the ratio dipped below the 0.97 level, a bearish trend followed the crypto&#8217;s price. The last time this signal formed was back in April 2022, before the market observed the LUNA and 3AC collapses. The bullish signal was last seen in July 2022, as the crypto built up towards its first relief rally of the bear market. Since then, however, there have been no other breaches of either of these levels, as is apparent from the chart. Related Reading: Litecoin Surges 7% In Strong 2023 Start, Jumps To 12th On Market Cap List In the period between then and now, the taker buy/sell ratio has been oscillating around 1, but the metric has just not been able to summon enough momentum to go all the way in either direction. &#8220;We cannot anticipate Bitcoin to move much as long as confidence &#8211; and subsequently demand &#8211; does not return to the market,&#8221; explains the analyst. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $16,700, down 1% in the last week. Looks like the value of the crypto has observed a small surge in the last 24 hours &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows the Bitcoin taker buy/sell ratio has been unable to give any real signal recently as the demand has remained low in the market.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Taker Buy/Sell Ratio Hasn&#8217;t Been Able To Catch Any Momentum Recently</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/quicktake/63b1f418c8ccf515a9ac5170-The-market-is-waiting-for-an-increase-in-demand" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, the taker buy/sell ratio hasn&#8217;t moved much above or below 1 since August 2022. The &#8220;<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-taker-buy-sell-ratio-highest-636-days/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin taker buy/sell ratio</a>&#8221; is an indicator that measures the ratio between the taker buy volume and the taker sell volume.</p>
<p>When the value of this metric is greater than one, it means the buy or the &#8220;long&#8221; volume is higher in the market right now. Basically, this means that there are more buyers willing to purchase BTC at a higher price currently, and thus the buying pressure is stronger.</p>
<p>On the other hand, values of the indicator under the threshold suggest the taker sell volume is more dominant at the moment. Such values imply a bearish sentiment is shared by the majority of the investors currently.</p>
<p>Naturally, the ratio being exactly equal to one indicates the taker buy and taker sell volumes are exactly equal right now, and therefore the market is evenly split between bullish and bearish mentalities.</p>

<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the 14-day simple moving average (SMA) Bitcoin taker buy/sell ratio over the last few years:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/333235/quicktake/CqJsyvA_195ca6e76417bbcae6c8f0973abb7dea0c4436c54d7875e46ccfe918e2495d32.png" alt="Bitcoin Taker Buy/Sell Ratio" width="1280" height="806" /></p>

<p>As you can see in the above graph, the quant has marked the relevant points of the trend for the 14-day SMA Bitcoin taker buy/sell ratio. It looks like whenever the indicator has crossed the 1.03 level, BTC has observed some bullish momentum shortly after.</p>
<p>On the contrary, whenever the ratio dipped below the 0.97 level, a bearish trend followed the crypto&#8217;s price. The last time this signal formed was back in April 2022, before the market observed the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-on-chain-activity-throttled-after-luna-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">LUNA</a> and <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/crypto-hedge-fund-3-arrows-capital-3ac-files-for-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">3AC</a> collapses.</p>
<p>The bullish signal was last seen in July 2022, as the crypto built up towards its first relief rally of the bear market. Since then, however, there have been no other breaches of either of these levels, as is apparent from the chart.</p>

<p>In the period between then and now, the taker buy/sell ratio has been oscillating around 1, but the metric has just not been able to summon enough momentum to go all the way in either direction. &#8220;We cannot anticipate Bitcoin to move much as long as confidence &#8211; and subsequently demand &#8211; does not return to the market,&#8221; explains the analyst.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $16,700, down 1% in the last week.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-514432 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-1-460x256.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="460" height="256" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-1-460x256.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-1-860x479.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-1-768x428.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-1-750x418.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-1.png 974w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/kanchanara-Lta5b8mPytw-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin Surges 7% In Strong 2023 Start, Jumps To 12th On Market Cap List</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/litecoin-surges-7-2023-12th-market-cap/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 13:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin bullish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin Market Cap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc/usd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514391</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Litecoin has kicked off 2023 to a bright start as the crypto has surged 7% in the last 24 hours and has climbed to 12th on the market cap list. Litecoin Starts 2023 On A Positive Note 2022 was a terrible year for the entire cryptocurrency sector as the long bear market resulted in losses of more than 50% for most of the coins. Litecoin was no exception; the asset ended the year with a drawdown of about 53%. This year, however, may very well turn out to be different for LTC as the coin seems to have observed a strong start so far. At the time of writing, Litecoin is trading around $75, up 7% in the last 24 hours. The below chart displays the recent trend in the crypto&#8217;s price. Looks like the value of the crypto has shot up during the past day &#124; Source: LTCUSD on TradingView The reason why this year could be better for LTC investors is that the next halving is set to take place this year. A &#8220;halving&#8221; is a periodic event where the block rewards of miners are permanently cut in half, meaning that the supply production of the coin itself is halved. Related Reading: Most Public Crypto Firms Underperformed Bitcoin In 2022, Miners Hit Worst Since supply being constrained like this makes the asset scarcer, such an event can have a bullish effect on the price. Therefore, Litecoin holders have been hoping that a rally would build up soon, ahead of the halving scheduled for this August. As the graph shows, Litecoin has certainly already made a great start to the year, observing sharper upwards momentum than any other top coin. Though, currently, it&#8217;s unclear whether this would be the push that leads the coin to a proper halving rally, or if it&#8217;s another temporary rise before the real rally starts. Despite LTC&#8217;s poor performance during 2022, there were still some positive takeaways for the coin. For example, the network processed over 39 million transactions in the year, a new record. The Litecoin Network completed over 39 million transactions in 2022. A new record! ⚡$LTC⚡ pic.twitter.com/DXbnuur2tI &#8212; Litecoin (@litecoin) December 31, 2022 Also, the chain added 52 million new addresses in 2022, the second highest out of all the cryptocurrencies. Litecoin added 52 million new addresses to the network in 2022. The second most of any crypto. #YearInReview pic.twitter.com/p5jAr9wZI0 &#8212; Litecoin (@litecoin) December 30, 2022 These achievements show that Litecoin is still very popular among users who want a reliable network for making cheap transactions, and continues to see more adoption. Related Reading: Ethereum Finishes 2022 With ATH Correlation To Bitcoin, Despite The Merge LTC Is Now The 12th Largest Crypto In The Sector The recent amazing growth in Litecoin has meant that its standing on the top crypto by market cap list has improved. Here is a table that shows where LTC ranks among its peers now: Shiba Inu (SHIB) seems to be 15th at the moment &#124; Source: CoinMarketCap As shown above, Litecoin has now overtaken Polkadot (DOT) to become the 12th largest coin in the market. Also, LTC&#8217;s cap is currently quite close to Dai (DAI), which means that with some more growth, the crypto can easily take the 11th spot from the stablecoin as well. Featured image from Michael Förtsch on Unsplash.com, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin has kicked off 2023 to a bright start as the crypto has surged 7% in the last 24 hours and has climbed to 12th on the market cap list.</p>
<h2>Litecoin Starts 2023 On A Positive Note</h2>
<p>2022 was a terrible year for the entire cryptocurrency sector as the long bear market resulted in losses of more than 50% for most of the coins. Litecoin was no exception; the asset ended the year with a drawdown of about 53%.</p>
<p>This year, however, may very well turn out to be different for LTC as the coin seems to have observed a strong start so far. At the time of writing, Litecoin is trading around $75, up 7% in the last 24 hours. The below chart displays the recent trend in the crypto&#8217;s price.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-514392 size-large aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-860x479.png" alt="Litecoin Price CHart" width="860" height="479" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-860x479.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-460x256.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-768x428.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-750x418.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart.png 973w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>

<p>The reason why this year could be better for LTC investors is that the next halving is set to take place this year. A &#8220;<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/is-the-bitcoin-halving-the-key-for-a-btc-price-bottom/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">halving</a>&#8221; is a periodic event where the block rewards of miners are permanently cut in half, meaning that the supply production of the coin itself is halved.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://newsbtc.com/crypto/crypto-firms-bitcoin-2022-miners-hit-worst/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Most Public Crypto Firms Underperformed Bitcoin In 2022, Miners Hit Worst</a></p>
<p>Since supply being constrained like this makes the asset scarcer, such an event can have a bullish effect on the price. Therefore, Litecoin holders have been hoping that a rally would build up soon, ahead of the halving scheduled for this August.</p>
<p>As the graph shows, Litecoin has certainly already made a great start to the year, observing sharper upwards momentum than any other top coin. Though, currently, it&#8217;s unclear whether this would be the push that leads the coin to a proper halving rally, or if it&#8217;s another temporary rise before the real rally starts.</p>
<p>Despite LTC&#8217;s poor performance during 2022, there were still some positive takeaways for the coin. For example, the network processed over 39 million transactions in the year, a new record.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The Litecoin Network completed over 39 million transactions in 2022. A new record!</p>
<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/26a1.png" alt="⚡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />$LTC<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/26a1.png" alt="⚡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/DXbnuur2tI" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/DXbnuur2tI</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Litecoin (@litecoin) <a href="https://twitter.com/litecoin/status/1609238092145393665?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">December 31, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>Also, the chain added 52 million <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/tron-adds-1-75-million-new-addresses-in-last-7-days-as-trx-regains-previous-losses/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">new addresses</a> in 2022, the second highest out of all the cryptocurrencies.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Litecoin added 52 million new addresses to the network in 2022.</p>
<p>The second most of any crypto. <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/YearInReview?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#YearInReview</a> <a href="https://t.co/p5jAr9wZI0" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/p5jAr9wZI0</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Litecoin (@litecoin) <a href="https://twitter.com/litecoin/status/1608869100058738689?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">December 30, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>These achievements show that Litecoin is still very popular among users who want a reliable network for making cheap transactions, and continues to see more adoption.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-ath-correlation-bitcoin-merge/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum Finishes 2022 With ATH Correlation To Bitcoin, Despite The Merge</a></p>
<h2>LTC Is Now The 12th Largest Crypto In The Sector</h2>
<p>The recent amazing growth in Litecoin has meant that its standing on the top crypto by market cap list has improved. Here is a table that shows where LTC ranks among its peers now:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-514402 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/table-460x320.png" alt="Litecoin Market Cap" width="460" height="320" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/table-460x320.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/table.png 738w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p>As shown above, Litecoin has now overtaken <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/is-polkadot-a-must-have/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Polkadot</a> (DOT) to become the 12th largest coin in the market. Also, LTC&#8217;s cap is currently quite close to Dai (DAI), which means that with some more growth, the crypto can easily take the 11th spot from the stablecoin as well.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/michael-fortsch-fYSVVQqiqPs-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
