<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 09:28:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>BNB Chain Inks New Record With Soaring User Activity &#8211; A Boost For Price?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bnb-chain-enjoys-soaring-user-activity/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 09:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnb chain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542782</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[BNB Chain, the blockchain platform powering the Binance ecosystem, has recently emerged as a formidable force in the crypto world, surpassing its competitors in terms of daily active users. This surge in user engagement has coincided with a surge in the value of the BNB token, which has experienced a steady increase of over 5% within a single week.  As BNB&#8217;s daily active users continue to soar, one can&#8217;t help but question the overall impact of this unprecedented growth. What lies behind BNB&#8217;s ability to outshine its rivals and attract a growing user base? Is there a hidden catalyst propelling its value upwards?  Moreover, as these metrics diverge from the norm, skeptics begin to raise valid concerns about the sustainability and potential risks associated with BNB&#8217;s rise. BNB Chain Surpasses BTC, ETH In Daily Active Users In the ever-evolving landscape of blockchain technology, BNB Chain has recently achieved a significant milestone, surpassing renowned chains such as Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) in terms of daily user activity. According to a BNB analysis, the chain secured the second position, solidifying its position as a formidable player in the crypto world. Related Reading: Cardano Development Activity Dropping – What Does It Mean For ADA Price? Token Terminal&#8217;s data also revealed that BNB Chain boasts an impressive count of over 1 million daily active users, a testament to the platform&#8217;s growing popularity and appeal. This notable achievement is even more remarkable considering the longstanding dominance of Bitcoin and Ethereum, which have traditionally held the top positions in the cryptocurrency market. Source: Token Terminal The BNB token has also made waves in the market. Currently priced at $248.78, it experienced a slight setback with a 3.5% slump in the past 24 hours. However, the token quickly bounced back with a decent 5.4% increase in the last week. Source: CoinMarketCap Mixed Signals While the BNB Chain has garnered widespread enthusiasm and positioned itself as a competitive player in the crypto market, recent data from Santiment reveals a nuanced picture. Despite the chain&#8217;s impressive user base, as measured by daily active addresses, the level of excitement appears to be relatively consistent without any notable spikes, according to Santiment&#8217;s analysis. &#160; Source: Santiment Related Reading: Optimism (OP) Rides The Wave Of Today’s Crypto Surge With 15% Rally When examining the Total Value Locked (TVL) metric, which indicates the amount of assets held within a blockchain protocol, BNB Chain falls behind Ethereum and Tron, occupying the third position. As of the latest data, the TVL for BNB Chain stands at approximately $3.4 billion, highlighting room for growth in this area. Total cryptocurrencies market cap at $1.18 trillion. Chart: TradingView.com Similarly, the stablecoin market cap on the BNB Chain has exceeded $5 billion. However, Santiment&#8217;s charts indicate that both the TVL and market cap metrics have yet to exhibit a significant upward trend, despite the chain&#8217;s growing user base. This suggests that while BNB Chain boasts a higher number of active users, the overall TVL and market cap have not fully reflected this growth. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Gadgets 360]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BNB Chain, the blockchain platform powering the Binance ecosystem, has recently emerged as a formidable force in the crypto world, surpassing its competitors in terms of daily active users. This surge in user engagement has coincided with a surge in the value of the BNB token, which has experienced a steady increase of over 5% within a single week. </p>
<p>As BNB&#8217;s daily active users continue to soar, one can&#8217;t help but question the overall impact of this unprecedented growth. What lies behind BNB&#8217;s ability to outshine its rivals and attract a growing user base? Is there a hidden catalyst propelling its value upwards? </p>
<p>Moreover, as these metrics diverge from the norm, skeptics begin to raise valid concerns about the sustainability and potential risks associated with BNB&#8217;s rise.</p>
<h2><strong>BNB Chain Surpasses BTC, ETH In Daily Active Users</strong></h2>
<p>In the ever-evolving landscape of blockchain technology, BNB Chain has recently achieved a significant milestone, surpassing renowned chains such as Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) in terms of daily user activity. According to a <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/bnb-chain-impresses-in-daily-active-users-but/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BNB analysis</a>, the chain secured the second position, solidifying its position as a formidable player in the crypto world.</p>

<p><a href="https://twitter.com/tokenterminal/status/1679517145053425669" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Token Terminal&#8217;s data</a> also revealed that BNB Chain boasts an impressive count of over 1 million daily active users, a testament to the platform&#8217;s growing popularity and appeal. This notable achievement is even more remarkable considering the longstanding dominance of Bitcoin and Ethereum, which have traditionally held the top positions in the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-542811 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-91-860x646.png" alt="" width="860" height="646" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-91-860x646.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-91-460x346.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-91-768x577.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-91-750x563.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-91-1140x856.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-91.png 1194w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>The <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bnb/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BNB token</a> has also made waves in the market. Currently priced at $248.78, it experienced a slight setback with a 3.5% slump in the past 24 hours. However, the token quickly bounced back with a decent 5.4% increase in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-542808" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-90.png" alt="" width="941" height="70" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-90.png 941w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-90-460x34.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-90-860x64.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-90-768x57.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-90-750x56.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 941px) 100vw, 941px"/></p>

<h2><strong>Mixed Signals</strong></h2>
<p>While the BNB Chain has garnered widespread enthusiasm and positioned itself as a competitive player in the crypto market, recent data from Santiment reveals a nuanced picture. Despite the chain&#8217;s impressive user base, as measured by daily active addresses, the level of excitement appears to be relatively consistent without any notable spikes, according to <a href="https://embed.santiment.net/chart?ps=binance-coin&amp;pt=BNB&amp;df=2023-03-04T00%3A00%3A00.000Z&amp;emcg=1&amp;wm=daily_active_addresses%3Bprice_usd&amp;wax=0%3B1&amp;wc=%23FFAD4D%3B%2326C953&amp;ws=%3B%7B%22interval%22%3A%221d%22%7D" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Santiment&#8217;s analysis</a>.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-542814 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-93-860x294.png" alt="" width="860" height="294" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-93-860x294.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-93-460x157.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-93-768x262.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-93-1536x524.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-93-750x256.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-93-1140x389.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-93.png 1541w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>


<p>When examining the Total Value Locked (TVL) metric, which indicates the amount of assets held within a blockchain protocol, BNB Chain falls behind Ethereum and Tron, occupying the third position. As of the latest data, the TVL for BNB Chain stands at approximately $3.4 billion, highlighting room for growth in this area.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/PQnzVqrp/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>

<p>Similarly, the stablecoin market cap on the BNB Chain has exceeded $5 billion. However, Santiment&#8217;s charts indicate that both the TVL and market cap metrics have yet to exhibit a significant upward trend, despite the chain&#8217;s growing user base. This suggests that while BNB Chain boasts a higher number of active users, the overall TVL and market cap have not fully reflected this growth.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Gadgets 360</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-94-460x212.png" width="460" height="212" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Explodes With 1,300% Surge In Trading Volume As crypto Exchanges Jump On Board</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-explodes-with-1300-surge-in-trading-volume-as-crypto-exchanges-jump-on-board/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 21:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542775</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a long-awaited decision, Judge Torres ruled in favor of XRP in their case against the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) yesterday. The verdict is a positive development for the cryptocurrency industry, particularly with a focus on whether digital assets should be deemed securities in the US. The ruling is expected to set a precedent for the industry moving forward. It is positive for both altcoins and the wider industry, as the default expectation is that these assets are not deemed securities so long as they are made available to the public.  This event will likely have wider implications for ongoing legal cases and may help rebuild confidence in the industry for developers and attract more liquidity to the ecosystem. XRP Defies Expectations With Massive Price Surge And Trading Volume Spike Following the news, XRP saw a surge in price, reaching as high as $0.93, the highest price since May 2021, and closing at $0.82.  According to data compiled by the research company CCData, the news led to an influx of trading activity, with XRP trading pairs on centralized exchanges (CEX) recording a total volume of $6.05 billion on the day, an increase of 1351% from the previous day. Related Reading: Crypto Liquidations Cross $300 Million Amid Massive Market Recovery The relisting of the asset on other centralized exchanges, including Coinbase, Kraken, and Gemini has also contributed to the spike in volumes.  The news surrounding the ruling also led to almost 100% daily gains for XRP, with other tokens such as Solana (SOL) and Cardano (ADA), recently deemed securities, seeing significant gains of 35% and 28%, respectively. Despite the negative backdrop that XRP has faced due to the lawsuit, its market depth liquidity at the 1% level has remained resilient year-to-date (YTD). XRP’s 1% bid/ask side depth at Yearly Open was 26.5 million XRP, which saw a variance of 0.41% throughout the year and remained strong at 25.1 million XRP on the 12th of July. Derivatives Data Shows Positive Sentiment According to the report, Derivatives data indicate that XRP&#8217;s positive funding rate remained steady over the past few days, in line with the wider positive market sentiment.  The lawsuit news generated a significant rise in speculative interest on the bid side, with a $280 million increase in Open Interest, from $635 million to a high of $913 million across exchanges. Moreover, funding rates reached over 0.03% across exchanges, over three times higher than its baseline level of under 0.01% before the announcement. On the other hand, the funding rate history of XRP shows that speculators trading perpetual contracts have been favoring the upside, with minimal time spent this year in negative funding rate territory.  This underscores the positive sentiment of traders for XRP, which was recently rewarded with a large price rise due to the announcement. While it remains to be seen whether XRP will maintain its extremely positive funding rate, it is currently a good standard for gauging positive sentiment within altcoins, given the attention and volume it is generating. Considering the lawsuit&#8217;s success, the implications for the market are overwhelmingly positive, and the ruling provides clarity that did not exist before the judgment.  Related Reading: Here’s What On-Chain Data Reveals About XRP Rally According to CCData, the market could see a few trends emerge, such as coins deemed securities recovering well and potentially outperforming and the potential for Bitcoin dominance to drop as an overall percent of market cap, given renewed optimism in altcoins. Despite the recent surge in positive sentiment and renewed investor confidence, XRP has experienced a significant price drop. After coming close to reaching the $1 mark, which it has not seen since November 2021, XRP is currently trading at $0.7002, marking a decrease of over 11% in the last 24 hours. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a long-awaited decision, Judge Torres ruled in favor of XRP in their case against the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) yesterday. The verdict is a positive development for the cryptocurrency industry, particularly with a focus on whether digital assets should be deemed securities in the US.</p>
<p>The ruling is expected to set a precedent for the industry moving forward. It is positive for both altcoins and the wider industry, as the default expectation is that these assets are not deemed securities so long as they are made available to the public. </p>
<p>This event will likely have wider implications for ongoing legal cases and may help rebuild confidence in the industry for developers and attract more liquidity to the ecosystem.</p>
<h2>XRP Defies Expectations With Massive Price Surge And Trading Volume Spike</h2>
<p>Following the news, XRP saw a surge in price, reaching as high as $0.93, the highest price since May 2021, and closing at $0.82. </p>
<p><a href="https://blog.ccdata.io/analysing-xrp-following-judge-torres-ruling-682bd8f345af" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to data compiled by the research company CCData, the news led to an influx of trading activity, with XRP trading pairs on centralized exchanges (CEX) recording a total volume of $6.05 billion on the day, an increase of 1351% from the previous day.</p>

<p>The <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/crypto-giant-coinbase-reverses-course-relists-xrp-after-landmark-ruling/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">relisting of the asset</a> on other centralized exchanges, including Coinbase, Kraken, and Gemini has also contributed to the spike in volumes. </p>
<p>The news surrounding the ruling also led to almost 100% daily gains for XRP, with other tokens such as Solana (SOL) and Cardano (ADA), recently deemed securities, seeing significant gains of 35% and 28%, respectively.</p>
<p>Despite the negative backdrop that XRP has faced due to the lawsuit, its market depth liquidity at the 1% level has remained resilient year-to-date (YTD). XRP’s 1% bid/ask side depth at Yearly Open was 26.5 million XRP, which saw a variance of 0.41% throughout the year and remained strong at 25.1 million XRP on the 12th of July.</p>
Derivatives Data Shows Positive Sentiment
<p>According to the report, Derivatives data indicate that XRP&#8217;s positive funding rate remained steady over the past few days, in line with the wider positive market sentiment. </p>
<p>The lawsuit news generated a significant rise in speculative interest on the bid side, with a $280 million increase in Open Interest, from $635 million to a high of $913 million across exchanges. Moreover, funding rates reached over 0.03% across exchanges, over three times higher than its baseline level of under 0.01% before the announcement.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the funding rate history of XRP shows that speculators trading perpetual contracts have been favoring the upside, with minimal time spent this year in negative funding rate territory. </p>
<p>This underscores the positive sentiment of traders for XRP, which was recently rewarded with a large price rise due to the announcement. While it remains to be seen whether XRP will maintain its extremely positive funding rate, it is currently a good standard for gauging positive sentiment within altcoins, given the attention and volume it is generating.</p>
<p>Considering the lawsuit&#8217;s success, the implications for the market are overwhelmingly positive, and the ruling provides clarity that did not exist before the judgment. </p>

<p>According to CCData, the market could see a few trends emerge, such as coins deemed securities recovering well and potentially outperforming and the potential for Bitcoin dominance to drop as an overall percent of market cap, given renewed optimism in altcoins.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/mJAK60uV/" alt="XRP" width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>Despite the recent surge in positive sentiment and renewed investor confidence, XRP has experienced a significant price drop. After coming close to reaching the $1 mark, which it has not seen since November 2021, XRP is currently trading at $0.7002, marking a decrease of over 11% in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1349331161-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Large Exchanges Relist XRP Following Ripple Victory Over SEC</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/large-exchanges-relist-xrp/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 19:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitstamp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto exchanges]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP exchange listings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542755</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a significant turn of events, large cryptocurrency exchanges Coinbase, Kraken, Bitstamp, and Gemini announced their decision to relist XRP after a significant legal victory for Ripple against the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). This momentous decision comes as a result of the exchanges reevaluating their previous delisting of XRP, showcasing a renewed confidence in the token&#8217;s regulatory standing.  This was brought about by the recent landmark court ruling by Judge Analisa Torres. Coinbase, Kraken, And Bitstamp Reinstate XRP Trading Coinbase, a leading cryptocurrency exchange, wasted no time in announcing the resumption of XRP trading following the court ruling. Brian Armstrong, the CEO of Coinbase, expressed the exchange&#8217;s decision in a tweet, stating: “Coinbase will re-enable trading for XRP (XRP) on the XRP network. Do not send this asset over other networks or your funds may be lost. Transfers for this asset remain available on @Coinbase &#38;  @CoinbaseExch.“ Related Reading: Ripple Eyes Tokenized Assets Sector As It Expects Market Cap To Reach $30 Trillion The reinstatement of the digital asset on Coinbase&#8217;s platform marks a significant shift in their position after delisting the token in January 2021. Kraken, another prominent exchange, also confirmed its plans to reinstate trading for the cryptocurrency, as Marco Santori, Kraken’ Legal Officer tweeted stated: “1/ This morning, the Federal Court for the Southern District of New York ruled that XRP is not a security. As such, just a few minutes ago, Kraken re-enabled trading in XRP for US users.”  Bitstamp, an early adopter of XRP, joined the bandwagon, emphasizing its role as a leading liquidity venue for the asset globally as it confirms the return of the token on its exchange for US users.  Token holding majority of gains from Thursday &#124; Source: XRPUSD on TradingView.com Ripple&#8217;s Legal Battle And Market Impact The court ruling stems from the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Ripple, which accused the company of conducting an unregistered securities offering through the sale and distribution of XRP. Ripple chose to fight the lawsuit, investing substantial resources into the legal proceedings. The outcome of this case carries significant weight for the cryptocurrency industry, as it determines the regulatory oversight faced by digital asset firms. Although Judge Torres&#8217; recent summary judgment concluded that while Ripple&#8217;s initial sale of XRP to institutional investors could be classified as a securities offering, the subsequent trading of the tokens on crypto exchanges did not fall under the same classification.  Related Reading: Fund Manager Vanguard Increases Stake In Bitcoin Mining Stocks To $600 Million This ruling provides a level of clarity regarding the regulatory status of the token and sets a precedent for similar cases involving other cryptocurrencies. The market responded with enthusiasm to the court ruling as XRP experienced a surge in value, rising by over 75% compared to its price at the beginning of Thursday. Coinbase&#8217;s share prices also witnessed a significant jump of more than 24% following the ruling. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a significant turn of events, large cryptocurrency exchanges Coinbase, Kraken, Bitstamp, and Gemini announced their decision to relist XRP after a significant legal victory for Ripple against the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<p>This momentous decision comes as a result of the exchanges reevaluating their previous delisting of XRP, showcasing a renewed confidence in the token&#8217;s regulatory standing.  This was brought about by the recent landmark court ruling by Judge Analisa Torres.</p>
<h2>Coinbase, Kraken, And Bitstamp Reinstate XRP Trading</h2>
<p>Coinbase, a leading cryptocurrency exchange, wasted no time in announcing the resumption of XRP trading following the court ruling. Brian Armstrong, the CEO of Coinbase, expressed the exchange&#8217;s decision in a <a href="https://twitter.com/CoinbaseAssets/status/1679575239657758721" rel="nofollow">tweet</a>, stating:</p>
<p>“Coinbase will re-enable trading for XRP (XRP) on the XRP network. Do not send this asset over other networks or your funds may be lost. Transfers for this asset remain available on @Coinbase &amp;  @CoinbaseExch.“</p>

<p>The reinstatement of the digital asset on Coinbase&#8217;s platform marks a significant shift in their position after delisting the token in January 2021. Kraken, another prominent exchange, also confirmed its plans to reinstate trading for the cryptocurrency, as Marco Santori, Kraken’ Legal Officer <a href="https://twitter.com/msantoriESQ/status/1679590081072594952" rel="nofollow">tweeted</a> stated:</p>
<p>“1/ This morning, the Federal Court for the Southern District of New York ruled that XRP is not a security. As such, just a few minutes ago, Kraken re-enabled trading in XRP for US users.” </p>
<p>Bitstamp, an early adopter of XRP, joined the bandwagon, emphasizing its role as a leading liquidity venue for the asset globally as it confirms the <a href="https://blog.bitstamp.net/post/xrp-is-back-in-the-us-start-trading-today/" rel="nofollow">return </a>of the token on its exchange for US users. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/T8EebvN5/" alt="Ripple (XRP) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>

<h2>Ripple&#8217;s Legal Battle And Market Impact</h2>
<p>The court ruling stems from the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Ripple, which accused the company of conducting an unregistered securities offering through the sale and distribution of XRP.</p>
<p>Ripple chose to fight the lawsuit, investing substantial resources into the legal proceedings. The outcome of this case carries significant weight for the cryptocurrency industry, as it determines the regulatory oversight faced by digital asset firms.</p>
<p>Although Judge Torres&#8217; recent summary judgment concluded that while Ripple&#8217;s initial sale of XRP to institutional investors could be classified as a securities offering, the subsequent trading of the tokens on crypto exchanges did not fall under the same classification. </p>

<p>This ruling provides a level of clarity regarding the regulatory status of the token and sets a precedent for similar cases involving other cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>The market responded with enthusiasm to the court ruling as XRP experienced a surge in value, rising by over 75% compared to its price at the beginning of Thursday. Coinbase&#8217;s share prices also witnessed a significant jump of more than 24% following the ruling.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1436037805-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>PEPE Sees Sharp 17% Surge, But Will This Whale Spoil The Party?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/pepe-sees-sharp-17-surge-but-whale-spoil-party/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 18:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE Rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE Whale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pepeusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542728</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows a PEPE whale has made a large deposit to Binance, something that could provide an impedance to the meme coin&#8217;s rally. PEPE Whale Has Deposited $7.2 Million To Binance According to data from the cryptocurrency transaction tracker service Whale Alert, a massive PEPE transfer has occurred on the Ethereum blockchain during the past day. The transaction in question involved the movement of 3.94 trillion PEPE, which was worth almost $7.2 million at the time the transfer went through on the network. Generally, only the whale entities are capable of making such large moves, so it&#8217;s reasonable to assume that a whale investor would have been behind this transfer. Due to the massive amount of capital involved in transactions of these humongous investors, they can sometimes cause noticeable fluctuations in the price of the asset. As such, the movements of the whales can be something to watch out for. How such transfers may affect the market, though, depends on the exact intent the investor had behind it. Related Reading: Perfect Storm: Why Bitcoin &#38; Crypto Are Poised For A Dramatic Recovery Here are some additional details regarding the relevant PEPE whale transfer, which may shed some light on what the whale wanted to achieve with the move: Looks like this large transfer on the Ethereum blockchain only cost a fee of about $2.5 to go through &#124; Source: Whale Alert As you can see above, the sending address in the case of this PEPE transfer is an unknown wallet, meaning that it&#8217;s an address unattached to any known centralized platform, making it likely that it&#8217;s the personal wallet of an investor. The receiving address, on the other hand, looks to be a wallet affiliated with a centralized platform. More specifically, this address is connected to the cryptocurrency exchange Binance. Transfers like these, where coins move from self-custodial wallets to exchanges are called &#8220;exchange inflows.&#8221; As one of the main reasons why investors may deposit their coins to these platforms is for selling-related purposes, exchange inflows can provide hints about the selling pressure in the market. In the current case, as the whale has made a rather large inflow to these platforms, it&#8217;s possible that the price of the meme coin may suffer bearish consequences from it. Naturally, this would only be so if the PEPE whale in question truly made these deposits with selling in mind, and not for using any of the other services the Binance platform offers. Though, considering that the exchange inflow has occurred following a rapid 17% rise in the meme coin&#8217;s value, there is probably a fair chance that the whale is indeed looking to sell and take advantage of this profitable exit opportunity. Related Reading: XRP Price Retreats After Massive 80% Rally, Buy The Dips? So far, however, the PEPE price has only moved mostly sideways since the whale made the transfer, implying that, if the whale indeed sold the coins, the market currently has enough buying pressure that the selling has simply been absorbed. Another possibility, though, may be that the whale has only made the deposit in advance and is yet to actually the pull trigger on selling the stack, perhaps to see if the price goes up further. Naturally, if this is the case, the price would feel a bearish effect from this later down the line. PEPE Price At the time of writing, PEPE is trading around $0.000001736, up 11% in the last week. PEPE has shot up during the past day &#124; Source: PEPEUSD on TradingView Featured image from iStock.com, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows a PEPE whale has made a large deposit to Binance, something that could provide an impedance to the meme coin&#8217;s rally.</p>
<h2>PEPE Whale Has Deposited $7.2 Million To Binance</h2>
<p>According to data from the cryptocurrency transaction tracker service <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1679674107145625601" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Whale Alert</a>, a massive PEPE transfer has occurred on the Ethereum blockchain during the past day.</p>
<p>The transaction in question involved the movement of 3.94 trillion PEPE, which was worth almost $7.2 million at the time the transfer went through on the network.</p>
<p>Generally, only the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-whale-10-total-shib-supply-shocks-market/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">whale</a> entities are capable of making such large moves, so it&#8217;s reasonable to assume that a whale investor would have been behind this transfer.</p>
<p>Due to the massive amount of capital involved in transactions of these humongous investors, they can sometimes cause noticeable fluctuations in the price of the asset.</p>
<p>As such, the movements of the whales can be something to watch out for. How such transfers may affect the market, though, depends on the exact intent the investor had behind it.</p>

<p>Here are some additional details regarding the relevant PEPE whale transfer, which may shed some light on what the whale wanted to achieve with the move:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-542733 size-large aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/details-860x445.png" alt="PEPE Whale" width="860" height="445" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/details-860x445.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/details-460x238.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/details-768x398.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/details-750x388.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/details-1140x590.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/details.png 1170w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>As you can see above, the sending address in the case of this PEPE transfer is an unknown wallet, meaning that it&#8217;s an address unattached to any known centralized platform, making it likely that it&#8217;s the personal wallet of an investor.</p>
<p>The receiving address, on the other hand, looks to be a wallet affiliated with a centralized platform. More specifically, this address is connected to the cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/nft/cristiano-ronaldo-goes-crypto-again-drops-second-nft-collection-on-binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Binance</a>.</p>
<p>Transfers like these, where coins move from self-custodial wallets to exchanges are called &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-short-term-holders-exchange-inflows-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">exchange inflows</a>.&#8221; As one of the main reasons why investors may deposit their coins to these platforms is for selling-related purposes, exchange inflows can provide hints about the selling pressure in the market.</p>
<p>In the current case, as the whale has made a rather large inflow to these platforms, it&#8217;s possible that the price of the meme coin may suffer bearish consequences from it.</p>
<p>Naturally, this would only be so if the PEPE whale in question truly made these deposits with selling in mind, and not for using any of the other services the Binance platform offers.</p>
<p>Though, considering that the exchange inflow has occurred following a rapid 17% rise in the meme coin&#8217;s value, there is probably a fair chance that the whale is indeed looking to sell and take advantage of this profitable exit opportunity.</p>

<p>So far, however, the PEPE price has only moved mostly sideways since the whale made the transfer, implying that, if the whale indeed sold the coins, the market currently has enough buying pressure that the selling has simply been absorbed.</p>
<p>Another possibility, though, may be that the whale has only made the deposit in advance and is yet to actually the pull trigger on selling the stack, perhaps to see if the price goes up further. Naturally, if this is the case, the price would feel a bearish effect from this later down the line.</p>
<h2>PEPE Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, PEPE is trading around $0.000001736, up 11% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Xf9TL9oY/" alt="PEPE Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1429119108-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here&#8217;s What On-Chain Data Reveals About XRP Rally</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ripple/heres-what-on-chain-data-reveals-about-xrp-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 16:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP On-Chain Data]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542683</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[XRP has observed a massive 67% rally during the past 24 hours. Here are some facts on-chain data reveals about this price surge. Several Indicators Have Surged Following The XRP Rally In its latest insight post, the on-chain analytics firm Santiment has looked into the underlying metrics related to XRP as the cryptocurrency has seen an extremely sharp surge during the last day. This rapid growth in the asset&#8217;s value has come following Ripple&#8217;s victory in court as XRP has been declared &#8220;not a security.&#8221; Immediately after the announcement, the coin had managed to rise by around 90%, but in the hours since then, the asset has taken some hit. Nonetheless, the cryptocurrency has still managed to hold onto the majority of its gains so far, as it&#8217;s still up 67%. This rise has now made the asset the fourth largest in the space in terms of market cap, as it has leapfrogged past BNB. Following the rally, the &#8220;social dominance&#8221; of XRP saw a sharp surge toward the 7.4% mark, as the below chart displays. Looks like the metric's value has spiked &#124; Source: Santiment Social dominance measures how the discussions on social media related to any given coin (which, in this case, is XRP) compare against the combined amount of talk the top 100 assets by market cap are receiving currently. At the current value of the metric, 7.4% of all discussions related to these top 100 coins are coming from XRP alone. Such a high amount of interest among social media users is generally a sign of euphoria, which usually leads to a correction in the price. This may explain why the asset has taken a hit since the initial jump. Related Reading: Bitcoin MVRV At Critical Level: Will A Break Happen? In terms of whale activity, the network has naturally been active during this surge, as these humongous investors have made a large number of transactions, as shown below. The value of the metric seems to have been quite high recently &#124; Source: Santiment The number of whale transfers has crossed the 637 mark during the past day, which is the highest level observed in 2023. &#8220;Clearly the pump is being fueled by these large transactions,&#8221; notes Santiment. The trading volume (the total amount of XRP being transacted on the chain) has also registered a steep increase, which isn&#8217;t too surprising considering the high amount of whale activity that has occurred during the past day. The volume has seen a spike &#124; Source: Santiment The current levels of the trading volume are the highest that they have been in around 10 months, further showcasing the extraordinary activity that the blockchain is observing right now. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Attempts To Follow XRP But This Resistance Is The Key The analytics firm has also pointed out how the sharks and whales of the cryptocurrency had been accumulating during the couple of months that have led to this rally. The sharks and whales have been constantly buying &#124; Source: Santiment &#8220;This group of wallets is essentially the one best to watch to understand how &#8216;smart money&#8217; is behaving,&#8221; explains Santiment. &#8220;And they had been showing confidence in the asset for over two months now, even prior to today&#8217;s court ruling.&#8221; XRP Price At the time of writing, XRP is trading around $0.78, up 69% in the last week. XRP's extraordinary rise during the past day &#124; Source: XRPUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Santiment.net]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>XRP has observed a massive 67% rally during the past 24 hours. Here are some facts on-chain data reveals about this price surge.</p>
<h2>Several Indicators Have Surged Following The XRP Rally</h2>
<p>In its latest insight post, the on-chain analytics firm <a href="https://insights.santiment.net/read/xrp-shocking-the-crypto-world-with-a-87-surge-over-the-span-of-3-hours-7340?fpr=twitter" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Santiment</a> has looked into the underlying metrics related to XRP as the cryptocurrency has seen an extremely sharp surge during the last day.</p>
<p>This rapid growth in the asset&#8217;s value has come following <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/ripples-legal-victory-boosts-xrp-price-could-reach-1-soon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ripple&#8217;s victory</a> in court as XRP has been declared &#8220;not a security.&#8221; Immediately after the announcement, the coin had managed to rise by around 90%, but in the hours since then, the asset has <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-price-retreats-rally-0-95/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">taken some hit</a>.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, the cryptocurrency has still managed to hold onto the majority of its gains so far, as it&#8217;s still up 67%. This rise has now made the asset the fourth largest in the space in terms of market cap, as it has leapfrogged past BNB.</p>
<p>Following the rally, the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/internet-computer-icp-social-dominance-hits-top-in/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">social dominance</a>&#8221; of XRP saw a sharp surge toward the 7.4% mark, as the below chart displays.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://production-sanbase-images.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/d0aa0a9e15da2f515f1559d2c49ae147d0bad25ebd6b11d15975713cdc9c76c4_1689276581762_Screenshot%202023-07-13%20122938.png" alt="XRP Social Dominance" width="3135" height="1668"/></p>

<p>Social dominance measures how the discussions on social media related to any given coin (which, in this case, is XRP) compare against the combined amount of talk the top 100 assets by market cap are receiving currently.</p>
<p>At the current value of the metric, 7.4% of all discussions related to these top 100 coins are coming from XRP alone. Such a high amount of interest among social media users is generally a sign of euphoria, which usually leads to a correction in the price. This may explain why the asset has taken a hit since the initial jump.</p>

<p>In terms of whale activity, the network has naturally been active during this surge, as these humongous investors have made a large number of transactions, as shown below.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://production-sanbase-images.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/aebcbae724e716848ba883714a75f92f229bf5b22be5952baa7cf76ff22269c7_1689276590190_Screenshot%202023-07-13%20122643.png" alt="XRP Whale Transaction Count" width="3118" height="1554"/></p>

<p>The number of whale transfers has crossed the 637 mark during the past day, which is the highest level observed in 2023. &#8220;Clearly the pump is being fueled by these large transactions,&#8221; notes Santiment.</p>
<p>The trading volume (the total amount of XRP being transacted on the chain) has also registered a steep increase, which isn&#8217;t too surprising considering the high amount of whale activity that has occurred during the past day.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter" src="https://production-sanbase-images.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/f36a41b34fa32b2abd12c7d40699820f8975110edb37ddcfb327adf0cb60f629_1689271169337_Screenshot%202023-07-13%20105552.png" loading="lazy"/></p>

<p>The current levels of the trading volume are the highest that they have been in around 10 months, further showcasing the extraordinary activity that the blockchain is observing right now.</p>

<p>The analytics firm has also pointed out how the sharks and whales of the cryptocurrency had been accumulating during the couple of months that have led to this rally.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://production-sanbase-images.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/ff36582f8215cc31ca938c2e0a8f002656de06dbc0ab40464853caabfde6ae07_1689276597582_Screenshot%202023-07-13%20122826.png" alt="Sharks &amp; Whales" width="3150" height="1669"/></p>

<p>&#8220;This group of wallets is essentially the one best to watch to understand how &#8216;smart money&#8217; is behaving,&#8221; explains Santiment. &#8220;And they had been showing confidence in the asset for over two months now, even prior to today&#8217;s court ruling.&#8221;</p>
<h2>XRP Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, XRP is trading around $0.78, up 69% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ho6lrwM8/" alt="Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/kanchanara-0kRsP5iRZI4-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Kicks Out BNB To Become 4th-Largest Crypto After 65% Rally</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-kicks-out-bnb-to-become-4th-largest-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542698</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[XRP, the token behind the Ripple payment network, has been on an absolute monster rally in the last day. The token has seen a 65% price surge that propelled it into the number 4 spot in the crypto rankings, pushing BNB down to 5th place, even though BNB on the other hand, is also up by 9% in the past week. XRP Overtakes BNB XRP recently overtook BNB after reaching a yearly high of $0.81, giving the cryptocurrency a market cap of $41 billion. The huge price spike can be attributed to investors jumping on the bandwagon with fear of missing out on XRP after the big news regarding its victory over the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).  Related Reading: Ripple Eyes Tokenized Assets Sector As It Expects Market Cap To Reach $30 Trillion The court determined on June 13 that the sale of XRP to regular investors does not constitute the sale of an unregistered security. As such, United States District Judge Analisa Torres ruled in partial favor of Ripple, saying that XRP sales on public cryptocurrency exchanges were not offers of securities under the law.  However, the judge remarked that Ripple&#8217;s direct sale of XRP to institutional investors in the amount of approximately $700 million violated federal legislation regarding the sale of securities. This catapulted XRP&#8217;s price from $0.478 to $0.7885 in just under a day. With its current market cap, this means XRP is now the third-largest native cryptocurrency behind Bitcoin and Ethereum when the USDT stablecoin is removed.  XRP price still holding gains &#124; Source: XRPUSD on Tradingview.com 24-Hour Trading Volume Spikes 1700%+ According to data from Coinmarketcap, XRP’s 24-hour trading volume has spiked a whopping 1,758.13% to over $13.49 billion. Trading volumes have surged on various exchanges, where Upbit, the South Korean-based crypto exchange, had over $2.7 billion in 24-hour trading volume. Binance also saw over $2.3 billion in trading volume as investors scurried to buy XRP.  Coinglass data shows more than $35 million short position trades on XRP have been liquidated in the past 24 hours. Most of these are from Bybit, OKX, and Binance, with $21 million, $14 million, and $14 million in short position liquidations, respectively. Of course, fast price rises often end in pullbacks as XRP remains a volatile digital asset. But its recent breakout shows it’s still an altcoin to watch, with the potential for even bigger gains if more investors continue to FOMO. However, XRP’s potential for long-term growth continues to be supported by Ripple Labs’ real-world value as a payments network. Related Reading: Fund Manager Vanguard Increases Stake In Bitcoin Mining Stocks To $600 Million At the time of writing, XRP is still trading at $0.797, which translates to 68% gains in the last day. It is currently the top gainer in the market with 70.66% and 56.79% gains in the last seven and 30 days, respectively. Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>XRP, the token behind the Ripple payment network, has been on an absolute monster rally in the last day. The token has seen a 65% price surge that propelled it into the number 4 spot in the crypto rankings, pushing BNB down to 5th place, even though BNB on the other hand, is also up by 9% in the past week.</p>
<h2>XRP Overtakes BNB</h2>
<p>XRP recently <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/xrp/" rel="nofollow">overtook</a> BNB after reaching a yearly high of $0.81, giving the cryptocurrency a market cap of $41 billion. The huge price spike can be attributed to investors jumping on the bandwagon with fear of missing out on XRP after the big news regarding its victory over the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). </p>

<p>The court determined on June 13 that the sale of XRP to regular investors does not constitute the sale of an unregistered security. As such, United States District Judge Analisa Torres ruled in partial favor of Ripple, saying that XRP sales on public cryptocurrency exchanges were not offers of securities under the law. </p>
<p>However, the judge <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-judge-deems-xrp-sale-non-investment-contract/" rel="nofollow">remarked</a> that Ripple&#8217;s direct sale of XRP to institutional investors in the amount of approximately $700 million violated federal legislation regarding the sale of securities.</p>
<p>This catapulted XRP&#8217;s price from $0.478 to $0.7885 in just under a day. With its current market cap, this means XRP is now the third-largest native cryptocurrency behind Bitcoin and Ethereum when the USDT stablecoin is removed. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/WuuNJc4B/" alt="Ripple (XRP) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>

<h2>24-Hour Trading Volume Spikes 1700%+</h2>
<p>According to data from Coinmarketcap, XRP’s 24-hour trading volume has spiked a whopping 1,758.13% to over $13.49 billion. Trading volumes have surged on various exchanges, where Upbit, the South Korean-based crypto exchange, had over $2.7 billion in 24-hour trading volume. Binance also saw over $2.3 billion in trading volume as investors scurried to buy XRP. </p>
<p>Coinglass <a href="https://www.coinglass.com/LiquidationData" rel="nofollow">data</a> shows more than $35 million short position trades on XRP have been liquidated in the past 24 hours. Most of these are from Bybit, OKX, and Binance, with $21 million, $14 million, and $14 million in short position liquidations, respectively.</p>
<p>Of course, fast price rises often end in pullbacks as XRP remains a volatile digital asset. But its recent breakout shows it’s still an altcoin to watch, with the potential for even bigger gains if more investors continue to FOMO. However, XRP’s potential for long-term growth continues to be supported by Ripple Labs’ real-world value as a payments network.</p>

<p>At the time of writing, XRP is still trading at $0.797, which translates to 68% gains in the last day. It is currently the <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/gainers-losers/" rel="nofollow">top gainer</a> in the market with 70.66% and 56.79% gains in the last seven and 30 days, respectively.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1305769484-460x272.jpg" width="460" height="272" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Liquidations Cross $300 Million Amid Massive Market Recovery</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/crypto-liquidations-cross-300-million/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 14:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto liquidations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[liquidations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542697</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The last 24 hours have been more than interesting for crypto investors across the globe. Thursday, July 13, saw one of the most important lawsuits in the history of the industry come to an end, and the ruling in favor of Ripple triggered a massive rally. As digital assets across the space recorded double-digit gains, liquidation volumes climbed quickly, now clocking over $300 million. Crypto Short Traders Take Big Losses The high volumes of crypto liquidations in the market so far have been a result of price recovery. As such, the vast majority of traders who have been losing money have been short traders, that is, traders who were betting on prices falling rather than recovering. Related Reading: Polygon Upgrade Proposal Pushes Price Over 5%, Is It Too Late To Buy? According to data from Coinglass, out of the over $300 million in liquidations, short traders made up for a total of $219 million. On the flip side, the volume from long traders was much lower, coming in at only $82.74 million for the same 24-hour period. This means that short traders made up 70.33% of all liquidations during this time, as long traders made the most money. Furthermore, over 86,000 traders saw their positions liquidated on the last day, but the single largest liquidation happened on the Bitmex exchange. This position was worth $2.82 million at the time of liquidation, taking place across the XRPUSD pair on the exchange. Liquidations cross $300 million in 24 hours &#124; Source: Coinglass As expected, Bitcoin led the liquidation volumes during this time, but interestingly, Ethereum was not the second-highest volume as it usually is. That title was claimed by XRP traders this time around with a total of $62.17 million liquidated in 24 hours. Will The Liquidations Continue? A major factor behind the liquidations was the wild price fluctuations that were triggered by the Ripple victory. Since the court declared that XRP was not a security, the price of the digital asset rallied over 60%, taking the rest of the crypto market with it. However, as the market has broken into a new trading day, prices are starting to stabilize and liquidations are beginning to settle out. If the market continues like this, then there would not be high liquidation volumes going forward. Unless something triggers a rally or a crash, which would lead to more liquidations. Related Reading: Litecoin Becomes 10th-Largest Cryptocurrency, But Is There Still Room To Run? For now, the prices of digital assets such as Bitcoin, Ethereum, and XRP are holding their gains from yesterday quite well. BTC’s price is still above $31,000, ETH is trading slightly below $2,000, and XRP is still seeing 60% gains with its price sitting at $0.779 at the time of this writing. Total crypto market cap crosses $1.2 trillion &#124; Source: Crypto Total Market Cap on Tradingview.com Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">The last 24 hours have been more than interesting for crypto investors across the globe. Thursday, July 13, saw one of the most important lawsuits in the history of the industry come to an end, and the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-judge-deems-xrp-sale-non-investment-contract/" rel="nofollow">ruling</a> in favor of Ripple triggered a massive rally. As digital assets across the space recorded double-digit gains, liquidation volumes climbed quickly, now clocking over $300 million.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Crypto Short Traders Take Big Losses</h2>
<p class="p2">The high volumes of crypto liquidations in the market so far have been a result of price recovery. As such, the vast majority of traders who have been losing money have been short traders, that is, traders who were betting on prices falling rather than recovering.</p>

<p class="p2">According to data from <a href="https://www.coinglass.com/LiquidationData" rel="nofollow">Coinglass</a>, out of the over $300 million in liquidations, short traders made up for a total of $219 million. On the flip side, the volume from long traders was much lower, coming in at only $82.74 million for the same 24-hour period. This means that short traders made up 70.33% of all liquidations during this time, as long traders made the most money.</p>
<p class="p2">Furthermore, over 86,000 traders saw their positions liquidated on the last day, but the single largest liquidation happened on the Bitmex exchange. This position was worth $2.82 million at the time of liquidation, taking place across the XRPUSD pair on the exchange.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-542703 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-14-at-13.07.58-460x147.png" alt="Crypto liquidations" width="460" height="147" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-14-at-13.07.58-460x147.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-14-at-13.07.58-860x276.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-14-at-13.07.58-768x246.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-14-at-13.07.58-1536x492.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-14-at-13.07.58-2048x656.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-14-at-13.07.58-750x240.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-14-at-13.07.58-1140x365.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>

<p class="p2">As expected, Bitcoin led the liquidation volumes during this time, but interestingly, Ethereum was not the second-highest volume as it usually is. That title was claimed by XRP traders this time around with a total of $62.17 million liquidated in 24 hours.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Will The Liquidations Continue?</h2>
<p class="p2">A major factor behind the liquidations was the wild price fluctuations that were triggered by the Ripple victory. Since the court declared that XRP was not a security, the price of the digital asset rallied over 60%, taking the rest of the crypto market with it.</p>
<p class="p2">However, as the market has broken into a new trading day, prices are starting to stabilize and liquidations are beginning to settle out. If the market continues like this, then there would not be high liquidation volumes going forward. Unless something triggers a rally or a crash, which would lead to more liquidations.</p>

<p class="p2">For now, the prices of digital assets such as Bitcoin, Ethereum, and XRP are holding their gains from yesterday quite well. BTC’s price is still above $31,000, ETH is trading slightly below $2,000, and XRP is still seeing 60% gains with its price sitting at $0.779 at the time of this writing.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/PxFwpvy0/" alt="Crypto total market cap chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1314042576-460x288.jpg" width="460" height="288" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polygon Reclaims 10th Position As MATIC Surges Nearly 30% In One Week</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/matic-analysis/polygon-reclaims-10th-position-as-matic-surges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 13:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542684</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The crypto market continues to exhibit dynamic shifts as Polygon&#8217;s native token, MATIC, outpaces Litecoin (LTC) in the global rankings to secure the 10th spot. This move comes after MATIC experienced a surge of nearly 30% over the past week. Resurgence Amid Crypto Rally The general upswing in the crypto market in the past week has presented opportunities for numerous cryptocurrencies to make significant strides. Polygon (MATIC), for one, has capitalized on this trend, breaking through multiple resistance levels to claim the 10th position in the global crypto market, thereby leaving Litecoin (LTC) trailing behind. Related Reading: MATIC Price Prediction: Polygon Bulls Aim For $0.80 The asset&#8217;s surge, which saw MATIC price climbing from a low of $0.67 last Friday to a high of $0.88 yesterday before retracting to $0.84 at the time of writing, marks a nearly 30% increase in the past 7 days. The surge also signals MATIC&#8217;s resilience, given that it comes just a month after the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) classified it as a security, triggering a drastic dip in its value. This move by the SEC made MATIC dwell in a bloodbath for a week to trade below the $0.6 mark. MATIC Road To Recovery MATIC&#8217;s recovery, however, has been somewhat fascinating. Over the past 24 hours, MATIC has rallied by nearly 10%, exhibiting a strong upward trajectory. Interestingly, this rally mirrors the movements of several notable altcoins in the market, indicating a wider market recovery trend. Despite the initial setback following the SEC&#8217;s classification, MATIC has demonstrated a comeback. Its rebound not only highlights the resilience of the asset but also underscores its growing popularity among investors, which can be attributed to the increasing interest in the Polygon platform, known for its scalability solutions for Ethereum transactions. MATIC has witnessed a dramatic rise in its market capitalization over the past week, marking a nearly $2 billion increase. The digital asset, starting from a valuation of $6.2 billion last Friday, has seen its market cap surge to $7.89 billion as of today. Interestingly, it&#8217;s not just MATIC&#8217;s price and market cap that has experienced a notable upswing. Within the same week, the daily trading volume for Polygon has nearly doubled from its figures last Friday. This surge is evident in the jump from a trading volume of $357 million late last week to as high as $952 million in the past 24 hours. Related Reading: Polygon 2.0 Upgrade – Potential Bullish Implications For MATIC Price? The sudden increase in trading volume indicates a significant uptick in trading activity within just a week. The overall rise in both price and trading volume paints a picture of significant market interest and increased investor activity around Polygon. Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto market continues to exhibit dynamic shifts as Polygon&#8217;s native token, MATIC, outpaces Litecoin (LTC) in the global rankings to secure the 10th spot. This move comes after <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/matic-analysis/matic-price-prediction-polygon-aim-0-80/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">MATIC</a> experienced a surge of nearly 30% over the past week.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Resurgence Amid Crypto Rally</h2>
<p>The general upswing in the crypto market in the past week has presented opportunities for numerous cryptocurrencies to make significant strides.<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/polygon-2-0-upgrade-potential-bullish-implications-for-matic-price/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> Polygon (MATIC)</a>, for one, has capitalized on this trend, breaking through multiple resistance levels to claim the 10th position in the global crypto market, thereby leaving Litecoin (LTC) trailing behind.</p>

<p>The asset&#8217;s surge, which saw <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/matic-analysis/matic-price-prediction-polygon-0-75/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">MATIC price</a> climbing from a low of $0.67 last Friday to a high of $0.88 yesterday before retracting to $0.84 at the time of writing, marks a nearly 30% increase in the past 7 days.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/emx6buIH/" alt="Polygon (MATIC) price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1412"/>
<p>The surge also signals MATIC&#8217;s resilience, given that it comes just a month after the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) classified it as a security, triggering a drastic dip in its value. This move by the SEC made MATIC dwell in a bloodbath for a week to trade below the $0.6 mark.</p>
<h2>MATIC Road To Recovery</h2>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">MATIC&#8217;s recovery, however, has been somewhat fascinating. Over the past 24 hours, MATIC has rallied by nearly 10%, exhibiting a strong upward trajectory. Interestingly, this rally mirrors the movements of several notable altcoins in the market, indicating a wider market recovery trend.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Despite the initial setback following the SEC&#8217;s classification, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/matic-analysis/polygon-matic-witnesses-high-volatility-amid-positive-developments/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">MATIC has demonstrated a comeback</a>. Its rebound not only highlights the resilience of the asset but also underscores its growing popularity among investors, which can be attributed to the increasing interest in the Polygon platform, known for its scalability solutions for Ethereum transactions.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">MATIC has witnessed a dramatic rise in its market capitalization over the past week, marking a nearly $2 billion increase. The digital asset, starting from a valuation of $6.2 billion last Friday, has seen its market cap surge to $7.89 billion as of today. Interestingly, it&#8217;s not just MATIC&#8217;s price and market cap that has experienced a notable upswing.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Within the same week, the daily trading volume for Polygon has nearly doubled from its figures last Friday. This surge is evident in the jump from a trading volume of $357 million late last week to as high as $952 million in the past 24 hours.</p>

<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">The sudden increase in trading volume indicates a significant uptick in trading activity within just a week. The overall rise in both price and trading volume paints a picture of significant market interest and increased investor activity around Polygon.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DeFi.jpg" width="350" height="250" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu (SHIB) Shows Strength With 5% Rally, Reversal Confirmed?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/all/shiba-inu-shib-5-rally-reversal-confirmed/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 12:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shibarium]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shytoshi Kusama']]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542671</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Shiba Inu price has risen over 5% in the last 24 hours amid the market-wide hype surrounding Ripple&#8217;s partial victory in its legal battle with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). But SHIB investors should still be cautious: While the SHIB price shows a clear uptrend of 23% over the last 30 days, a complete confirmation of a trend reversal is still pending. Shiba Inu Price Analysis Technically, the Shiba Inu price remains in bearish territory for several reasons. As explained in previous analyses, the Shib price entered a downtrend channel in early February this year. The breakout from the bearish chart pattern succeeded six days ago, however, there is still a possibility that it is a fakeout. Shib&#8217;s trading volume was rather below average during and after the breakout. Only yesterday there was a noticeable increase. Within the last few hours, trading volume rose to $232 million, 200% higher than the previous day. In the best case, the volume should remain high to avoid a fakeout. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Whale Holding 10% Of Total SHIB Supply Shocks The Market More of a bearish argument is that yesterday&#8217;s SHIB rally stopped at $0.00000813. Thus, the price could not break above resistance at $0.00000816, nor could it set a new local high on the 4-hour chart. A look at the 1-day chart also shows that the SHIB price continues to trade below the 23.6% Fibonacci retracement level at $0.00000832. The following days could become crucial to confirm a sustainable trend change or a fakeout. The battle between bulls and bears is still in full swing. The bull side would ideally like to break out above the 23.6% Fibonacci retracement level with a high trading volume. This could be a first confirmation for a sustainable trend change. Related Reading: Shiba Inu (SHIB) Breakout Alert: Potential 30% Rally Looming In this case, the 38.2% Fibonacci retracement level at $0.00000977 could come into focus. Close to it is also the long-term &#8220;bull boundary line&#8221;, the 200-day exponential moving average (EMA) at $0.00000961. If SHIB also exceeds this level, one can finally speak of a trend reversal. Before that, however, the current gains stand on shaky legs. Shibarium As Catalyst As NewsBTC reported, Shiba Inu chief developer Shytoshi Kusama has hinted a few days ago that the long-awaited layer-2 solution Shibarium will be unveiled along with numerous other innovations at the ETHToronto conference on August 15-16. With only 32 days left until this event, the hype could undoubtedly serve as a catalyst for SHIB. At least Shiba Inu ecosystem token BONE has already benefited from the announcement, raking in high double-digit percentage gains. Just today, Kusama fueled anticipation for Shibarium when he announced the relaunch of the official Shiba Inu website Shib.io. Via Twitter, Kusama teased &#8220;Enjoying the summer of Shibarium.&#8221; As the #summerofshibarium continues we are proud to introduce new branding for https://t.co/vRofmNPr53 and other #SHIBARMY websites! Give it a look! #WOOF pic.twitter.com/TY7x5hlDS5 — Shytoshi Kusama™ (@ShytoshiKusama) July 13, 2023 Featured image from Twitter, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Shiba Inu price has risen over 5% in the last 24 hours amid the market-wide hype surrounding Ripple&#8217;s partial victory in its legal battle with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). But SHIB investors should still be cautious: While the SHIB price shows a clear uptrend of 23% over the last 30 days, a complete confirmation of a trend reversal is still pending.</p>
<h2>Shiba Inu Price Analysis</h2>
<p>Technically, the Shiba Inu price remains in bearish territory for several reasons. As explained in previous <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-shib-breakout-alert-potential-30-rally/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">analyses</a>, the Shib price entered a downtrend channel in early February this year. The breakout from the bearish chart pattern succeeded six days ago, however, there is still a possibility that it is a fakeout.</p>
<p>Shib&#8217;s trading volume was rather below average during and after the breakout. Only yesterday there was a noticeable increase. Within the last few hours, trading volume rose to $232 million, 200% higher than the previous day. In the best case, the volume should remain high to avoid a fakeout.</p>

<p>More of a bearish argument is that yesterday&#8217;s SHIB rally stopped at $0.00000813. Thus, the price could not break above resistance at $0.00000816, nor could it set a new local high on the 4-hour chart.</p>
<p>A look at the 1-day chart also shows that the SHIB price continues to trade below the 23.6% Fibonacci retracement level at $0.00000832. The following days could become crucial to confirm a sustainable trend change or a fakeout.</p>
<p>The battle between bulls and bears is still in full swing. The bull side would ideally like to break out above the 23.6% Fibonacci retracement level with a high trading volume. This could be a first confirmation for a sustainable trend change.</p>

<p>In this case, the 38.2% Fibonacci retracement level at $0.00000977 could come into focus. Close to it is also the long-term &#8220;bull boundary line&#8221;, the 200-day exponential moving average (EMA) at $0.00000961. If SHIB also exceeds this level, one can finally speak of a trend reversal. Before that, however, the current gains stand on shaky legs.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-542688 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-14_13-21-09.png" alt="Shiba Inu price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-14_13-21-09.png 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-14_13-21-09-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-14_13-21-09-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-14_13-21-09-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-14_13-21-09-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-14_13-21-09-2048x944.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-14_13-21-09-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIBUSD_2023-07-14_13-21-09-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3628px) 100vw, 3628px"/>
<h2>Shibarium As Catalyst</h2>
<p>As NewsBTC reported, Shiba Inu chief developer Shytoshi Kusama has hinted a few days ago that the long-awaited layer-2 solution Shibarium will be <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-lead-teases-shibarium-launch-shib-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">unveiled</a> along with numerous other innovations at the ETHToronto conference on August 15-16. With only 32 days left until this event, the hype could undoubtedly serve as a catalyst for SHIB. At least Shiba Inu ecosystem token BONE has already <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-token-bone-surges-88-too-late-to-buy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">benefited</a> from the announcement, raking in high double-digit percentage gains.</p>
<p>Just today, Kusama fueled anticipation for Shibarium when he announced the relaunch of the official Shiba Inu website Shib.io. Via Twitter, Kusama teased &#8220;Enjoying the summer of Shibarium.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">As the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/summerofshibarium?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#summerofshibarium</a> continues we are proud to introduce new branding for <a href="https://t.co/vRofmNPr53" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/vRofmNPr53</a> and other <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/SHIBARMY?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#SHIBARMY</a> websites! Give it a look! <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/WOOF?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#WOOF</a> <a href="https://t.co/TY7x5hlDS5" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/TY7x5hlDS5</a></p>
<p>— Shytoshi Kusama<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@ShytoshiKusama) <a href="https://twitter.com/ShytoshiKusama/status/1679567756503523331?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 13, 2023</a></p></blockquote>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F08F-VXXgAIIxvY-460x191.jpg" width="460" height="191" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar (XLM) Basks In XRP Euphoria, Soars 52% In One Day</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/stellar/stellar-xlm-basks-in-xrp-euphoria-soars-52-in-one-day/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 11:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xlmusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542661</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The price of Stellar (XLM) has experienced a similar meteoric rise to the XRP token in the last 24 hours. This rise was triggered by news that Ripple, the company behind XRP, had won its long-running case against the US Securities and Exchange Commission SEC. The SEC&#8217;s case that XRP is a security was the focus of the court trial. To the delight of the crypto community, Judge Annalisa Torres of the US District Court for the Southern District of New York ruled in Ripple&#8217;s favor, declaring the XRP token not to be a security. Stellar Looks To Enter The Top 20 Crypto Ranking The altcoin market had been dominated by bearish pressure in recent weeks due partly to the SEC’s declaration of tokens tied to Solana, Polygon, and Cardano as securities. This declaration formed the foundation of the regulator’s case against prominent crypto exchanges Coinbase and Binance. Related Reading: Optimism (OP) Rides The Wave Of Today’s Crypto Surge With 15% Rally That said, the market was jolted back to life yesterday following the announcement of Ripple’s court victory, with most tokens basking in green. Stellar also reacted swiftly to positive market sentiment, going on an almost 90% price rally within a few hours. The token&#8217;s price has since steadied, with Stellar currently trading with a 52.4 % gain. With this, XLM’s price rise places it amongst the top daily gainers in the cryptocurrency market today. As of this writing, XLM is valued at $0.147189, with a 3.9% price decrease in the past hour. The token has a 24-hour trading volume of over $1.26 billion, representing a 3,386% surge in the past day. According to CoinGecko data, the Stellar token is closing in on a spot in the top 20 largest cryptocurrencies, with a market cap of nearly $4 billion. Is $0.8 Within Reach For XLM? A look at the broader market shows that XLM has been underwhelming in recent days. Although the token scored some significant gains last month, it appears to have also been affected by the dour market conditions in July. Following the positive price movement of yesterday, investors are hoping to see the XLM price visit the $0.8 again. However, after hitting its all-time high of $0.875563 in 2018, the coin has only ever reached the $0.8 level once. Related Reading: XRP Price Retreats After Massive 80% Rally, Buy The Dips? On the weekly chart, the XLM token must overcome resistance at $0.2 and $ 0.4 price levels. So, it would take extraordinary bullish pressure for Stellar to reach $0.8 again.  XLMUSD trading at $0.146982 &#124; Source: chart from TradingView That said, the Relative Strength Index (RSI), an indicator that tracks the balance between the buying pressure and selling pressure of a token, suggests that the current bullish momentum might be waning. The daily RSI has crossed above the 70-mark, which represents the overbought zone. This indicates that the buying pressure is at its peak, and a reversal might be on the horizon. Featured image from Shutterstock, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price of Stellar (XLM) has experienced a similar meteoric rise to the XRP token in the last 24 hours. This rise was triggered by <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-judge-deems-xrp-sale-non-investment-contract/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">news that Ripple</a>, the company behind XRP, had won its long-running case against the US Securities and Exchange Commission SEC.</p>
<p>The SEC&#8217;s case that XRP is a security was the focus of the court trial. To the delight of the crypto community, Judge Annalisa Torres of the US District Court for the Southern District of New York ruled in Ripple&#8217;s favor, declaring the XRP token not to be a security.</p>
<h2>Stellar Looks To Enter The Top 20 Crypto Ranking</h2>
<p>The altcoin market had been dominated by bearish pressure in recent weeks due partly to the SEC’s declaration of tokens tied to Solana, Polygon, and Cardano as securities. This declaration formed the foundation of the regulator’s case against prominent crypto exchanges Coinbase and Binance.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/optimism-rides-wave-of-crypto-surge/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Optimism (OP) Rides The Wave Of Today’s Crypto Surge With 15% Rally</a></p>
<p>That said, the market was jolted back to life yesterday following the announcement of Ripple’s court victory, with most tokens basking in green. Stellar also reacted swiftly to positive market sentiment, going on an almost 90% price rally within a few hours.</p>
<p>The token&#8217;s price has since steadied, with Stellar currently trading with a 52.4 % gain. With this, XLM’s price rise places it amongst the top daily gainers in the cryptocurrency market today.</p>
<p>As of this writing, XLM is valued at $0.147189, with a 3.9% price decrease in the past hour. The token has a 24-hour trading volume of over $1.26 billion, representing a 3,386% surge in the past day.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/stellar" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko data</a>, the Stellar token is closing in on a spot in the top 20 largest cryptocurrencies, with a market cap of nearly $4 billion.</p>
<h2>Is $0.8 Within Reach For XLM?</h2>
<p>A look at the broader market shows that XLM has been underwhelming in recent days. Although the token scored some significant gains last month, it appears to have also been affected by the dour market conditions in July.</p>
<p>Following the positive price movement of yesterday, investors are hoping to see the XLM price visit the $0.8 again. However, after hitting its all-time high of $0.875563 in 2018, the coin has only ever reached the $0.8 level once.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-price-retreats-rally-0-95/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">XRP Price Retreats After Massive 80% Rally, Buy The Dips?</a></p>
<p>On the weekly chart, the XLM token must overcome resistance at $0.2 and $ 0.4 price levels. So, it would take extraordinary bullish pressure for Stellar to reach $0.8 again. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/QB6RnfFc/" alt="Stellar" width="997" height="586"/></p>

<p>That said, the Relative Strength Index (RSI), an indicator that tracks the balance between the buying pressure and selling pressure of a token, suggests that the current bullish momentum might be waning.</p>
<p>The daily RSI has crossed above the 70-mark, which represents the overbought zone. This indicates that the buying pressure is at its peak, and a reversal might be on the horizon.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bullchart-460x247.jpg" width="460" height="247" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
