<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 13:54:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Will Reach $175,000 If Prices Break Above This Rising Channel, Trader Claims</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-175000-break-above-rising-channel/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 14:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin bulls]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543863</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin&#8217;s six-year range inside a rising channel has drawn the attention of a curious but optimistic analyst. Previewing the price chart shows that the coin has been in range over the years, capturing all of its volatility. Despite occasional dumps and pumps, the structure is yet to be broken.  By the time the screenshot was shared on July 21, Bitcoin was trading in the lower part of the rising channel, skirting the support trend line, an indicator that prices have been generally lower in recent months. The rejection of lower lows and bounce from the support trend line, the analyst says, is bullish and squarely puts back bulls in contention. Bitcoin To $175,000? According to the trader&#8217;s assessment, a breakout above the upper resistance level at around $32,000 could potentially trigger a new bull run that may see the world&#8217;s most valuable cryptocurrency retest highs of the rising channel at $175,000, a level that upbeat HODLers can mark as a feasible target.  Related Reading: Maker (MKR) Surges 26% In A Week As Token Buyback Program Goes Live Still, considering the volatility in crypto, this bullish forecast cannot be dismissed. To illustrate, the last bull run drove Bitcoin prices from sub-$10,000 to peaks of $69,000 in less than two years. Therefore, if Bitcoin bulls push above $32,000, a price level that the analyst claim is important, it could be a bullish signal that may be the beginning of another leg up in the resumption of the bullish formation set in motion between 2020 and 2021.  Bitcoin is trading below the $30,000 level at spot rates with resistance at $31,800. Despite the general optimism across the board, bulls are yet to breach July 2023 highs as prices consolidate. Halving And ETF Approval As Tailwinds? Specific triggers for the next run are unknown for now. Even so, considering past cycles, the upcoming Bitcoin halving event may provide the impetus for a leg up toward 2021 highs at $69,000. Besides, traders are closely monitoring how the spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) applications in the United States progresses.  The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has rejected several spot Bitcoin ETF applications in the past. However, the involvement of BlackRock has been received positively, lifting prices in the past few weeks. BlackRock is the world&#8217;s largest asset manager, managing trillions.  Related Reading: From Polygon NFT Wins To MATIC Gains: Understanding The Connection The approval of a Bitcoin ETF would ease institutional investors&#8217; involvement in the sphere, potentially driving demand and lifting prices. Most importantly, a Bitcoin ETF legitimizes Bitcoin as an investment asset. Bitcoin is the most dominant crypto asset, and complex derivatives instruments, including exchange-traded products (ETPs), have been approved and listed in various markets across Canada, Europe, and Brazil. Feature image from Canva, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s six-year range inside a rising channel has drawn the attention of a curious but optimistic analyst. Previewing the price chart shows that the coin has been in range over the years, capturing all of its volatility. Despite occasional dumps and pumps, the structure is yet to be broken. </p>
<p>By the time the screenshot was <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/CryptoJelleNL/status/1682289250321014785" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shared</a> on July 21, Bitcoin was trading in the lower part of the rising channel, skirting the support trend line, an indicator that prices have been generally lower in recent months. The rejection of lower lows and bounce from the support trend line, the analyst says, is bullish and squarely puts back bulls in contention.</p>
<h2><strong>Bitcoin To $175,000?</strong></h2>
<p>According to the trader&#8217;s assessment, a breakout above the upper resistance level at around $32,000 could potentially trigger a new bull run that may see the world&#8217;s most valuable cryptocurrency retest highs of the rising channel at $175,000, a level that upbeat HODLers can mark as a feasible target. </p>

<p>Still, considering the volatility in crypto, this bullish forecast cannot be dismissed. To illustrate, the last bull run drove Bitcoin prices from sub-$10,000 to peaks of $69,000 in less than two years. Therefore, if Bitcoin bulls push above $32,000, a price level that the analyst claim is important, it could be a bullish signal that may be the beginning of another leg up in the resumption of the bullish formation set in motion between 2020 and 2021. </p>
<p>Bitcoin is trading below the $30,000 level at spot rates with resistance at $31,800. Despite the general optimism across the board, bulls are yet to breach July 2023 highs as prices consolidate.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/dVOTNHsg/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/dVOTNHsg/" alt="Bitcoin price on July 22| Source: BTCUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595" loading="lazy"/></a>
<h2><strong>Halving And ETF Approval As Tailwinds?</strong></h2>
<p>Specific triggers for the next run are unknown for now. Even so, considering past cycles, the upcoming Bitcoin halving event may provide the impetus for a leg up toward 2021 highs at $69,000. Besides, traders are closely monitoring how the spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) applications in the United States progresses. </p>
<p>The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has rejected several spot Bitcoin ETF applications in the past. However, the involvement of BlackRock has been received positively, lifting prices in the past few weeks. BlackRock is the world&#8217;s largest asset manager, managing trillions. </p>

<p>The approval of a Bitcoin ETF would ease institutional investors&#8217; involvement in the sphere, potentially driving demand and lifting prices. Most importantly, a Bitcoin ETF legitimizes Bitcoin as an investment asset. Bitcoin is the most dominant crypto asset, and complex derivatives instruments, including exchange-traded products (ETPs), have been approved and listed in various markets across Canada, Europe, and Brazil.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-To-175000-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>From Polygon NFT Wins To MATIC Gains: Understanding The Connection</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/from-polygon-nft-wins-to-matic-gains-understanding-the-connection/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 13:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATIC Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543828</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Polygon has recently witnessed a remarkable surge in its non-fungible tokens (NFTs) sales volume and the influx of sellers participating in this burgeoning market. This growth in the NFT sector has sparked considerable interest and speculation among investors, prompting many to ponder the potential impact it may have on the price of MATIC, the native cryptocurrency of the Polygon network.  However, despite the impressive surge in NFT sales volume and seller participation, a closer examination reveals that not everything works in Polygon&#8217;s favor.  While the NFT market on the platform may be flourishing, other factors could impact the overall sentiment and performance of MATIC. Polygon NFT sales are trending up. Polygon NFT summer? pic.twitter.com/9Jh2ENkyjj — Narb (@NarbTrading) July 20, 2023 MATIC Price Movement In Response To Metric Movement The recent MATIC price report indicates a remarkable surge in Polygon NFT sellers, recording a staggering increase of over 480% within the last 30 days.  Related Reading: Dogecoin Sees Positive Price Movement, Bulls Set Crosshair At $0.075 Meanwhile, MATIC&#8217;s current price stands at $0.772874 according to Coingecko, experiencing a 1.6% rally in the last 24 hours but also facing a 4.3% decline. Several factors could explain this lackluster price performance.  Source: Cryptoslam For one, market sentiment plays a crucial role in shaping cryptocurrency prices, and during this period, overall opinion towards cryptocurrencies, including MATIC, might not have been favorable. Source: Coingecko Regulatory uncertainties, macroeconomic events, and broader market trends could have overshadowed the positive impact of the NFT growth on Polygon. However, price movements in the cryptocurrency market may only sometimes reflect immediate developments. There could be a time lag between the surge in NFT volume and its direct impact on MATIC&#8217;s price. Market reactions can be delayed, and sustained growth in NFT activity may be required to affect the token&#8217;s value significantly. Rising Competition Poses Challenge For Polygon  A recent report also highlights the increasing competition that Polygon, a Layer-2 scaling solution for Ethereum, is facing within its market niche. Polygon has been known for its ability to enhance Ethereum&#8217;s performance, making it faster, cheaper, and more efficient. MATIC market cap currently at $7.11 billion. Chart: TradingView.com However, the emergence of numerous other cryptocurrencies offering similar services, including Optimism, poses a significant challenge to Polygon&#8217;s once-dominant position in the sector.  In the past, Polygon enjoyed a clear lead in the Layer-2 scaling niche, capturing investor attention and interest. However, the current market dynamics indicate that this advantage has diminished. Related Reading: Chainlink Holds Strong With 19% Rally – More Gains In The Pipeline? Despite its impressive features, the price of Polygon has exhibited minimal movement throughout the year, indicating subdued investor sentiment and potentially reduced demand. On the other hand, Optimism, a direct competitor to Polygon, has experienced remarkable growth over the year, with its yearly growth soaring by over 80%. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Coin Chapter]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Polygon has recently witnessed a remarkable surge in its non-fungible tokens (NFTs) sales volume and the influx of sellers participating in this burgeoning market. </p>
<p>This growth in the NFT sector has sparked considerable interest and speculation among investors, prompting many to ponder the potential impact it may have on the price of MATIC, the native cryptocurrency of the Polygon network. </p>
<p>However, despite the impressive <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/NarbTrading/status/1682019353275817984" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">surge in NFT sales volume</a> and seller participation, a closer examination reveals that not everything works in Polygon&#8217;s favor. </p>
<p>While the NFT market on the platform may be flourishing, other factors could impact the overall sentiment and performance of MATIC.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Polygon NFT sales are trending up.</p>
<p>Polygon NFT summer? <a href="https://t.co/9Jh2ENkyjj" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/9Jh2ENkyjj</a></p>
<p>— Narb (@NarbTrading) <a href="https://twitter.com/NarbTrading/status/1682019353275817984?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 20, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<h2><strong>MATIC Price Movement In Response To Metric Movement</strong></h2>
<p>The recent MATIC price report indicates a remarkable surge in Polygon NFT sellers, recording a staggering increase of over 480% within the last 30 days. </p>

<p>Meanwhile, MATIC&#8217;s current price stands at $0.772874 according to <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/polygon" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Coingecko</a>, experiencing a 1.6% rally in the last 24 hours but also facing a 4.3% decline. Several factors could explain this lackluster price performance. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-543832 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-141-860x153.png" alt="" width="860" height="153" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-141-860x153.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-141-460x82.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-141-768x137.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-141-750x133.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-141.png 1136w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>For one, market sentiment plays a crucial role in shaping cryptocurrency prices, and during this period, overall opinion towards cryptocurrencies, including MATIC, might not have been favorable. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-543833" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-142.png" alt="" width="1136" height="60" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-142.png 1136w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-142-460x24.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-142-860x45.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-142-768x41.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-142-750x40.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1136px) 100vw, 1136px"/></p>

<p>Regulatory uncertainties, macroeconomic events, and broader market trends could have overshadowed the positive impact of the NFT growth on Polygon.</p>
<p>However, price movements in the cryptocurrency market may only sometimes reflect immediate developments. There could be a time lag between the surge in NFT volume and its direct impact on MATIC&#8217;s price. Market reactions can be delayed, and sustained growth in NFT activity may be required to affect the token&#8217;s value significantly.</p>
<h2><strong>Rising Competition Poses Challenge For Polygon </strong></h2>
<p>A recent <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.fool.com/investing/2023/07/21/is-it-time-to-sell-polygon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a> also highlights the increasing competition that Polygon, a Layer-2 scaling solution for Ethereum, is facing within its market niche. Polygon has been known for its ability to enhance Ethereum&#8217;s performance, making it faster, cheaper, and more efficient. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/dd0QyfDv/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>

<p>However, the emergence of numerous other cryptocurrencies offering similar services, including Optimism, poses a significant challenge to Polygon&#8217;s once-dominant position in the sector. </p>
<p>In the past, Polygon enjoyed a clear lead in the Layer-2 scaling niche, capturing investor attention and interest. However, the current market dynamics indicate that this advantage has diminished.</p>

<p>Despite its impressive features, the price of Polygon has exhibited minimal movement throughout the year, indicating subdued investor sentiment and potentially reduced demand.</p>
<p>On the other hand, Optimism, a direct competitor to Polygon, has experienced remarkable growth over the year, with its <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/optimism" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">yearly growth soaring by over 80%</a>.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Coin Chapter</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-143-460x307.png" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Maker (MKR) Surges 26% In A Week As Token Buyback Program Goes Live</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/maker-mkr/maker-mkr-surges-26-in-a-week-as-token-buyback-program-goes-live/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olowoporoku Adeniyi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 12:20:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Maker (MKR)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[maker]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Maker analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MKR]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543826</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the past week, Maker (MKR) token has captured significant attention in the crypto market, surging an impressive 26%. This remarkable price action coincides with the introduction of a groundbreaking token buyback program by the leading decentralized finance (DeFi) lending platform, MakerDAO. As the DeFi ecosystem continues to expand, Maker (MKR) stands out as one of the largest and oldest DeFi lending protocols, gaining popularity for its issuance of the widely used DAI stablecoin with a market value of $4.6 billion. MKR Token Buyback Program Triggers Surge The recent surge in Maker (MKR), the governance token of the $5.3 billion decentralized finance (DeFi) lender MakerDAO, can be attributed to the implementation of a token buyback program. The token buyback scheme, named the Smart Burn Engine, is designed to remove MKR tokens from the market. The mechanism involves allocating excess DAI stablecoins from Maker&#8217;s surplus buffer to purchase MKR tokens from a UniSwap pool. The governance proposal behind this initiative aims to strengthen the token&#8217;s value and governance while actively engaging MKR holders in voting on crucial proposals. Related Reading: Dogecoin Becomes 8th-Largest Cryptocurrency After Adding $1 Billion To Market Cap According to blockchain data, the lending platform is poised to remove approximately $7 million worth of MKR governance tokens from the market over the next month through this buyback initiative. With the token&#8217;s total market capitalization standing at around $1 billion, the buyback represents a 0.7% reduction in the token&#8217;s supply per month, potentially enhancing MKR&#8217;s scarcity and value proposition. This strategic move is likely to attract further interest and investment from the crypto community. The token buyback program has already shown promising results, with MakerDAO purchasing approximately $230,000 worth of MKR tokens within the last 24 hours. This early success indicates positive momentum and investor interest in the buyback initiative.  Maker: Significant Developments In 2023 In addition to the token buyback program, MakerDAO has been proactively diversifying its revenue streams by investing its DAI reserve assets into traditional financial products, such as bank loans and government bonds. This strategic decision has proven to be fruitful, as it enables the platform to generate sustainable revenue from yields, providing a solid basis for potential growth and long-term value. Unlike meme coins lacking tangible business prospects, Maker&#8217;s diversified revenue streams instill confidence in investors and the broader DeFi community, making it an attractive investment option. Related Reading: Bitfinex Hackers Surrender: Couple Agrees to Forfeit 120,000 Bitcoin in Plea Deal Beyond the token buyback and DAI reserve investments, MakerDAO is also undergoing a significant overhaul that includes upgrades for both the DAI and MKR tokens. Furthermore, the platform is transitioning into smaller autonomous organizations known as SubDAOs, which have the potential to issue their own tokens. These developments signal a dynamic future for MakerDAO and highlight the platform&#8217;s commitment to continuous innovation and progress. Over the past 24 hours, there has been a 9.98% decrease in the price. However, in the last hour alone, the price has shown a modest increase of 0.28%. As of now, the current price of MKR stands at $1,094.53. It&#8217;s important to note that Maker is currently 82.73% below its all-time high, which was recorded at $6,339.02. (This site’s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured Image from istock, chart from TradingView.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the past week, Maker (MKR) token has captured significant attention in the crypto market, surging an impressive 26%. This remarkable price action coincides with the introduction of a groundbreaking token buyback program by the leading decentralized finance (DeFi) lending platform, MakerDAO. As the DeFi ecosystem continues to expand, Maker (MKR) stands out as one of the largest and oldest DeFi lending protocols, gaining popularity for its issuance of the widely used DAI stablecoin with a market value of $4.6 billion.</p>
<h2><strong>MKR Token Buyback Program Triggers Surge</strong></h2>
<p>The recent surge in Maker (MKR), the governance token of the $5.3 billion decentralized finance (DeFi) lender MakerDAO, can be attributed to the implementation of a token buyback program. The token buyback scheme, named the Smart Burn Engine, is designed to remove MKR tokens from the market. The mechanism involves allocating excess DAI stablecoins from Maker&#8217;s surplus buffer to purchase MKR tokens from a UniSwap pool. The governance proposal behind this initiative aims to strengthen the token&#8217;s value and governance while actively engaging MKR holders in voting on crucial proposals.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading</strong>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/dogecoin-becomes-8th-largest-crypto/?swcfpc=1">Dogecoin Becomes 8th-Largest Cryptocurrency After Adding $1 Billion To Market Cap</a></p>
<p>According to blockchain data, the lending platform is poised to remove approximately $7 million worth of MKR governance tokens from the market over the next month through this buyback initiative. With the token&#8217;s total market capitalization standing at around $1 billion, the buyback represents a 0.7% reduction in the token&#8217;s supply per month, potentially enhancing MKR&#8217;s scarcity and value proposition. This strategic move is likely to attract further interest and investment from the crypto community.</p>
<p>The token buyback program has already shown promising results, with MakerDAO purchasing approximately $230,000 worth of MKR tokens within the last 24 hours. This early success indicates positive momentum and investor interest in the buyback initiative. </p>
<h2><strong>Maker: Significant Developments In 2023</strong></h2>
<p>In addition to the token buyback program, MakerDAO has been proactively diversifying its revenue streams by investing its <a href="https://www.dai.com/" rel="nofollow">DAI</a> reserve assets into traditional financial products, such as bank loans and government bonds. This strategic decision has proven to be fruitful, as it enables the platform to generate sustainable revenue from yields, providing a solid basis for potential growth and long-term value. Unlike meme coins lacking tangible business prospects, Maker&#8217;s diversified revenue streams instill confidence in investors and the broader DeFi community, making it an attractive investment option.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading: </strong><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitfinex-hackers-surrender-couple-agrees-to-forfeit-120000-bitcoin-in-plea-deal/?swcfpc=1">Bitfinex Hackers Surrender: Couple Agrees to Forfeit 120,000 Bitcoin in Plea Deal</a></p>
<p>Beyond the token buyback and DAI reserve investments, MakerDAO is also undergoing a significant overhaul that includes upgrades for both the DAI and MKR tokens. Furthermore, the platform is transitioning into smaller autonomous organizations known as SubDAOs, which have the potential to issue their own tokens. These developments signal a dynamic future for MakerDAO and highlight the platform&#8217;s commitment to continuous innovation and progress.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-543827 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image1-4-860x474.png" alt="MakerDAO continue to show bullish trend in the past 24 hours: Source @Tradingview" width="860" height="474" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image1-4-860x474.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image1-4-460x253.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image1-4-768x423.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image1-4-750x413.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image1-4.png 1080w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>Over the past 24 hours, there has been a 9.98% decrease in the price. However, in the last hour alone, the price has shown a modest increase of 0.28%. As of now, the current price of MKR stands at $1,094.53. It&#8217;s important to note that Maker is currently 82.73% below its all-time high, which was recorded at $6,339.02.</p>
<p><i>(This site’s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</i></p>
<p><i>Featured Image from istock, chart from TradingView.</i></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-157559643-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum (ETH) Records Highest CEX Inflows In 2 Months</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-eth-records-highest-cex-inflows-in-2-months/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:33:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543807</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Over the past week, Ethereum (ETH) registered the highest inflows into centralized exchanges (CEX) in the past two months. These significant asset movements have suggested a potential price dip for ETH. CoinGecko data shows that the second-largest cryptocurrency has been experiencing a slight price decline, losing 2.5% of its value in the past week. As of this writing, the Ether token changes hand at $1,892.65, with a negligible 0.2% gain in the last 24 hours. Related Reading: XDC Network Dominates Weekend Top 100 Roster With 50% Rally Ethereum Registers $383 Million Worth Of ETH In CEX Inflows According to data from IntoTheBlock, Ethereum witnessed the largest inflows into centralized exchanges in the past two months. The data analytics platform found that at least $383 million worth of ETH was deposited into these exchanges. IntoTheBlock also revealed that a significant percentage of the CEX inflows came from a single address and in a single transaction. This deposit came from an old wallet that accumulated 61,216 ETH during the Ethereum Initial Coin Offering (ICO). This pre-mine wallet had been dormant for eight years, with its constituent ETH worth more than $116 million untouched. On Wednesday, July 19, this address became activated, and its stash of Ether tokens was abruptly moved to another address associated with the Kraken exchange. Data from Whale Alert shows that a significant amount of Ether tokens has been transferred to crypto exchanges by several whales over the past week. Notably, more than 200,000 Ether tokens have been transferred to Coinbase in separate transactions within this period. Indeed, the movement of massive amounts of ETH to centralized exchanges can signal impending selling pressure, which can drive the asset’s price down. However, not all large transfers to an exchange precipitate a downward price movement, as the whales might not intend to sell immediately or all at once. Total ETH Staked Reaches All-Time High The Ethereum network has been experiencing a steady increase in the total amount of ETH staked on the blockchain. According to data from IntoTheBlock, this figure has reached $52.3 billion, representing its highest value ever. The data analytics company also noted that with an increasing amount of staked ETH, the Ethereum blockchain is bound to become even more secure, as there will be a corresponding decrease in the risk of the network being taken over by a single entity.  Related Reading: Dogecoin Becomes 8th-Largest Cryptocurrency After Adding $1 Billion To Market Cap It is worth noting that this surge in staking activity can be linked to the successful launch of the Shapella upgrade. The Shapella upgrade offered a new dimension to ETH staking, as investors can now lock and unlock their assets at will. This increased flexibility eliminated a substantial portion of risk that has been attributed to ETH staking in the past. ETHUSD trading at $1,886.82 &#124; Source: ETHUSD daily chart from TradingView &#160; Featured image from Getty, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Over the past week, Ethereum (ETH) registered the highest inflows into centralized exchanges (CEX) in the past two months. These significant asset movements have suggested a potential price dip for ETH.</p>
<p>CoinGecko data shows that the second-largest cryptocurrency has been experiencing a slight price decline, losing 2.5% of its value in the past week. As of this writing, the Ether token changes hand at $1,892.65, with a negligible 0.2% gain in the last 24 hours.</p>

<h2><strong>Ethereum Registers $383 Million Worth Of ETH In CEX Inflows</strong></h2>
<p>According to data from <a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1682304210476343296?s=46&amp;t=mgC1X0u3l4anrG2qLqYMzw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">IntoTheBlock</a>, Ethereum witnessed the largest inflows into centralized exchanges in the past two months. The data analytics platform found that at least $383 million worth of ETH was deposited into these exchanges.</p>
<p>IntoTheBlock also revealed that a significant percentage of the CEX inflows came from a single address and in a single transaction. This deposit came from an <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/pre-mined-ethereum-moves-after-8-years-price-dip-imminent/amp/">old wallet that accumulated 61,216 ETH</a> during the Ethereum Initial Coin Offering (ICO).</p>
<p>This pre-mine wallet had been dormant for eight years, with its constituent ETH worth more than $116 million untouched. On Wednesday, July 19, this address became activated, and its stash of Ether tokens was abruptly moved to another address associated with the Kraken exchange.</p>
<p>Data from<a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert?s=21&amp;t=mgC1X0u3l4anrG2qLqYMzw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> Whale Alert</a> shows that a significant amount of Ether tokens has been transferred to crypto exchanges by several whales over the past week. Notably, more than 200,000 Ether tokens have been transferred to Coinbase in separate transactions within this period.</p>
<p>Indeed, the movement of massive amounts of ETH to centralized exchanges can signal impending selling pressure, which can drive the asset’s price down. However, not all large transfers to an exchange precipitate a downward price movement, as the whales might not intend to sell immediately or all at once.</p>
<h2><strong>Total ETH Staked Reaches All-Time High</strong></h2>
<p>The Ethereum network has been experiencing a steady increase in the total amount of ETH staked on the blockchain. According to<a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1682420398577598465?s=46&amp;t=mgC1X0u3l4anrG2qLqYMzw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> data from IntoTheBlock</a>, this figure has reached $52.3 billion, representing its highest value ever.</p>
<p>The data analytics company also noted that with an increasing amount of staked ETH, the Ethereum blockchain is bound to become even more secure, as there will be a corresponding decrease in the risk of the network being taken over by a single entity. </p>

<p>It is worth noting that this surge in staking activity can be linked to the successful launch of the Shapella upgrade. The Shapella upgrade offered a new dimension to ETH staking, as investors can now lock and unlock their assets at will.</p>
<p>This increased flexibility eliminated a substantial portion of risk that has been attributed to ETH staking in the past.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/oJOJDvp1/" alt="Ethereum" width="997" height="529"/></p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-06-30_20-22-39-1-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Did Shiba Inu Price React To 3 Trillion SHIB Investor Accumulation?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/how-did-shiba-inu-price-react-to-3-trillion-shib-investor-accumulation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543808</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) has emerged as a force to be reckoned with in the digital asset landscape despite the lack of significant bullish momentum in the past few weeks. However, recent events have catapulted this canine-inspired cryptocurrency into the spotlight, as an astonishing 3 trillion SHIB tokens were accumulated by investors.  Cryptocurrencies are renowned for their inherent volatility, and Shiba Inu is no exception. The token&#8217;s meteoric popularity and the passionate community backing it have contributed to its roller-coaster journey on the market. But with the recent accumulation of such an astronomical number of SHIB tokens, questions arise about how this development will reverberate throughout the ecosystem and influence its market value. SHIB Token Accumulation And Price Stability A recent SHIB price report highlights a notable surge in SHIB token accumulation by investors, indicating heightened interest and confidence in the cryptocurrency. Related Reading: XDC Network Dominates Weekend Top 100 Roster With 50% Rally With approximately 3 trillion SHIB tokens, amounting to a significant value of over $23 million being bought from exchanges within a two-day period, it appears that investors are actively seeking to bolster their positions in the Shiba Inu ecosystem. Within two days, exchanges sold 3 trillion SHIB coins worth $23 million. Source: Santiment Despite the substantial increase in token accumulation, the Shiba Inu price has not witnessed any significant change, leaving investors somewhat disconcerted. A lack of price movement often results in a scenario where investors adopt a &#8220;wait-and-see&#8221; approach, keeping their holdings static rather than engaging in active trades. This phenomenon, commonly known as &#8220;sitting ducks,&#8221; can hinder the overall liquidity and dynamism of the SHIB market. SHIB feeling the pain on the weekly timeframe. Source: Coingecko Based on the latest data from crypto market tracker Coingecko, the current price of SHIB stands at $0.00000785. Over the past 24 hours, the token has experienced a modest 1.2% rally, which indicates some level of short-term market activity. However, over the last seven days, SHIB has faced a decline of 5.8%, hinting at potential challenges in sustaining positive price momentum. Shibarium’s Potential Meanwhile, Shiba Inu is gearing up to introduce an innovative layer-2 solution known as Shibarium, aiming to revolutionize the process of purchasing SHIB tokens by enhancing cost-effectiveness, efficiency, and speed. Shiba Inu market cap currently at $4.5 billion on the weekend chart: TradingView.com This highly anticipated L2 network has garnered immense excitement within the Shiba Inu community, with investors hailing it as the potential catalyst for propelling SHIB&#8217;s price to unprecedented heights, even setting the ambitious target of reaching $0.01. Related Reading: Chainlink Holds Strong With 19% Rally – More Gains In The Pipeline? The impending launch of Shibarium has ignited a surge of optimism among SHIB enthusiasts, as it promises to address the inherent limitations of the current token acquisition process. By leveraging the power of layer-2 technology, the network intends to streamline transactions and reduce fees, making the buying experience more accessible and seamless for users. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from The Currency Analytics]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB) has emerged as a force to be reckoned with in the digital asset landscape despite the lack of significant bullish momentum in the past few weeks. However, recent events have catapulted this canine-inspired cryptocurrency into the spotlight, as an astonishing 3 trillion SHIB tokens were accumulated by investors. </p>
<p>Cryptocurrencies are renowned for their inherent volatility, and Shiba Inu is no exception. The token&#8217;s meteoric popularity and the passionate community backing it have contributed to its roller-coaster journey on the market.</p>
<p>But with the recent accumulation of such an astronomical number of SHIB tokens, questions arise about how this development will reverberate throughout the ecosystem and influence its market value.</p>
<h2><strong>SHIB Token Accumulation And Price Stability</strong></h2>
<p>A recent <a href="https://www.fxstreet.com/cryptocurrencies/news/shiba-inu-price-fails-to-rally-despite-a-3-trillion-shib-accumulation-from-investors-202307210034" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">SHIB price report</a> highlights a notable surge in SHIB token accumulation by investors, indicating heightened interest and confidence in the cryptocurrency.</p>

<p>With approximately 3 trillion SHIB tokens, amounting to a significant value of over $23 million being bought from exchanges within a two-day period, it appears that investors are actively seeking to bolster their positions in the Shiba Inu ecosystem.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-543812 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-139-860x290.png" alt="" width="860" height="290" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-139-860x290.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-139-460x155.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-139-768x259.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-139-1536x518.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-139-750x253.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-139-1140x384.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-139.png 1920w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>Despite the substantial increase in token accumulation, the Shiba Inu price has not witnessed any significant change, leaving investors somewhat disconcerted. </p>
<p>A lack of price movement often results in a scenario where investors adopt a &#8220;wait-and-see&#8221; approach, keeping their holdings static rather than engaging in active trades. This phenomenon, commonly known as &#8220;sitting ducks,&#8221; can hinder the overall liquidity and dynamism of the SHIB market.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-543810" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-138.png" alt="" width="1131" height="59" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-138.png 1131w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-138-460x24.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-138-860x45.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-138-768x40.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-138-750x39.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1131px) 100vw, 1131px"/></p>

<p>Based on the latest data from crypto market tracker <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/shiba-inu" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Coingecko</a>, the current price of SHIB stands at $0.00000785. Over the past 24 hours, the token has experienced a modest 1.2% rally, which indicates some level of short-term market activity. However, over the last seven days, SHIB has faced a decline of 5.8%, hinting at potential challenges in sustaining positive price momentum.</p>
<h2><strong>Shibarium’s Potential</strong></h2>
<p>Meanwhile, Shiba Inu is gearing up to introduce an innovative layer-2 solution known as Shibarium, aiming to revolutionize the process of purchasing SHIB tokens by enhancing cost-effectiveness, efficiency, and speed. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ni7A5A4C/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>

<p>This highly anticipated L2 network has garnered immense excitement within the Shiba Inu community, with investors hailing it as the potential catalyst for propelling SHIB&#8217;s price to unprecedented heights, even setting the <a href="https://watcher.guru/news/shiba-inu-25-experts-believe-shibarium-will-scale-shib-price-up" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ambitious target of reaching $0.01</a>.</p>



<p>The impending launch of Shibarium has ignited a surge of optimism among SHIB enthusiasts, as it promises to address the inherent limitations of the current token acquisition process. </p>
<p>By leveraging the power of layer-2 technology, the network intends to streamline transactions and reduce fees, making the buying experience more accessible and seamless for users.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from The Currency Analytics</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-140-460x270.png" width="460" height="270" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XDC Network Dominates Weekend Top 100 Roster With 50% Rally</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/xdc-network-dominates-weekend-top-100-roster-with-50-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 09:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XDC Network]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543794</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The price of the XDC Network token, XDC, has increased for a total of five consecutive days and is currently trading at its highest level since April 2022. The token climbed more than 40% from its lowest point this month to its highest level. At the time of writing, XDC was priced at 0.049, up a solid 16.6% in the last 24 hours. But it was the token&#8217;s seven-day performance that was most impressive when it soared 50%, dominating the list of the weekend&#8217;s top 100 coin listing at crypto market tracker Coingecko. XDC Network has experienced an improvement of 97.17% so far this year. The price of the token is rising with a chance of trend reversal, recovering from the trendline to hit new peaks while bumping up against resistance at $0.04 and support at $0.03. It is anticipated that strong support will raise prices and establish new demand regions. XDC shows strong price action in the weekly timeframe. Source: Coingecko The coin has gone over the 50-day and 25-day moving averages on the daily chart, which is positive. The market capitalization of XDC Network&#8217;s token is now $683,630,126 following recent price movement. Most importantly, since this price was the highest on June 1st, XDC is clinging to a key resistance level. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) has risen to an overbought state. Related Reading: Chainlink Holds Strong With 19% Rally – More Gains In The Pipeline? Enterprises can use the XDC Network (XDC), as it is a blockchain that has both public and private components. It&#8217;s the XinFin Network&#8217;s fuel token, allowing for a wide range of blockchain applications. Enterprises wishing to create or extend their infrastructure in a blockchain ecosystem will find the network&#8217;s interoperable smart contracts and frictionless payments appealing. Cryptocurrencies total market cap at $1.16 trillion on the weekend chart: TradingView.com The 2017-founded XDC Network has seen price swings during the course of its existence. It experienced a period of fall after achieving its all-time high of $0.17 during the 2021 bull cycle, before reaching new lows in July 2022. It experienced an upsurge in 2023 and spiked to a high of $0.050 before becoming volatile with sporadic upward and negative swings. XDC is currently challenging the $0.049 level, and an increase of 10% would enable it to test its 2023 highs once more. The ChainIDE for #XDCNetwork is finally LIVE! 🔥 Together, let&#8217;s strengthen the XDC Ecosystem and accelerate innovation. Let&#8217;s #BuildonXDC ! 💪 #Blockchain #XDC https://t.co/XVy7fpGQlt — XinFin (@XinFin_Official) July 19, 2023 Meanwhile, XDC network&#8217;s unexpected linear rise, despite its relative obscurity, happened at the same time as Bitcoin briefly fell below $30. The introduction of Chain IDE was a major factor in this rise. This year, XDC could reach a price of $0.05850 if it maintains its upward trend. However, if the market&#8217;s opinion changes, the price might fall below $0.02993. Related Reading: Dogecoin Sees Positive Price Movement, Bulls Set Crosshair At $0.075 With continued improvements, XDC is poised to shatter its existing price of $0.049. As developers tirelessly work to enhance the network&#8217;s performance, security, and functionality, XDC could attract attention from investors and blockchain enthusiasts alike. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Ledgernomic]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price of the <a href="https://insidebitcoins.com/news/xdc-network-is-top-gainer-on-coinmarketcap-with-21-price-surge-how-high-can-xdc-go" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">XDC Network</a> token, XDC, has increased for a total of five consecutive days and is currently trading at its highest level since April 2022. The token climbed more than 40% from its lowest point this month to its highest level.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, XDC was priced at 0.049, up a solid 16.6% in the last 24 hours. But it was the token&#8217;s seven-day performance that was most impressive when it <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">soared 50%,</a> dominating the list of the weekend&#8217;s top 100 coin listing at crypto market tracker <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Coingecko.</a></p>
<p>XDC Network has experienced an improvement of 97.17% so far this year. The price of the token is rising with a chance of trend reversal, recovering from the trendline to hit new peaks while bumping up against resistance at $0.04 and support at $0.03. It is anticipated that strong support will raise prices and establish new demand regions.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-543796" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XDC.png" alt="" width="1135" height="58" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XDC.png 1135w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XDC-460x24.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XDC-860x44.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XDC-768x39.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XDC-750x38.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1135px) 100vw, 1135px"/></p>

<p>The coin has gone over the 50-day and 25-day moving averages on the daily chart, which is positive. The market capitalization of XDC Network&#8217;s token is now $683,630,126 following recent price movement. Most importantly, since this price was the highest on June 1st, XDC is clinging to a key resistance level. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) has risen to an overbought state.</p>

<p>Enterprises can use the XDC Network (XDC), as it is a blockchain that has both public and private components. It&#8217;s the XinFin Network&#8217;s fuel token, allowing for a wide range of blockchain applications. Enterprises wishing to create or extend their infrastructure in a blockchain ecosystem will find the network&#8217;s interoperable smart contracts and frictionless payments appealing.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/sdPDArsZ/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>

<p>The 2017-founded XDC Network has seen price swings during the course of its existence. It experienced a period of fall after achieving its all-time high of $0.17 during the 2021 bull cycle, before reaching new lows in July 2022.</p>
<p>It experienced an upsurge in 2023 and spiked to a high of $0.050 before becoming volatile with sporadic upward and negative swings. XDC is currently challenging the $0.049 level, and an increase of 10% would enable it to test its 2023 highs once more.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">The ChainIDE for <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/XDCNetwork?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#XDCNetwork</a> is finally LIVE! <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f525.png" alt="🔥" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>Together, let&#8217;s strengthen the XDC Ecosystem and accelerate innovation. Let&#8217;s <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BuildonXDC?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#BuildonXDC</a> ! <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4aa.png" alt="💪" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Blockchain?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Blockchain</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/XDC?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#XDC</a> <a href="https://t.co/XVy7fpGQlt" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/XVy7fpGQlt</a></p>
<p>— XinFin (@XinFin_Official) <a href="https://twitter.com/XinFin_Official/status/1681677677181259776?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 19, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Meanwhile, XDC network&#8217;s unexpected linear rise, despite its relative obscurity, happened at the same time as Bitcoin briefly fell below $30. The introduction of Chain IDE was a major factor in this rise.</p>
<p>This year, XDC could reach a price of $0.05850 if it maintains its upward trend. However, if the market&#8217;s opinion changes, the price might fall below $0.02993.</p>

<p>With continued improvements, XDC is poised to shatter its existing price of $0.049. As developers tirelessly work to enhance the network&#8217;s performance, security, and functionality, XDC could attract attention from investors and blockchain enthusiasts alike.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Ledgernomic</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-137-460x207.png" width="460" height="207" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Becomes 8th-Largest Cryptocurrency After Adding $1 Billion To Market Cap</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/dogecoin-becomes-8th-largest-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 22:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doge price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin performance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543769</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dogecoin continues to cement itself as the largest meme coin by market cap, displaying signs of renewed enthusiasm every so often. This week, the meme-inspired cryptocurrency added over $1 billion to its market cap, making it the 8th-largest crypto. This was a result of Dogecoin’s surge of over 10%, boosting its market cap to more than $10 billion in a matter of hours. Dogecoin Pushes Solana To Number 9 Dogecoin has come a long way since its creation as a joke. Fueled by the hype on social media, the meme cryptocurrency has skyrocketed up the rankings to become the 8th-largest cryptocurrency by market cap. The price of Dogecoin recently crossed over the $0.070 resistance level to reach $0.076. As a result, more than $1 billion was added to its market cap, surging from $9.67 billion to $10.66 billion.  Related Reading: Coinbase Exchange Tells Borrowers That They Have Four Months To Pay Back Although its price has now dropped to $0.074 at the time of writing, Dogecoin still has a $10.35 billion market cap, pushing Solana down to the number 9 spot. On the other hand, Solana is down by 7% in a 7-day timeframe and has lost more than $1.4 billion in market cap. What’s Pushing The Price? A big part of Dogecoin’s past success has come mostly from social media hype and a few influential people and groups hyping it up. A major influence is billionaire Elon Musk. Ever since Musk began tweeting about the meme coin, Dogecoin has gained more attention from crypto investors and his tweets praising the crypto have led to major spikes in interest and price.  DOGE price retraces to $0.73 following 10% surge &#124; Source: DOGEUSD on Tradingview.com The latest spike in the price of Dogecoin seems to have come from rumors of Tesla retaining the cryptocurrency in its payment page source code. Dogecoin is the second cryptocurrency to be accepted by the automobile manufacturer after Tesla added Bitcoin as an option back in 2021. However, Tesla has since discontinued the option to pay with Bitcoin and has deleted the option in the source code of its payment page.   At present, Tesla has deleted &#8220;bitcoin&#8221; in the source code of its payment page, but still retains &#8220;dogecoin&#8221;. pic.twitter.com/BQrRtuTN8Z — Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) July 21, 2023 DOGE Price Prediction Dogecoin (DOGE) is currently trading at $0.07378, ranging between $0.065 and $0.075 for the past week. If the $0.075 resistance is broken through, we could see DOGE rise to as high as its February price of $0.096.  Interestingly, the asset has bounced off the $0.060 support level multiple times since August 2022, making it a significant support for the meme coin. So a break below $0.060 could see DOGE fall to its lowest point in over a year. Related Reading: Ethereum Daily Users Plunge Amid Declining Network Revenue While Dogecoin lacks the scarcity of Bitcoin or the smart contract capabilities of Ethereum, it’s won over an enthusiastic community of supporters and has become relatively stable over the years. However, Dogecoin is still a very volatile investment, and its value is largely based on social media hype rather than real-world utility. Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dogecoin continues to cement itself as the largest meme coin by market cap, displaying signs of renewed enthusiasm every so often. This week, the meme-inspired cryptocurrency added over $1 billion to its market cap, making it the 8th-largest crypto. This was a result of Dogecoin’s surge of over 10%, boosting its market cap to more than $10 billion in a matter of hours.</p>
<h2>Dogecoin Pushes Solana To Number 9</h2>
<p>Dogecoin has come a long way since its creation as a joke. Fueled by the hype on social media, the meme cryptocurrency has skyrocketed up the rankings to become the 8th-largest cryptocurrency by market cap. The price of Dogecoin recently crossed over the $0.070 resistance level to reach $0.076. As a result, more than $1 billion was added to its market cap, surging from $9.67 billion to $10.66 billion. </p>

<p>Although its price has now dropped to $0.074 at the time of writing, Dogecoin still has a $10.35 billion market cap, pushing Solana down to the number 9 spot. On the other hand, Solana is down by 7% in a 7-day timeframe and has lost more than $1.4 billion in market cap.</p>
<h2>What’s Pushing The Price?</h2>
<p>A big part of Dogecoin’s past success has come mostly from social media hype and a few influential people and groups hyping it up. A major influence is billionaire Elon Musk. Ever since Musk began tweeting about the meme coin, Dogecoin has gained more attention from crypto investors and his tweets praising the crypto have led to major spikes in interest and price. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/vNnaE6CI/" alt="Dogecoin (DOGE) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>

<p>The latest spike in the price of Dogecoin seems to have come from rumors of Tesla retaining the cryptocurrency in its payment page source code. Dogecoin is the second cryptocurrency to be accepted by the automobile manufacturer after Tesla added Bitcoin as an option back in 2021. However, Tesla has since discontinued the option to pay with Bitcoin and has deleted the option in the source code of its payment page.  </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">At present, Tesla has deleted &#8220;bitcoin&#8221; in the source code of its payment page, but still retains &#8220;dogecoin&#8221;. <a href="https://t.co/BQrRtuTN8Z" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/BQrRtuTN8Z</a></p>
<p>— Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1682300362563411968?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 21, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
DOGE Price Prediction
<p>Dogecoin (DOGE) is currently trading at $0.07378, ranging between $0.065 and $0.075 for the past week. If the $0.075 resistance is broken through, we could see DOGE rise to as high as its February price of $0.096. </p>
<p>Interestingly, the asset has bounced off the $0.060 support level multiple times since August 2022, making it a significant support for the meme coin. So a break below $0.060 could see DOGE fall to its lowest point in over a year.</p>

<p>While Dogecoin lacks the scarcity of Bitcoin or the smart contract capabilities of Ethereum, it’s won over an enthusiastic community of supporters and has become relatively stable over the years. However, Dogecoin is still a very volatile investment, and its value is largely based on social media hype rather than real-world utility.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-950107050-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitfinex Hackers Surrender: Couple Agrees to Forfeit 120,000 Bitcoin in Plea Deal</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitfinex-hackers-surrender-couple-agrees-to-forfeit-120000-bitcoin-in-plea-deal/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 20:03:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[seized bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543782</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[An American couple accused of laundering billions of dollars worth of Bitcoin stolen from the 2016 hacking of virtual currency exchange Bitfinex has entered into a plea agreement, according to court records reported by Reuters.  Heather Morgan, who used the hip-hop alias &#8220;Razzlekhan&#8221; to push her music online, and her husband Ilya Lichtenstein were arrested earlier this year and are set to appear for a plea hearing on August 3 before Senior Judge Colleen Kollar-Kotelly in Washington. Laundered Bitcoin Exceeds $4.5 Billion Ilya Lichtenstein and Heather Morgan, both residents of New York, are facing charges for allegedly conspiring to launder the proceeds of 119,754 Bitcoin (BTC) that were stolen from Bitfinex in 2016.  After the hacker breached the platform&#8217;s systems and initiated over 2,000 unauthorized transactions, the stolen Bitcoin was transferred to a digital wallet controlled by Lichtenstein.  Over five years, approximately 25,000 of those stolen Bitcoin were moved out of Lichtenstein&#8217;s wallet via a complex money-laundering process, which ultimately resulted in some of the stolen funds being deposited into financial accounts controlled by the couple. Related Reading: Riding The Ripple Effect: What’s Next For Stellar Lumens (XLM)? More than 94,000 Bitcoin, the remainder of the stolen funds, were left in the wallet used to receive and store the illegal proceeds from the hack.  However, after executing court-authorized search warrants for online accounts controlled by Lichtenstein and Morgan, special agents accessed files in an online account controlled by Lichtenstein.  These files contained the private keys required to access the digital wallet that directly received the funds stolen from Bitfinex, enabling law enforcement to lawfully seize and recover over 94,000 Bitcoin, valued at over $3.6 billion at the time of seizure. According to the criminal complaint, Lichtenstein and Morgan used various sophisticated laundering techniques, including setting up online accounts using fictitious identities, automating transactions using computer programs, depositing the stolen funds into accounts at virtual currency exchanges and darknet markets, converting Bitcoin to other forms of virtual currency, and using U.S.-based business accounts to legitimize their banking activity. Related Reading: Ethereum Daily Users Plunge Amid Declining Network Revenue While Bitcoin was worth $71 million at the time of the hack, it had appreciated to over $4.5 billion at the time of their arrest earlier this year. Prosecutors are now seeking to have the pair forfeit assets worth around $3 billion, including cash from bank accounts and tokens from crypto wallets. Additionally, prosecutors are seeking to have the couple forfeit gold coins that were &#8220;excavated and recovered by law enforcement&#8221; from an undisclosed location in California.  At present, Bitcoin remains the largest cryptocurrency in the market, based on trading volume and capitalization. It is currently trading at $29,860, which is relatively stable compared to the previous 24 hours, with a slight increase of 0.5%. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An American couple accused of laundering billions of dollars worth of Bitcoin stolen from the 2016 hacking of virtual currency exchange Bitfinex has entered into a plea agreement, according to court records <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-couple-accused-laundering-crypto-bitfinex-hack-reach-plea-deal-2023-07-21/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reported </a>by Reuters. </p>
<p>Heather Morgan, who used the hip-hop alias &#8220;Razzlekhan&#8221; to push her music online, and her husband Ilya Lichtenstein were arrested earlier this year and are set to appear for a plea hearing on August 3 before Senior Judge Colleen Kollar-Kotelly in Washington.</p>
<h2>Laundered Bitcoin Exceeds $4.5 Billion</h2>
<p>Ilya Lichtenstein and Heather Morgan, both residents of New York, are facing charges for allegedly conspiring to launder the proceeds of 119,754 Bitcoin (BTC) that were stolen from Bitfinex in 2016. </p>
<p>After the hacker breached the platform&#8217;s systems and initiated over 2,000 unauthorized transactions, the stolen Bitcoin was transferred to a digital wallet controlled by Lichtenstein. </p>
<p>Over five years, approximately 25,000 of those stolen Bitcoin were moved out of Lichtenstein&#8217;s wallet via a complex money-laundering process, which ultimately resulted in some of the stolen funds being deposited into financial accounts controlled by the couple.</p>

<p>More than 94,000 Bitcoin, the remainder of the stolen funds, were left in the wallet used to receive and store the illegal proceeds from the hack. </p>
<p>However, after executing court-authorized search warrants for online accounts controlled by Lichtenstein and Morgan, special agents accessed files in an online account controlled by Lichtenstein. </p>
<p>These files contained the private keys required to access the digital wallet that directly received the funds stolen from Bitfinex, enabling law enforcement to lawfully seize and recover over 94,000 Bitcoin, valued at over $3.6 billion at the time of seizure.</p>
<p>According to the criminal <a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/pr/two-arrested-alleged-conspiracy-launder-45-billion-stolen-cryptocurrency" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">complaint</a>, Lichtenstein and Morgan used various sophisticated laundering techniques, including setting up online accounts using fictitious identities, automating transactions using computer programs, depositing the stolen funds into accounts at virtual currency exchanges and darknet markets, converting Bitcoin to other forms of virtual currency, and using U.S.-based business accounts to legitimize their banking activity.</p>

<p>While Bitcoin was worth $71 million at the time of the hack, it had appreciated to over $4.5 billion at the time of their arrest earlier this year. Prosecutors are now seeking to have the pair forfeit assets worth around $3 billion, including cash from bank accounts and tokens from crypto wallets.</p>
<p>Additionally, prosecutors are seeking to have the couple forfeit gold coins that were &#8220;excavated and recovered by law enforcement&#8221; from an undisclosed location in California. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/GyVV2zdS/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>At present, Bitcoin remains the largest cryptocurrency in the market, based on trading volume and capitalization. It is currently trading at $29,860, which is relatively stable compared to the previous 24 hours, with a slight increase of 0.5%.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/jon-tyson-93G1WoVzS5A-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>South Park&#8217;s Kenny Powers Up: Meme Coin Raises Over $400,000 In Market Cap On Presale</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/south-parks-kenny-powers-up-meme-coin-raises-over-400000-in-presale/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 20:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[burn kenny]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543762</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[South Park&#8217;s Kenny McCormick may be perpetually doomed, but his latest venture in the world of cryptocurrency is anything but. Burn Kenny, the new hilariously irreverent meme coin has raised over $400,000 in market cap on its presale, leaving fans excited for what&#8217;s to come.  Inspired by the beloved South Park character, Burn Kenny is a super deflationary token that&#8217;s designed to do one thing &#8211; get burnt. How Burn Kenny&#8217;s Meme Coin Token Burning Could Benefit Investors Burn Kenny&#8217;s token burning process is designed to gradually decrease the total supply of the token, creating scarcity and potentially increasing the value of the remaining tokens. The process works by gradually burning a portion of the total token supply over a set period until a predetermined percentage of the tokens have been destroyed. In Burn Kenny&#8217;s case, 30% of the total token supply will be burnt over three days, starting 24 hours after the token&#8217;s initial listing. This will be done by sending a portion of the tokens straight to the &#8220;fiery depths of token hell,&#8221; effectively removing them from circulation. The burning process will continue at a rate of 10% every 24 hours until the 30% burn target is reached. Related Reading: Ethereum Daily Users Plunge Amid Declining Network Revenue The value of the remaining tokens could potentially increase as a result of the token-burning process, as there will be fewer tokens in circulation.  This creates a situation of increased demand for the remaining tokens, which could drive up their price. With a total token supply of 6,666,666,666, an arbitrary number Burn Kenny&#8217;s tokenomics are as unique as the character himself.  The presale accounts for 40% of the total token supply, while another 30% will be thrown into the Uniswap liquidity pool, locked for three months. The remaining 30% will be sent straight to the fiery depths of token hell, gradually burnt over three days, starting 24 hours after listing. By the end of Q3 2023, the team behind Burn Kenny aims to have fulfilled all their roadmap goals.  In recent updates, they have announced that they have deployed the contract, paired and locked Liquidity Pool (LP), and updated DexTools with hot pairs ready for trading. These preparations are all essential steps in ensuring a smooth and successful launch for Burn Kenny. Deploying the contract and pairing and locking LP are key technical components of the launch process. The contract deployment involves setting up the smart contract that will govern the token and ensure its functionality.  In addition to these technical preparations, the Burn Kenny team has also been working to build hype and generate excitement for the launch. They have noted that Ethereum is trending and that DexTools is ready for hot pairs, which could help to drive interest and increase demand for the token. Related Reading: New Crypto Bill Demands SEC And CFTC To Draft Rules For Trading Platforms Burn Kenny&#8217;s irreverent approach to cryptocurrency and its use of the South Park character Kenny McCormick as its mascot give it a distinct personality and make it stand out from other meme coins. Of course, like any meme coin, Burn Kenny&#8217;s success will ultimately depend on the strength of its community and the demand for its tokens. However, its unique concept and approach to the meme coin genre could potentially make it a standout project in the crowded world of cryptocurrency. Featured image from Burn Kenny on Twitter, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>South Park&#8217;s Kenny McCormick may be perpetually doomed, but his latest venture in the world of cryptocurrency is anything but. <a href="https://burnkenny.vip/assets/documents/whitepaper.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Burn Kenny</a>, the new hilariously irreverent meme coin has raised over $400,000 in market cap on its presale, leaving fans excited for what&#8217;s to come. </p>
<p>Inspired by the beloved South Park character, Burn Kenny is a super deflationary token that&#8217;s designed to do one thing &#8211; get burnt.</p>
<h2>How Burn Kenny&#8217;s Meme Coin Token Burning Could Benefit Investors</h2>
<p>Burn Kenny&#8217;s token burning process is designed to gradually decrease the total supply of the token, creating scarcity and potentially increasing the value of the remaining tokens. The process works by gradually burning a portion of the total token supply over a set period until a predetermined percentage of the tokens have been destroyed.</p>
<p>In Burn Kenny&#8217;s case, 30% of the total token supply will be burnt over three days, starting 24 hours after the token&#8217;s initial listing. This will be done by sending a portion of the tokens straight to the &#8220;fiery depths of token hell,&#8221; effectively removing them from circulation. The burning process will continue at a rate of 10% every 24 hours until the 30% burn target is reached.</p>

<p>The value of the remaining tokens could potentially increase as a result of the token-burning process, as there will be fewer tokens in circulation.  This creates a situation of increased demand for the remaining tokens, which could drive up their price.</p>
<p>With a total token supply of 6,666,666,666, an arbitrary number Burn Kenny&#8217;s tokenomics are as unique as the character himself. </p>
<p>The presale accounts for 40% of the total token supply, while another 30% will be thrown into the Uniswap liquidity pool, locked for three months. The remaining 30% will be sent straight to the fiery depths of token hell, gradually burnt over three days, starting 24 hours after listing. By the end of Q3 2023, the team behind Burn Kenny aims to have fulfilled all their roadmap goals. </p>
<p>In recent <a href="https://twitter.com/BurnKennyCoin/status/1682448340284502016?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">updates</a>, they have announced that they have deployed the contract, paired and locked Liquidity Pool (LP), and updated DexTools with hot pairs ready for trading. These preparations are all essential steps in ensuring a smooth and successful launch for Burn Kenny.</p>
<p>Deploying the contract and pairing and locking LP are key technical components of the launch process. The contract deployment involves setting up the smart contract that will govern the token and ensure its functionality. </p>
<p>In addition to these technical preparations, the Burn Kenny team has also been working to build hype and generate excitement for the launch. They have noted that Ethereum is trending and that DexTools is ready for hot pairs, which could help to drive interest and increase demand for the token.</p>

<p>Burn Kenny&#8217;s irreverent approach to cryptocurrency and its use of the South Park character Kenny McCormick as its mascot give it a distinct personality and make it stand out from other meme coins.</p>
<p>Of course, like any meme coin, Burn Kenny&#8217;s success will ultimately depend on the strength of its community and the demand for its tokens. However, its unique concept and approach to the meme coin genre could potentially make it a standout project in the crowded world of cryptocurrency.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/FClaiMuB/" alt="meme coin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from Burn Kenny on Twitter, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1fzSBZX0AAh7rx-460x460.jpg" width="460" height="460" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>We gave ChatGPT $20,000 to invest and this is how it spent it</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/research/we-gave-chatgpt-20000-to-invest-and-this-is-how-it-spent-it/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[newsbtc]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 18:53:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Research]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543760</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[2023 has seen the rise of AI, with programs such as Bard and ChatGPT offering answers to any and all queries, ranging from what the weather is to writing college essays. We all know AI is based on machine learning, but how much can we trust the advice it gives? We wanted to find out if we can trust these programs, so we gave ChatGPT a budget of $10k to invest in stocks and $10k to invest in cryptocurrencies, subsequently following the advice provided.  Before following this advice, it is worth noting ChatGPT states the information given is not financial advice, and consulting with a financial advisor is always recommended. ChatGPT also suggests doing your own research to make more informed decisions regarding which stocks are worth investing in. The program provides further advice for cryptocurrencies, stressing the volatility of cryptocurrencies and the importance of considering your financial situation when making investment decisions. Regularly reviewing your portfolio based on market conditions and investment performance is also advised. The Breakdown It took a little bit of training, but we eventually got ChatGPT to suggest exactly how much of my budget to invest in each stock/ coin, the breakdown is as follows: &#160; Stock Percentage Total Invested Apple Inc 10% $1000 Amazon.com Inc 10% $1000 Microsoft Corporation 9% $900 Alphabet Inc 9% $900 NVIDIA Corporation 8% $800 Tesla Inc 7% $700 NextEra Energy, Inc 7% $700 Amgen Inc 4% $400 Johnson &#38; Johnson 4% $400 Moderna, Inc 4% $400 Pfizer Inc 4% $400 Gilead Sciences, Inc 3% $300 PayPal Holdings Inc 3% $300 General Motors Company 3% $300 NIO Inc 3% $300 First Solar, Inc 2% $200 Enphase Energy, Inc 2% $200 Shopify Inc 2% $200 Vestas Wind Systems A/S 2% $200 MercadoLibre, Inc 1% $100 Johnson Controls International plc 1% $100 Square, Inc 1% $100 Rivian 1% $100 Coin Percentage Total Invested Bitcoin 20% $2000 Ethereum 20% $2000 Binance Coin 10% $1000 Litecoin 10% $1000 Solana 10% $1000 Polkadot 10% $1000 Ripple 10% $1000 Cardano 10% $1000 The suggested stocks are rather expected; higher investments in stable stocks and a lower investment into stocks with more fluctuations. The cryptocurrency investments are slightly more interesting, however, as, of the 1000+ coins currently on the market, it’s given me a short list of eight to invest in.  &#160; The Experiment The first week The experiment started off on unsteady legs with stocks ending with a profit of $159 and cryptocurrencies making a loss of $64 after the first day. Five of the eight cryptocurrencies invested in made a loss, with Binance Coin performing the worst, with our $956 investment suffering a $44 decrease. Stocks increased throughout the week but decreased right at the end ($25 lower compared to the previous day), making the final weekly total $10,220. This is a $220 increase from the initial investment, a solid start for our experiment. Our crypto investment did not perform nearly as well in the first week, with only three  days ending in a profit from the initial $10k investment. The fourth day was the worst of our whole experiment, with an ending total of $9,741. Only two of the coins invested turned a profit on that day, with Ethereum making a loss of $114 from the initial investment. Our week ended on a slightly more positive note with a final total of $10,021, a $21 increase from the initial investment. &#160; The second week During the second week,  the total reached $10,643 by the end of the second day. This is $423 more than the total at the end of week one. However, this high was short-lived as the final value decreased for the remainder of the week, ending on $10,492. Whilst $272 more than the final value of the first week, it’s $151 less than the second day’s total. After a shaky beginning, our cryptocurrency investment far outperformed our stocks investment in the second week, peaking at $11,118 on the fourth day. This then decreased on the fifth and final day, making the final value of the week $10,987, a $967 increase from the first week. &#160; The third week The start of the third week saw more decreases for our stocks investments. Nine of our 23 investments decreased on the second and third day. The latter half of the week performed better, increasing to $10,559 in total by the final day. Our cryptocurrency investment performed similarly, with a decrease at the start of the week and an increase towards the end. The final value dropped to $10,609 on the fourth day, then increased dramatically to $10,974 by the end of the fifth. The final value of the week was $11,402, a $415 increase from week two. &#160; The final week The final week of our stock investments was a disappointment with the overall value decreasing slightly for a final figure of $10,587. This is an overall increase of $587 from our initial investment, which is an overall ROI of 6%. On the first day of the final week, our crypto investments increased by $314 to $11,719 in total, this is the highest end of day total we reached in our experiment. This was the high point, however, as we decreased throughout the rest of the week, ending with a final total of $11,359, a 14% ROI. &#160; Overall Performance Stocks Whilst we ended up turning a profit from our stock investments, there were ten investments which made a loss from the initial investment, almost 45% of investments made. The worst-performing stock was Pfizer inc. which decreased from the third week and ended up with an ROI of -10%. This was after the company announced they were discontinuing the development of the type 2 diabetes and obesity candidate lotiglipron over safety concerns.  Rivian proved the best-performing stock, with an ROI of 88%, initially priced at $14.03 per stock it increased to $25.51 over the month. This is after the company announced that Q2 2023 was the best financial quarter in the company’s history. &#160; Cryptocurrency On the other hand, we had much more luck with our crypto investments, with only one of the investments returning a loss, making up 13% of the initial investment. This was Ripple (XRP), there are several reasons for this, one being that the transaction volume of XRP is down 90%. The coin with the highest ROI is Solana (SOL) with an ROI of 39%, which is a $389 increase. SOL is considered a relatively stable coin with strong community backing, making it a good coin to invest in. Hits or Misses? Whilst it’s possible Bitcoin was suggested as one of the largest investments because it’s the biggest cryptocurrency. It was actually a great crypto to invest in as the price went from $26k to $30k, this was due to news that a new, safer, crypto exchange launched, receiving investments from Invesco and WisdomTree. There is one stock we feel could have been missed from ChatGPT’s suggestions, this is Meta, the company who owns Facebook and Instagram. They’ve recently released a new app as part of Instagram called Threads, a Twitter competitor. It was released at the perfect time, after news that Twitter was limiting the number of Tweets its users could see.  This isn’t one of the stocks ChatGPT suggested investing in, so we wanted to see what could have happened had ChatGPT suggested investing in META stocks. Using historical data for the last month, we calculated that if we had invested $1,000, we would have $1,100 by the end of the experiment. This is more than we earned from the $1,000 we invested in Amazon and Apple stocks. Methodology We started by asking ChatGPT for stock market opportunities. Initially, it gave a generic answer of the types of industries which should be invested in and why. From these industries, we asked it to recommend specific companies from each. We then sent the list of all the suggested stocks back to it and asked for a weighting of a $10k investment. We found that one of the stocks suggested, Waymo, is not a publicly traded business, we had to go back to ChatGPT and ask for it to remove this stock and add a new one. It was replaced by Johnson Controls International plc. It was a much easier process to get answers about which cryptocurrencies to invest in. As ChatGPT gave us an initial list of coins, and when asked how much to invest in each it gave a general strategy for investing in cryptocurrency. 40-50% should come from Bitcoin and Ethereum combined and 10-20% for each of the remaining coins. We decided to put 20% into Bitcoin, 20% into Ethereum and 10% for the remaining coins.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>2023 has seen the rise of AI, with programs such as Bard and ChatGPT offering answers to any and all queries, ranging from what the weather is to writing college essays. We all know AI is based on machine learning, but how much can we trust the advice it gives? We wanted to find out if we can trust these programs, so we gave ChatGPT a budget of $10k to invest in stocks and $10k to invest in cryptocurrencies, subsequently following the advice provided. </p>
<p>Before following this advice, it is worth noting ChatGPT states the information given is not financial advice, and consulting with a financial advisor is always recommended. ChatGPT also suggests doing your own research to make more informed decisions regarding which stocks are worth investing in.</p>
<p>The program provides further advice for cryptocurrencies, stressing the volatility of cryptocurrencies and the importance of considering your financial situation when making investment decisions. Regularly reviewing your portfolio based on market conditions and investment performance is also advised.</p>
<h2><b>The Breakdown</b></h2>
<p>It took a little bit of training, but we eventually got ChatGPT to suggest exactly how much of my budget to invest in each stock/ coin, the breakdown is as follows:</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<table style="height: 1468px" width="800" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td valign="top"><b>Stock</b></td>
<td valign="top"><b>Percentage</b></td>
<td valign="top"><b>Total Invested</b></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top">Apple Inc</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">10%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$1000</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top">Amazon.com Inc</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">10%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$1000</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top">Microsoft Corporation</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">9%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$900</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top">Alphabet Inc</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">9%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$900</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top">NVIDIA Corporation</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">8%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$800</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top">Tesla Inc</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">7%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$700</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top">NextEra Energy, Inc</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">7%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$700</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top">Amgen Inc</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">4%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$400</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top">Johnson &amp; Johnson</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">4%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$400</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top">Moderna, Inc</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">4%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$400</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top">Pfizer Inc</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">4%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$400</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top">Gilead Sciences, Inc</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">3%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$300</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top">PayPal Holdings Inc</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">3%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$300</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top">General Motors Company</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">3%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$300</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top">NIO Inc</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">3%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$300</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top">First Solar, Inc</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">2%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$200</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top">Enphase Energy, Inc</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">2%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$200</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top">Shopify Inc</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">2%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$200</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top">Vestas Wind Systems A/S</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">2%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$200</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top">MercadoLibre, Inc</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">1%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$100</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top">Johnson Controls International plc</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">1%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$100</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top">Square, Inc</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">1%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$100</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top">Rivian</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">1%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$100</p>
</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<table cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td valign="top"><b>Coin</b></td>
<td valign="top"><b>Percentage</b></td>
<td valign="top"><b>Total Invested</b></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="bottom">Bitcoin</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">20%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$2000</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="bottom">Ethereum</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">20%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$2000</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="bottom">Binance Coin</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">10%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$1000</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="bottom">Litecoin </td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">10%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$1000</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="bottom">Solana</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">10%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$1000</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="bottom">Polkadot</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">10%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$1000</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="bottom">Ripple</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">10%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$1000</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="bottom">Cardano </td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">10%</p>
</td>
<td valign="bottom">
<p align="right">$1000</p>
</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p>The suggested stocks are rather expected; higher investments in stable stocks and a lower investment into stocks with more fluctuations. The cryptocurrency investments are slightly more interesting, however, as, of the 1000+ coins currently on the market, it’s given me a short list of eight to invest in. </p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2><b>The Experiment</b></h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-543767 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Stocks-crypto-line-us-860x801.png" alt="" width="860" height="801" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Stocks-crypto-line-us-860x801.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Stocks-crypto-line-us-460x428.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Stocks-crypto-line-us-768x715.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Stocks-crypto-line-us-1536x1430.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Stocks-crypto-line-us-2048x1906.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Stocks-crypto-line-us-750x698.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Stocks-crypto-line-us-1140x1061.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>
The first week
<p>The experiment started off on unsteady legs with stocks ending with a profit of $159 and cryptocurrencies making a loss of $64 after the first day. Five of the eight cryptocurrencies invested in made a loss, with Binance Coin performing the worst, with our $956 investment suffering a $44 decrease.</p>
<p>Stocks increased throughout the week but decreased right at the end ($25 lower compared to the previous day), making the final weekly total $10,220. This is a $220 increase from the initial investment, a solid start for our experiment.</p>
<p>Our crypto investment did not perform nearly as well in the first week, with only three  days ending in a profit from the initial $10k investment. The fourth day was the worst of our whole experiment, with an ending total of $9,741. Only two of the coins invested turned a profit on that day, with Ethereum making a loss of $114 from the initial investment. Our week ended on a slightly more positive note with a final total of $10,021, a $21 increase from the initial investment.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
The second week
<p>During the second week,  the total reached $10,643 by the end of the second day. This is $423 more than the total at the end of week one. However, this high was short-lived as the final value decreased for the remainder of the week, ending on $10,492. Whilst $272 more than the final value of the first week, it’s $151 less than the second day’s total.</p>
<p>After a shaky beginning, our cryptocurrency investment far outperformed our stocks investment in the second week, peaking at $11,118 on the fourth day. This then decreased on the fifth and final day, making the final value of the week $10,987, a $967 increase from the first week.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
The third week
<p>The start of the third week saw more decreases for our stocks investments. Nine of our 23 investments decreased on the second and third day. The latter half of the week performed better, increasing to $10,559 in total by the final day.</p>
<p>Our cryptocurrency investment performed similarly, with a decrease at the start of the week and an increase towards the end. The final value dropped to $10,609 on the fourth day, then increased dramatically to $10,974 by the end of the fifth. The final value of the week was $11,402, a $415 increase from week two.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
The final week
<p>The final week of our stock investments was a disappointment with the overall value decreasing slightly for a final figure of $10,587. This is an overall increase of $587 from our initial investment, which is an overall ROI of 6%.</p>
<p>On the first day of the final week, our crypto investments increased by $314 to $11,719 in total, this is the highest end of day total we reached in our experiment. This was the high point, however, as we decreased throughout the rest of the week, ending with a final total of $11,359, a 14% ROI.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2><b>Overall Performance</b></h2>
Stocks
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-543770 size-jnews-featured-1140" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AI-stock-breakdown-1140x2020.png" alt="" width="1140" height="2020" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AI-stock-breakdown-1140x2020.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AI-stock-breakdown-260x460.png 260w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AI-stock-breakdown-485x860.png 485w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AI-stock-breakdown-768x1361.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AI-stock-breakdown-867x1536.png 867w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AI-stock-breakdown-1156x2048.png 1156w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AI-stock-breakdown-750x1329.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1140px) 100vw, 1140px"/></p>
<p>Whilst we ended up turning a profit from our stock investments, there were ten investments which made a loss from the initial investment, almost 45% of investments made. The worst-performing stock was Pfizer inc. which decreased from the third week and ended up with an ROI of -10%. This was after the company announced they were <a href="https://www.fool.com/investing/2023/06/26/why-pfizer-stock-is-tanking-today/" rel="nofollow">discontinuing the development</a> of the type 2 diabetes and obesity candidate lotiglipron over safety concerns. </p>
<p>Rivian proved the best-performing stock, with an ROI of 88%, initially priced at $14.03 per stock it increased to $25.51 over the month. This is after the <a href="https://insideevs.com/news/676385/rivian-stock-up-almost-90-percent-past-two-weeks/" rel="nofollow">company announced</a> that Q2 2023 was the best financial quarter in the company’s history.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Cryptocurrency
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-543771 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ai-crypto-breakdown-860x818.png" alt="" width="860" height="818" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ai-crypto-breakdown-860x818.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ai-crypto-breakdown-460x438.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ai-crypto-breakdown-768x731.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ai-crypto-breakdown-1536x1462.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ai-crypto-breakdown-2048x1949.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ai-crypto-breakdown-750x714.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ai-crypto-breakdown-1140x1085.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>
<p>On the other hand, we had much more luck with our crypto investments, with only one of the investments returning a loss, making up 13% of the initial investment. This was Ripple (XRP), there are several reasons for this, one being that the transaction volume of XRP is <a href="https://beincrypto.com/xrp-price-remains-stagnant-whale-investment/" rel="nofollow">down 90%.</a></p>
<p>The coin with the highest ROI is Solana (SOL) with an ROI of 39%, which is a $389 increase. SOL is considered a relatively stable coin with strong community backing, making it a good coin to invest in.</p>
<h2><b>Hits or Misses?</b></h2>
<p>Whilst it’s possible Bitcoin was suggested as one of the largest investments because it’s the biggest cryptocurrency. It was actually a great crypto to invest in as the price went from $26k to $30k, this was due to news that a <a href="https://fortune.com/crypto/2023/06/21/bitcoin-30000-highest-price-in-more-than-a-year-spot-etfs/" rel="nofollow">new, safer, crypto exchange</a> launched, receiving investments from Invesco and WisdomTree.</p>
<p>There is one stock we feel could have been missed from ChatGPT’s suggestions, this is Meta, the company who owns Facebook and Instagram. They’ve recently released a new app as part of Instagram called Threads, a Twitter competitor. It was released at the perfect time, after news that <a href="https://help.twitter.com/en/rules-and-policies/twitter-limits" rel="nofollow">Twitter was limiting</a> the number of Tweets its users could see. </p>
<p>This isn’t one of the stocks ChatGPT suggested investing in, so we wanted to see what could have happened had ChatGPT suggested investing in META stocks. Using historical data for the last month, we calculated that if we had invested $1,000, we would have $1,100 by the end of the experiment. This is more than we earned from the $1,000 we invested in Amazon and Apple stocks.</p>
<h2><b>Methodology</b></h2>
<p>We started by asking ChatGPT for stock market opportunities. Initially, it gave a generic answer of the types of industries which should be invested in and why. From these industries, we asked it to recommend specific companies from each. We then sent the list of all the suggested stocks back to it and asked for a weighting of a $10k investment.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-543773 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image4-37-860x568.png" alt="" width="860" height="568" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image4-37-860x568.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image4-37-460x304.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image4-37-768x507.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image4-37-750x495.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image4-37-1140x753.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image4-37.png 1379w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>
<p>We found that one of the stocks suggested, Waymo, is not a publicly traded business, we had to go back to ChatGPT and ask for it to remove this stock and add a new one. It was replaced by Johnson Controls International plc.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-large wp-image-543775" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image5-39-860x571.png" alt="" width="860" height="571" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image5-39-860x571.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image5-39-460x306.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image5-39-768x510.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image5-39-750x498.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image5-39-1140x758.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image5-39.png 1380w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>
<p>It was a much easier process to get answers about which cryptocurrencies to invest in. As ChatGPT gave us an initial list of coins, and when asked how much to invest in each it gave a general strategy for investing in cryptocurrency. 40-50% should come from Bitcoin and Ethereum combined and 10-20% for each of the remaining coins. We decided to put 20% into Bitcoin, 20% into Ethereum and 10% for the remaining coins.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Header-Image-460x307.jpeg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
