<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 23:02:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin, XRP, &#038; Ethereum: Three Top Coins On Brink Of Golden Cross</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-xrp-ethereum-three-top-coins-golden-cross/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 23:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpeth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543431</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin, XRP, and Ethereum — three of the cryptocurrency market’s most dominant coins — are about to simultaneously form a 3-day golden cross. This signal is rare, happening only a handful of times in the past in each individual asset. However, never have all three of these major cryptocurrencies triggered this signal all at the same time. What exactly does this mean, and what are the results of the 3-day golden cross? Bitcoin, XRP, &#38; Ethereum Lead Market Recovery The crypto market outlook is a lot less bleak than it was just weeks ago, between BlackRock and other institutions seeking to launch Bitcoin ETFs and the massive win for XRP and Ripple against the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Related Reading: Perfect Storm: Why Bitcoin &#38; Crypto Are Poised For A Dramatic Recovery Even the technical environment is starting to show signs of a possible uptrend brewing. Notably, several top cryptocurrencies are inching closer to a golden cross on the 3-day timeframe, which has only occurred a handful of times in the past. This is about to happen in Bitcoin, Ethereum, and XRP, simultaneously, for the first time in their history. Previously, these signals arrived at different phases of previous bull markets. It wasn’t until all three coins golden crossed that a stronger rally began. Three top crypto assets — #Bitcoin, Ethereum, and #XRP — are on the brink of a golden cross on the 3-day timeframe All three firing at the same time has never happened before It will also be the third in history for BTC and XRP, second ever for Ether pic.twitter.com/bzVfK3ZpBp — Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221; (@tonythebullBTC) July 19, 2023 What Is A Golden Cross In Crypto? A golden cross occurs when a higher timeframe moving average, typically a 200-period MA, crosses above a lower timeframe moving average, usually a 50-period MA, from below. In contrast, a death cross happens when the two cross down from from above. These crossovers generate a buy or sell signal in a moving average-based trading system. Such systems are designed to capture the majority of a trend, but tend to miss much of the early part of a rally as it awaits confirmation. The 3-day golden cross throughout the years &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com Moving Average Crossover: How Does The Signal Stack Up? The only time the signal suffered a drawdown was in Bitcoin in 2019. In all other instances, the buy signal using nothing more than a simple moving average crossover, was wildly profitable with limited downside. In 2015, the BTCUSD 3-day golden cross yielded over 2,000% ROI before crossing back down and giving the corresponding sell signal. XRP’s golden cross to death cross kept more than 9,000% of the uptrend’s gains. Ethereum never fired a signal back then, however, due to insufficient price history. Related Reading: This Bitcoin Continuation Pattern Points To 3-6 Months Of Uptrend Ahead Come 2019, Bitcoin had its misfire where the buy signal then sat through a long drawdown. Neither XRP nor Ethereum triggered a signal until 2020, when the entire crypto market began to rally together. The 2020 ETHUSD golden cross held onto over 1100% ROI before the death cross closed out the position. XRP failed to set a new all-time high, but the golden cross still clocked in 200% ROI. Even though Bitcoin fired early in 2019 and sat through a drawdown, the buy signal was still ultimately effective and retained 550% ROI by the time a death cross caused the position to close. Across the five historic buy signals, there was an average of 2,570% ROI when a golden cross occurred. While such returns aren’t likely in the future, this does suggest the signal is effective. Tony is the author of the CoinChartist (VIP) newsletter. Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter. Or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin, XRP, and Ethereum — three of the cryptocurrency market’s most dominant coins — are about to simultaneously form a 3-day golden cross.</p>
<p>This signal is rare, happening only a handful of times in the past in each individual asset. However, never have all three of these major cryptocurrencies triggered this signal all at the same time. What exactly does this mean, and what are the results of the 3-day golden cross?</p>
<h2>Bitcoin, XRP, &amp; Ethereum Lead Market Recovery</h2>
<p>The crypto market outlook is a lot less bleak than it was just weeks ago, between BlackRock and other institutions seeking to launch Bitcoin ETFs and the massive win for XRP and Ripple against the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>

<p>Even the technical environment is starting to show signs of a possible uptrend brewing. Notably, several top cryptocurrencies are inching closer to a golden cross on the 3-day timeframe, which has only occurred a handful of times in the past.</p>
<p>This is about to happen in Bitcoin, Ethereum, and XRP, simultaneously, for the first time in their history. Previously, these signals arrived at different phases of previous bull markets. It wasn’t until all three coins golden crossed that a stronger rally began.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Three top crypto assets — <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Bitcoin</a>, Ethereum, and <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/XRP?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#XRP</a> — are on the brink of a golden cross on the 3-day timeframe</p>
<p>All three firing at the same time has never happened before</p>
<p>It will also be the third in history for BTC and XRP, second ever for Ether <a href="https://t.co/bzVfK3ZpBp" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/bzVfK3ZpBp</a></p>
<p>— Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221; (@tonythebullBTC) <a href="https://twitter.com/tonythebullBTC/status/1681751145201401860?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 19, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<h2>What Is A Golden Cross In Crypto?</h2>
<p>A golden cross occurs when a higher timeframe moving average, typically a 200-period MA, crosses above a lower timeframe moving average, usually a 50-period MA, from below. In contrast, a death cross happens when the two cross down from from above.</p>
<p>These crossovers generate a buy or sell signal in a moving average-based trading system. Such systems are designed to capture the majority of a trend, but tend to miss much of the early part of a rally as it awaits confirmation.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-543432 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1bHwMAWwAUNPLe-860x539.jpeg" alt="bitcoin xrp ethereum golden cross" width="860" height="539" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1bHwMAWwAUNPLe-860x539.jpeg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1bHwMAWwAUNPLe-460x288.jpeg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1bHwMAWwAUNPLe-768x482.jpeg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1bHwMAWwAUNPLe-1536x963.jpeg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1bHwMAWwAUNPLe-750x470.jpeg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1bHwMAWwAUNPLe-1140x715.jpeg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F1bHwMAWwAUNPLe.jpeg 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<h2>Moving Average Crossover: How Does The Signal Stack Up?</h2>
<p>The only time the signal suffered a drawdown was in Bitcoin in 2019. In all other instances, the buy signal using nothing more than a simple moving average crossover, was wildly profitable with limited downside. In 2015, the BTCUSD 3-day golden cross yielded over 2,000% ROI before crossing back down and giving the corresponding sell signal. XRP’s golden cross to death cross kept more than 9,000% of the uptrend’s gains. Ethereum never fired a signal back then, however, due to insufficient price history.</p>

<p>Come 2019, Bitcoin had its misfire where the buy signal then sat through a long drawdown. Neither XRP nor Ethereum triggered a signal until 2020, when the entire crypto market began to rally together. The 2020 ETHUSD golden cross held onto over 1100% ROI before the death cross closed out the position. XRP failed to set a new all-time high, but the golden cross still clocked in 200% ROI.</p>
<p>Even though Bitcoin fired early in 2019 and sat through a drawdown, the buy signal was still ultimately effective and retained 550% ROI by the time a death cross caused the position to close. Across the five historic buy signals, there was an average of 2,570% ROI when a golden cross occurred. While such returns aren’t likely in the future, this does suggest the signal is effective.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-121922368-460x308.jpg" width="460" height="308" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Back In The Game: Ripple Joins $54 Million Funding Round For Metaverse Startup</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/ripple-2/back-in-the-game-ripple-joins-54-million-funding-round-for-metaverse-startup/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 23:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Futureverse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple investment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543370</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ripple has been mostly preoccupied with its lawsuit with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). However, with a partially favorable ruling from Judge Analisa Torres last week stating that XRP tokens sold on the secondary market are not securities, the crypto firm has turned its attention to other things. This time around, Ripple has dipped its toes into the metaverse sector, joining a massive funding round for Futureverse. Ripple Joins $54 Million Funding Round For Futureverse On Tuesday, Bloomberg reported that Futureverse, a metaverse startup, had raised a total of $54 million. The company completed the Series A funding round, although at an undisclosed valuation. But the interesting part of the raise was the parties involved. Related Reading: Why This Upcoming Event Is Bearish For Axie Infinity (AXS) The raise was led by 10T Holdings, a crypto investment firm. However, the funding round seems to have managed to draw the attention of Ripple Labs as well. The raise is also significant in the fact that it took place at a time when crypto-related companies are seeing a decline in funding. Interestingly, the Futureverse startup is a combination of other startups. According to the Bloomberg report, Futureverse is actually a combination of 11 startups that span across different industries. These include metaverse, gaming, and artificial intelligence (AI), among others. XRP price sitting at $0.79 &#124; Source: XRPUSD on TradingView.com Nevertheless, most of Futureverse’s products so far seem to be combining metaverse, gaming, and AI. The startup currently has a football (soccer) game that can be played on mobile called ‘AI League’ that has also been licensed by FIFA. Its next gamin product is said to be a boxing game leveraging the power of AI. A Return Fueled By Positive Sentiment Ripple has regained its foothold in the crypto industry following the court’s ruling against the SEC last week. With this, both the company and its native token, XRP, have experienced renewed vigor in the market. One example is Ripple looking to leverage real-world assets which it expects to reach a $30 trillion market cap in the next decade. Related Reading: Bearish Signal: BNB Open Interest Skyrockets To New Highs Following the ruling as well, the price of XRP jumped by over 60%, bringing the digital asset to its highest level since December 2021. Since then, XRP has continued on a bullish streak, surpassing Bitcoin in terms of average weekly volume, and emerging as one of the top performers in the space. Presently, the price of XRP is sitting at $0.791, representing a 4.92% increase in the last 24 hours. On the 7-day chart, the cryptocurrency is seeing gains of 67% and is now the 4th-largest cryptocurrency with its market cap resting at $41.5 billion. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Ripple has been mostly preoccupied with its lawsuit with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). However, with a partially favorable ruling from Judge Analisa Torres last week stating that XRP tokens sold on the secondary market are not securities, the crypto firm has turned its attention to other things. This time around, Ripple has dipped its toes into the metaverse sector, joining a massive funding round for Futureverse.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Ripple Joins $54 Million Funding Round For Futureverse</h2>
<p class="p2">On Tuesday, Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-18/ai-metaverse-startup-futureverse-raises-54-million" rel="nofollow">reported</a> that Futureverse, a metaverse startup, had raised a total of $54 million. The company completed the Series A funding round, although at an undisclosed valuation. But the interesting part of the raise was the parties involved.</p>

<p class="p2">The raise was led by 10T Holdings, a crypto investment firm. However, the funding round seems to have managed to draw the attention of Ripple Labs as well. The raise is also significant in the fact that it took place at a time when crypto-related companies are seeing a decline in funding.</p>
<p class="p2">Interestingly, the Futureverse startup is a combination of other startups. According to the Bloomberg report, Futureverse is actually a combination of 11 startups that span across different industries. These include metaverse, gaming, and artificial intelligence (AI), among others.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Oyu1qlzM/" alt="Ripple (XRP) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>

<p class="p2">Nevertheless, most of Futureverse’s products so far seem to be combining metaverse, gaming, and AI. The startup currently has a football (soccer) game that can be played on mobile called ‘AI League’ that has also been licensed by FIFA. Its next gamin product is said to be a boxing game leveraging the power of AI.</p>
<h2 class="p2">A Return Fueled By Positive Sentiment</h2>
<p class="p2">Ripple has regained its foothold in the crypto industry following the court’s ruling against the SEC last week. With this, both the company and its native token, XRP, have experienced renewed vigor in the market. One example is Ripple looking to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ripple/ripple-eyes-tokenized-assets-sector/?swcfpc=1">leverage real-world assets</a> which it expects to reach a $30 trillion market cap in the next decade.</p>

<p class="p2">Following the ruling as well, the price of XRP jumped by over 60%, bringing the digital asset to its highest level since December 2021. Since then, XRP has continued on a bullish streak, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-overtakes-bitcoin-in-highest-weekly-trading-volume-following-legal-triumph/?swcfpc=1">surpassing Bitcoin in terms of average weekly volume</a>, and emerging as one of the top performers in the space.</p>
<p class="p2">Presently, the price of XRP is sitting at $0.791, representing a 4.92% increase in the last 24 hours. On the 7-day chart, the cryptocurrency is seeing gains of 67% and is now the 4th-largest cryptocurrency with its market cap resting at $41.5 billion.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-471085352-1-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BREAKING: No Bitcoin Sale From Tesla, Electric Car Giant Holds On As BTC Bounces Back To $30,000</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/breaking-no-bitcoin-sale-from-tesla-electric-car-giant-holds-on-as-btc-bounces-back-to-30000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 21:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Breaking News Ticker]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tesla bitcoin holdings]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543425</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tesla has released its Q2 2023 earnings report, which has been highly anticipated by investors, and it shows no signs of Bitcoin movement for the electric car giant in the previous quarter. The report shows that the company has had a record-breaking quarter, with the best-ever production and deliveries and revenue approaching $25 billion in a single quarter, despite the current macroeconomic environment. Tesla Stands Firm On BTC Investment One important aspect of the report is the section on Tesla&#8217;s balance sheet, which shows the company&#8217;s holdings in digital assets, specifically Bitcoin (BTC). As of June 30, 2023, Tesla&#8217;s digital assets holdings stood at $184 million, which is the same amount as the previous quarter.  This indicates that the company has not sold any of its Bitcoin holdings, despite the recent volatility in the cryptocurrency market. Related Reading: Dogecoin Barks Upwards: Elon Musk’s Twitter Feed Sends DOGE Up 3% Tesla&#8217;s decision to hold onto its Bitcoin holdings is significant, as it shows the company&#8217;s confidence in the long-term potential of digital assets.  This is in line with Elon Musk&#8217;s previous statements about Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies, in which he has expressed support for their underlying technology and potential to transform the financial industry. Bitcoin Rebounds To $30,000 At present, the largest cryptocurrency in terms of market capitalization and trading volume has surpassed the $30,000 threshold, recovering from its sharp decline to $29,400 on Tuesday.  Despite reaching a new yearly high of $31,800 on July 13th, Bitcoin&#8217;s bullish momentum suddenly dissipated, causing a retracement of over 1.6% in the last 14 days. However, the cryptocurrency has managed to maintain a 12% gain over the 30 days. In the event of further price drops and a failure to consolidate above the $30,000 mark, Bitcoin has the advantage of its 50-day Moving Average, which could serve as a strong support level at $29,100. However, sudden price movements have become increasingly common in recent months, following the thaw of the crypto winter.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Exchange Inflow Spikes, Is This Bearish? Typically, when Bitcoin experiences a price drop, it is followed by a period of consolidation. As long as BTC does not drop below its 50-day and 200-day Moving Averages, it can be seen as a short-term victory for Bitcoin bulls who have weathered another round of selling pressure. It remains to be seen whether BTC&#8217;s nearest support level will be able to hold and prevent another decline attempt.  Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tesla has <a href="https://digitalassets.tesla.com/tesla-contents/image/upload/TSLA-Q2-2023-Update.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">released </a>its Q2 2023 earnings report, which has been highly anticipated by investors, and it shows no signs of Bitcoin movement for the electric car giant in the previous quarter.</p>
<p>The report shows that the company has had a record-breaking quarter, with the best-ever production and deliveries and revenue approaching $25 billion in a single quarter, despite the current macroeconomic environment.</p>
<h2>Tesla Stands Firm On BTC Investment</h2>
<p>One important aspect of the report is the section on Tesla&#8217;s balance sheet, which shows the company&#8217;s holdings in digital assets, specifically Bitcoin (BTC). As of June 30, 2023, Tesla&#8217;s digital assets holdings stood at $184 million, which is the same amount as the previous quarter. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-543427" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_25-860x161.jpg" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="161" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_25-860x161.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_25-460x86.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_25-768x144.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_25-750x141.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_25-1140x214.jpg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_25.jpg 1406w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>This indicates that the company has not sold any of its Bitcoin holdings, despite the recent volatility in the cryptocurrency market.</p>

<p>Tesla&#8217;s decision to hold onto its Bitcoin holdings is significant, as it shows the company&#8217;s confidence in the long-term potential of digital assets. </p>
<p>This is in line with Elon Musk&#8217;s previous statements about Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies, in which he has expressed support for their underlying technology and potential to transform the financial industry.</p>
Bitcoin Rebounds To $30,000
<p>At present, the largest cryptocurrency in terms of market capitalization and trading volume has surpassed the $30,000 threshold, recovering from its sharp decline to $29,400 on Tuesday. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ilBYVuZc/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Despite reaching a new yearly high of $31,800 on July 13th, Bitcoin&#8217;s bullish momentum suddenly dissipated, causing a retracement of over 1.6% in the last 14 days. However, the cryptocurrency has managed to maintain a 12% gain over the 30 days.</p>
<p>In the event of further price drops and a failure to consolidate above the $30,000 mark, Bitcoin has the advantage of its 50-day Moving Average, which could serve as a strong support level at $29,100.</p>
<p>However, sudden price movements have become increasingly common in recent months, following the thaw of the crypto winter. </p>

<p>Typically, when Bitcoin experiences a price drop, it is followed by a period of consolidation. As long as BTC does not drop below its 50-day and 200-day Moving Averages, it can be seen as a short-term victory for Bitcoin bulls who have weathered another round of selling pressure.</p>
<p>It remains to be seen whether BTC&#8217;s nearest support level will be able to hold and prevent another decline attempt. </p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/milan-csizmadia-d0V_DQO_xUM-unsplash-368x460.jpg" width="368" height="460" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Barks Upwards: Elon Musk&#8217;s Twitter Feed Sends DOGE Up 3%</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/dogecoin-2/dogecoin-barks-upwards-elon-musks-twitter-feed-sends-doge-up-3/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 21:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusdt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543419</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Popular cryptocurrency Dogecoin (DOGE) experienced another price surge following a tweet from Tesla CEO Elon Musk. The dog-themed cryptocurrency saw a 4% jump just a few minutes after Musk&#8217;s post. Musk has previously supported DOGE on multiple occasions via his Twitter account, often posting memes and comments about the cryptocurrency. His tweets have been known to cause significant price movements in the market, with DOGE often surging by double-digit percentages following his endorsements. Musk&#8217;s Tweet Causes Another Dogecoin Surge, But Will It Be Short-Lived? Despite experiencing a surge in price following Elon Musk&#8217;s tweet, DOGE&#8217;s value remains considerably lower than its July high of $0.07518. At its peak, the cryptocurrency rose from $0.069 to $0.072 but soon lost some of its gains.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Has Broken This Open Interest Pattern, Quant Explains Currently, DOGE is trading around the $0.070 mark, at $0.0687 at the time of writing. Nonetheless, DOGE is still up by 3% in the 24-hour timeframe. It&#8217;s important to note that DOGE&#8217;s recent price movements have been encouraging. Despite being range-bound for the past two weeks, DOGE&#8217;s price has managed to maintain above its 200-day Moving Average (MA), which is a positive sign for the potential continuation of bullish momentum. In addition, DOGE&#8217;s average directional movement index (ADX) indicator is pointing towards another attempt to breach and regain its July high. The ADX is currently peaking to the upside, which indicates that the altcoin is gaining strength. Furthermore, DOGE&#8217;s Squeeze Momentum Indicator suggests that the cryptocurrency is entering another potential uptrend phase, which its ADX also supports. All these factors combined could help DOGE regain the $0.01 mark it reached in April. Nevertheless, despite its recent surge in price, DOGE may face challenges in maintaining its uptrend due to low trading volume. In addition, the cryptocurrency is expected to encounter significant resistance in the near term. If DOGE can sustain its uptrend, it will likely face challenges from the 50-day Moving Average (MA) currently at $0.07481. Furthermore, DOGE must overcome a resistance wall at $0.0752 to regain its July high. Related Reading: Ethereum Monthly Burn Surpasses 146,000 ETH As Total Clears $6.5 Billion According to Token Terminal data, DOGE&#8217;s market capitalization is $9.83 billion, with a circulating supply of tokens. Its fully diluted market capitalization is also $9.83 billion.  However, DOGE&#8217;s price-to-fully-diluted ratio (P/F ratio) is currently at an extremely high level of 16,006.25x, indicating that the cryptocurrency is trading at a premium relative to its fully diluted market capitalization. The P/F ratio has increased by 226.7% over the past 24 hours, suggesting that there may be increased demand for DOGE in the market. In conclusion, while DOGE&#8217;s recent surge in price can be attributed to Musk&#8217;s tweet, it remains to be seen whether it will continue to experience significant price movements in response to social media mentions and other media attention. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Popular cryptocurrency Dogecoin (DOGE) experienced another price surge following a <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1681691639922806784?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">tweet</a><a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1681691639922806784?s=20" rel="nofollow"> </a>from Tesla CEO Elon Musk. The dog-themed cryptocurrency saw a 4% jump just a few minutes after Musk&#8217;s post.</p>
<p>Musk has previously supported DOGE on multiple occasions via his Twitter account, often posting memes and comments about the cryptocurrency. His tweets have been known to cause significant price movements in the market, with DOGE often surging by double-digit percentages following his endorsements.</p>
<h2>Musk&#8217;s Tweet Causes Another Dogecoin Surge, But Will It Be Short-Lived?</h2>
<p>Despite experiencing a surge in price following Elon Musk&#8217;s tweet, DOGE&#8217;s value remains considerably lower than its July high of $0.07518. At its peak, the cryptocurrency rose from $0.069 to $0.072 but soon lost some of its gains. </p>

<p>Currently, DOGE is trading around the $0.070 mark, at $0.0687 at the time of writing. Nonetheless, DOGE is still up by 3% in the 24-hour timeframe.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/KW20N1nR/" alt="Dogecoin " width="1813" height="858"/>
<p>It&#8217;s important to note that DOGE&#8217;s recent price movements have been encouraging. Despite being range-bound for the past two weeks, DOGE&#8217;s price has managed to maintain above its 200-day Moving Average (MA), which is a positive sign for the potential continuation of bullish momentum.</p>
<p>In addition, DOGE&#8217;s average directional movement index (ADX) indicator is pointing towards another attempt to breach and regain its July high. The ADX is currently peaking to the upside, which indicates that the altcoin is gaining strength. Furthermore, DOGE&#8217;s Squeeze Momentum Indicator suggests that the cryptocurrency is entering another potential uptrend phase, which its ADX also supports.</p>
<p>All these factors combined could help DOGE regain the $0.01 mark it reached in April. Nevertheless, despite its recent surge in price, DOGE may face challenges in maintaining its uptrend due to low trading volume. In addition, the cryptocurrency is expected to encounter significant resistance in the near term.</p>
<p>If DOGE can sustain its uptrend, it will likely face challenges from the 50-day Moving Average (MA) currently at $0.07481. Furthermore, DOGE must overcome a resistance wall at $0.0752 to regain its July high.</p>

<p>According to Token Terminal <a href="https://tokenterminal.com/terminal/projects/dogecoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a>, DOGE&#8217;s market capitalization is $9.83 billion, with a circulating supply of tokens. Its fully diluted market capitalization is also $9.83 billion. </p>
<p>However, DOGE&#8217;s price-to-fully-diluted ratio (P/F ratio) is currently at an extremely high level of 16,006.25x, indicating that the cryptocurrency is trading at a premium relative to its fully diluted market capitalization. The P/F ratio has increased by 226.7% over the past 24 hours, suggesting that there may be increased demand for DOGE in the market.</p>
<p>In conclusion, while DOGE&#8217;s recent surge in price can be attributed to Musk&#8217;s tweet, it remains to be seen whether it will continue to experience significant price movements in response to social media mentions and other media attention.</p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1344716049-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Exchange Inflow Spikes, Is This Bearish?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-exchange-inflow-spikes-is-this-bearish/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 19:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin bearish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Exchange Inflow]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543376</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Bitcoin exchange inflow towards Binance has spiked during the past day, which may be bearish for the price. Bitcoin Exchange Inflow Has Registered A Large Spike As an analyst in a CryptoQuant post pointed out, a whale has made a large deposit to the cryptocurrency exchange Binance. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;exchange inflow,&#8221; which measures the total amount of Bitcoin that investors send to a specific centralized exchange (which, in this case, is Binance). When the value of this metric is high, it means that the holders are depositing large amounts to the platform right now. The investors may have made these transfers for selling-related purposes, depending on which type of exchange these inflows are for. Naturally, if that is the case, the price could feel a bearish effect from the inflows. On the other hand, low values imply the exchange in question isn&#8217;t receiving that many coins currently. Such a trend would imply that the market&#8217;s selling pressure may be low. Related Reading: Bitcoin Has Broken This Open Interest Pattern, Quant Explains Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin exchange inflow for the cryptocurrency exchange Binance over the past day: The value of the metric seems to have been quite high in recent hours &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As shown in the above graph, the Bitcoin exchange inflow for Binance has observed a rather large spike in the past day. With this deposit, around 4,451 BTC (approximately worth $133 million at the current exchange rate) has entered the platform&#8217;s wallets. Interestingly, this deposit has come from a whale that has bought 20,000 BTC over the last eight months, meaning that the investor still has over 15,000 BTC left in their wallet after the transaction. The whale may have made this transfer to take some profit at the current prices. Since the scale of the deposit is quite sizeable, it could potentially cause bearish ripples in the market. However, as another quant has explained, the deposits have been towards the derivatives side of the exchange and not the spot platform. Looks like the spot exchanges inflow hasn't moved today &#124; Source: CryptoQuant It would appear likely that the transfer hasn&#8217;t been made to sell the coins (at least not directly) but rather for opening positions on the derivatives market. Related Reading: Signal With Perfect Track Record Predicts Bitcoin Bull Market Parabola: Analyst &#8220;This category of large wallets rarely moves directly to derivative exchanges,&#8221; notes the analyst, given that the size of the wallet in question is in the 10,000+ BTC range, the class of the largest whales on the network. Such a large position can lead to volatility in the Bitcoin price, but unlike selling from spot deposits, this price action may not necessarily be bearish for the asset. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,800, down 3% in the last week. BTC has gone downhill during the last few days &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows the Bitcoin exchange inflow towards Binance has spiked during the past day, which may be bearish for the price.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Exchange Inflow Has Registered A Large Spike</h2>
<p>As an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/64b7b5e89d70843ab91eadab-The-20K-BTC-whale-is-taking-profits" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post pointed out</a>, a whale has made a large deposit to the cryptocurrency exchange Binance. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-short-term-holders-exchange-inflows-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">exchange inflow</a>,&#8221; which measures the total amount of Bitcoin that investors send to a specific centralized exchange (which, in this case, is Binance).</p>
<p>When the value of this metric is high, it means that the holders are depositing large amounts to the platform right now. The investors may have made these transfers for selling-related purposes, depending on which type of exchange these inflows are for. Naturally, if that is the case, the price could feel a bearish effect from the inflows.</p>
<p>On the other hand, low values imply the exchange in question isn&#8217;t receiving that many coins currently. Such a trend would imply that the market&#8217;s selling pressure may be low.</p>

<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin exchange inflow for the cryptocurrency exchange Binance over the past day:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/359684/quicktake/5I5gSW4oP_ddbac6d4ce03aa7ac21afe5a08f11c330c2849615506eaeca8584b21864f2444.png" alt="Bitcoin Exchange Inflow To Binance" width="1280" height="806"/></p>

<p>As shown in the above graph, the Bitcoin exchange inflow for Binance has observed a rather large spike in the past day. With this deposit, around 4,451 BTC (approximately worth $133 million at the current exchange rate) has entered the platform&#8217;s wallets.</p>
<p>Interestingly, this deposit has come from a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/litecoin-whales-deposit-big-to-exchanges-bearish-sign/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">whale</a> that has bought 20,000 BTC over the last eight months, meaning that the investor still has over 15,000 BTC left in their wallet after the transaction.</p>
<p>The whale may have made this transfer to take some profit at the current prices. Since the scale of the deposit is quite sizeable, it could potentially cause bearish ripples in the market.</p>
<p>However, as another quant has <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/64b7dfca9d70843ab91eec3e-BTC-Fluctuations-are-coming" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">explained</a>, the deposits have been towards the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-rally-appears-to-be-fueled-by-derivatives-will-it-last/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">derivatives</a> side of the exchange and not the spot platform.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/256099/quicktake/D7nnH_a9bbfce526c5670b0062e3e7a6ecec5280745983133cbc19eaf0baf2a7ca8dd5.png" alt="Bitcoin Derivative Inflow" width="1280" height="530"/></p>

<p>It would appear likely that the transfer hasn&#8217;t been made to sell the coins (at least not directly) but rather for opening positions on the derivatives market.</p>

<p>&#8220;This category of large wallets rarely moves directly to derivative exchanges,&#8221; notes the analyst, given that the size of the wallet in question is in the 10,000+ BTC range, the class of the largest whales on the network.</p>
<p>Such a large position can lead to volatility in the Bitcoin price, but unlike selling from spot deposits, this price action may not necessarily be bearish for the asset.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,800, down 3% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/156EIs9u/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/kanchanara-PjhxKgiCXGg-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>OKX Wallet Introduces Staking Function For Bitcoin And BRC-20 Tokens</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/okb/okx-wallet-introduces-staking-function-for-bitcoin-and-brc-20-tokens/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 18:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[OKB]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543380</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency exchange OKX, has announced that its multichain wallet will now allow users to lock up and stake their Bitcoin (BTC) and BRC-20 tokens. This function is described as a token reward system for holders of Bitcoin and BRC-20 tokens. OKX Unveils Staking System On Multichain Wallet On Tuesday, OKX unveiled a new functionality on its multichain digital asset wallet, which enables users to stake Bitcoin (BTC) and BRC-20 tokens. According to the company&#8217;s media release, this token reward system is possible due to the integration of OKX&#8217;s open-source BRC20-S protocol.  Related Reading: Pre-Mined Ethereum Worth $116M Moves After 8 Years: Is A Major Price Dip Imminent? This protocol is an extended version of the BRC-20 standard that integrates functionalities for staking operations, like depositing, minting, and withdrawing. It allows users to earn BRC20-S tokens through the OKX Web3 DeFi aggregator. Furthermore, the BRC20-S protocol enables decentralized finance (DeFi) developers and projects to create staking pools on OKX Wallet. With these staking pools, Bitcoin holders and BRC-20 token holders can receive BRC20-S tokens. Additionally, this will help DeFi projects drive up user engagement and community-building efforts, according to OKX&#8217;s press statement. Jason Lau, OKX’s Chief Innovation Officer, claims that the wallet is the first multichain digital asset storage to support Bitcoin and BRC-20 token staking. “We have heard from OKX Wallet users that they want more opportunities to participate in the ecosystem, and we are thrilled to deliver that for them,” the CIO said. This staking capability comes as an addition to an existing host of Web3 Earn products on the OKX wallet. In the announcement, the company also mentioned the future introduction of complementary features, like a marketplace for selling BRC20-S tokens. OKX Wallet Announces Integration With Kava Blockchain In a separate announcement, OKX Wallet disclosed its partnership with Kava, an EVM-compatible blockchain built with Cosmos’ SDK (Software Development Kit). This integration will reportedly enrich the users’ options for digital asset transfer and transactions on the wallet. This represents another positive move by OKX Wallet in pursuit of maximum customer satisfaction as only a few days ago, the multichain wallet unveiled a partnership with PulseChain, another blockchain platform. Related Reading: BNB Chain Unveils Beacon Update – What’s Its Bearing On Price? Despite these positive moves and collaborations, OKB, the utility token of the OKX ecosystem, has seen a negligible market performance. According to CoinGecko data, the token’s value has only increased by 0.3% in the last 24 hours, with a 0.7% dip in the past week. As of this writing, OKB is chasing hands at $43.14, with a daily trading volume of over $2.02 million. The token has a market cap of roughly $2.59 billion, making it the 29th-largest cryptocurrency in the industry. OKBUSD trading at $43.2 &#124; Source: OKBUSD chart from TradingView Featured image from OKX, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency exchange OKX, has announced that its multichain wallet will now allow users to lock up and stake their Bitcoin (BTC) and BRC-20 tokens. This function is described as a token reward system for holders of Bitcoin and BRC-20 tokens.</p>
<h2>OKX Unveils Staking System On Multichain Wallet</h2>
<p>On Tuesday, OKX unveiled a new functionality on its multichain digital asset wallet, which enables users to stake Bitcoin (BTC) and BRC-20 tokens. According to the company&#8217;s <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/ae/news-releases/okx-wallet-is-first-multi-chain-wallet-to-offer-staking-for-bitcoin-and-brc-20-tokens-301880772.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">media release</a>, this token reward system is possible due to the integration of OKX&#8217;s open-source BRC20-S protocol. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/pre-mined-ethereum-moves-after-8-years-price-dip-imminent/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Pre-Mined Ethereum Worth $116M Moves After 8 Years: Is A Major Price Dip Imminent?</a></p>
<p>This <a href="https://www.okx.com/web3/build/docs/bitcoin-ecosystem/brc20-s" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">protocol</a> is an extended version of the BRC-20 standard that integrates functionalities for staking operations, like depositing, minting, and withdrawing. It allows users to earn BRC20-S tokens through the OKX Web3 DeFi aggregator.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the BRC20-S protocol enables decentralized finance (DeFi) developers and projects to create staking pools on OKX Wallet. </p>
<p>With these staking pools, Bitcoin holders and BRC-20 token holders can receive BRC20-S tokens. Additionally, this will help DeFi projects drive up user engagement and community-building efforts, according to OKX&#8217;s press statement.</p>
<p>Jason Lau, OKX’s Chief Innovation Officer, claims that the wallet is the first multichain digital asset storage to support Bitcoin and BRC-20 token staking. </p>
<p>“We have heard from OKX Wallet users that they want more opportunities to participate in the ecosystem, and we are thrilled to deliver that for them,” the CIO said.</p>
<p>This staking capability comes as an addition to an existing host of Web3 Earn products on the OKX wallet. In the announcement, the company also mentioned the future introduction of complementary features, like a marketplace for selling BRC20-S tokens.</p>
<h2>OKX Wallet Announces Integration With Kava Blockchain</h2>
<p>In a separate <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2023/07/19/2707150/0/en/Flash-News-OKX-Wallet-is-Now-Integrated-with-Kava-a-Decentralized-Blockchain-Platform.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announcement</a>, OKX Wallet disclosed its partnership with Kava, an EVM-compatible blockchain built with Cosmos’ SDK (Software Development Kit). This integration will reportedly enrich the users’ options for digital asset transfer and transactions on the wallet.</p>
<p>This represents another positive move by OKX Wallet in pursuit of maximum customer satisfaction as only a few days ago, the multichain wallet unveiled a <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2023/07/16/2705283/0/en/Flash-News-OKX-Wallet-Partners-with-PulseChain.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">partnership with PulseChain</a>, another blockchain platform.</p>

<p>Despite these positive moves and collaborations, OKB, the utility token of the OKX ecosystem, has seen a negligible market performance. According to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/okb" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko data</a>, the token’s value has only increased by 0.3% in the last 24 hours, with a 0.7% dip in the past week.</p>
<p>As of this writing, OKB is chasing hands at $43.14, with a daily trading volume of over $2.02 million. The token has a market cap of roughly $2.59 billion, making it the 29th-largest cryptocurrency in the industry.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/H0G4RXMi/" alt="OKX" width="997" height="586"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/07104210-2048x1152-1-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Monthly Burn Surpasses 146,000 ETH As Total Clears $6.5 Billion</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-monthly-burn-surpasses-146000-eth/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 17:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH burn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum upgrade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543384</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Featuring Ethereum Improvement Proposal (EIP) 1559, the London hard fork introduced significant changes to Ethereum’s transaction fee mechanism. Users now pay a base fee that is subsequently burned, effectively removing ether from circulation forever. This approach significantly impacted the token&#8217;s supply, resulting in a monthly burn rate of approximately 146,000 ETH. The London Hard Fork And Its Deflationary Impact Integrated into the Ethereum network on August 5, 2021, the London hard fork brought a paradigm shift in the cryptocurrency&#8217;s transaction fee structure. Through the EIP-1559, the network introduced a unique mechanism that involved the burning of a significant portion of transaction fees, known as the &#8220;base fee.&#8221; This innovative approach aimed to counterbalance Ethereum&#8217;s inflation while providing block rewards and priority fees to miners. Related Reading: ARK Invest CEO Says Firm Is Still Bullish On Coinbase Despite Selling COIN Stocks As a result, the base fee is permanently removed from circulation, leading to a deflationary effect on the token&#8217;s supply. The scale of the burn has been enormous, with over 3.46 million ETH, worth $6.68 billion, annihilated since the London hard fork&#8217;s enforcement. This translates to an average monthly burn rate of more than 146,000 ETH over the 710-day period that followed the upgrade. 146,000 ETH burned per month &#124; Source: Beaconcha.in Ethereum&#8217;s deflationary path effectively offset the issuance of new tokens, curbing its supply growth by approximately 0.1% annually. Leading Contributors To The Ethereum Burn The principal factors driving Ethereum&#8217;s burn phenomenon include regular ETH transfers, non-fungible token (NFT) transactions on Opensea, and activities on the decentralized exchange Uniswap. Regular ETH transfers accounted for the most substantial reduction in supply, leading to the incineration of nearly 300,000 ETH. Uniswap v2 follows closely, with $56.5 million worth of ETH burned since the hard fork, while transfers of Tether stablecoins contributed to the destruction of $50.5 million worth of ETH. ETH price struggles to hold $1,900 support &#124; Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com Blockchain gaming platform Axie Infinity and Uniswap v3 each burned $32 million and $30 million worth of ETH, respectively. At the same time, the number of ETH staked in the Ethereum Beacon contract has also been on the rise. It is now sitting at over 26.87 million ETH, translating to a dollar value of $51.35 billion. Related Reading: USDC Market Cap Drops As Redemptions Climb To $1.4 Billion With the Ethereum supply sitting at 120.2 million, it means that over 11% of its supply is currently locked up while the burn continues to take coins out of circulation. Both of these developments combined could see the circulating supply of the digital asset reduce drastically, leading to a rise in the price of ETH as time goes on. ETH is currently trading at a price of $1,903 at the time of this writing, representing a 0.72% increase in the last day. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Featuring Ethereum Improvement Proposal (EIP) 1559, the London hard fork introduced significant changes to Ethereum’s transaction fee mechanism. Users now pay a base fee that is subsequently burned, effectively removing ether from circulation forever.</p>
<p>This approach significantly impacted the token&#8217;s supply, resulting in a <a href="https://beaconcha.in/burn" rel="nofollow">monthly burn rate of approximately 146,000 ETH</a>.</p>
<h2>The London Hard Fork And Its Deflationary Impact</h2>
<p>Integrated into the Ethereum network on August 5, 2021, the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-price-surges-as-london-hard-fork-goes-live/" rel="nofollow">London hard fork</a> brought a paradigm shift in the cryptocurrency&#8217;s transaction fee structure.</p>
<p>Through the EIP-1559, the network introduced a unique mechanism that involved the burning of a significant portion of transaction fees, known as the &#8220;base fee.&#8221; This innovative approach aimed to counterbalance Ethereum&#8217;s inflation while providing block rewards and priority fees to miners.</p>

<p>As a result, the base fee is permanently removed from circulation, leading to a deflationary effect on the token&#8217;s supply.</p>
<p>The scale of the burn has been enormous, with over 3.46 million ETH, worth $6.68 billion, annihilated since the London hard fork&#8217;s enforcement. This translates to an average monthly burn rate of more than 146,000 ETH over the 710-day period that followed the upgrade.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-543385 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-19-at-15.11.13-460x187.png" alt="Ethereum (eth) burn" width="460" height="187" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-19-at-15.11.13-460x187.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-19-at-15.11.13-860x350.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-19-at-15.11.13-768x313.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-19-at-15.11.13-1536x626.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-19-at-15.11.13-2048x835.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-19-at-15.11.13-750x306.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-19-at-15.11.13-1140x465.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>

<p>Ethereum&#8217;s deflationary path effectively offset the issuance of new tokens, curbing its supply growth by approximately <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/community/articles/64b79a54bd6e5433fa8ed770/" rel="nofollow">0.1%</a> annually.</p>
<h2>Leading Contributors To The Ethereum Burn</h2>
<p>The principal factors driving Ethereum&#8217;s burn phenomenon include regular ETH transfers, non-fungible token (NFT) transactions on Opensea, and activities on the decentralized exchange Uniswap.</p>
<p>Regular ETH transfers accounted for the most substantial reduction in supply, leading to the incineration of nearly 300,000 ETH.</p>
<p>Uniswap v2 follows closely, with $56.5 million worth of ETH burned since the hard fork, while transfers of Tether stablecoins contributed to the destruction of $50.5 million worth of ETH.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/1m3PIQDU/" alt="Ethereum (ETH) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>

<p>Blockchain gaming platform Axie Infinity and Uniswap v3 each burned $32 million and $30 million worth of ETH, respectively.</p>
<p>At the same time, the number of ETH staked in the Ethereum <a href="https://etherscan.io/address/0x00000000219ab540356cbb839cbe05303d7705fa" rel="nofollow">Beacon contract</a> has also been on the rise. It is now sitting at over 26.87 million ETH, translating to a dollar value of $51.35 billion.</p>

<p>With the Ethereum supply sitting at 120.2 million, it means that over 11% of its supply is currently locked up while the burn continues to take coins out of circulation. 

Both of these developments combined could see the circulating supply of the digital asset reduce drastically, leading to a rise in the price of ETH as time goes on.</p>
<p>ETH is currently trading at a price of $1,903 at the time of this writing, representing a 0.72% increase in the last day.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1383710952-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Burns $480 Million In BNB, Will Price Recover?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/bnb/binance-burns-480-million/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 16:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB burn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnbusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543373</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Binance, the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange, just completed its quarterly BNB burn, destroying $480 million worth of its native BNB token. According to the company&#8217;s blog post, 1,991,854.33 BNB was recently burned in its 24th quarterly BNB burn, with 747.51 BNB going through the Pioneer Burn Program. Binance Completes 24th Quarterly BNB Burn BNB Chain’s token-burning events are not new and have become somewhat of a routine. BNB has an auto-burn protocol that removes a predetermined amount of BNB from the crypto market every quarter of the year. Related Reading: USDC Market Cap Drops As Redemptions Climb To $1.4 Billion The number to be burned each quarter is determined by the price of BNB and the number of blocks mined on the BSC blockchain. With the circulating supply of BNB now at 153.8 million, the latest 24th burn represents 1.2% of the total supply. The initial total supply of BNB was 200 million BNB, but the supply is gradually decreasing due to the regular coin burn events. According to Binance, the auto-burn protocol will continue until its total supply is 100 million BNB. Earlier today, #Binance completed the 24th quarterly #BNB token burn of 1,991,854 BNB through BNB Auto-Burn. Not sure what the BNB Auto-Burn is? Give this a read 👇 https://t.co/C5wlki9Lmb — Binance (@binance) July 19, 2023 $480 Million In BNB Destroyed: The Impact On Price And Supply For BNB holders, token burns are usually a reason to celebrate since they reduce the total BNB supply and should make the cryptocurrency more valuable. In the days following the burn, the BNB price may increase slightly as the circulating supply drops. However, these price spikes are often temporary. At this time, the BNB price barely budged despite the burn.  BNB price fails to move despite latest burn &#124; Source: BNBUSD on TradingView.com After hitting an all-time high of around $600 in September 2021, BNB has declined along with the rest of the crypto market. At its peak, the market cap of BNB went over $90 billion, making it the third-largest cryptocurrency behind Bitcoin and Ethereum.  Now, the cryptocurrency has been ranging between $300 and $200 since the beginning of the year, bringing its market cap to $37.1 billion. With its current market cap, the coin is now the 5th-largest cryptocurrency after XRP overtook it to claim the fourth position.  With less BNB floating around, the remaining tokens should become more scarce and valuable. However, scheduled or routine coin burns tend to have a negligible impact on price over the long run, as evidenced by BNB’s performance over the last day.  Related Reading: ARK Invest CEO Says Firm Is Still Bullish On Coinbase Despite Selling COIN Stocks While the burn is meant to be a bullish event for BNB holders, the price hasn&#8217;t skyrocketed immediately as many investors had hoped. Considering the price of BNB is affected by various market conditions, past burns have had different outcomes on BNB.  The cryptocurrency is currently trading at $241.84 and is down by 2.39% over a 7-day timeframe. Trading volume in the past 24 hours is also down by 17.91% to $585 million. Featured image from Currency.com, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance, the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange, just completed its quarterly BNB burn, destroying $480 million worth of its native BNB token. According to the company&#8217;s blog <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/the-24th-quarterly-bnb-burn-completed-via-bnb-auto-burn-11cb4b1ea3d84a209bc90e4132312ff5" rel="nofollow">post</a>, 1,991,854.33 BNB was recently burned in its 24th quarterly BNB burn, with 747.51 BNB going through the Pioneer Burn Program.</p>
<h2>Binance Completes 24th Quarterly BNB Burn</h2>
<p>BNB Chain’s token-burning events are not new and have become somewhat of a routine. BNB has an auto-burn protocol that removes a predetermined amount of BNB from the crypto market every quarter of the year.</p>

<p>The number to be burned each quarter is determined by the price of BNB and the number of blocks mined on the BSC blockchain. With the circulating supply of BNB now at 153.8 million, the latest 24th burn represents 1.2% of the total supply.</p>
<p>The initial total supply of BNB was 200 million BNB, but the supply is gradually decreasing due to the regular coin burn events. According to Binance, the auto-burn protocol will continue until its total supply is 100 million BNB.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Earlier today, <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Binance</a> completed the 24th quarterly <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BNB?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#BNB</a> token burn of 1,991,854 BNB through BNB Auto-Burn.</p>
<p>Not sure what the BNB Auto-Burn is?</p>
<p>Give this a read <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f447.png" alt="👇" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/C5wlki9Lmb" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/C5wlki9Lmb</a></p>
<p>— Binance (@binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1681604828127019008?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 19, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<h2>$480 Million In BNB Destroyed: The Impact On Price And Supply</h2>
<p>For BNB holders, token burns are usually a reason to celebrate since they reduce the total BNB supply and should make the cryptocurrency more valuable. In the days following the burn, the BNB price may increase slightly as the circulating supply drops. However, these price spikes are often temporary. At this time, the BNB price barely budged despite the burn. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/TEQUJafl/" alt="Binance Coin (BNB) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>

<p>After hitting an all-time high of around $600 in September 2021, BNB has declined along with the rest of the crypto market. At its peak, the market cap of BNB went over $90 billion, making it the third-largest cryptocurrency behind Bitcoin and Ethereum. </p>
<p>Now, the cryptocurrency has been ranging between $300 and $200 since the beginning of the year, bringing its market cap to $37.1 billion. With its current market cap, the coin is now the 5th-largest cryptocurrency after XRP overtook it to claim the fourth position. </p>
<p>With less BNB floating around, the remaining tokens should become more scarce and valuable. However, scheduled or routine coin burns tend to have a negligible impact on price over the long run, as evidenced by BNB’s performance over the last day. </p>

<p>While the burn is meant to be a bullish event for BNB holders, the price hasn&#8217;t skyrocketed immediately as many investors had hoped. Considering the price of BNB is affected by various market conditions, past burns have had different outcomes on BNB. </p>
<p>The cryptocurrency is currently trading at $241.84 and is down by 2.39% over a 7-day timeframe. Trading volume in the past 24 hours is also down by 17.91% to $585 million.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Coin-BNB--460x383.jpeg" width="460" height="383" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Has Broken This Open Interest Pattern, Quant Explains</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-broken-open-interest-pattern-quant-explains/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 15:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Open interest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Pattern]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543320</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A quant has explained how a pattern in the Bitcoin open interest that held during the past month now appears to be broken. Bitcoin Open Interest Is Now Moving Against The Price As explained by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, the BTC price had earlier been rising along with increases in the open interest. The &#8220;open interest&#8221; here refers to an indicator that measures the total amount of Bitcoin futures contracts that are currently open on all derivative exchanges. When the value of this metric goes up, it means that users are opening up more positions on the futures market right now. As leverage generally increases when this happens, the price of the asset may become more volatile following this trend. On the other hand, the value of the indicator decreasing suggests the users are either closing up their contracts of their own volition or are being liquidated by their platforms currently. Such a trend may lead to the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price becoming more stable. Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin open interest over the past few weeks: Looks like the value of the metric has been going up in recent days &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As displayed in the above graph, the Bitcoin open interest has been steadily rising during the past few days. This suggests that investors have been slowly opening up more contracts on derivative exchanges. Related Reading: Signal With Perfect Track Record Predicts Bitcoin Bull Market Parabola: Analyst During the last month or so, whenever the open interest had risen, the price of the cryptocurrency had also registered an increase. The quant notes that this would imply that the bulls had been dominating the futures market in this period, as the open interest going up alongside the price implies that the increase in contracts had been coming from long contract holders. This pattern had held up until the surge BTC had observed a few days back. This sharp increase in the price had ended up only being temporary, and as the price had plunged down, the longs had seen liquidation. As the longs had previously dominated the Bitcoin market, this decrease in the open interest was quite sharp, as is visible in the chart. The indicator didn&#8217;t take too long to rebound, however, as it initially sharply rose and then fell back to a trend of gradual growth. which has continued until today. Related Reading: Litecoin Whales Deposit Big To Exchanges, Bearish Sign? But as the price has in fact been going down in this same period, it would appear that the increase in the open interest is now being driven by the shorts. This would imply that a shift in the market may have occurred, as the open interest pattern that had previously held up now seems to be invalid. &#8220;Have the bears returned once again? In any case, it is advisable to exercise caution in the current area,&#8221; warns the quant. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $30,000, down 2% in the last week. BTC has been struggling recently &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from iStock.com, charts from TradingView.com, Blockchain.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A quant has explained how a pattern in the Bitcoin open interest that held during the past month now appears to be broken.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Open Interest Is Now Moving Against The Price</h2>
<p>As explained by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/64b68d1441768f4ed3168f8d-Buyers-have-turned-into-sellers" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, the BTC price had earlier been rising along with increases in the open interest. The &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/bnb/bnb-open-interest-new-highs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">open interest</a>&#8221; here refers to an indicator that measures the total amount of Bitcoin futures contracts that are currently open on all derivative exchanges.</p>
<p>When the value of this metric goes up, it means that users are opening up more positions on the futures market right now. As leverage generally increases when this happens, the price of the asset may become more volatile following this trend.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the value of the indicator decreasing suggests the users are either closing up their contracts of their own volition or are being <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/crypto-liquidations-cross-300-million/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">liquidated</a> by their platforms currently. Such a trend may lead to the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price becoming more stable.</p>
<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin open interest over the past few weeks:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/256099/quicktake/uvU65n_4422370673843683d108b3214c764fb191c37a223d069532864fdf5ea6b30fd0.png" alt="Bitcoin Open Interest" width="1280" height="529"/></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the Bitcoin open interest has been steadily rising during the past few days. This suggests that investors have been slowly opening up more contracts on derivative exchanges.</p>

<p>During the last month or so, whenever the open interest had risen, the price of the cryptocurrency had also registered an increase. The quant notes that this would imply that the bulls had been dominating the futures market in this period, as the open interest going up alongside the price implies that the increase in contracts had been coming from <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/over-41-million-of-ethereum-longs-liquidated-reaching-a-new-4-week-high/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">long contract holders</a>.</p>
<p>This pattern had held up until the surge BTC had observed a few days back. This sharp increase in the price had ended up only being temporary, and as the price had plunged down, the longs had seen liquidation.</p>
<p>As the longs had previously dominated the Bitcoin market, this decrease in the open interest was quite sharp, as is visible in the chart. The indicator didn&#8217;t take too long to rebound, however, as it initially sharply rose and then fell back to a trend of gradual growth. which has continued until today.</p>

<p>But as the price has in fact been going down in this same period, it would appear that the increase in the open interest is now being driven by the shorts. This would imply that a shift in the market may have occurred, as the open interest pattern that had previously held up now seems to be invalid.</p>
<p>&#8220;Have the bears returned once again? In any case, it is advisable to exercise caution in the current area,&#8221; warns the quant.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $30,000, down 2% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/LMEM4OBG/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1367449613-2-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar (XLM) Surges Over 43% In One Week, What&#8217;s Pushing It?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xlm/stellar-xlm-surges-over-43-in-one-week-whats-pushing-it/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kent Glory]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 14:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XLM]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar (XLM)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xlmusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543352</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[While Bitcoin price recedes from the $30,000 support, payment solutions Stellar (XLM) and XRP continue riding the bullish wave, with Stellar (XLM) outranking top gainers today amid impressive ecosystem developments. Determined to break all barriers to the $0.2 target, XLM painted all charts green, with a whopping 43.29% gain in value on the week. The cross-border payment facilitator has added over 8.79% to its valuation over the past 24-hour trading session. XLM Rides On Bullish Momentum From Impressive Ecosystem Developments Following ecosystem developments, XLM continues to soar as interest in its innovative payment and remittance solution increase. In a recent development, Stellar partnered with MoneyGram and HoneyCoin app to support global digital assets cash out with USDC across Nigeria, Ghana, Tanzania, Kenya, Uganda, and the UK. Related Reading: Pre-Mined Ethereum Worth $116M Moves After 8 Years: Is A Major Price Dip Imminent? In another announcement, Stellar partnered with Fonbnk to provide payment solutions to the unbanked in Africa. Considering that millions of Africans lack access to banking services, Stellar&#8217;s partnership with MoneyGram and Fonbnk could bring more users to the digital finance landscape, further expanding the crypto industry. Moreover, Stellar is now available on multiple chains, including Ethereum, Solana, Celo, and Polygon, through Allbridge’s interoperability and bridge solution. Announced on July 11, the integration marks a significant milestone for Stellar, demonstrating its utility for innovative opportunities in decentralized finance. This feat could be among the factors pushing XLM&#8217;s price over the past seven days. Again, the token still enjoys the bullish wave of its close relative, XRP&#8217;s victory in the SEC/Ripple lawsuit.  Stellar (XLM) Price Movement In The Last Seven Days Over the past seven days, XLM witnessed a significant shoot-up. On July 13, when news of Ripple (XRP)’s victory broke out, XLM’s price went from $0.096 to $0.153, a 60% boost within 24 hours. Though it experienced a minute correction as the buzz subsided, XLM remains bullish, fighting for more gains to surpass $0.1 and claim $0.2.  CoinMarketCap data shows XLM has surged more than 42% in the last seven days, bringing its value over 73% higher than it was 30 days ago. As of 6:19 AM EST on July 19, XLM&#8217;s price had added more than 21% to its past year&#8217;s value. The token’s growth in value is reflected in its over 11,173% rise from its November 18, 2014, all-time low of $0.001227.  Stellar’s spree of cross-border payment partnerships has undoubtedly improved XLM’s trading activity. The coin&#8217;s trading volume currently surpasses $321 million, with a 130% increase in 24-hour trading volume, according to CoinMarketcap.  Related Reading: XRP Price Resumes Rally – Here’s Why It Could Surpass $1 This Time An increase in trading volume often points toward two factors: large selloffs and high demand or buying pressure. However, in Stellar&#8217;s case, the price resurgence shows the bulls (buyers) are at work and may push prices near $0.2 if they persist. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While Bitcoin price recedes from the $30,000 support, payment solutions Stellar (XLM) and XRP continue riding the bullish wave, with Stellar (XLM) outranking<a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/gainers-losers/" rel="nofollow"> top gainers today</a> amid impressive ecosystem developments.</p>
<p>Determined to break all barriers to the $0.2 target, XLM painted all charts green, with a whopping 43.29% gain in value on the week. The cross-border payment facilitator has added over 8.79% to its valuation over the past 24-hour trading session.</p>
<h2>XLM Rides On Bullish Momentum From Impressive Ecosystem Developments</h2>
<p>Following ecosystem developments, XLM continues to soar as interest in its innovative payment and remittance solution increase. In a recent <a href="https://twitter.com/StellarOrg/status/1681014631048024064" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">development</a>, Stellar partnered with MoneyGram and HoneyCoin app to support global digital assets cash out with USDC across Nigeria, Ghana, Tanzania, Kenya, Uganda, and the UK.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/pre-mined-ethereum-moves-after-8-years-price-dip-imminent/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Pre-Mined Ethereum Worth $116M Moves After 8 Years: Is A Major Price Dip Imminent?</a></p>
<p>In another <a href="https://twitter.com/StellarOrg/status/1681396712756379648" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announcement</a>, Stellar partnered with Fonbnk to provide payment solutions to the unbanked in Africa. Considering that millions of Africans lack access to banking services, Stellar&#8217;s partnership with MoneyGram and Fonbnk could bring more users to the digital finance landscape, further expanding the crypto industry.</p>
<p>Moreover, Stellar is now available on multiple chains, including Ethereum, Solana, Celo, and Polygon, through Allbridge’s interoperability and bridge solution. <a href="https://stellar.org/press-releases/allbridge-launch-connects-stellar-network-to-ethereum-solana-and-polygon" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Announced</a> on July 11, the integration marks a significant milestone for Stellar, demonstrating its utility for innovative opportunities in decentralized finance.</p>
<p>This feat could be among the factors pushing XLM&#8217;s price over the past seven days. Again, the token still enjoys the bullish wave of its close relative, XRP&#8217;s victory in the SEC/Ripple lawsuit. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/oC4g0YQy/" alt="XLMUSD price chart" width="980" height="538"/>
<h2>Stellar (XLM) Price Movement In The Last Seven Days</h2>
<p>Over the past seven days, XLM witnessed a significant shoot-up. On July 13, when news of Ripple (XRP)’s victory broke out, XLM’s price went from $0.096 to $0.153, a 60% boost within 24 hours. Though it experienced a minute correction as the buzz subsided, XLM remains bullish, fighting for more gains to surpass $0.1 and claim $0.2. </p>
<p>CoinMarketCap <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/stellar/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a> shows XLM has surged more than 42% in the last seven days, bringing its value over 73% higher than it was 30 days ago. As of 6:19 AM EST on July 19, XLM&#8217;s price had added more than 21% to its past year&#8217;s value. The token’s growth in value is reflected in its over 11,173% rise from its November 18, 2014, all-time low of $0.001227. </p>
<p>Stellar’s spree of cross-border payment partnerships has undoubtedly improved XLM’s trading activity. The coin&#8217;s trading volume currently surpasses $321 million, with a 130% increase in 24-hour trading volume, according to CoinMarketcap. </p>

<p>An increase in trading volume often points toward two factors: large selloffs and high demand or buying pressure. However, in Stellar&#8217;s case, the price resurgence shows the bulls (buyers) are at work and may push prices near $0.2 if they persist.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XLM-460x305.jpg" width="460" height="305" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
