<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 20:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Japanese Government To Ease 30% Crypto Tax Requirement &#8211; A Good Move?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/japanese-government-to-ease-30-crypto-tax-requirement-a-good-move/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ana N.]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 20:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[japan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tax]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512698</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Presently Japanese crypto firms pay a set 30% corporate tax rate on their holdings, regardless of whether or not they made a profit. Due to this stringent tax law over the past years, some local crypto firms reportedly chose to move their business elsewhere. Related Reading: Solana: This Minor Hiccup Didn’t Discourage Investors From Acquiring SOL – Until Today This development has impacted the country&#8217;s economic growth, and the LDP, having identified it as its primary task, wants to set things right. The Liberal Democratic Party (LDP) of Japan addresses issues with administrative reform and collaborates with the U.S. to enact defensive and foreign policies. The term Administrative Reform refers to multiple themes in the nation. An example of such themes is adopting measures like tax reform to stand the test of economic strain. Japan Set To Ease Stringent Tax Rules In line with its objectives to promote fast economic growth, the Japanese ruling party&#8217;s (LDP) tax committee held a meeting on December 15. The meeting was to deliberate on tax reforms. While at it, they approved an August-tabled proposal. The proposal seeks to remove taxes on crypto companies’ paper gains from issuance or custody tokens. The Japanese government seeks to ease tax requirements on domestic crypto firms to facilitate the growth of the tech and finance sectors. Submission of more lenient crypto tax laws to parliament will commence in January and will take effect in the next financial year beginning in April. LDP lawmaker and member of the Web3 policy office, Akihisa Shiozaki, spoke on the recent development in an interview with Bloomberg. Shiozaki noted that the move is a step forward in the economic reforms. He added that it would allow more companies to start token issuance businesses. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Crystal Ball – What Happens To BTC After Christmas 2022? Japan&#8217;s Passion For Digital Currency Remains Unfazed Despite Crypto Winter The new move from the Japanese government suggests it is keen to promote and foster the growth of the domestic crypto and Web3 sector. It also indicates that the current bearish trend in the crypto industry, including FTX&#8217;s crisis, did not affect its interest in blockchain technology. Japanese Prime Minister, Fumio Kishida, hammered on the roles of NFTs, blockchain, and Metaverse in the county&#8217;s digital evolution in a statement in October. He cited practical examples using the digitization of national identity cards. In October, the Japan Virtual and Crypto Assets Exchange Association announced plans to ease the strict screening process for listing tokens on exchanges. Kishida addressed this issue in June, asking the organization to loosen its stringent rules on the screening process. Some top leaders in the private sector also shared the same thoughts with the Prime Minister. On December 8, Sumitomo Mitsui Financial Group (SMBC) announced an ongoing project to explore use cases of soulbound tokens (SBTs). SBTs were part of Vitalik Buterin&#8217;s, co-founder of Ethereum, proposal to use tokens to represent people&#8217;s digital identity.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Presently Japanese crypto firms pay a set 30% corporate tax rate on their holdings, regardless of whether or not they made a profit. Due to this stringent tax law over the past years, some local crypto firms <a href="https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2022/07/27/business/japan-crypto-talent-exodus/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reportedly</a> chose to move their business elsewhere.</p>

<p>This development has impacted the country&#8217;s economic growth, and the LDP, having identified it as its primary task, wants to set things right.</p>
<p>The Liberal Democratic Party (LDP) of Japan addresses issues with administrative reform and collaborates with the U.S. to enact defensive and foreign policies.</p>
<p>The term Administrative Reform refers to multiple themes in the nation. An example of such themes is adopting measures like tax reform to stand the test of economic strain.</p>
<h2>Japan Set To Ease Stringent Tax Rules</h2>
<p>In line with its objectives to promote fast economic growth, the Japanese ruling party&#8217;s (LDP) tax committee held a meeting on December 15. The meeting was to deliberate on tax reforms. While at it, they approved an <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-08-31/japan-s-regulator-proposes-tax-breaks-for-investors-crypto?leadSource=uverify%20wall" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">August-tabled</a> proposal. The proposal seeks to remove taxes on crypto companies’ paper gains from issuance or custody tokens.</p>
<p>The Japanese government seeks to ease tax requirements on domestic crypto firms to facilitate the growth of the tech and finance sectors. Submission of more lenient crypto tax laws to parliament will commence in January and will take effect in the next financial year beginning in April.</p>
<img class="wp-image-512703 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TOTAL_2022-12-16_21-07-07-860x485.png" alt="Japanese Government To Ease 30% Crypto Tax Requirement - A Good Move?" width="860" height="485" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TOTAL_2022-12-16_21-07-07-860x485.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TOTAL_2022-12-16_21-07-07-460x259.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TOTAL_2022-12-16_21-07-07-768x433.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TOTAL_2022-12-16_21-07-07-750x423.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TOTAL_2022-12-16_21-07-07-1140x642.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TOTAL_2022-12-16_21-07-07.png 1519w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>LDP lawmaker and member of the Web3 policy office, Akihisa Shiozaki, spoke on the recent development in an <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-12-15/japan-moves-closer-to-easing-tax-on-corporate-crypto-holdings?leadSource=uverify%20wall" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">interview with Bloomberg</a>. Shiozaki noted that the move is a step forward in the economic reforms. He added that it would allow more companies to start token issuance businesses.</p>

Japan&#8217;s Passion For Digital Currency Remains Unfazed Despite Crypto Winter
<p>The new move from the Japanese government suggests it is keen to promote and foster the growth of the domestic crypto and Web3 sector. It also indicates that the current bearish trend in the crypto industry, including FTX&#8217;s crisis, did not affect its interest in blockchain technology.</p>
<p>Japanese Prime Minister, Fumio Kishida, hammered on the roles of NFTs, blockchain, and Metaverse in the county&#8217;s digital evolution in a<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QK8h-iPU-V0" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> statement</a> in October. He cited practical examples using the digitization of national identity cards.</p>
<p>In October, the Japan Virtual and Crypto Assets Exchange Association announced plans to ease the strict screening process for listing tokens on exchanges. Kishida <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-06-08/japan-crypto-exchanges-may-scrap-system-for-screening-tokens#xj4y7vzkg" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">addressed</a> this issue in June, asking the organization to loosen its stringent rules on the screening process.</p>
<p>Some top leaders in the private sector also shared the same thoughts with the Prime Minister. On December 8, Sumitomo Mitsui Financial Group (SMBC) <a href="https://www.smfg.co.jp/news_e/pdf/e20221208_01.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced</a> an ongoing project to explore use cases of soulbound tokens (SBTs).</p>
<p>SBTs were part of Vitalik Buterin&#8217;s, co-founder of Ethereum, proposal to use tokens to represent people&#8217;s digital identity.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/fushimi-inari-shrine-g7f6ddefa3_1280-460x309.jpg" width="460" height="309" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stablecoins Flow Into Spot Exchanges, Fuel For Christmas Bitcoin Rally?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/stablecoins-fuel-christmas-bitcoin-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 20:18:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Christmas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Christmas Rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin Inflows]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin Outflows]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512649</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the number of stablecoin transactions going into spot exchanges have risen recently, something that could help fuel a Christmas Bitcoin rally. Stablecoin Deposits To Spot Exchanges Have Shown Increasing Demand Recently As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, there has been an increasing demand on spot exchanges recently. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;stablecoin exchange depositing transactions,&#8221; which measures the total number of transfers involving these fiat-tied tokens that are heading towards exchanges. Investors usually use stablecoins whenever they want to escape the volatility associated with coins like Bitcoin. Once the holders feel the prices are right to re-enter into these volatile markets, they transfer their accumulated stables to exchanges for swapping them into their desired cryptocurrency. So, a large amount of these tokens entering into exchanges can act as buying pressure for other markets, and thus provide a bullish effect to the prices of Bitcoin and other assets. Unlike the normal inflow metric, which simply measures the total amount flowing into exchanges, this indicator paints an idea about the actual demand in the market since it counts individual transfers, which can&#8217;t be inflated by a few large investors as their transaction count will be much lesser than their inflow values. Related Reading: Ethereum Active Addresses At Highest Since May 2021, Good News For ETH? Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in this metric, as well as the opposite one that keeps track of withdrawal transactions: The value of the metric seems to have increased in recent days &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As the above graph shows, the stablecoin exchange depositing transactions metric has observed some growth recently, and at the same time, the withdrawing transactions have gone down instead. This means that there is demand to buy with stables right now, while there isn&#8217;t much interest in exiting from volatile markets using these fiat-tied tokens. Related Reading: Why This Bitcoin Bearish Divergence Could Spell Doom For BTC Rally Such a situation has proved to be bullish for the price of Bitcoin in the last few months, as the previous instances of this trend in the chart display. &#8220;With the number of stablecoin deposits up-trending &#38; the number of stablecoin withdraws down-trending, the capitulation events could be reaching an end,&#8221; notes the quant. The analyst believes these inflows can fuel a new rally, saying &#8220;such pick up in retail investor sentiment could potentially lead to a Christmas rally.&#8221; It now remains to be seen whether these stablecoin inflows will turn out to be constructive for the price this time or not. Looks like BTC has observed a decline in the last few days &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView At the time of writing, Bitcoin&#8217;s price is floating around $16,900, down 1% in the last week.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows the number of stablecoin transactions going into spot exchanges have risen recently, something that could help fuel a Christmas Bitcoin rally.</p>
<h2>Stablecoin Deposits To Spot Exchanges Have Shown Increasing Demand Recently</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/quicktake/639c2bf24370fd07b6106528-Increasing-Spot-Exchange-Demand" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">post</a>, there has been an increasing demand on spot exchanges recently. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;stablecoin exchange depositing transactions,&#8221; which measures the total number of transfers involving these fiat-tied tokens that are heading towards exchanges.</p>
<p>Investors usually use <a href="https://newsbtc.com/stablecoin/whales-across-these-five-chains-are-heavy-on-stablecoins-should-you-be-too/">stablecoins</a> whenever they want to escape the volatility associated with coins like Bitcoin. Once the holders feel the prices are right to re-enter into these volatile markets, they transfer their accumulated stables to exchanges for swapping them into their desired cryptocurrency. So, a large amount of these tokens entering into exchanges can act as buying pressure for other markets, and thus provide a bullish effect to the prices of Bitcoin and other assets.</p>
<p>Unlike the normal <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-bullish-whale-exchange-inflows-down/">inflow</a> metric, which simply measures the total amount flowing into exchanges, this indicator paints an idea about the actual demand in the market since it counts individual transfers, which can&#8217;t be inflated by a few large investors as their transaction count will be much lesser than their inflow values.</p>

<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in this metric, as well as the opposite one that keeps track of withdrawal transactions:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/148277/quicktake/NjN5l4irO_b30e3488a3476fa9e2dd14833b873b0c8fe207cfac4962299476d5584e092e66.png" alt="Stablecoin Transfers To Spot Exchanges Bitcoin Fuel" width="1280" height="691" /></p>

<p>As the above graph shows, the stablecoin exchange depositing transactions metric has observed some growth recently, and at the same time, the withdrawing transactions have gone down instead. This means that there is demand to buy with stables right now, while there isn&#8217;t much interest in exiting from volatile markets using these fiat-tied tokens.</p>

<p>Such a situation has proved to be bullish for the price of Bitcoin in the last few months, as the previous instances of this trend in the chart display. &#8220;With the number of stablecoin deposits up-trending &amp; the number of stablecoin withdraws down-trending, the capitulation events could be reaching an end,&#8221; notes the quant.</p>
<p>The analyst believes these inflows can fuel a new rally, saying &#8220;such pick up in retail investor sentiment could potentially lead to a Christmas rally.&#8221; It now remains to be seen whether these stablecoin inflows will turn out to be constructive for the price this time or not.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-512664 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-18-460x255.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="460" height="255" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-18-460x255.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-18-860x477.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-18-768x426.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-18-750x416.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-18.png 974w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p>At the time of writing, <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-below-17000-mazars-binance-pause/">Bitcoin&#8217;s price</a> is floating around $16,900, down 1% in the last week.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/kanchanara-Lta5b8mPytw-unsplash-1-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Glassnode Raises Concerns Over Binance PoR Data, Was There A Mistake?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/crypto/glassnode-raises-concerns-over-binance-por-data/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ana N.]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 17:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512689</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Binance, as one of the leading crypto exchanges, tried to exhibit transparency in its operations, especially on the security of customers&#8217; funds. This led it to publish its proof of reserve (PoR) reports. However, the collapse of some firms like Celsius Network, FTX, and others has instilled fear and doubts about crypto exchanges and platforms. Investors lost confidence majorly in centralized platforms. Hence, most CEXs have taken to publishing their proof of reserve assets to indicate the safety of users&#8217; funds. Related Reading: Solana: This Minor Hiccup Didn’t Discourage Investors From Acquiring SOL – Until Today Difference In Binance&#8217;s Reported BTC Holding Some revelations hint at the under-reporting of the Binance PoR assets. For example, according to on-chain data provider Glassnode, the crypto exchange balance shows a total Bitcoin holding of almost 584,600 BTC. But the exchange reported having about 359,300 BTC in its Proof of Reserves (PoR). This discrepancy of 200,000 BTC, Glassnode points out, shows an under-reporting of its BTC holdings. The difference is worth approximately $3.4 billion at the current market price. The Ethereum balance, as reported by Binance in its proof of reserve and the on-chain data provider, was similar. Both reports showed about 4.65 million ETH held in Binance reserves. Also, data from Glassnode showed that the exchange&#8217;s balances witnessed increased volatility through December. This happened due to the FUD surrounding Binance, as the exchange faced a similar situation to FTX. The FUD had triggered increased withdrawals from the crypto exchange. Ethereum balance vs self-reported reserves Binance Records Massive Outflows The exchange has witnessed more outflows with the growing tension regarding the PoR report. In addition, according to on-chain data, Binance Bitcoin Deposit and Withdrawal Volume revealed more BTC withdrawals over the past few days. The platform recently recorded significant outflows of 57,300 BTC. However, the flows of Ether have been more stable on Binance than Bitcoin. Data on Ethereum Deposit and Withdrawal Volume shows the largest daily outflow of 456,700 ETH. Notably, most investors preferred the self-custody approach after the collapse of the FTX exchange. Also, the exchange recorded considerable volume in combined outflows of stablecoins. An equivalent of about $3.2 billion worth of stablecoins left the exchange in the last 30 days. This is because the coins remained the central part of the Binance FUD. Some withdrawn stablecoins include BUSD, USDT, USDC, and DAI. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Crystal Ball – What Happens To BTC After Christmas 2022? However, the CEO of Binance, Changpeng Zhao (CZ), took to Twitter to calm customers concerning their financial security and withdrawals  CZ assured users of the safety of their crypto assets  He noted that the &#8220;stress tests&#8221; contribute to building trust in their users and the entire crypto community.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance, as one of the leading crypto exchanges, tried to exhibit transparency in its operations, especially on the security of customers&#8217; funds. This led it to publish its proof of reserve (PoR) reports. However, the collapse of some firms like Celsius Network, FTX, and others has instilled fear and doubts about crypto exchanges and platforms.</p>
<p>Investors lost confidence majorly in centralized platforms. Hence, most CEXs have taken to publishing their proof of reserve assets to indicate the safety of users&#8217; funds.</p>

<h2>Difference In Binance&#8217;s Reported BTC Holding</h2>
<p>Some revelations hint at the under-reporting of the Binance PoR assets. For example, according to on-chain data provider <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1603566339545001984" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Glassnode</a>, the crypto exchange balance shows a total Bitcoin holding of almost 584,600 BTC. But the exchange reported having about 359,300 BTC in its Proof of Reserves (PoR).</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-512694 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT_2022-12-16_20-35-11-860x499.png" alt="Binance" width="860" height="499" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT_2022-12-16_20-35-11-860x499.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT_2022-12-16_20-35-11-460x267.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT_2022-12-16_20-35-11-768x446.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT_2022-12-16_20-35-11-750x435.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT_2022-12-16_20-35-11.png 1116w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>This discrepancy of 200,000 BTC, Glassnode points out, shows an under-reporting of its BTC holdings. The difference is worth approximately $3.4 billion at the current market price.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-512690 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-Bitcoin-Balance-vs-Self-Reported-Reserves-860x495.jpg" alt="Glassnode Raises Concerns Over Binance PoR Data, Was There Any Mistake?" width="860" height="495" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-Bitcoin-Balance-vs-Self-Reported-Reserves-860x495.jpg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-Bitcoin-Balance-vs-Self-Reported-Reserves-460x265.jpg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-Bitcoin-Balance-vs-Self-Reported-Reserves-768x442.jpg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-Bitcoin-Balance-vs-Self-Reported-Reserves-1536x885.jpg 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-Bitcoin-Balance-vs-Self-Reported-Reserves-2048x1180.jpg 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-Bitcoin-Balance-vs-Self-Reported-Reserves-750x432.jpg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-Bitcoin-Balance-vs-Self-Reported-Reserves-1140x657.jpg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>The Ethereum balance, as reported by Binance in its proof of reserve and the on-chain data provider, was similar. Both reports showed about 4.65 million ETH held in Binance reserves.</p>
<p>Also, data from Glassnode showed that the exchange&#8217;s balances witnessed increased volatility through December. This happened due to the FUD surrounding Binance, as the exchange faced a similar situation to FTX. The FUD had triggered increased withdrawals from the crypto exchange. <img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-512692 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-Ethereum-Balance-vs-Self-Reported-Reserves-860x495.jpg" alt="Glassnode Raises Concerns Over Binance PoR Data, Was There Any Mistake?" width="860" height="495" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-Ethereum-Balance-vs-Self-Reported-Reserves-860x495.jpg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-Ethereum-Balance-vs-Self-Reported-Reserves-460x265.jpg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-Ethereum-Balance-vs-Self-Reported-Reserves-768x442.jpg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-Ethereum-Balance-vs-Self-Reported-Reserves-1536x885.jpg 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-Ethereum-Balance-vs-Self-Reported-Reserves-2048x1180.jpg 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-Ethereum-Balance-vs-Self-Reported-Reserves-750x432.jpg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-Ethereum-Balance-vs-Self-Reported-Reserves-1140x657.jpg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>
<p>Ethereum balance vs self-reported reserves</p>
Binance Records Massive Outflows
<p>The exchange has witnessed more outflows with the growing tension regarding the PoR report. In addition, according to on-chain data, Binance Bitcoin Deposit and Withdrawal Volume revealed more BTC withdrawals over the past few days.</p>
<p>The platform recently recorded significant outflows of 57,300 BTC. However, the flows of Ether have been more stable on Binance than Bitcoin.</p>
<p>Data on Ethereum Deposit and Withdrawal Volume shows the largest daily outflow of 456,700 ETH. Notably, most investors preferred the self-custody approach after the collapse of the FTX exchange.</p>
<p>Also, the exchange recorded considerable volume in combined outflows of stablecoins. An equivalent of about $3.2 billion worth of stablecoins left the exchange in the last 30 days. This is because the coins remained the central part of the Binance FUD. Some withdrawn stablecoins include BUSD, USDT, USDC, and DAI.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-512693 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/K-860x495.jpg" alt="Glassnode Raises Concerns Over Binance PoR Data, Was There Any Mistake?" width="860" height="495" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/K-860x495.jpg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/K-460x265.jpg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/K-768x442.jpg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/K-1536x885.jpg 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/K-2048x1180.jpg 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/K-750x432.jpg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/K-1140x657.jpg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />

<p>However, the CEO of Binance, Changpeng Zhao (CZ), took to <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Twitter</a> to calm customers concerning their financial security and withdrawals  CZ assured users of the safety of their crypto assets  He noted that the &#8220;stress tests&#8221; contribute to building trust in their users and the entire crypto community.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screenshot-2022-12-16-203721-460x222.png" width="460" height="222" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polygon Profitability Tanks As MATIC Nosedives 5.6%</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/matic-analysis/polygon-profitability-tanks-as-matic-nosedives-5-6/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 16:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATIC performance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATIC Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATICUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[maticusdt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512675</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MATIC has had a rollercoaster of a year. Its price has fluctuated between cycle peaks and cycle lows year-to-date but has seen some good recoveries as well. However, as the week draws to a close, MATIC dove off its $0.9 cliff, and investor profitability has plummeted right along with it. MATIC Loses 5.6% In 24 Hours Over the last 24 hours, the price of MATIC is already down more than 5.6%, according to data from TradingView. The digital asset which had been able to maintain its $0.9 level for the last few weeks had eventually succumbed and drifted down. Related Reading: Whale Accumulation Paints Bullish Picture For XRP By the time the markets opened for trading on Friday, MATIC had already touched its 24-hour low of $0.84 before marking a small recovery back above $0.85. Its 5.6% decline coincided with a broader decline in the crypto market, which means it wasn’t an isolated incident for the token.  It followed the likes of Ethereum (ETH) and Binance Coin (BNB), both of which had recorded more than 5% losses in the same time period. Volume was also down across the space with MATIC seeing an 18% decline in volume.  Price trending at $0.85 &#124; Source: MATICUSD on TradingView.com The digital asset also lost about $300 million from its market cap. Nevertheless, it retains its position as the 10th largest cryptocurrency in the space, sitting right behind Cardano (ADA) which was down almost 5% in the same 24-hour period. Profitability Drops Drastically An offshoot of the recent decline in MATIC price has been the drop in profitability for investors who hold the token. Data from IntoTheBlock shows that presently, only 23% of all wallets holding the cryptocurrency are recording a profit. Related Reading: What Ethereum’s Rejection At $1,350 Says About The Cryptocurrency The vast majority of holders, accounting for 68% of all wallets, are seeing losses. The remaining 9% are sitting in the neutral territory, putting them right at the price that they purchased their coins for. Only 23% of holders in profit &#124; Source: IntoTheBlock Interestingly, unlike Bitcoin and Dogecoin, MATIC has a lower composition of long-term holders which could provide a reason for such low-profit percentages. Only 33% have held their coins for more than one year, whereas 57% have held them between one and 12 months, and 10% have only had their coins for less than one month. However, it is also important to note that MATIC’s 70% decline from its all-time high price of $2.90 in December 2021 plays a huge role in this. MATIC was exchanging hands at $5.11 at the time of this writing, down almost 8% over the last seven days. Featured image from Capital.com, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">MATIC has had a rollercoaster of a year. Its price has fluctuated between cycle peaks and cycle lows year-to-date but has seen some good recoveries as well. However, as the week draws to a close, MATIC dove off its $0.9 cliff, and investor profitability has plummeted right along with it.</p>
<h2 class="p2">MATIC Loses 5.6% In 24 Hours</h2>
<p class="p2">Over the last 24 hours, the price of MATIC is already down more than 5.6%, according to data from TradingView. The digital asset which had been able to maintain its $0.9 level for the last few weeks had eventually succumbed and drifted down.</p>

<p class="p2">By the time the markets opened for trading on Friday, MATIC had already touched its 24-hour low of $0.84 before marking a small recovery back above $0.85. Its 5.6% decline coincided with a broader decline in the crypto market, which means it wasn’t an isolated incident for the token. </p>
<p class="p2">It followed the likes of Ethereum (ETH) and Binance Coin (BNB), both of which had recorded more than 5% losses in the same time period. Volume was also down across the space with MATIC seeing an 18% decline in volume. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/QmUM49Oa/" alt="Polygon (MATIC) price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1760" /></p>

<p class="p2">The digital asset also lost about $300 million from its market cap. Nevertheless, it retains its position as the 10th largest cryptocurrency in the space, sitting right behind Cardano (ADA) which was down almost 5% in the same 24-hour period.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Profitability Drops Drastically</h2>
<p class="p2">An offshoot of the recent decline in MATIC price has been the drop in profitability for investors who hold the token. <a href="https://app.intotheblock.com/coin/MATIC" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Data from IntoTheBlock</a> shows that presently, only 23% of all wallets holding the cryptocurrency are recording a profit.</p>

<p class="p2">The vast majority of holders, accounting for 68% of all wallets, are seeing losses. The remaining 9% are sitting in the neutral territory, putting them right at the price that they purchased their coins for.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-512678 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-16-at-12.32.13.png" alt="MATIC holders in profit" width="290" height="224" /></p>

<p class="p2">Interestingly, unlike Bitcoin and Dogecoin, MATIC has a lower composition of long-term holders which could provide a reason for such low-profit percentages. Only 33% have held their coins for more than one year, whereas 57% have held them between one and 12 months, and 10% have only had their coins for less than one month. However, it is also important to note that MATIC’s 70% decline from its all-time high price of $2.90 in December 2021 plays a huge role in this.</p>
<p class="p2">MATIC was exchanging hands at $5.11 at the time of this writing, down almost 8% over the last seven days.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATIC-Polygon-460x259.jpeg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Double-Digit Losses Brings Doge Below Critical Level, More Pain To Follow?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/doge-below-critical-level/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 15:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doge price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin performance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512674</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE) has seen some of the worst declines in the last week. The meme coin is already down double-digits during this time and is also recording losses on the daily charts. While this is not out of the ordinary given the current crypto market trend, the digital asset has been pulled below important critical levels, which would imply more declines. DOGE Could Go Down Further Given Elon Musk’s recent radio silence on his crypto plans for Twitter and thus Dogecoin by extension, the meme coin has been unable to maintain its upward momentum. It is now down almost 50% from its most recent November peak of $0.15. But perhaps more concerning is the fact that its 15% decline over the last 7 days has dragged it down below the 50-day moving average. Related Reading: What Ethereum’s Rejection At $1,350 Says About The Cryptocurrency DOGE’s 50-day MA is currently sitting at $0.086, whereas the price of the digital asset has now fallen to $0.082 in the last 24 hours. Previously, the cryptocurrency had been on a bullish path as it continued to maintain its value above this level. However, a decline below this point shows that there is now less buying in the market. The meme coin is continuing to maintain above its 100-day MA of $0.075 but this could also be short-lived if the sellers continue to gain momentum in the market. If the price were to fall below the 100-day MA, it would turn forecasts for the digital asset to sell not just for the medium term, but for the long term as well. DOGE price at $0.082 &#124; Source: DOGEUSD on TradingView.com The Weekend Impact The weekend is already established as a period of low volatility. This is because while the crypto market does not see a close of the trading week, the close of the broader financial markets impacts the market as well. It leads to less volume and less momentum in the market. Related Reading: Whale Accumulation Paints Bullish Picture For XRP Given this, it is important for cryptocurrencies such as DOGE to finish strong on Friday if they are to maintain a bullish trend through the weekend. Otherwise, the impact of this low volume can push the prices further down. If  DOGE is unable to beat the $0.09 resistance level before the end of Friday, then it could see the $0.07 territory before the weekend is over. There is not much support for the meme coin at this level, so bulls will likely have to build support around $0.065 to hold off the bears if this happens. However, if the digital asset can finish strong above $0.09, then there is the possibility of a rally above $0.1. DOGE was trading at $0.0826 at the time of this writing, according to data from Coinmarketcap. It is down 5.85% in the last 24 hours and 25.83% in the last seven days. Featured image from Freepik, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Dogecoin (DOGE) has seen some of the worst declines in the last week. The meme coin is already down double-digits during this time and is also recording losses on the daily charts. While this is not out of the ordinary given the current crypto market trend, the digital asset has been pulled below important critical levels, which would imply more declines.</p>
<h2 class="p2">DOGE Could Go Down Further</h2>
<p class="p2">Given Elon Musk’s recent radio silence on his crypto plans for Twitter and thus Dogecoin by extension, the meme coin has been unable to maintain its upward momentum. It is now down almost 50% from its most recent November peak of $0.15. But perhaps more concerning is the fact that its 15% decline over the last 7 days has dragged it down below the 50-day moving average.</p>

<p class="p2">DOGE’s 50-day MA is currently sitting at $0.086, whereas the price of the digital asset has now fallen to $0.082 in the last 24 hours. Previously, the cryptocurrency had been on a bullish path as it continued to maintain its value above this level. However, a decline below this point shows that there is now less buying in the market.</p>
<p class="p2">The meme coin is continuing to maintain above its 100-day MA of $0.075 but this could also be short-lived if the sellers continue to gain momentum in the market. If the price were to fall below the 100-day MA, it would turn forecasts for the digital asset to sell not just for the medium term, but for the long term as well.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/J8d5imrN/" alt="price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1760" /></p>

<h2 class="p2">The Weekend Impact</h2>
<p class="p2">The weekend is already established as a period of low volatility. This is because while the crypto market does not see a close of the trading week, the close of the broader financial markets impacts the market as well. It leads to less volume and less momentum in the market.</p>

<p class="p2">Given this, it is important for cryptocurrencies such as DOGE to finish strong on Friday if they are to maintain a bullish trend through the weekend. Otherwise, the impact of this low volume can push the prices further down.</p>
<p class="p2">If  DOGE is unable to beat the $0.09 resistance level before the end of Friday, then it could see the $0.07 territory before the weekend is over. There is not much support for the meme coin at this level, so bulls will likely have to build support around $0.065 to hold off the bears if this happens. However, if the digital asset can finish strong above $0.09, then there is the possibility of a rally above $0.1.</p>
<p class="p2">DOGE was trading at $0.0826 at the time of this writing, according to data from <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Coinmarketcap</a>. It is down 5.85% in the last 24 hours and 25.83% in the last seven days.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Dogecoin-1-460x307.jpeg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>ADA Price Sheds 5% In The Last 7 Days Even As Trade Volume Soars</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/ada-price-down-5-in-last-week/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 14:37:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[federal reserve]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512669</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cardano has been on the downside since ADA reached an all-time-high of $3.10 back in September 2021. As of writing, the 9th top crypto has dropped 5% in the last seven days. In comparison, major cryptocurrencies like Ethereum lost over 4.5%, and Bitcoin shed 2% in the same timeframe. However, CoinMarketCap displays a rise in trade volume from $221,898,095 to $277,239,103, which represents an increase of over 25%. Nonetheless, as the price of ADA continues to decline, this could be the beginning of something else for Cardano. Macroeconomics At Play In response to persistently strong inflation in the United States, the Federal Reserve had to increase interest rates by 50 basis points, taking it from 4.25% to 4.50%. Despite the fact that inflation has been prevented from fully exploding since the Fed&#8217;s prior rate hikes, they still intend to boost interest rates to 5%, which could be a problem for Cardano investors. Related Reading: Solana: This Minor Hiccup Didn’t Discourage Investors From Acquiring SOL – Until Today ADA total market cap at $9.8 billion &#124; Chart: TradingView.com Since the central bank&#8217;s interest rate hike, ADA&#8217;s price has broken through the $0.3 support level, however it failed to keep the momentum and is now trading at $0.28. This significant price decline suggests that the rumored Ethereum-killer might be losing its aggressiveness. Cardano&#8217;s TVL is only $71.05 million, compared to Ethereum&#8217;s $23.4 billion. Additionally, NFT sales on the ecosystem have decreased, exerting additional downward pressure on ADA&#8217;s price. On Optimism &#38; Following The Right Path Despite the confluence of these events, the leaders of Cardano appear optimistic about the future. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Crystal Ball – What Happens To BTC After Christmas 2022? Jerry Fragiskatos, chief commercial officer at Input Output Global, stated in an interview with crypto space influencer Scott Merkel that he believes Cardano is following the right path. “I think time will tell, and I think we’re taking the right approach,” he said. In addition, he compared the ecosystem&#8217;s dire state to the corporations that survived the dot-com bubble. This comment relates to analogies between the demise of FTX and the dot-com era of the early 2000s. He also discussed the manner in which ADA tokens are distributed to investors, highlighting the fact that there are few whales and ecosystem insiders. As Fragiskatos stated, only time will tell if ADA survives the current bear market.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cardano has been on the downside since ADA reached an all-time-high of $3.10 back in September 2021. As of writing, the 9th top crypto has <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/cardano" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">dropped 5%</a> in the last seven days. In comparison, major cryptocurrencies like Ethereum lost over 4.5%, and Bitcoin shed 2% in the same timeframe.</p>
<p>However, CoinMarketCap displays<a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/cardano/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> a rise</a> in trade volume from $221,898,095 to $277,239,103, which represents an increase of over 25%.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, as the price of ADA continues to decline, this could be the beginning of something else for Cardano.</p>
<h2>Macroeconomics At Play</h2>
<p>In response to persistently strong <a href="https://www.newstalkzb.co.nz/on-air/heather-du-plessis-allan-drive/audio/deborah-lambie-milford-asset-management-investment-analyst-on-the-us-cpi-data-and-what-it-means-for-inflation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">inflation</a> in the United States, the Federal Reserve had to increase interest rates by 50 basis points, taking it from 4.25% to 4.50%.</p>
<p>Despite the fact that inflation has been prevented from fully exploding since the Fed&#8217;s prior rate hikes, they still intend to boost interest rates to 5%, which could be a problem for Cardano investors.</p>

<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/V6d20Po6/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>

<p>Since the central bank&#8217;s interest rate hike, ADA&#8217;s price has broken through the $0.3 support level, however it failed to keep the momentum and is now trading at $0.28. This significant price decline suggests that the rumored Ethereum-killer might be losing its aggressiveness.</p>
<p>Cardano&#8217;s <a href="https://defillama.com/chain/Cardano" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">TVL</a> is only $71.05 million, compared to Ethereum&#8217;s <a href="https://defillama.com/chain/Ethereum" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">$23.4</a> billion. Additionally, <a href="https://www.cryptoslam.io/blockchains/cardano" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">NFT sales</a> on the ecosystem have decreased, exerting additional downward pressure on ADA&#8217;s price.</p>
<h2>On Optimism &amp; Following The Right Path</h2>
<p>Despite the confluence of these events, the leaders of Cardano appear optimistic about the future.</p>

<p>Jerry Fragiskatos, chief commercial officer at Input Output Global, stated in an<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wAXUtYovHv0" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> interview</a> with crypto space influencer Scott Merkel that he believes Cardano is following the right path.</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>“I think time will tell, and I think we’re taking the right approach,” he said.</strong></p></blockquote>
<p>In addition, he compared the ecosystem&#8217;s dire state to the corporations that survived the dot-com bubble. This comment relates to analogies between the demise of FTX and the <a href="https://businessinsider.mx/ftx-collapse-crypto-crash-dot-com-bubble-tech-stocks-investing-2022-11/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">dot-com</a> era of the early 2000s.</p>
<p>He also discussed the manner in which ADA tokens are distributed to investors, highlighting the fact that there are few whales and ecosystem insiders.</p>
<p>As Fragiskatos stated, only time will tell if ADA survives the current bear market.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/a-3-460x299.png" width="460" height="299" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Plummets Below $17,000 After Audit Firm Mazars Pauses Work For Binance</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-below-17000-mazars-binance-pause/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 14:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cnbc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mazars]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512641</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin price has once again fallen below the $17,000 mark after it became known that the auditing firm Mazars will pause its work with Binance. Already in the last few days, rumors and FUD about Binance intensified. As NewsBTC reported, investors are worried that Binance is not keeping enough reserves on hand for all their client funds. The impetus for the outcry was a proof-of-reserves conducted by Mazars that raised numerous new questions instead of answering the old ones. Remarkably, the auditing firm worked not only with Binance but also with other cryptocurrency exchanges such as Crypto.com and KuCoin to attest to proof-of-reserves. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Prediction: Why BTC Could Still Tumble Below $16K An email to Binance now indicates that Mazars is pausing all work for crypto clients. &#8220;Unfortunately, this means that we will not be able to work with Mazars for the moment,&#8221; a Binance spokesperson said. Binance Rumors Are Dragging Down Market Sentiment The crypto market is not settling down after the collapse of FTX. Rumors of insufficient backing of client funds by Binance, Tether (USDT), and Digital Currency Group&#8217;s troubles as a result of Genesis Trading&#8217;s liquidity problems hang over the crypto market like a sword of Damocles. Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao had tried to mitigate the turmoil several times in recent days. Thus, he took questions from the community in an AMA and appeared in an interview on CNBC. Related Reading: Bitcoin Miner Capitulation Is An Exaggerated Fear, Analyst Claims When asked if Binance would be able to pay out $2.1 billion if that amount was due. CZ said, &#8220;We are financially okay. We are financially strong.&#8221; The Binance CEO was also asked why the company has not yet disclosed its liabilities and whether the exchange plans to do so. CZ said: We are working with the audit firms to audit the financial liabilities. [..] Audits don&#8217;t reveal any problem. CNBC anchors interrupted CZ and made the claim that an audit by one of the Big Four could put all the rumors to rest. &#8220;When you say that some of them don&#8217;t want to work with you, that raises questions! They don&#8217;t want to work with you because you don&#8217;t have the documentation and data that would make them feel comfortable&#8221;, they said. CZ, for his part, refuted this statement and claimed that &#8220;actually many of them do not know how to audit crypto exchanges.&#8221; Binance CEO CZ on CNBC: Many big four firms do not know how to audit crypto exchanges. pic.twitter.com/r3C15cMwbK &#8212; unusual_whales (@unusual_whales) December 15, 2022 Bitcoin Price Plunges Below $17,000 The interview has in no way helped to calm the crypto market, especially since CZ was also unable to provide a satisfactory response via Twitter in the aftermath. CZ only retweeted the following and stated in his newest tweet that &#8220;Blockchains are public, permanent records. It&#8217;s the most auditable ledger.&#8221; The pausing of the collaboration with Mazars also puts the interview in a bad light. Mazars has not yet communicated why it has paused cooperation with Binance and the other crypto exchanges, other than that the term &#8220;audit&#8221; would be used falsely. Bitcoin investors have taken the interview overwhelmingly bearish. Within the last six hours, the Bitcoin price has lost around $500 and was at $17,004 at press time.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin price has once again fallen below the $17,000 mark after it became known that the auditing firm Mazars will pause its work with Binance. Already in the last few days, <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/fud-intensifies-can-binance-survive-or-is-this-the-end/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">rumors and FUD</a> about Binance intensified.</p>
<p>As NewsBTC reported, investors are worried that Binance is not keeping enough reserves on hand for all their client funds. The impetus for the outcry was a proof-of-reserves conducted by Mazars that raised numerous new questions instead of answering the old ones.</p>
<p>Remarkably, the auditing firm worked not only with Binance but also with other cryptocurrency exchanges such as Crypto.com and KuCoin to attest to proof-of-reserves.</p>

<p>An <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/auditing-firm-mazars-pauses-binance-112511798.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">email</a> to Binance now indicates that Mazars is pausing all work for crypto clients. &#8220;Unfortunately, this means that we will not be able to work with Mazars for the moment,&#8221; a Binance spokesperson said.</p>
<h2>Binance Rumors Are Dragging Down Market Sentiment</h2>
<p>The crypto market is not settling down after the collapse of FTX. Rumors of insufficient backing of client funds by Binance, Tether (USDT), and Digital Currency Group&#8217;s troubles as a result of Genesis Trading&#8217;s liquidity problems hang over the crypto market like a sword of Damocles.</p>
<p>Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao had tried to mitigate the turmoil several times in recent days. Thus, he took questions from the community in an AMA and appeared in an interview on CNBC.</p>

<p>When asked if Binance would be able to pay out $2.1 billion if that amount was due. CZ said, &#8220;We are financially okay. We are financially strong.&#8221; The Binance CEO was also asked why the company has not yet disclosed its liabilities and whether the exchange plans to do so. CZ said:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>We are working with the audit firms to audit the financial liabilities. [..] Audits don&#8217;t reveal any problem.</strong></p></blockquote>
<p>CNBC anchors interrupted CZ and made the claim that an audit by one of the Big Four could put all the rumors to rest. &#8220;When you say that some of them don&#8217;t want to work with you, that raises questions! They don&#8217;t want to work with you because you don&#8217;t have the documentation and data that would make them feel comfortable&#8221;, they said.</p>
<p>CZ, for his part, refuted this statement and claimed that &#8220;actually many of them do not know how to audit crypto exchanges.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Binance CEO CZ on CNBC:</p>
<p>Many big four firms do not know how to audit crypto exchanges. <a href="https://t.co/r3C15cMwbK" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/r3C15cMwbK</a></p>
<p>&mdash; unusual_whales (@unusual_whales) <a href="https://twitter.com/unusual_whales/status/1603503573220069376?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">December 15, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Plunges Below $17,000</h2>
<p>The interview has in no way helped to calm the crypto market, especially since CZ was also unable to provide a satisfactory response via Twitter in the aftermath. CZ only retweeted the following and <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1603693488436137987" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">stated</a> in his newest tweet that &#8220;Blockchains are public, permanent records. It&#8217;s the most auditable ledger.&#8221;</p>
<p>The pausing of the collaboration with Mazars also puts the interview in a bad light. Mazars has not yet communicated why it has paused cooperation with Binance and the other crypto exchanges, other than that the term &#8220;audit&#8221; would be used falsely.</p>
<p>Bitcoin investors have taken the interview overwhelmingly bearish. Within the last six hours, the Bitcoin price has lost around $500 and was at $17,004 at press time.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-512654 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-16_14-06-01.png" alt="Bitcoin BTC USD 2022-12-16" width="2958" height="1605" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-16_14-06-01.png 2958w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-16_14-06-01-460x250.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-16_14-06-01-860x467.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-16_14-06-01-768x417.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-16_14-06-01-1536x833.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-16_14-06-01-2048x1111.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-16_14-06-01-750x407.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-16_14-06-01-1140x619.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2958px) 100vw, 2958px" />
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/CZ-460x294.png" width="460" height="294" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>End Of Litecoin Rally? LTC Plunges 7% In Last 24 Hours</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/litecoin-rally-ltc-plunges-7-24-hours/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 13:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin bullish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin Bullish Momentum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin Plunge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin Rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc/usd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512616</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Litecoin has observed a plunge of more than 7% in the last 24 hours, suggesting that the coin&#8217;s bullish momentum may have come to an end. Litecoin Drops Hard TodayS But Is Up 20% In The Last Month While the rest of the crypto market was struggling, LTC enjoyed some sharp bullish momentum in the third leg of November, leading some to believe the &#8220;pre-halving rally&#8221; had begun for the crypto. But the first half of December proved disappointing as the coin mostly consolidated, and now in the last two days, the trend seems to have completely reversed as Litecoin has been rapidly going down instead. At the time of writing, LTC is trading around $69, down 7% in the last 24 hours. The below chart shows how the asset&#8217;s price has changed in recent months. The rise in the coin's value during the last three months &#124; Source: LTCUSD on TradingView As the graph displays, Litecoin was initially on the way up in early November and crossed $70. But then the FTX crash struck the market, and the coin&#8217;s price plummeted to a low of less than $50. However, unlike other big cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum, LTC quickly found its feet and started on a steady recovery. In the third part of November, the coin rapidly blew up and shattered the peak seen just before the FTX debacle, ending the month in double-digit gains while the rest of the sector was deep in the red. Related Reading: Why This Bitcoin Bearish Divergence Could Spell Doom For BTC Rally LTC was consolidating this month after setting a peak above $80, but holders were optimistic as the coin&#8217;s halving, an event where block production would be cut in half, is scheduled to take place next year. Historically, halvings have usually had a bullish effect on the prices of cryptocurrencies due to supply-demand dynamics, as supply production is reduced by 50% following them. Related Reading: Ethereum Active Addresses At Highest Since May 2021, Good News For ETH? In the last couple of days, LTC has sharply plunged instead and has retreated below the pre-FTX peak. This could mean that the coin may have lost its recent bullish steam and that this may not have been the halving buildup run that some thought it would be. Though, even after this decline, LTC investors are still 20% in profit over the last month. LTC Slips Further Down The Market Cap List During the recent consolidation, LTC lost its spot as the 12th largest crypto by market cap to Dai (DAI), and now with this latest drawdown, the coin has dropped even lower to 14th as Tron (TRX) takes over. LTC market cap continues to drop &#124; Source: CoinMarketCap Still, when compared to October&#8217;s end when Litecoin was 20th on the list, the coin&#8217;s current position is a major improvement.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin has observed a plunge of more than 7% in the last 24 hours, suggesting that the coin&#8217;s bullish momentum may have come to an end.</p>
<h2>Litecoin Drops Hard TodayS But Is Up 20% In The Last Month</h2>
<p>While the rest of the crypto market was struggling, LTC enjoyed some sharp bullish momentum in the third leg of November, leading some to believe the &#8220;<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin-halving-stock-to-flow/">pre-halving rally</a>&#8221; had begun for the crypto. But the first half of December proved disappointing as the coin mostly consolidated, and now in the last two days, the trend seems to have completely reversed as Litecoin has been rapidly going down instead.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, LTC is trading around $69, down 7% in the last 24 hours. The below chart shows how the asset&#8217;s price has changed in recent months.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-512619 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-17-460x255.png" alt="Litecoin Price Chart" width="460" height="255" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-17-460x255.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-17-860x477.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-17-768x426.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-17-750x416.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-17.png 973w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p>As the graph displays, Litecoin was initially on the way up in early November and crossed $70. But then the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/ftx-crash-triggers-major-selloff-in-solana-price-how-deep-will-sol-dive/">FTX crash</a> struck the market, and the coin&#8217;s price plummeted to a low of less than $50. However, unlike other big cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum, LTC quickly found its feet and started on a steady recovery.</p>
<p>In the third part of November, the coin rapidly blew up and shattered the peak seen just before the FTX debacle, ending the month in double-digit gains while the rest of the sector was deep in the red.</p>

<p>LTC was consolidating this month after setting a peak above $80, but holders were optimistic as the coin&#8217;s halving, an event where block production would be cut in half, is scheduled to take place next year. Historically, halvings have usually had a bullish effect on the prices of cryptocurrencies due to supply-demand dynamics, as supply production is reduced by 50% following them.</p>

<p>In the last couple of days, LTC has sharply plunged instead and has retreated below the pre-FTX peak. This could mean that the coin may have lost its recent bullish steam and that this may not have been the halving buildup run that some thought it would be. Though, even after this decline, LTC investors are still 20% in profit over the last month.</p>
<h2>LTC Slips Further Down The Market Cap List</h2>
<p>During the recent consolidation, LTC lost its spot as the 12th largest crypto by <a href="https://newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-decline-sinks-15th-market-cap-list/">market cap</a> to Dai (DAI), and now with this latest drawdown, the coin has dropped even lower to 14th as Tron (TRX) takes over.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-512618 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/details-460x150.png" alt="Litecoin Market Cap" width="460" height="150" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/details-460x150.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/details-860x281.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/details-768x251.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/details-750x245.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/details-1140x372.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/details.png 1272w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p>Still, when compared to October&#8217;s end when Litecoin was 20th on the list, the coin&#8217;s current position is a major improvement.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/michael-fortsch-fYSVVQqiqPs-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana: This Minor Hiccup Didn&#8217;t Discourage Investors From Acquiring SOL &#8211; Until Today</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/solana-minor-hiccup-didnt-discourage-investors/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 13:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana Ecosystem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tags: Federal Reserve]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512647</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On the day following the implementation by the US Federal Reserve of the 50-basis point hike, Solana (SOL) saw accumulation rather than a sell-off, despite the altcoin&#8217;s 4% decline. Prices for Bitcoin and Ethereum and other cryptocurrencies fell on December 14 as reports surfaced that the central bank raised its interest rates. The situation is different now, though. CoinGecko reports that the token dropped another 5% today, with significant declines over the past week, biweekly, and monthly periods. SOL price is currently 135% lower than its intrinsic value. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Crystal Ball – What Happens To BTC After Christmas 2022? SOL Change In Public Opinion The futures market for SOL coin indicates a positive investment rate from yesterday, confirming the optimistic tone of on-chain analytics. However, it soon turned negative, reflecting a change in public opinion regarding SOL. Speculation may be to blame for the recent price increase of the altcoin and subsequent price drop, as is normal with most cryptos. The current support at $13.38 is important because the market is already factoring in the central bank&#8217;s interest rate hike. Even if there is news of greater institutional interest in crypto and blockchain technology, the broader crypto market will be dragged down if big cryptocurrencies like BTC and ETH continue to suffer. SOL total market cap at $4.9 billion &#124; Chart: TradingView.com Solana: Down But Not Finished The crypto research firm Messari has recently published a comprehensive assessment of the Solana Ecosystem. Positively, even though FTX and Solana are tightly intertwined because of Alameda, the ecosystem has continued to implement technical advancements centered on the key pillars of Solana, namely speed and scalability. According to the overview, Solana&#8217;s DeFi space has been severely damaged. However, the environment is not dead. The study indicates that there are numerous applications on Solana, despite the fact that the TVL has decreased by a staggering 70% since the FTX disaster. Related Reading: LINK Still On ETH Whales’ Shopping Cart Despite Dismal Performance In Last 7 Days In the first quarter of 2023, Helium will migrate all of its activities on Solana&#8217;s blockchain. This is an extremely positive venture for both Helium and Solana, which might boost the price of HNT and SOL. However, investors in SOL should be wary of short- and medium-term losses, as the rising correlation between the token and BTC and ETH could render Messari&#8217;s research bearish. SOL investors anticipate greater long-term gains as the Solana Ecosystem evolves and as the market strives to recover from the catastrophe brought about by the implosion of FTX.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On the day following the implementation by the US<a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/business/economy/interest-rate-increase-december-2022-federal-reserve-how-much-rcna61297" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> Federal Reserve</a> of the 50-basis point hike, Solana (SOL) saw accumulation rather than a sell-off, despite the altcoin&#8217;s 4% <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/solana-this-minor-setback-did-not-stop-sol-accumulation-by-day-traders/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">decline.</a></p>
<p>Prices for Bitcoin and Ethereum and other cryptocurrencies fell on December 14 as reports surfaced that the central bank raised its interest rates.</p>
<p>The situation is different now, though. CoinGecko reports that the token dropped another 5% today, with significant declines over the past week, biweekly, and monthly periods. SOL price is currently 135% lower than its intrinsic value.</p>

<h2>SOL Change In Public Opinion</h2>
<p>The futures market for SOL coin indicates a positive investment rate from yesterday, confirming the optimistic tone of on-chain analytics. However, it soon turned <a href="https://www.coinglass.com/funding/SOL" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">negative</a>, reflecting a change in public opinion regarding SOL.</p>
<p>Speculation may be to blame for the recent price increase of the altcoin and subsequent price drop, as is normal with most cryptos. The current support at $13.38 is important because the market is already factoring in the central bank&#8217;s interest rate hike.</p>
<p>Even if there is news of greater institutional interest in crypto and blockchain technology, the broader crypto market will be dragged down if big cryptocurrencies like BTC and ETH continue to suffer.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/HEsS6K80/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>

<h2>Solana: Down But Not Finished</h2>
<p>The crypto research firm Messari has recently published a comprehensive <a href="https://messari.io/report/solana-ecosystem-overview?referrer=all-research" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">assessment</a> of the Solana Ecosystem.</p>
<p>Positively, even though FTX and Solana are tightly intertwined because of Alameda, the ecosystem has continued to implement technical advancements centered on the key pillars of Solana, namely speed and scalability.</p>
<p>According to the overview, Solana&#8217;s DeFi space has been severely damaged. However, the environment is not dead. The study indicates that there are numerous applications on Solana, despite the fact that the <a href="https://defillama.com/chain/Solana?currency=USD" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">TVL</a> has decreased by a staggering 70% since the FTX disaster.</p>

<p>In the first quarter of 2023, Helium will migrate all of its activities on Solana&#8217;s blockchain.</p>
<p>This is an extremely positive venture for both Helium and Solana, which might boost the price of HNT and SOL.</p>
<p>However, investors in SOL should be wary of short- and medium-term losses, as the rising correlation between the token and BTC and ETH could render Messari&#8217;s research bearish.</p>
<p>SOL investors anticipate greater long-term gains as the Solana Ecosystem evolves and as the market strives to recover from the catastrophe brought about by the implosion of FTX.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Solana-1-460x347.png" width="460" height="347" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Miner Capitulation Is An Exaggerated Fear, Analyst Claims</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-miner-capitulation-is-exaggerated/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[miner]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512623</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Jaran Mellerud of Hashrate Index recently released a &#8216;comprehensive analysis&#8217; on the thesis that a Bitcoin miner capitulation could put massive selling pressure on the market, causing a crash.  The topic has been a recurring part of the discussion in recent weeks as to whether the BTC bear market could be prolonged by the tight mining industry. Charles Edwards of Capriole Investments stated two weeks ago that miner capitulation has begun, as indicated by hash ribbons. Investment giant VanEck also recently published an analysis that the bear market could extend into the second quarter of 2023 due to miner capitulation. The company predicted that BTC could bottom at $10,000 to $12,000 in Q1 2023. Mellerud counters this assumption by saying that the miners&#8217; total BTC holdings are not significant enough to move the spot market. Are Bitcoin Miners Not As Powerful As Believed? The Hashrate Index analyst writes that all miners must collectively own a significant portion of the circulating supply to have a meaningful impact. However, the question of the number of their holdings is a great mystery, although estimates do exist. On-chain data providers such as CoinMetrics and Glassnode provide the best-known guesses, by grouping wallet addresses according to their proximity to the Coinbase transaction. Mellerud claims that these numbers likely significantly overestimate miners&#8217; Bitcoin holdings. CoinMetrics estimates 820,000 BTC for all miners worldwide. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Prediction: Why BTC Could Still Tumble Below $16K Another possibility is to derive the number from the Bitcoin holdings of public miners. Using these figures, Mellerud estimates 470,000 Bitcoin. With 19.2 million BTC currently in circulation, miners thus hold only between 2% and 4%. &#8220;The public&#8217;s image of miners as enormous bitcoin holders and influential market participants might have been accurate ten years ago [&#8230;]. Times have changed, and miners no longer hold a meaningful share of the Bitcoin supply,&#8221; Mellerud claims. BTC Holdings By Miners Vs. Spot Volume However, in terms of potential selling pressure, it is also important to know the size of the spot market to find out how well the market can absorb the selling pressure. According to Mellerud, the best way to estimate the absolute selling pressure of miners is to look at how much BTC they receive each day. Generally speaking, about 900 freshly minted Bitcoins flow into miners&#8217; wallets every day. When miners sell less than 100% of their production, they accumulate Bitcoin; when they sell more than 100%, they reduce their holdings. The chart below shows that Bitcoin sales by miners peaked in June when they sold 350% of their production. For the rest of the year, the rate was 150% at maximum. Using Binance spot volume, Mellerud shows in the chart below that a selling pressure of 100% of the production accounts for only 0.2% of the spot volume. At 200%, it represents only 0.4%, and at 300%, it is still only 0.6% of the total volume. Mellerud concludes: Due to the small share of Bitcoin miners&#8217; hypothetical volume compared to Bitcoin&#8217;s total spot volume, we see that Bitcoin should have more than enough liquidity in its spot market to accommodate the selling pressure from miners. In a worst-case scenario by Mellerud, in which all miners dump their entire holdings within 30 days (equally distributed over all days), the selling pressure of 470,000 BTC (4,900 BTC per day) would only amount to 1% of the total spot volume. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Poised To Continue Its Rally As Whales Turn Bullish After 14 Months Only if the holdings actually amount to 820,000 BTC and they were all liquidated within 30 days, it might lead to a crash in the Bitcoin price, Mellerud says. Miners would then account for nearly 7% of the spot volume. The Bitcoin price is currently experiencing a plunge of around 3.5% within the last few hours. At press time, BTC was trading at $17,035.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jaran Mellerud of Hashrate Index recently released a &#8216;comprehensive analysis&#8217; on the thesis that a Bitcoin miner capitulation could put massive selling pressure on the market, causing a crash.  The topic has been a recurring part of the discussion in recent weeks as to whether the BTC bear market could be prolonged by the tight mining industry.</p>
<p>Charles Edwards of Capriole Investments stated two weeks ago that miner capitulation <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/hash-ribbon-reversal-signals-bitcoin-miner-capitulation-phase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">has begun</a>, as indicated by hash ribbons. Investment giant VanEck also recently <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/vanecks-bitcoin-prediction-stands-at-10k-12k-by-q1-2023/">published</a> an analysis that the bear market could extend into the second quarter of 2023 due to miner capitulation. The company predicted that BTC could bottom at $10,000 to $12,000 in Q1 2023.</p>
<p>Mellerud counters this assumption by saying that the miners&#8217; total BTC holdings are not significant enough to move the spot market.</p>
<h2>Are Bitcoin Miners Not As Powerful As Believed?</h2>
<p>The Hashrate Index analyst <a href="https://twitter.com/JMellerud/status/1603681161405812736" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">writes </a>that all miners must collectively own a significant portion of the circulating supply to have a meaningful impact. However, the question of the number of their holdings is a great mystery, although estimates do exist.</p>
<p>On-chain data providers such as CoinMetrics and Glassnode provide the best-known guesses, by grouping wallet addresses according to their proximity to the Coinbase transaction. Mellerud claims that these numbers likely significantly overestimate miners&#8217; Bitcoin holdings. CoinMetrics estimates 820,000 BTC for all miners worldwide.</p>

<p>Another possibility is to derive the number from the Bitcoin holdings of public miners. Using these figures, Mellerud estimates 470,000 Bitcoin.</p>
<p>With 19.2 million BTC currently in circulation, miners thus hold only between 2% and 4%. &#8220;The public&#8217;s image of miners as enormous bitcoin holders and influential market participants might have been accurate ten years ago [&#8230;]. Times have changed, and miners no longer hold a meaningful share of the Bitcoin supply,&#8221; Mellerud claims.</p>
<h2>BTC Holdings By Miners Vs. Spot Volume</h2>
<p>However, in terms of potential selling pressure, it is also important to know the size of the spot market to find out how well the market can absorb the selling pressure. According to Mellerud, the best way to estimate the absolute selling pressure of miners is to look at how much BTC they receive each day.</p>
<p>Generally speaking, about 900 freshly minted Bitcoins flow into miners&#8217; wallets every day. When miners sell less than 100% of their production, they accumulate Bitcoin; when they sell more than 100%, they reduce their holdings.</p>
<p>The chart below shows that Bitcoin sales by miners peaked in June when they sold 350% of their production. For the rest of the year, the rate was 150% at maximum.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-512628 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Public-miners-BTC-sold-by-month-860x567.png" alt="Public Bitcoin miners BTC sold by month" width="860" height="567" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Public-miners-BTC-sold-by-month-860x567.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Public-miners-BTC-sold-by-month-460x303.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Public-miners-BTC-sold-by-month-768x506.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Public-miners-BTC-sold-by-month-1536x1013.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Public-miners-BTC-sold-by-month-750x495.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Public-miners-BTC-sold-by-month-1140x752.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Public-miners-BTC-sold-by-month.png 1624w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>Using Binance spot volume, Mellerud shows in the chart below that a selling pressure of 100% of the production accounts for only 0.2% of the spot volume. At 200%, it represents only 0.4%, and at 300%, it is still only 0.6% of the total volume. Mellerud concludes:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>Due to the small share of Bitcoin miners&#8217; hypothetical volume compared to Bitcoin&#8217;s total spot volume, we see that Bitcoin should have more than enough liquidity in its spot market to accommodate the selling pressure from miners.</strong></p></blockquote>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-512627 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/miners-potential-btc-sales-as-share-of-daily-spot-volume-860x567.png" alt="Miners potential btc sales as share of daily spot volume" width="860" height="567" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/miners-potential-btc-sales-as-share-of-daily-spot-volume-860x567.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/miners-potential-btc-sales-as-share-of-daily-spot-volume-460x303.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/miners-potential-btc-sales-as-share-of-daily-spot-volume-768x506.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/miners-potential-btc-sales-as-share-of-daily-spot-volume-1536x1013.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/miners-potential-btc-sales-as-share-of-daily-spot-volume-750x495.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/miners-potential-btc-sales-as-share-of-daily-spot-volume-1140x752.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/miners-potential-btc-sales-as-share-of-daily-spot-volume.png 1624w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>In a worst-case scenario by Mellerud, in which all miners dump their entire holdings within 30 days (equally distributed over all days), the selling pressure of 470,000 BTC (4,900 BTC per day) would only amount to 1% of the total spot volume.</p>

<p>Only if the holdings actually amount to 820,000 BTC and they were all liquidated within 30 days, it might lead to a crash in the Bitcoin price, Mellerud says. Miners would then account for nearly 7% of the spot volume.</p>
<p>The Bitcoin price is currently experiencing a plunge of around 3.5% within the last few hours. At press time, BTC was trading at $17,035.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-512631 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-16_12-38-26.png" alt="Bitcoin BTC USD 2022-12-16" width="2954" height="1614" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-16_12-38-26.png 2954w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-16_12-38-26-460x251.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-16_12-38-26-860x470.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-16_12-38-26-768x420.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-16_12-38-26-1536x839.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-16_12-38-26-2048x1119.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-16_12-38-26-750x410.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-16_12-38-26-1140x623.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2954px) 100vw, 2954px" />
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/cryptocurrency-g9db57b6ed_1280-460x310.jpg" width="460" height="310" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/

Object Caching 199/201 objects using apc
Page Caching using disk: enhanced (Page is feed) 
Database Caching 35/42 queries in 0.007 seconds using memcached

Served from: newsbtc.com @ 2022-12-16 22:14:51 by W3 Total Cache
-->