<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 20:52:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>XRP Allegedly Attacked By SEC&#8217;s Hinman For Ethereum&#8217;s Benefit</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-allegedly-attacked-by-secs-hinman-for-ethereums-benefit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 22:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538309</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The legal battle between Ripple and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has taken a new twist as top lawyers accuse former SEC Director William Hinman of being paid to attack XRP in favor of Ethereum (ETH).  Following the release of Hinman&#8217;s emails and drafts of his June 2018 speech, pro-XRP attorney John Deaton expressed his frustration with the intent of the released documents on a recent live CryptoLaw podcast.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Bullish Momentum Building: Expert Predicts Rise To $27,200 Payments To Disparage XRP In Favor Of Ethereum? Jeremy Hogan, lawyer and cryptocurrency expert, also weighed in on the matter alleging that former SEC Director of Corporate Finance, Bill Hinman, was paid to give a speech in which he declared that Ethereum was not a security.  According to Hogan, Ripple, a leading cryptocurrency company, has suggested that Hinman was paid by the Ethereum Foundation or someone related to Ethereum to give the speech and give Ethereum a free pass. Hogan&#8217;s claims are based on email exchanges between Hinman and his colleagues, which reportedly show that Hinman had already named his first email &#8220;the Ether speech&#8221; before he began crafting the speech.  This, according to Hogan, suggests that &#8220;right from the get-go&#8221;, Hinman is saying that ETH is not a security, and that was the point of him making the speech. Hinman&#8217;s speech, which was delivered in 2018, was seen by many in the cryptocurrency industry as a landmark moment in which the SEC effectively declared that Ethereum was not a security.  This was seen as a significant victory for Ethereum and the wider cryptocurrency industry, as it provided clarity on how the SEC would regulate cryptocurrencies. However, Hogan has suggested that the speech was not only a free pass for Ethereum but also an attack on XRP, which was at the time Ethereum&#8217;s biggest competition. Hogan&#8217;s claims are based on Ripple&#8217;s ongoing legal battle with the SEC, in which Ripple has argued that XRP is not a security and should not be regulated as such. Related Reading: Percentage Of ETH Addresses In Profit Reaches 5-Month Low Hogan&#8217;s allegations are likely to fuel speculation about the relationship between the SEC and the cryptocurrency industry, and the extent to which the SEC&#8217;s decisions are influenced by external factors. However, it is important to note that Hogan&#8217;s claims are based on speculation and have not been proven. At present, the value of XRP stands at $0.4731, indicating a marginal recovery of 0.6% over the past day. This comes after a dip to $0.4564 on Wednesday. Despite the recent drop, XRP enthusiasts remain optimistic and are looking forward to a positive outcome that could potentially boost the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price to a new yearly high, surpassing the $0.5833 mark hit in May.  This could position XRP, the sixth largest cryptocurrency on the market, in a favorable position to reach the $1 milestone. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The legal battle between Ripple and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has taken a new twist as top lawyers accuse former SEC Director William Hinman of being paid to attack XRP in favor of Ethereum (ETH). </p>
<p>Following the release of Hinman&#8217;s emails and drafts of his June 2018 speech, pro-XRP attorney John Deaton <a href="https://twitter.com/DigPerspectives/status/1669071745435697153?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">expressed </a>his frustration with the intent of the released documents on a recent live CryptoLaw podcast. </p>

<h2>Payments To Disparage XRP In Favor Of Ethereum?</h2>
<p>Jeremy Hogan, lawyer and cryptocurrency expert, also weighed in on the matter alleging that former SEC Director of Corporate Finance, Bill Hinman, was paid to give a speech in which he declared that Ethereum was not a security. </p>
<p>According to Hogan, Ripple, a leading cryptocurrency company, has suggested that Hinman was paid by the Ethereum Foundation or someone related to Ethereum to give the speech and give Ethereum a free pass.</p>
<p>Hogan&#8217;s claims are based on email exchanges between Hinman and his colleagues, which reportedly show that Hinman had already named his first email &#8220;the Ether speech&#8221; before he began crafting the speech. </p>
<p>This, according to Hogan, suggests that &#8220;right from the get-go&#8221;, Hinman is saying that ETH is not a security, and that was the point of him making the speech.</p>
<p>Hinman&#8217;s speech, which was delivered in 2018, was seen by many in the cryptocurrency industry as a landmark moment in which the SEC effectively declared that Ethereum was not a security. </p>
<p>This was seen as a significant victory for Ethereum and the wider cryptocurrency industry, as it provided clarity on how the SEC would regulate cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>However, Hogan has suggested that the speech was not only a free pass for Ethereum but also an attack on XRP, which was at the time Ethereum&#8217;s biggest competition. Hogan&#8217;s claims are based on Ripple&#8217;s ongoing legal battle with the SEC, in which Ripple has argued that XRP is not a security and should not be regulated as such.</p>

<p>Hogan&#8217;s allegations are likely to fuel speculation about the relationship between the SEC and the cryptocurrency industry, and the extent to which the SEC&#8217;s decisions are influenced by external factors. However, it is important to note that Hogan&#8217;s claims are based on speculation and have not been proven.</p>
<img decoding="async" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/AtbcaRhD/" alt="XRP" width="1815" height="858" loading="lazy"/>
<p>At present, the value of XRP stands at $0.4731, indicating a marginal recovery of 0.6% over the past day. This comes after a dip to $0.4564 on Wednesday. Despite the recent drop, XRP enthusiasts remain optimistic and are looking forward to a positive outcome that could potentially boost the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price to a new yearly high, surpassing the $0.5833 mark hit in May. </p>
<p>This could position XRP, the sixth largest cryptocurrency on the market, in a favorable position to reach the $1 milestone.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/possessed-photography-_E1PQXKUkMw-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Percentage Of ETH Addresses In Profit Reaches 5-Month Low</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/percentage-of-eth-addresses-in-profit-reaches-5-month-low/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 20:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538303</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The brutal bear market in crypto over the past few months has taken a serious toll on ETH’s price and profitability. The price of Ethereum has been stuck in a sideways range recently, and many ETH holders have been unlucky for it. According to data from Glassnode, the percentage of Ethereum addresses in profit has now dropped to a 5-month low. Percentage Of Addresses In The Green Drops To 55.414% Back in 2021, when the price of ETH was at its highest, the majority of addresses held a comfortable position. Now, two years later, for new investors who bought at higher prices, the wait for their positions to go green again has been a long one. Related Reading: Curve (CRV) Observes 7% Bounce As Short Squeeze Occurs Glassnode, a crypto analytics platform, reports that the percentage of Ethereum addresses in green while measuring over a 7-day moving average is now at a 5-month low of 55.414%. Percentage of addresses in profit drop to five-month low &#124; Source: Glassnode on Twitter This indicates that more than 44 percent of the people who own ETH are currently at a loss. In the same vein, the number of profitable addresses has dropped to its lowest point since March of this year, standing at 56,311,171.899 at the moment. Moving ETH Off Exchanges The amount of ETH held on cryptocurrency exchanges has also dropped to its lowest level in over 5 years. This means less ETH is available for trading on exchanges, which can impact the price and liquidity. Traders are withdrawing their ETH from exchanges and holding it in private digital wallets.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Bullish Momentum Building: Expert Predicts Rise To $27,200 The drop can also be linked to an all-time high level of staking in the ETH 2.0 deposit contract. Data shows that the majority of ETH held by large investors are now moving ETH into the contract, showing that interest in ETH staking is growing. This declining supply, coupled with increasing mainstream interest in ETH, could drive the price higher if demand remains strong. Ethereum Plunges Below $1,700 Meanwhile, Ethereum broke below critical price support earlier this week. The price plunged below $1,700 to $1,630 yesterday, marking its lowest value since March 16. The plunge in price and profitability is largely attributed to negative sentiment around rising inflation fears and the overall weakness in the crypto market recently. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Lead Developer Unveils Shibacals, Advancing Shibarium Development ETH has since then recovered and is now trading at $1,720, looking to retest the $1,800 resistance once more. Of course, if $1,700 fails to hold, Ethereum could fall further to test support at $1,400 or even $1,300. A drop below $1,700 again would be very bearish and see the profitability percentage drop further.  Ethereum price recovers above $1,700 &#124; Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com Featured image from The Cryptoknowmist, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The brutal bear market in crypto over the past few months has taken a serious toll on ETH’s price and profitability. The price of Ethereum has been stuck in a sideways range recently, and many ETH holders have been unlucky for it. According to data from Glassnode, the percentage of Ethereum addresses in profit has now dropped to a 5-month low.</p>
<h2>Percentage Of Addresses In The Green Drops To 55.414%</h2>
<p>Back in 2021, when the price of ETH was at its highest, the majority of addresses held a comfortable position. Now, two years later, for new investors who bought at higher prices, the wait for their positions to go green again has been a long one.</p>

<p>Glassnode, a crypto analytics platform, <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnodealerts/status/1669574431658606598?s=20" rel="nofollow">reports </a>that the percentage of Ethereum addresses in green while measuring over a 7-day moving average is now at a 5-month low of 55.414%. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-538304 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-profitability-460x230.jpeg" alt="ETH profitability" width="460" height="230" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-profitability-460x230.jpeg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-profitability-860x430.jpeg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-profitability-768x384.jpeg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-profitability-1536x768.jpeg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-profitability-2048x1024.jpeg 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-profitability-360x180.jpeg 360w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-profitability-750x375.jpeg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-profitability-1140x570.jpeg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>

<p>This indicates that more than 44 percent of the people who own ETH are currently at a loss. In the same vein, the number of profitable addresses has <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnodealerts/status/1669438475391717401?s=20" rel="nofollow">dropped </a>to its lowest point since March of this year, standing at 56,311,171.899 at the moment.</p>
<h2>Moving ETH Off Exchanges</h2>
<p>The amount of ETH held on cryptocurrency exchanges has also dropped to its lowest level in over 5 years. This means less ETH is available for trading on exchanges, which can impact the price and liquidity. Traders are withdrawing their ETH from exchanges and holding it in private digital wallets. </p>

<p>The drop can also be linked to an all-time high level of staking in the ETH 2.0 deposit contract. Data shows that the majority of ETH held by large investors are now moving ETH into the contract, showing that interest in ETH staking is growing. This declining supply, coupled with increasing mainstream interest in ETH, could drive the price higher if demand remains strong.</p>
Ethereum Plunges Below $1,700
<p>Meanwhile, Ethereum broke below critical price support earlier this week. The price plunged below $1,700 to $1,630 yesterday, marking its lowest value since March 16. The plunge in price and profitability is largely attributed to negative sentiment around rising inflation fears and the overall weakness in the crypto market recently.</p>

<p>ETH has since then recovered and is now trading at $1,720, looking to retest the $1,800 resistance once more. Of course, if $1,700 fails to hold, Ethereum could fall further to test support at $1,400 or even $1,300. A drop below $1,700 again would be very bearish and see the profitability percentage drop further. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/fPjFNAxo/" alt="Ethereum (ETH) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1610"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-dollar-460x306.jpeg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Bullish Momentum Building: Expert Predicts Rise To $27,200</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-bullish-momentum-rise-to-27200/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 19:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538295</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin has been on a rollercoaster ride recently, with sudden price drops and spikes keeping investors on their toes. Last week, the cryptocurrency failed to break through its $27,500 resistance level and dropped to a low of $24,700.  However, Bitcoin has again shown signs of regaining its bullish momentum, with a 5% increase in the last 24 hours and trading at $26,400 at the time of writing. Many analysts have predicted a continuation of the uptrend in Bitcoin&#8217;s price, which has been ongoing since January 2023. Related Reading: Curve (CRV) Observes 7% Bounce As Short Squeeze Occurs Bearish Momentum Fades As Bitcoin Retests $26,500 According to Glassnode co-founder Yan Allemann, the current stage in this trend is the retesting of the $26,200 level as bearish momentum fades.  Allemann believes that this is an important stage, as it will determine whether Bitcoin can break through its previous resistance and move toward the next target of $27,200 However, while Bitcoin is showing signs of regaining its bullish momentum, it&#8217;s important to recognize that it is still fragile at this level. Therefore, building confidence among investors is crucial to sustaining Bitcoin&#8217;s upward trend. On a positive note, BlackRock&#8217;s recent application with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for its new exchange-traded fund (ETF) has given Bitcoin holders and bulls hope.  As reported by NewsBTC, the recent announcement of BlackRock&#8217;s Bitcoin exchange-traded fund has the potential to impact BTC’s price significantly. If approved, this ETF would enable a wider range of investors to gain exposure to Bitcoin, which could drive up demand and ultimately increase its price. ETFs provide a convenient way for institutional investors to access Bitcoin, creating a new demand avenue for the cryptocurrency. This could increase buying pressure and a potential surge in Bitcoin&#8217;s price. Potential BTC Reversal From Support Bitcoin has recently bounced from its bullish trend and the top of its range, indicating that it still has some work to do before establishing a sustainable upward trend.  According to market analyst Crypto Con, one of the most accurate indicators of Bitcoin&#8217;s bullish or bearish momentum is the 140-day moving average (MA), which shows that BTC’s price is below this crucial level. The 140DMA is a widely followed indicator in the cryptocurrency market, as it clearly signals whether Bitcoin is in a bullish or bearish phase.  When BTC’s price is above the 140DMA, it&#8217;s a bullish signal, indicating that the cryptocurrency will likely continue its upward trend. Conversely, when the price is below the 140DMA, it&#8217;s a bearish signal, suggesting that the cryptocurrency will likely experience a downward trend. Bitcoin&#8217;s price is below the 140DMA, indicating that it&#8217;s in a bearish phase. However, Crypto Con hopes the cryptocurrency will experience a huge reversal from this support level, leading to a bearish fakeout of the 140DMA. This strong bullish signal could indicate that Bitcoin is ready to continue its upward trend. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Lead Developer Unveils Shibacals, Advancing Shibarium Development As BlackRock&#8217;s potential Bitcoin ETF gains attention and BTC gradually regains its bullish momentum, investors are increasingly optimistic that Bitcoin&#8217;s bottom is already behind. There is a growing belief that the largest cryptocurrency in the market is poised to reach new annual highs in 2023 and possibly even surpass its all-time high. However, for BTC to continue its upward trend, the cryptocurrency needs to maintain its current level of $26,000 throughout the weekend. A sustained price above this price mark could indicate that BTC is on track for a green week in the coming days. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has been on a rollercoaster ride recently, with sudden price drops and spikes keeping investors on their toes. Last week, the cryptocurrency failed to break through its $27,500 resistance level and dropped to a low of $24,700. </p>
<p>However, Bitcoin has again shown signs of regaining its bullish momentum, with a 5% increase in the last 24 hours and trading at $26,400 at the time of writing.</p>
<p>Many analysts have predicted a continuation of the uptrend in Bitcoin&#8217;s price, which has been ongoing since January 2023.</p>

<h2>Bearish Momentum Fades As Bitcoin Retests $26,500</h2>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/Negentropic_/status/1669758961254379545?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to Glassnode co-founder Yan Allemann, the current stage in this trend is the retesting of the $26,200 level as bearish momentum fades. </p>
<p>Allemann believes that this is an important stage, as it will determine whether Bitcoin can break through its previous resistance and move toward the next target of $27,200</p>
<p>However, while Bitcoin is showing signs of regaining its bullish momentum, it&#8217;s important to recognize that it is still fragile at this level. Therefore, building confidence among investors is crucial to sustaining Bitcoin&#8217;s upward trend.</p>
<p>On a positive note, BlackRock&#8217;s recent application with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for its new exchange-traded fund (ETF) has given Bitcoin holders and bulls hope. </p>
<p>As reported by <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/blackrock-inches-closer-to-launching-bitcoin-etf-impact-on-btc-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">NewsBTC</a>, the recent announcement of BlackRock&#8217;s Bitcoin exchange-traded fund has the potential to impact BTC’s price significantly. If approved, this ETF would enable a wider range of investors to gain exposure to Bitcoin, which could drive up demand and ultimately increase its price.</p>
<p>ETFs provide a convenient way for institutional investors to access Bitcoin, creating a new demand avenue for the cryptocurrency. This could increase buying pressure and a potential surge in Bitcoin&#8217;s price.</p>
Potential BTC Reversal From Support
<p>Bitcoin has recently bounced from its bullish trend and the top of its range, indicating that it still has some work to do before establishing a sustainable upward trend. </p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoCon_/status/1669723509780520961?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to market analyst Crypto Con, one of the most accurate indicators of Bitcoin&#8217;s bullish or bearish momentum is the 140-day moving average (MA), which shows that BTC’s price is below this crucial level.</p>
<p>The 140DMA is a widely followed indicator in the cryptocurrency market, as it clearly signals whether Bitcoin is in a bullish or bearish phase. </p>
<p>When BTC’s price is above the 140DMA, it&#8217;s a bullish signal, indicating that the cryptocurrency will likely continue its upward trend. Conversely, when the price is below the 140DMA, it&#8217;s a bearish signal, suggesting that the cryptocurrency will likely experience a downward trend.</p>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price is below the 140DMA, indicating that it&#8217;s in a bearish phase. However, Crypto Con hopes the cryptocurrency will experience a huge reversal from this support level, leading to a bearish fakeout of the 140DMA. This strong bullish signal could indicate that Bitcoin is ready to continue its upward trend.</p>

<p>As BlackRock&#8217;s potential Bitcoin ETF gains attention and BTC gradually regains its bullish momentum, investors are increasingly optimistic that Bitcoin&#8217;s bottom is already behind. There is a growing belief that the largest cryptocurrency in the market is poised to reach new annual highs in 2023 and possibly even surpass its all-time high.</p>
<p>However, for BTC to continue its upward trend, the cryptocurrency needs to maintain its current level of $26,000 throughout the weekend. A sustained price above this price mark could indicate that BTC is on track for a green week in the coming days.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/BacPd4kq/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-531282429-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Curve (CRV) Observes 7% Bounce As Short Squeeze Occurs</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/curve-crv-observes-7-bounce-as-short-squeeze-occurs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 15:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CRV]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CRVUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curve Funding Rates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curve Short Squeeze]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curve Shorts]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538233</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Curve DAO token (CRV) has observed a 7% bounce during the last 24 hours as mass liquidations of short traders have occurred in the market. Curve Funding Rates Turned Extremely Negative Following Price Decline According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, an extreme amount of shorts had accumulated on the cryptocurrency exchange Binance recently. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;funding rate,&#8221; which keeps track of the periodic fee that Curve perpetual contract traders on a specific exchange are paying each other right now. When the value of this metric is positive, it means that the long contract holders are willing to pay a premium to the short contract holders in order to keep their position currently. Such a trend implies that bullish sentiment is held by the majority of investors. On the other hand, negative values suggest that a bearish mentality is the dominant force in the market at the moment as the shorts are paying a fee to the longs. Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Curve funding rates on the cryptocurrency exchange Binance over the past month or so: The value of the metric seems to have been quite red not too long ago &#124; Source: Santiment on Twitter As displayed in the above graph, the Curve Binance funding rate had assumed negative values recently as the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price had continued to head downwards. The decline in the asset&#8217;s price came in part because of all the FUD in the wider cryptocurrency sector, like the SEC charges against Binance and Coinbase, or the Fed interest rates decision, while the other factor was CRV-specific uncertainty. The root cause of this FUD is the fact that the Curve Finance founder has taken up a large loan against a wallet that currently holds around 30% of the entire circulating supply of the token. As the price of the asset has taken a hit recently, concerns about this position getting liquidated have grown in the market. Since the wallet holds such a significant part of the cryptocurrency&#8217;s supply (288.7 million tokens to be precise), a potential liquidation could have wide-reaching consequences for the project. From the graph, it&#8217;s visible that the Binance funding rate had become extremely red as this FUD spread around. This means that the sentiment on the exchange had become quite bearish. Related Reading: Bitcoin Holders Show No Panic Loss Selling, What Does It Mean? Historically, whenever the traders have leaned too hard into any particular direction, the market has tended to actually show a sharp move in the opposite direction. The reason behind this is an event called a squeeze, which takes place whenever a sudden swing in the price occurs and causes a mass amount of liquidations to go off at once. These liquidations only end up fueling said price swing further, leading to even more liquidations happening in the market. In this way, liquidations can sort of waterfall together during a squeeze. Related Reading: What Happens To Bitcoin Price If Spot ETF Is Approved? Gold ETF Story Reveals In the graph, it&#8217;s visible that after the funding rate had turned very negative, the indicator suddenly started going the other way, and it has now already turned very slightly positive. This suggests that a short squeeze has taken place in the market, as the shorts that had accumulated have all been washed away. The Curve price has jumped off this squeeze, registering a rise of about 7%. CRV Price At the time of writing, the Curve DAO token is trading around $0.61, down 20% in the last week. Looks like the asset has seen some recovery &#124; Source: CRVUSD on TradingView Featured image from iStock.com, charts from TradingView.com, Santiment.net]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Curve DAO token (CRV) has observed a 7% bounce during the last 24 hours as mass liquidations of short traders have occurred in the market.</p>
<h2>Curve Funding Rates Turned Extremely Negative Following Price Decline</h2>
<p>According to data from the on-chain analytics firm <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1669435676511854594" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Santiment</a>, an extreme amount of shorts had accumulated on the cryptocurrency exchange Binance recently. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-funding-rates-bitmex-deep-red-why-bullish/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">funding rate</a>,&#8221; which keeps track of the periodic fee that Curve perpetual contract traders on a specific exchange are paying each other right now.</p>
<p>When the value of this metric is positive, it means that the long contract holders are willing to pay a premium to the short contract holders in order to keep their position currently. Such a trend implies that bullish sentiment is held by the majority of investors.</p>
<p>On the other hand, negative values suggest that a bearish mentality is the dominant force in the market at the moment as the shorts are paying a fee to the longs.</p>
<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Curve funding rates on the cryptocurrency exchange Binance over the past month or so:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FysGADsacAEAMOR?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Curve Funding Rates" width="2825" height="1788"/></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the Curve Binance funding rate had assumed negative values recently as the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price had continued to head downwards.</p>
<p>The decline in the asset&#8217;s price came in part because of all the FUD in the wider cryptocurrency sector, like the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/crypto-market-bleeds-as-sec-pressures-mount-is-it-time-to-buy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">SEC charges</a> against Binance and Coinbase, or the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-plunges-24k-next/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Fed interest rates decision</a>, while the other factor was CRV-specific uncertainty.</p>
<p>The root cause of this FUD is the fact that the Curve Finance founder has taken up a large loan against a wallet that currently holds around 30% of the entire circulating supply of the token. As the price of the asset has taken a hit recently, concerns about this position getting liquidated have grown in the market.</p>
<p>Since the wallet holds such a significant part of the cryptocurrency&#8217;s supply (288.7 million tokens to be precise), a potential liquidation could have wide-reaching consequences for the project.</p>
<p>From the graph, it&#8217;s visible that the Binance funding rate had become extremely red as this FUD spread around. This means that the sentiment on the exchange had become quite bearish.</p>

<p>Historically, whenever the traders have leaned too hard into any particular direction, the market has tended to actually show a sharp move in the opposite direction.</p>
<p>The reason behind this is an event called a squeeze, which takes place whenever a sudden swing in the price occurs and causes a mass amount of liquidations to go off at once.</p>
<p>These liquidations only end up fueling said price swing further, leading to even more liquidations happening in the market. In this way, liquidations can sort of waterfall together during a squeeze.</p>

<p>In the graph, it&#8217;s visible that after the funding rate had turned very negative, the indicator suddenly started going the other way, and it has now already turned very slightly positive.</p>
<p>This suggests that a short squeeze has taken place in the market, as the shorts that had accumulated have all been washed away. The Curve price has jumped off this squeeze, registering a rise of about 7%.</p>
<h2>CRV Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, the Curve DAO token is trading around $0.61, down 20% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/rCN2RUVL/" alt="Curve Price Chart" width="1534" height="911"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1359416693-1-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Lead Developer Unveils Shibacals, Advancing Shibarium Development</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-lead-developer-unveils-shibacals-advancing-shibarium-development/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli Dambel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 14:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shibarium]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538250</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In an exciting development for the Shiba Inu community, the top developer working behind the scenes has unveiled another project before the launch of Shibarium. The lead developer introduced their newest innovation, &#8216;Shibacals,&#8217; bringing them one step closer to their ambitious vision. Shiba Inu enthusiasts and investors can anticipate even greater possibilities with this new advancement. Shytoshi Kusama Unveils Shibacals, A Promising Step Towards Shibarium Launch Shiba Inu lead developer Shytoshi Kusama introduced ‘Shibacals,&#8217; sparking positive speculations and anticipation among the community. Kusama shared the hint in the Shibarium official Telegram group, directing the community to visit www.shibacals.com. Related Reading: Cardano (ADA) Price Sheds 19% As Bearish Sentiment Looms Large In a recent tweet, Shiba Inu’s content marketing specialist, Lucie, asked the community to follow Shibacal’s account with an attachment of Kusama’s statement. The news about the Shibacals followed hints that Lucie gave regarding an upcoming physical reveal. Shytoshi Kusama also hinted at the project&#8217;s launch, which he classified as &#8220;Something Physical.&#8221; However, a community member expresses displeasure with the launch of the Shibacals, raising questions regarding how the project will benefit the Shibarium community. He expressed his concern that this action may solely be focused on taking advantage of the community to generate profit: “t has nothing to do with decreasing the #Shib’s total supply or impacting the price by utility. If I am missing something, please educate me! What Does Shibacals Entail? As described on its official website, Shibacals brings a unique real-world feature to the Shiba Inu ecosystem. The project transforms digital NFTs into first-class, high-quality physical items like plushies or toys. Shibacals&#8217; primary goal is to add an extra touch of excitement and value to the community, bridging the digital and physical realms meaningfully. Shibacals aims to empower the wider crypto community through strategic partnerships with prominent manufacturers. Shibacals hopes to introduce various physical goods by collaborating with these manufacturers. According to Shibacals, its products will come with a ‘super-cool SHIB tag or classy white-labeled one” and an inbuilt NFC chip which they describe as a secret handshake for true-blue authenticity. Lucie also took to Twitter to share captivating images of a Shibacals hoodie, offering a sneak peek at one of their latest creations. Meanwhile, the Shibacals is hosting a contest titled Shibacals Hoodie Contest, where Shiba Inu community members are allowed to present 3 designs of their Shibacal Hoodie. A vote will be conducted to get the winner, and the winning design will be made available as a pre-sale item with the tag &#8220;Shiba Inu: 1st edition” for 5-7 days. According to Shibacals, each winner will receive a percentage of the proceeds they realize from the pre-sale. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In an exciting development for the Shiba Inu community, the top developer working behind the scenes has unveiled another project before the launch of Shibarium.</p>
<p>The lead developer introduced their newest innovation, &#8216;Shibacals,&#8217; bringing them one step closer to their ambitious vision. Shiba Inu enthusiasts and investors can anticipate even greater possibilities with this new advancement.</p>
<h2>Shytoshi Kusama Unveils Shibacals, A Promising Step Towards Shibarium Launch</h2>
<p>Shiba Inu lead developer Shytoshi Kusama introduced ‘Shibacals,&#8217; sparking positive speculations and anticipation among the community. Kusama shared the hint in the Shibarium official Telegram group, directing the community to visit <a href="http://www.shibacals.com" rel="nofollow">www.shibacals.com</a>.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano-ada-price-sheds-19/">Cardano (ADA) Price Sheds 19% As Bearish Sentiment Looms Large</a></p>
<p>In a <a href="https://twitter.com/LucieSHIB/status/1669430140152020992?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1669430140152020992%7Ctwgr%5Efdca5af51f1e802a77d5fbfe18a4b9cc09325f8b%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fthecryptobasic.com%2F2023%2F06%2F16%2Fshiba-inu-lead-developer-takes-one-more-step-toward-shibarium-introducing-shibacals%2F" rel="nofollow">recent tweet</a>, Shiba Inu’s content marketing specialist, Lucie, asked the community to follow Shibacal’s account with an attachment of Kusama’s statement.</p>
<p>The news about the Shibacals followed <a href="https://twitter.com/LucieSHIB/status/1668923178658193410?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1668923178658193410%7Ctwgr%5E411fb3e6cb81c03fdfdce03d334ca779881df91b%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fthecryptobasic.com%2F2023%2F06%2F14%2Fshiba-inu-team-member-teases-something-special-incoming%2F" rel="nofollow">hints</a> that Lucie gave regarding an upcoming physical reveal. Shytoshi Kusama also hinted at the project&#8217;s launch, which he classified as <i>&#8220;</i>Something Physical.&#8221;</p>
<p>However, a community member expresses displeasure with the launch of the Shibacals, raising questions regarding how the project will benefit the Shibarium community.</p>
<p>He <a href="https://twitter.com/4enWatch/status/1669438339487879172" rel="nofollow">expressed</a> his concern that this action may solely be focused on taking advantage of the community to generate profit:</p>
<blockquote><p>“t has nothing to do with decreasing the #Shib’s total supply or impacting the price by utility. If I am missing something, please educate me!</p></blockquote>
<h2>What Does Shibacals Entail?</h2>
<p>As described on its <a href="https://www.shibacals.com/" rel="nofollow">official website</a>, Shibacals brings a unique real-world feature to the Shiba Inu ecosystem. The project transforms digital NFTs into first-class, high-quality physical items like plushies or toys.</p>
<p>Shibacals&#8217; primary goal is to add an extra touch of excitement and value to the community, bridging the digital and physical realms meaningfully.</p>
<p>Shibacals aims to empower the wider crypto community through strategic partnerships with prominent manufacturers. Shibacals hopes to introduce various physical goods by collaborating with these manufacturers.</p>
<p>According to Shibacals, its products will come with a ‘super-cool SHIB tag or classy white-labeled one” and an inbuilt NFC chip which they describe as a secret handshake for true-blue authenticity.</p>
<p>Lucie also took to <a href="https://twitter.com/LucieSHIB/status/1669470053887090688?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1669470053887090688%7Ctwgr%5E614af50c666460745e6fb79e5ce7bf5adb090ca8%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fthecryptobasic.com%2F2023%2F06%2F16%2Fshiba-inu-lead-developer-takes-one-more-step-toward-shibarium-introducing-shibacals%2F" rel="nofollow">Twitter</a> to share captivating images of a Shibacals hoodie, offering a sneak peek at one of their latest creations.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-538258 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSDT_2023-06-16_17-37-38-860x454.png" alt="Shiba Inu Lead Developer Unveils Shibacals, Advancing Shibarium Development" width="860" height="454" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSDT_2023-06-16_17-37-38-860x454.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSDT_2023-06-16_17-37-38-460x243.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSDT_2023-06-16_17-37-38-768x406.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSDT_2023-06-16_17-37-38-1536x811.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSDT_2023-06-16_17-37-38-2048x1082.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSDT_2023-06-16_17-37-38-750x396.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SHIBUSDT_2023-06-16_17-37-38-1140x602.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>Meanwhile, the Shibacals is <a href="https://www.shibacals.com/shiba-on-champion" rel="nofollow">hosting a contest</a> titled Shibacals Hoodie Contest, where Shiba Inu community members are allowed to present 3 designs of their Shibacal Hoodie.</p>
<p>A vote will be conducted to get the winner, and the winning design will be made available as a pre-sale item with the tag &#8220;Shiba Inu: 1st edition” for 5-7 days. According to Shibacals, each winner will receive a percentage of the proceeds they realize from the pre-sale.</p>
<p>Featured image from Pixabay and chart from tradingview.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/dog-breed-gd0d89bcb4_1280-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Market Dominance Touches Two-Year Peak, Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-market-dominance-peaks-in-nearly-two-years/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 13:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538251</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Amid the ongoing crypto regulatory uncertainty, Bitcoin&#8217;s market dominance has surged to its highest level since July 2021, suggesting a shift in the sentiments of traders and investors towards the world&#8217;s pioneer and most substantial cryptocurrency, Bitcoin. This milestone highlights the current volatility of the crypto market as it continues to grapple with regulatory uncertainty and the various factors that impact Bitcoin&#8217;s value. The Resurgence Of Bitcoin Dominance The latest data from TradingView reveals that Bitcoin dominance, defined as Bitcoin&#8217;s share of the total cryptocurrency market capitalization, has hit a high of 49.5%. This level has not been recorded since July 2021 when Bitcoin&#8217;s dominance touched a peak of over 48%. It is worth noting that earlier this year in April, Bitcoin&#8217;s dominance momentarily reached 48.83%, after which it fluctuated within a specific range. Related Reading: BlackRock Inches Closer To Launching Bitcoin ETF: Potential Impact On BTC Price However, the past week saw a notable increase in Bitcoin&#8217;s market dominance, correlating with the time when the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) categorized numerous tokens as unregistered securities in its lawsuits against the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchanges &#8211; Binance and Coinbase. Consequently, many of these tokens such as Cardano (ADA), Solana (SOL), and Binance Coin (BNB) have experienced significant price drops, while Bitcoin&#8217;s value has remained comparatively stable. Market Influences And The Upcoming BTC Halving The regulatory actions by the SEC underscore an environment of uncertainty that has had noticeable effects on the crypto market. Amid this backdrop, Bitcoin emerges as a sort of safe haven. Micheal Saylor, a prominent Bitcoin advocate, echoed these sentiments in a recent interview with Bloomberg, predicting that: &#8220;the entire industry is kind of destined to be rationalized down to Bitcoin and a half a dozen to a dozen other proof-of-work tokens.&#8221; Furthermore, anticipation around the upcoming Bitcoin halving event, slated for April or May 2024, could be a contributing factor to Bitcoin&#8217;s increasing dominance. This quadrennial event reduces the reward for mining new Bitcoin blocks by half, effectively slowing the rate at which new Bitcoins are created to manage inflation and maintain their scarcity. The impending halving will result in a block reward decrease from 6.25 bitcoins to 3.125 bitcoins. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price On Shaky Ground: Market Analysts Warn Of Potential Fall To $20,000 Level Notably, BTC has been in a downward trend in the past week. The largest crypto asset by market capitalization has recorded a bearish movement falling by nearly 5% in the past 7 days. However, over the past 24 hours, BTC has picked up an uptrend, seeing a 2.3% gain in its value. Bitcoin currently has a market price of $25,515, at the time of writing after initially trading below that price range earlier this week. Meanwhile, Bitcoin’s trading volume has plunged over the past 24 hours from over $15 billion on Thursday to $7.7 billion at the time of writing indicating less trading activity. Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Amid the ongoing crypto regulatory uncertainty, Bitcoin&#8217;s market dominance has surged to its highest level since July 2021, suggesting a shift in the sentiments of traders and investors towards the world&#8217;s pioneer and most substantial cryptocurrency, Bitcoin.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">This milestone highlights the current volatility of the crypto market as it continues to grapple with regulatory uncertainty and the various factors that impact Bitcoin&#8217;s value.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The Resurgence Of Bitcoin Dominance</h2>
<p>The latest <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/chart/HSuSIPeM/?symbol=CRYPTOCAP%3ABTC.D" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a> from TradingView reveals that Bitcoin dominance, defined as Bitcoin&#8217;s share of the total cryptocurrency market capitalization, has hit a high of 49.5%. This level has not been recorded since July 2021 when Bitcoin&#8217;s dominance touched a peak of over 48%.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/WgCemKq2/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) market dominance on TradingView" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<p>It is worth noting that earlier this year in April, Bitcoin&#8217;s dominance momentarily reached 48.83%, after which it fluctuated within a specific range.</p>

<p>However, the past week saw a notable increase in Bitcoin&#8217;s market dominance, correlating with the time when the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) categorized numerous tokens as unregistered securities in its lawsuits against the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchanges &#8211; Binance and Coinbase. </p>
<p>Consequently, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/crypto-market-tension-ada-bnb-matic-sol-crashes/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">many of these tokens</a> such as Cardano (ADA), Solana (SOL), and Binance Coin (BNB) have experienced significant price drops, while Bitcoin&#8217;s value has <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/blackrock-inches-closer-to-launching-bitcoin-etf-impact-on-btc-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">remained comparatively stable</a>.</p>
<h2>Market Influences And The Upcoming BTC Halving</h2>
<p>The regulatory actions by the SEC underscore an environment of uncertainty that has had noticeable effects on the crypto market. Amid this backdrop, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-btc-stored-on-exchanges-plummets-amid-regulatory/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin emerges as a sort of safe haven</a>. </p>
<p>Micheal Saylor, a prominent Bitcoin advocate, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-13/microstrategy-s-mstr-saylor-says-bitcoin-btc-market-share-will-climb-to-80" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">echoed</a> these sentiments in a recent interview with Bloomberg, predicting that: &#8220;the entire industry is kind of destined to be rationalized down to Bitcoin and a half a dozen to a dozen other proof-of-work tokens.&#8221;</p>
<p>Furthermore, anticipation around the upcoming <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/data-reveals-short-term-bitcoin-holders-refuse-to-sell/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a> halving event, slated for April or May 2024, could be a contributing factor to Bitcoin&#8217;s increasing dominance. </p>
<p>This quadrennial event reduces the reward for mining new Bitcoin blocks by half, effectively slowing the rate at which new Bitcoins are created to manage inflation and maintain their scarcity. The impending halving will result in a block reward decrease from 6.25 bitcoins to 3.125 bitcoins.</p>

<p>Notably, BTC has been in a downward trend in the past week. The largest crypto asset by market capitalization has recorded a bearish movement falling by nearly 5% in the past 7 days. However, over the past 24 hours, BTC has picked up an uptrend, seeing a 2.3% gain in its value.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/jLrMVDXg/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC)’s price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<p>Bitcoin currently has a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-price-on-shaky-ground-market-analysts-warn-potential-fall/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">market price</a> of $25,515, at the time of writing after initially trading below that price range earlier this week. Meanwhile, Bitcoin’s trading volume has plunged over the past 24 hours from over $15 billion on Thursday to $7.7 billion at the time of writing indicating less trading activity.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-460x282.jpg" width="460" height="282" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polygon (MATIC) Sees Surge In Whale Buying Despite US Regulatory Pressure</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/polygon-sees-surge-in-whale-buying/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 12:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATIC Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538234</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Polygon (MATIC), a blockchain scalability platform, finds itself in the grip of negative sentiment that casts a shadow over its prospects for a strong price recovery. The crypto market has been a volatile space, prone to sudden shifts in sentiment, and MATIC is no exception. The recent downturn in the sentiment surrounding MATIC has left investors and traders cautiously observing the price charts. Once considered a promising project in the crypto space, Polygon&#8217;s potential for growth has been impeded by the recent actions of the US Securities and Exchange Commission against altcoins. Will the negative sentiment continue to hinder MATIC’s potential for a strong price recovery? Related Reading: Cardano (ADA) Price Sheds 19% As Bearish Sentiment Looms Large Polygon Whales Unfazed By US Regulatory Pressure? The latest data on MATIC reveals that the pressure from US regulators has not seemed to totally unsettle some prominent investors, as evidenced by a notable increase in whale transactions exceeding $1 million in recent days. Source: Santiment However, despite the increase in whale appetite, the cryptocurrency has failed to sustain a strong upward momentum at the time of writing. Source: CoinMarketCap CoinMarketCap reports MATIC&#8217;s current price as $0.5818, reflecting a decline of 2.33% within the past 24 hours. Additionally, the cryptocurrency has witnessed a substantial slump of 25.93% over the past seven days. In addition to the impact of regulatory pressure, the movements of MATIC&#8217;s supply on exchanges, which serves as an indicator of short-term selling pressure, have exhibited rapid fluctuations during the same period. MATIC 24-hour price movement. Source: CoinMarketCap It experienced a sharp increase, followed by a decline, and then another spike before eventually easing at the time of publication. These developments indicate that the selling pressure on MATIC remains a significant concern, primarily due to the prevailing regulatory uncertainty. MATIC market cap currently at $5.4 billion. Chart: TradingView.com Fed&#8217;s Pause On Rate Hikes Fails To Stabilize Crypto Markets On the whole, financial markets have continued to exhibit volatile movements, causing cryptocurrencies to decouple from the performance of traditional equities markets. The recent downturn in the crypto market seems to be linked to the press conference held by Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell on June 14, during which he announced that the central bank would temporarily halt rate hikes for the month of June. Related Reading: XRP Price Projection: Assessing The Ripple-Colombia Central Bank Partnership While this decision aligned with investors&#8217; expectations, it had an unexpected effect on the crypto market. Instead of stabilizing, the market experienced a reversal in its course and resumed the ongoing sell-off that has persisted for the past three weeks. The presence of substantial macroeconomic challenges, coupled with the anticipation of future rate hikes and low trading volume, suggests that the volatility in the cryptocurrency market is likely to persist in the foreseeable future.  The prevailing headwinds, including economic factors on a larger scale, have contributed to the unpredictability and turbulence in the crypto market. Featured image from Analytics Insight]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Polygon (MATIC), a blockchain scalability platform, finds itself in the grip of negative sentiment that casts a shadow over its prospects for a strong price recovery. The crypto market has been a volatile space, prone to sudden shifts in sentiment, and MATIC is no exception.</p>
<p>The recent downturn in the sentiment surrounding MATIC has left investors and traders cautiously observing the price charts. </p>
<p>Once considered a promising project in the crypto space, Polygon&#8217;s potential for growth has been impeded by the recent actions of the US Securities and Exchange Commission against altcoins.</p>
<p>Will the negative sentiment continue to hinder MATIC’s potential for a strong price recovery?</p>

<h2><strong>Polygon Whales Unfazed By US Regulatory Pressure?</strong></h2>
<p>The <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/matics-recovery-elusive-amidst-regulatory-uncertainty/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">latest data on MATIC</a> reveals that the pressure from US regulators has not seemed to totally unsettle some prominent investors, as evidenced by a notable increase in whale transactions exceeding $1 million in recent days.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-538244 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-98-860x290.png" alt="" width="860" height="290" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-98-860x290.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-98-460x155.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-98-768x259.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-98-1536x519.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-98-750x253.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-98-1140x385.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-98.png 1543w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>However, despite the increase in whale appetite, the cryptocurrency has failed to sustain a strong upward momentum at the time of writing.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-538239" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-96.png" alt="" width="1159" height="91" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-96.png 1159w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-96-460x36.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-96-860x68.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-96-768x60.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-96-1140x90.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-96-750x59.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1159px) 100vw, 1159px"/></p>

<p>CoinMarketCap reports MATIC&#8217;s current price as $0.5818, reflecting <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">a decline of 2.33%</a> within the past 24 hours. Additionally, the cryptocurrency has witnessed a substantial slump of 25.93% over the past seven days.</p>
<p>In addition to the impact of regulatory pressure, the movements of MATIC&#8217;s supply on exchanges, which serves as an indicator of short-term selling pressure, have exhibited rapid fluctuations during the same period.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-538240 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-97-860x382.png" alt="" width="860" height="382" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-97-860x382.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-97-460x204.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-97-768x341.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-97-750x333.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-97.png 1045w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>It experienced a sharp increase, followed by a decline, and then another spike before eventually easing at the time of publication. </p>
<p>These developments indicate that the selling pressure on MATIC remains a significant concern, primarily due to the prevailing regulatory uncertainty.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/5WjMSO4N/" width="2315" height="1109"/></p>

<h2><strong>Fed&#8217;s Pause On Rate Hikes Fails To Stabilize Crypto Markets</strong></h2>
<p>On the whole, financial markets have continued to exhibit volatile movements, causing cryptocurrencies to decouple from the performance of traditional equities markets. </p>
<p>The recent downturn in the crypto market seems to be linked to the <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/transcript-fed-chief-powells-postmeeting-press-conference-fa29e77e" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">press conference held by Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell</a> on June 14, during which he announced that the central bank would temporarily halt rate hikes for the month of June.</p>

<p>While this decision aligned with investors&#8217; expectations, it had an unexpected effect on the crypto market. Instead of stabilizing, the market experienced a reversal in its course and resumed the ongoing sell-off that has persisted for the past three weeks.</p>
<p>The presence of substantial macroeconomic challenges, coupled with the anticipation of future rate hikes and low trading volume, suggests that the volatility in the cryptocurrency market is likely to persist in the foreseeable future. </p>
<p>The prevailing headwinds, including economic factors on a larger scale, have contributed to the unpredictability and turbulence in the crypto market.</p>
<p><em>Featured image from Analytics Insight</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Polygon-460x260.png" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Happens To Bitcoin Price If Spot ETF Is Approved? Gold ETF Story Reveals</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin-price-if-spot-etf-is-approved-gold-story/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 10:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[etf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538224</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The application by BlackRock, the world&#8217;s largest asset manager, for approval of a Bitcoin spot ETF with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is the biggest story in the crypto market today. Numerous experts are extremely optimistic that an approval of the first Bitcoin spot ETF in the US will be a massively bullish event, attracting huge amounts of new capital and triggering a new bull run. But where does this theory come from? Bitcoin is often referred to as the digital gold of the 21st century, so it&#8217;s an obvious choice to look at the history of gold and the first gold based spot ETF. Why The BlackRock Bitcoin ETF Would Be So Bullish The first thing to note is that BlackRock applied for a spot ETF and not a Futures ETF. The SEC has already approved a number of Bitcoin Futures ETFs that hold Bitcoin futures contracts on the CME. These are currently traded on the US equity markets, but have relatively low popularity. And this has its reasons, first and foremost the so-called &#8220;drag&#8221;, as Scimitar Capital explains. Drag refers to the underperformance of a fund that attempts to replicate the return of a particular underlying asset and is a long-term result of regular portfolio rebalancing. To track the spot price, BITO, the largest bitcoin futures ETF, holds 2/3 in the front-month future and 1/3 in the following month. Related Reading: Why Is Bitcoin Up Today? However, this &#8220;rolling&#8221; is costly because of transaction fees, slippage and because futures for the last month are usually traded at a premium over the first month in BTC (&#8220;contango&#8221;). For this reason, futures ETFs are not a good investment for retail traders in the long run and are therefore unpopular. A Bitcoin spot ETF does not have these disadvantages. &#8220;This is the reason why physically backed ETFs like GLD and IAU for gold have a combined 90B of AUM whereas futures backed ones like BITO and USO have a paltry 1.6B,&#8221; Scimitar Capital says. The first gold ETF, the SPDR Gold Trust ETF (GLD), was listed on the NYSE on November 15, 2004 and revolutionized gold trading. Before GLD came on the market, it was possible to invest in gold in the form of bars, coins, certificates and shares of gold mining companies. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Aims $26,200 But 100 SMA Hold The Key In Short-Term The exchange-traded fund made investing in precious metals a no-brainer and eliminated the problems of shipping and vaults. The same revolution could be coming to Bitcoin by a Bitcoin spot ETF. Retail investors could hold Bitcoin long-term through the ETF without worrying about custody and private keys. And the revolution in gold also made itself felt in the price. While the price of gold was still below $450 per ounce in November 2004, gold saw a meteoric rise in the years that followed. In September 2011, less than seven years after the launch, gold was trading at $1920 per ounce. Many economic factors have influenced the price of gold, but the launch of ETFs certainly played an influential role in attracting global institutional funds to the market. The digital gold of the 21st century, Bitcoin, may yet see this price explosion if history repeats itself. At press time, BTC traded at $25,604, reclaiming the 200-day EMA (blue line). Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The application by BlackRock, the world&#8217;s largest asset manager, for approval of a Bitcoin spot ETF with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is the biggest story in the crypto market today. Numerous experts are extremely optimistic that an approval of the first Bitcoin spot ETF in the US will be a massively bullish event, attracting huge amounts of new capital and triggering a new bull run.</p>
<p>But where does this theory come from? Bitcoin is often referred to as the digital gold of the 21st century, so it&#8217;s an obvious choice to look at the history of gold and the first gold based spot ETF.</p>
<h2>Why The BlackRock Bitcoin ETF Would Be So Bullish</h2>
<p>The first thing to note is that BlackRock applied for a spot ETF and not a Futures ETF. The SEC has already approved a number of Bitcoin Futures ETFs that hold Bitcoin futures contracts on the CME. These are currently traded on the US equity markets, but have relatively low popularity. And this has its reasons, first and foremost the so-called &#8220;drag&#8221;, as Scimitar Capital <a href="https://twitter.com/thiccythot_/status/1669582487226310662" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">explains</a>.</p>
<p>Drag refers to the underperformance of a fund that attempts to replicate the return of a particular underlying asset and is a long-term result of regular portfolio rebalancing. To track the spot price, BITO, the largest bitcoin futures ETF, holds 2/3 in the front-month future and 1/3 in the following month.</p>

<p>However, this &#8220;rolling&#8221; is costly because of transaction fees, slippage and because futures for the last month are usually traded at a premium over the first month in BTC (&#8220;contango&#8221;). For this reason, futures ETFs are not a good investment for retail traders in the long run and are therefore unpopular.</p>
<p>A Bitcoin spot ETF does not have these disadvantages. &#8220;This is the reason why physically backed ETFs like GLD and IAU for gold have a combined 90B of AUM whereas futures backed ones like BITO and USO have a paltry 1.6B,&#8221; Scimitar Capital says.</p>
<p>The first gold ETF, the SPDR Gold Trust ETF (GLD), was listed on the NYSE on November 15, 2004 and revolutionized gold trading. Before GLD came on the market, it was possible to invest in gold in the form of bars, coins, certificates and shares of gold mining companies.</p>

<p>The exchange-traded fund made investing in precious metals a no-brainer and eliminated the problems of shipping and vaults. The same revolution could be coming to Bitcoin by a Bitcoin spot ETF. Retail investors could hold Bitcoin long-term through the ETF without worrying about custody and private keys.</p>
<p>And the revolution in gold also made itself felt in the price. While the price of gold was still below $450 per ounce in November 2004, gold saw a meteoric rise in the years that followed.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-538229 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/GOLD_2023-06-16_11-08-18.png" alt="Gold GLD price history" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/GOLD_2023-06-16_11-08-18.png 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/GOLD_2023-06-16_11-08-18-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/GOLD_2023-06-16_11-08-18-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/GOLD_2023-06-16_11-08-18-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/GOLD_2023-06-16_11-08-18-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/GOLD_2023-06-16_11-08-18-2048x944.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/GOLD_2023-06-16_11-08-18-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/GOLD_2023-06-16_11-08-18-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3628px) 100vw, 3628px"/>
<p>In September 2011, less than seven years after the launch, gold was trading at $1920 per ounce. Many economic factors have influenced the price of gold, but the launch of ETFs certainly played an influential role in attracting global institutional funds to the market.</p>
<p>The digital gold of the 21st century, Bitcoin, may yet see this price explosion if history repeats itself.</p>
<p>At press time, BTC traded at $25,604, reclaiming the 200-day EMA (blue line).</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-538230 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-16_11-30-18.png" alt="Bitcoin price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-16_11-30-18.png 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-16_11-30-18-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-16_11-30-18-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-16_11-30-18-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-16_11-30-18-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-16_11-30-18-2048x944.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-16_11-30-18-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-16_11-30-18-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3628px) 100vw, 3628px"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/space-shuttle-in-sky-with-stars-and-clouds-rocket-in-deep-space-scifi-picture-id1360144430-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Is Bitcoin Up Today?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/why-is-bitcoin-up-today-btc-rises-3/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 08:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538199</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin price has risen 3.2% since yesterday&#8217;s low of $24,827. At press time, BTC was trading at $25,590 and has thus reclaimed two extremely important price levels for the moment: first, the Bitcoin price has once again risen above the 200-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA) currently at $25,299, and second, the price is now also back above the 200-week EMA at $25,304 (with the weekly close becoming of crucial importance). As always, there are several narratives for yesterday&#8217;s rise in price. The most obvious narrative and currently the biggest topic in the market is the Bitcoin spot ETF filing by BlackRock, the world&#8217;s largest asset manager, with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). A spot ETF is seen as the holy grail that could finally open the floodgates for institutional liquidity, as Bitcoinist reported today. Reasons For The Bitcoin Rally BlackRock is believed to have a strong chance of getting the first spot-based Bitcoin ETF approved by the SEC due to its political influence and network. The new capital inflows made possible may have the potential to be the next bull run catalyst, according to many experts. &#8220;BlackRock getting a BTC ETF through would be the best thing that could happen to BTC,&#8221; Galaxy Digital CEO Mike Novogratz said yesterday. Accordingly, the news is likely to have created a bullish sentiment in the market. Related Reading: Here’s Why The Tether FUD Could Be Good For Bitcoin However, as always, several reasons play a role in the price movement on the Bitcoin market. One issue that should not be neglected is always the macro situation and the US dollar index (DXY). The latter has seen a setback in the last three days, falling from 104.70 to currently 102.21. This is likely to have favored BTC for now. As for the macro situation, Wednesday&#8217;s interest rate decision by the US Federal Reserve (Fed) certainly still plays a role. The main story is that the market is not buying Fed Chair Jerome Powell&#8217;s hawkish stance. Analysts believe that the two more rate hikes announced in the dot plot are a feint to prevent a bullish breakout in the financial markets. Finally, BTC&#8217;s decoupling from the S&#38;P 500 has also been seen in recent days. Yesterday&#8217;s move could have been the start of a catch-up rally in which BTC shakes off the unnecessary losses caused by the Tether FUD and the SEC lawsuits against Coinbase and Binance US. Related Reading: Bitcoin Holders Show No Panic Loss Selling, What Does It Mean? In addition, Bitcoin hodlers continue to show historically high conviction. As on-chain analyst Axel Adler Jr explained via Twitter, the total BTC inflow across all exchanges is currently at a low, suggesting that Bitcoin holders are in no hurry to sell their coins. The total BTC inflow across all exchanges is currently at a low, indicating that Bitcoin owners are not in a rush to sell their coins. #Bitcoin #HODL pic.twitter.com/JTscheVcgO — Axel 💎🙌 Adler Jr (@AxelAdlerJr) June 16, 2023 As NewsBTC reported, yesterday&#8217;s Tether FUD may also have once again marked the bottom for Bitcoin. Within the last bear market, there have already been three de-pegging events of stablecoins, all of them were marking the local bottom. At press time, BTC changed hands for $25,590. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin price has risen 3.2% since yesterday&#8217;s low of $24,827. At press time, BTC was trading at $25,590 and has thus reclaimed two extremely important price levels for the moment: first, the Bitcoin price has once again risen above the 200-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA) currently at $25,299, and second, the price is now also back above the 200-week EMA at $25,304 (with the weekly close becoming of crucial importance).</p>
<p>As always, there are several narratives for yesterday&#8217;s rise in price. The most obvious narrative and currently the biggest topic in the market is the Bitcoin spot ETF filing by BlackRock, the world&#8217;s largest asset manager, with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). A spot ETF is seen as the holy grail that could finally open the floodgates for institutional liquidity, as Bitcoinist <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/blackrock-bitcoin-etf-good-or-bad-chances/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reported</a> today.</p>
<h2>Reasons For The Bitcoin Rally</h2>
<p>BlackRock is believed to have a strong chance of getting the first spot-based Bitcoin ETF approved by the SEC due to its political influence and network. The new capital inflows made possible may have the potential to be the next bull run catalyst, according to many experts.</p>
<p>&#8220;BlackRock getting a BTC ETF through would be the best thing that could happen to BTC,&#8221; Galaxy Digital CEO Mike Novogratz <a href="https://twitter.com/novogratz/status/1669506355143557121" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">said</a> yesterday. Accordingly, the news is likely to have created a bullish sentiment in the market.</p>

<p>However, as always, several reasons play a role in the price movement on the Bitcoin market. One issue that should not be neglected is always the macro situation and the US dollar index (DXY). The latter has seen a setback in the last three days, falling from 104.70 to currently 102.21. This is likely to have favored BTC for now.</p>
<p>As for the macro situation, Wednesday&#8217;s interest rate decision by the US Federal Reserve (Fed) certainly still plays a role. The main story is that the market is not buying Fed Chair Jerome Powell&#8217;s hawkish stance. Analysts believe that the two more rate hikes announced in the dot plot are a feint to prevent a bullish breakout in the financial markets.</p>
<p>Finally, BTC&#8217;s decoupling from the S&amp;P 500 has also been seen in recent days. Yesterday&#8217;s move could have been the start of a catch-up rally in which BTC shakes off the unnecessary losses caused by the Tether FUD and the SEC lawsuits against Coinbase and Binance US.</p>

<p>In addition, Bitcoin hodlers continue to show historically high conviction. As on-chain analyst Axel Adler Jr explained via Twitter, the total BTC inflow across all exchanges is currently at a low, suggesting that Bitcoin holders are in no hurry to sell their coins.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">The total BTC inflow across all exchanges is currently at a low, indicating that Bitcoin owners are not in a rush to sell their coins. <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Bitcoin</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/HODL?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#HODL</a> <a href="https://t.co/JTscheVcgO" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/JTscheVcgO</a></p>
<p>— Axel <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f48e.png" alt="💎" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f64c.png" alt="🙌" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Adler Jr (@AxelAdlerJr) <a href="https://twitter.com/AxelAdlerJr/status/1669579815635103744?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>As NewsBTC <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/heres-why-tether-fud-could-be-good-for-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">reported</a>, yesterday&#8217;s Tether FUD may also have once again marked the bottom for Bitcoin. Within the last bear market, there have already been three de-pegging events of stablecoins, all of them were marking the local bottom.</p>
<p>At press time, BTC changed hands for $25,590.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-538217 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-16_09-29-21.png" alt="Bitcoin BTC price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-16_09-29-21.png 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-16_09-29-21-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-16_09-29-21-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-16_09-29-21-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-16_09-29-21-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-16_09-29-21-2048x944.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-16_09-29-21-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-16_09-29-21-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3628px) 100vw, 3628px"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1371987095-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Price Projection: Assessing The Ripple-Colombia Central Bank Partnership</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/xrp-price-projection-assessing-the-ripple-colombia-central-bank-partnership/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 07:12:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[colombia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=538202</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To improve the country&#8217;s high-value payment system, Colombia&#8217;s central bank is experimenting with Ripple&#8217;s new end-to-end central bank digital currency technology. How will this collaboration affect the price of XRP? On Thursday, Ripple announced that the central bank of Colombia and the Ministry of Information and Communication Technologies (MinTIC) would be exploring the use of blockchain technology in the country&#8217;s high value electronic payment system with Ripple. The central bank did not specifically state it will pilot test a central bank digital currency, even though it will employ Ripple&#8217;s CBDC platform, supported by a private version of the XRP Ledger. Ripple and @Peersyst are partnering with Colombia’s @BancoRepublica in conjunction with @Ministerio_TIC to pilot use cases that will enhance Colombia’s high-value payment system.🇨🇴 Learn more about the partnership: https://t.co/X9jyJ3pvDa — Ripple (@Ripple) June 15, 2023 Ripple has not let regulatory constraints prevent it from innovating and expanding its reach, notably in Colombia, despite the fact that the blockchain startup is still engaged in a highly publicized legal dispute with the US Securities and Exchange Commission. A Technological Solution In The Offing For Colombia? Blockchain technology was highlighted by Colombia&#8217;s minister of information and communication technology, Mauricio Lizcano, who claimed that it would offer a technological solution (Prototype) that would enable simulations of various use cases in the high-value payment system. Peersyst Technology, a blockchain technology company based in the region, is MinTIC&#8217;s direct partner. According to James Wallis, vice president of central bank engagements and CBDCs, Ripple: &#8220;By harnessing the power of the CBDC Platform, based upon the XRPL, this project will pave the way for transformative advancements in the utilization of blockchain technology within the public sector.&#8221; Ripple previously introduced its end-to-end XRPL-driven CBDC solution, which would enable central banks, financial service providers, and governments to establish their own digital currencies while also assisting them in resolving issues with CBDC deployments. The Colombian government said in August 2022 that it was looking into introducing a CBDC to facilitate transactions and decrease tax evasion, and that it also planned to prohibit cash transactions for quantities more than 10 million Colombian pesos (about $2,390). Related Reading: XRP Smothered In Red Despite Massive Whale Accumulation, Hinman Docs Release A digital asset custody technology provider, Metaco was bought by Ripple a few months ago, and its clientele includes several large, systemically significant institutions. What The Latest Collaboration Means For XRP Price Meanwhile, XRP is back in the red despite briefly rising above $0.55 earlier, adding more than $2 billion to its market capitalization in a 24-hour span, and the publication of the contentious papers pertinent to the Ripple lawsuit. At the time of writing, and after news of the Ripple-Colombia central bank partnership broke out, the price of the XRP token looked it could use more energy to extricate itself out of negative territory. According to the most recent data provided by cryptocurrency market tracker CoinMarketCap, XRP was down by almost a percent in the twenty-four hour time frame, down 8.56 percent in the last seven days, and threatening the 18 percent gain over the past month. XRP is currently trading at $0.47. XRP market cap currently at $24.8 billion. Chart: TradingView.com There are a number of possible explanations for the recent drop in the price of XRP following the announcement of the partnership between Ripple and the central bank of Colombia. XRP price all in red. Source: CoinMarketCap First, investors may not put much stock in the relationship because of the regulatory concerns that typically accompany partnerships between cryptocurrencies and traditional financial institutions. The trend of XRP&#8217;s price could be affected by selling pressure due to this uncertainty. The general state of the market and the attitude of investors could also be factors in the drop of cryptocurrency prices. Related Reading: Cardano (ADA) Price Sheds 19% As Bearish Sentiment Looms Large XRP Price Trajectory: Factors To Consider The price of XRP may fall regardless of specific news or collaborations if there is a lack of confidence in the crypto sector or a general slowdown in the broader economy. Investor emotion, market conditions, and regulatory considerations all play a role in how much of an effect the Ripple-Colombia central bank agreement has on XRP&#8217;s price. At the same time, the dispute between the SEC and Ripple is a major factor influencing the value of XRP. Although the release of the Hinman documents first boosted XRP since they appeared to support Ripple&#8217;s case, the altcoin&#8217;s price eventually fell as investors&#8217; confusion and worry overcame their initial joy. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from The Coin Republic]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>To improve the country&#8217;s high-value payment system, Colombia&#8217;s central bank is experimenting with Ripple&#8217;s new end-to-end central bank digital currency technology. How will this collaboration affect the price of XRP?</p>
<p>On Thursday, <a href="https://www.ledgerinsights.com/ripple-colombia-central-bank-blockchain/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Ripple</a> announced that the central bank of Colombia and the Ministry of Information and Communication Technologies (MinTIC) would be exploring the use of blockchain technology in the country&#8217;s high value electronic payment system with Ripple.</p>
<p>The central bank did not specifically state it will pilot test a central bank digital currency, even though it will employ Ripple&#8217;s CBDC platform, supported by a private version of the XRP Ledger.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Ripple and <a href="https://twitter.com/Peersyst?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@Peersyst</a> are partnering with Colombia’s <a href="https://twitter.com/BancoRepublica?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@BancoRepublica</a> in conjunction with <a href="https://twitter.com/Ministerio_TIC?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@Ministerio_TIC</a> to pilot use cases that will enhance Colombia’s high-value payment system.<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f1e8-1f1f4.png" alt="🇨🇴" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>Learn more about the partnership: <a href="https://t.co/X9jyJ3pvDa" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/X9jyJ3pvDa</a></p>
<p>— Ripple (@Ripple) <a href="https://twitter.com/Ripple/status/1669317477971505152?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Ripple has not let regulatory constraints prevent it from innovating and expanding its reach, notably in Colombia, despite the fact that the blockchain startup is still engaged in a highly publicized legal dispute with the US Securities and Exchange Commission.</p>
<h2><strong>A Technological Solution In The Offing For Colombia?</strong></h2>
<p><a href="https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/42487/colombian-central-bank-partners-ripple-for-blockchain-pilot" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Blockchain technology</a> was highlighted by Colombia&#8217;s minister of information and communication technology, Mauricio Lizcano, who claimed that it would offer a technological solution (Prototype) that would enable simulations of various use cases in the high-value payment system.</p>
<p>Peersyst Technology, a blockchain technology company based in the region, is MinTIC&#8217;s direct partner.</p>
<p>According to James Wallis, vice president of central bank engagements and CBDCs, Ripple:</p>
<blockquote>
<strong>&#8220;By harnessing the power of the CBDC Platform, based upon the XRPL, this project will pave the way for transformative advancements in the utilization of blockchain technology within the public sector.&#8221;</strong>
</blockquote>
<p>Ripple previously introduced its end-to-end XRPL-driven CBDC solution, which would enable central banks, financial service providers, and governments to establish their own digital currencies while also assisting them in resolving issues with CBDC deployments.</p>
<p>The Colombian government said in August 2022 that it was looking into introducing a CBDC to facilitate transactions and decrease tax evasion, and that it also planned to prohibit cash transactions for quantities more than 10 million Colombian pesos (about $2,390).</p>

<p>A digital asset custody technology provider, Metaco was bought by Ripple a few months ago, and its clientele includes several large, systemically significant institutions.</p>
<h2><strong>What The Latest Collaboration Means For XRP Price</strong></h2>
<p>Meanwhile, XRP is back in the red despite briefly rising above $0.55 earlier, adding more than $2 billion to its market capitalization in a 24-hour span, and the publication of the contentious papers pertinent to the Ripple lawsuit.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, and after news of the Ripple-Colombia central bank partnership broke out, the price of the XRP token looked it could use more energy to extricate itself out of negative territory.</p>
<p>According to the most recent data provided by cryptocurrency market tracker CoinMarketCap,<a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> XRP was down</a> by almost a percent in the twenty-four hour time frame, down 8.56 percent in the last seven days, and threatening the 18 percent gain over the past month. XRP is currently trading at $0.47.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/fWRoHFI6/" width="2315" height="1109"/></p>

<p>There are a number of possible explanations for the recent drop in the price of XRP following the announcement of the partnership between Ripple and the central bank of Colombia.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-538210" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRP-2.png" alt="" width="1164" height="91" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRP-2.png 1164w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRP-2-460x36.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRP-2-860x67.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRP-2-768x60.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRP-2-750x59.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRP-2-1140x89.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1164px) 100vw, 1164px"/></p>

<p>First, investors may not put much stock in the relationship because of the regulatory concerns that typically accompany partnerships between cryptocurrencies and traditional financial institutions.</p>
<p>The trend of XRP&#8217;s price could be affected by selling pressure due to this uncertainty. The general state of the market and the attitude of investors could also be factors in the drop of cryptocurrency prices.</p>

<strong>XRP Price Trajectory: Factors To Consider</strong>
<p>The price of XRP may fall regardless of specific news or collaborations if there is a lack of confidence in the crypto sector or a general slowdown in the broader economy.</p>
<p>Investor emotion, market conditions, and regulatory considerations all play a role in how much of an effect the Ripple-Colombia central bank agreement has on XRP&#8217;s price.</p>
<p>At the same time, the dispute between the SEC and Ripple is a major factor influencing the value of XRP. Although the release of the Hinman documents first boosted XRP since they appeared to support Ripple&#8217;s case, the altcoin&#8217;s price eventually fell as investors&#8217; confusion and worry overcame their initial joy.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from The Coin Republic</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a-95-460x257.png" width="460" height="257" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
