<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 02:28:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Hints At Potential Reversal, Buy The Dip?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-reversal-18k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 02:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512363</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price gained pace above the $17,500 resistance after the US CPI release. BTC tested the $18,000 resistance and might correct lower in the short-term. Bitcoin was able to clear the $17,450 and $17,500 resistance levels. The price is trading above $17,500 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There was a break above a key contracting triangle with resistance near $17,240 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could correct lower, but dips might be limited below the $17,500 support zone. Bitcoin Price Rallies 5% Bitcoin price remained strong above the $16,800 support zone. BTC formed a base and started a fresh increase above the $17,000 resistance zone and the 100 hourly simple moving average. The price gained bullish momentum after the US CPI release (+7.1%) and rallied above the $17,500 resistance zone. There was a break above a key contracting triangle with resistance near $17,240 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Bitcoin price is now trading above $17,500 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. A high was formed near $18,070 and the price is now correcting gains. It traded below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent rally from the $17,090 low to $18,070 high. However, the bulls were active above the $17,500 support zone. It remained stable above the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent rally from the $17,090 low to $18,070 high. On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $17,850 level. The first major resistance is near the $18,000 zone, above which the price may perhaps rise towards the $18,250 zone. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The next major resistance is near $18,500, above which the price start a steady increase and rise towards the $19,200 zone in the near term. Dips Supported in BTC? If bitcoin fails to clear the $17,850 resistance, there could be a downside correction. An immediate support on the downside is near the $17,580 level. The next major support is near the $17,500 zone. A downside break below the $17,500 support might call a drop towards $17,200 or the 100 hourly simple moving average. Any more losses might push the price towards the $17,000 zone in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $17,500, followed by $17,200. Major Resistance Levels – $17,850, $18,000 and $18,500. Featured Image from iStock]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price gained pace above the $17,500 resistance after the US CPI release. BTC tested the $18,000 resistance and might correct lower in the short-term.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin was able to clear the $17,450 and $17,500 resistance levels.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $17,500 and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</li>
<li>There was a break above a key contracting triangle with resistance near $17,240 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could correct lower, but dips might be limited below the $17,500 support zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Rallies 5%</h2>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-ready-17-5k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin price remained strong</a> above the $16,800 support zone. BTC formed a base and started a fresh increase above the $17,000 resistance zone and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</p>
<p>The price gained bullish momentum after the US CPI release (+7.1%) and rallied above the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-stuck-17k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$17,500 resistance zone</a>. There was a break above a key contracting triangle with resistance near $17,240 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is now trading above $17,500 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. A high was formed near $18,070 and the price is now correcting gains. It traded below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent rally from the $17,090 low to $18,070 high.</p>
<p>However, the bulls were active above the $17,500 support zone. It remained stable above the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent rally from the $17,090 low to $18,070 high.</p>
<p>On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $17,850 level. The first major resistance is near the $18,000 zone, above which the price may perhaps rise towards the $18,250 zone.</p>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-9.png"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-512364" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-9.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-9.png 1834w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-9-460x212.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-9-860x396.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-9-768x354.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-9-1536x708.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-9-750x346.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-9-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The next major resistance is near $18,500, above which the price start a steady increase and rise towards the $19,200 zone in the near term.</p>
<h2>Dips Supported in BTC?</h2>
<p>If bitcoin fails to clear the $17,850 resistance, there could be a downside correction. An immediate support on the downside is near the $17,580 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $17,500 zone. A downside break below the $17,500 support might call a drop towards $17,200 or the 100 hourly simple moving average. Any more losses might push the price towards the $17,000 zone in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $17,500, followed by $17,200.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $17,850, $18,000 and $18,500.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/iStock-1220738671-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Toncoin (TON) Leads Market Gains With Over 27% In A Week</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/toncoin-ton/toncoin-ton-leads-market-gains-with-over-27-in-a-week/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alyz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 01:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Toncoin (TON)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[telegram]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TON analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ton price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Toncoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TONUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512345</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Toincoin is trading at $2.30, gaining 10.61% in 24 hours. The price change in this period is 0.3172. The 24-hour low is $2.05, while the 24-hour high is $2.37. Despite the recent events in the crypto space, TON has enjoyed a positive price surge today, recording gains in a volatile crypto market. Related Reading: SEC Charges SBF Of Allegedly Conducting Fraud Schemes The trading volume is up by 40% at $66,552,790. According to CoinMarketCap, its market capitalization stands at $2,808,494,330. TON is currently ranked number 22 on the crypto market list showing massive investor attention. Its affiliation with Telegram has also helped the project to soar in popularity even if it has been rebranded. Although the TON coin is still some way off its all-time high value of $5.84, it has enjoyed a positive week and might close 2022 on a high note. What Is Behind Toncoin’s Price Gains? Toncoin is a decentralized blockchain (layer-1) built by the developers of the popular social messaging app Telegram. Toncoin utilizes a proof-of-stake mechanism which has increased its adoption time. This mechanism encourages investors to profit by staking their tokens for rewards rather than going through the rigors of mining. Toncoin price has seemingly surged due to investors rekindling their interest in the project. The Network uses sharding to operate its blockchains and is efficient and scalable. While the crypto winter has persisted and with the dip in bitcoin, investors are looking to diversify. Also, the general crypto market has seen little gains in the last two weeks despite investors&#8217; fears. TON Likely To Sustain Its Rally  TON&#8217;s support levels of 1.123 and 1.572 have been held. TON has broken through the resistance level of 1.835 with 2.998, the next level it will likely surpass. Overtaking the next resistance level will launch Toncoin into a full bull run. TON is currently trading above its 50-day and 200-day SMA. This shows that the assets&#8217; short-term and long-term price movements are positive. The formation of long green candles on the chart&#8217;s right side indicates the bullish pressure. The RSI reading is firmly in the overbought region at 72.48, meaning the asset is giving off a strong buy signal for investors.  The MACD (Moving Average Convergence/Divergence) is above its signal line and displays the positive price movement on the chart. TON will likely sustain this pressure and finish the year strong if the bulls don&#8217;t back out or a major market capitulation. Most crypto assets have fluctuated in the past weeks but are slowly beginning to show signs of life. Related Reading: Dogecoin (DOGE) Climbs 2.58% In 24 Hours, Can It Reach $0.1 Before The Week Runs Out? Toncoin’s usability, scalability, and fast transaction times will likely see its increased adoption in the coming months. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Toincoin is trading at $2.30, gaining 10.61% in 24 hours. The price change in this period is 0.3172. The 24-hour low is $2.05, while the 24-hour high is $2.37.</p>
<p>Despite the recent events in the crypto space, TON has enjoyed a positive price surge today, recording gains in a volatile crypto market.</p>

<p>The trading volume is up by 40% at $66,552,790. According to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/toncoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinMarketCap</a>, its market capitalization stands at $2,808,494,330.</p>
<p>TON is currently ranked number 22 on the crypto market list showing massive investor attention. Its affiliation with Telegram has also helped the project to soar in popularity even if it has been rebranded.</p>
<p>Although the TON coin is still some way off its all-time high value of $5.84, it has enjoyed a positive week and might close 2022 on a high note.</p>
<h2><b>What Is Behind Toncoin’s Price Gains?</b></h2>
<p>Toncoin is a decentralized blockchain (layer-1) built by the developers of the popular social messaging app Telegram.</p>
<p>Toncoin utilizes a proof-of-stake mechanism which has increased its adoption time. This mechanism encourages investors to profit by staking their tokens for rewards rather than going through the rigors of mining.</p>
<p>Toncoin price has seemingly surged due to investors rekindling their interest in the project. The Network uses sharding to operate its blockchains and is efficient and scalable.</p>
<p>While the crypto winter has persisted and with the dip in bitcoin, investors are looking to diversify. Also, the general crypto market has seen little gains in the last two weeks despite investors&#8217; fears.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-512351" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TONUSDT_2022-12-13_23-05-26-860x473.png" alt="TONUSDT" width="860" height="473" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TONUSDT_2022-12-13_23-05-26-860x473.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TONUSDT_2022-12-13_23-05-26-460x253.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TONUSDT_2022-12-13_23-05-26-768x422.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TONUSDT_2022-12-13_23-05-26-750x412.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TONUSDT_2022-12-13_23-05-26.png 979w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<b>TON Likely To Sustain Its Rally </b>
<p>TON&#8217;s support levels of 1.123 and 1.572 have been held. TON has broken through the resistance level of 1.835 with 2.998, the next level it will likely surpass. Overtaking the next resistance level will launch Toncoin into a full bull run.</p>
<p>TON is currently trading above its 50-day and 200-day SMA. This shows that the assets&#8217; short-term and long-term price movements are positive. The formation of long green candles on the chart&#8217;s right side indicates the bullish pressure.</p>
<p>The RSI reading is firmly in the overbought region at 72.48, meaning the asset is giving off a strong buy signal for investors. </p>
<p>The MACD (Moving Average Convergence/Divergence) is above its signal line and displays the positive price movement on the chart.</p>
<p>TON will likely sustain this pressure and finish the year strong if the bulls don&#8217;t back out or a major market capitulation. Most crypto assets have fluctuated in the past weeks but are slowly beginning to show signs of life.</p>

<p>Toncoin’s usability, scalability, and fast transaction times will likely see its increased adoption in the coming months. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Toncoin-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Sees Largest Bitcoin Withdrawal In Its History, BTC Rally Set To Benefit?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/binance-sees-largest-bitcoin-withdrawal-in-its-history-btc-rally-set-to-benefit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 18:57:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512329</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The largest crypto exchange in the world, Binance has experienced the most significant Bitcoin withdrawal in its history, per recent data. The company might face a bank run as crypto investors’ confidence continues to decline following the collapse of trading venue FTX and a U.S. investigation into major crypto exchanges.  Related Reading: PancakeSwap (CAKE) Slides Below Range, Is This An Entry Point For Buyers? At the same time, positive economic data from the U.S. is positively impacting the market. Bitcoin is back above its previous yearly lows. As of this writing, BTC’s price trades at $17,750 with a 4% and 5% profit in the last 24 hours and the previous week, respectively.  Bitcoin Rally In Danger, Binance Makes A Stand Data from on-chain analytic firm Glassnode, shared by Dylan LeClair, indicates that Binance has seen a massive withdrawal of 40,000 BTC in the last 24 hours. The outflows are almost double those seen in July 2021.  At that time, the crypto market was experiencing a second capitulation event after hitting an all-time high north of $60,000. The cryptocurrency lost over 50% of its value from May to late July.  In early November, the crypto exchange saw a significant outflow as FTX went belly up. However, the market seems more bearish on crypto exchanges now that at two of its worst sentiments, during the 2021 capitulation and the FTX collapse.  In addition, the crypto exchange has experienced its worst stablecoin outflow since its inception. Additional data from LeClair indicates that Binance has seen $2.1 billion in outflows in the last 24 hours. There are $20 billion in stablecoin reserves.  Overall, the exchange has enough funds to cover ten times its withdrawals, but the market sentiment is negative, and crypto investors’ confidence continues to dip. Changpeng “CZ” Zhao, CEO of Binance, welcomed the withdrawals and classified them as “stress testing”: We saw some withdrawals today (net $1.14b ish). We have seen this before. Some days we have net withdrawals; some days, we have net deposits. Business as usual for us. I actually think it is a good idea to “stress test withdrawals” on each CEX on a rotating basis. Bitcoin exchange outflows are often a bullish indicator. In the current context, with inflation declining and a potential U.S. Federal Reserve (Fed) pivot, the perception around outflows changed.  Related Reading: Dogecoin (DOGE) Climbs 2.58% In 24 Hours, Can It Reach $0.1 Before The Week Runs Out? However, there is less Bitcoin on exchanges, regardless of market sentiment. The less the BTC supply on these venues, the more support for a market rally. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>The largest crypto exchange in the world, Binance has experienced the most significant Bitcoin withdrawal in its history, per recent data. The company might face a bank run as crypto investors’ confidence continues to decline following the collapse of trading venue FTX and a U.S. investigation into major crypto exchanges. </strong></p>

<p>At the same time, positive economic data from the U.S. is positively impacting the market. Bitcoin is back above its previous yearly lows. As of this writing, BTC’s price trades at $17,750 with a 4% and 5% profit in the last 24 hours and the previous week, respectively. </p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-512360 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-7-860x376.png" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT" width="860" height="376" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-7-860x376.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-7-460x201.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-7-768x336.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-7-1536x672.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-7-750x328.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-7-1140x499.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-7.png 1813w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<h2>Bitcoin Rally In Danger, Binance Makes A Stand</h2>
<p>Data from on-chain analytic firm Glassnode, shared by Dylan LeClair, <a href="https://twitter.com/DylanLeClair_/status/1602704506172706816" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">indicates</a> that Binance has seen a massive withdrawal of 40,000 BTC in the last 24 hours. The outflows are almost double those seen in July 2021. </p>
<p>At that time, the crypto market was experiencing a second capitulation event after hitting an all-time high north of $60,000. The cryptocurrency lost over 50% of its value from May to late July. </p>
<p>In early November, the crypto exchange saw a significant outflow as FTX went belly up. However, the market seems more bearish on crypto exchanges now that at two of its worst sentiments, during the 2021 capitulation and the FTX collapse. </p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-512361 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-1-860x484.jpeg" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT Chart 2" width="860" height="484" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-1-860x484.jpeg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-1-460x259.jpeg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-1-768x433.jpeg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-1-750x423.jpeg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-1.jpeg 900w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>In addition, the crypto exchange has experienced its worst stablecoin outflow since its inception. Additional data from LeClair indicates that Binance has seen $2.1 billion in outflows in the last 24 hours. There are $20 billion in stablecoin reserves. </p>
<p>Overall, the exchange has enough funds to cover ten times its withdrawals, but the market sentiment is negative, and crypto investors’ confidence continues to dip. Changpeng “CZ” Zhao, CEO of Binance, <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1602676998094069760" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">welcomed</a> the withdrawals and classified them as “stress testing”:</p>
<blockquote><p>We saw some withdrawals today (net $1.14b ish). We have seen this before. Some days we have net withdrawals; some days, we have net deposits. Business as usual for us. I actually think it is a good idea to “stress test withdrawals” on each CEX on a rotating basis.</p></blockquote>
<p>Bitcoin exchange outflows are often a bullish indicator. In the current context, with inflation declining and a potential U.S. Federal Reserve (Fed) pivot, the perception around outflows changed. </p>

<p>However, there is less Bitcoin on exchanges, regardless of market sentiment. The less the BTC supply on these venues, the more support for a market rally. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/todd-cravens-QnBrjY-nFUs-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Exchange Binance Refutes Allegations Of Money Laundering</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/crypto-exchange-binance-refutes-allegations-of-money-laundering/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 18:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security And Exchange Commission]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512196</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The crypto sector has been a subject of divided opinions since the inception of Bitcoin and its meteoric rise. While the assets have benefits like fast transactions and decentralization, some risks include fraud and criminal activities. Related Reading: Bitcoin Drops Below $17,000 Pre-CPI And FOMC – Scenarios To Prepare For This Week More recently, during the crypto winter of 2022, some catastrophic events led to negativity among crypto users. The collapse of FTX – one of the world&#8217;s largest exchanges, was a pivot point sending shockwaves throughout the crypto world. Since the event, individuals and bodies have called for crypto regulation. Some individuals now prefer to hold their tokens in personal wallets than leave them in the custody of an exchange. All crypto organizations are under scrutiny, with most governments determined to protect their citizens from fraud at all costs. Binance, the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange by trading volume; is now facing a possible money laundering investigation. The case has been ongoing since 2018 and has gained popularity in light of recent happenings. Reuters has alleged that Binance was employing different tactics to keep information away from public knowledge. There have been divided opinions on how far the regulations can go. The prolonged case between Ripple Labs and the Security and Exchange Commission has led to fears for a possibly bleak future for crypto. Crypto Giant Binance Denies The Allegations Binance, in a series of tweets, denied any wrongdoing citing it as an attack on their law enforcement team. According to the statement posted on Twitter, Binance made it clear that they have top-notch cyber investigators on their books. Also, the company said that it always cooperates during investigations. Binance also went further to share its activities in combating ransomware and hacking cases with training organized in different locations. CEO of Binance Changpeng Zhao had tweeted earlier this year on this issue. According to Zhao, the article by Reuters on money laundering is a waste of time. Related Reading: Inconsistent Metrics Indicate Further Struggle For SUSHI – Colder Winter Ahead? He also labelled the story as fiction and stated that everyone makes mistakes, but the Reuters story was imbalanced. Binance Drums Up Praise For Followers Binance &#8211; the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange, had taken to Twitter to celebrate having ten million followers on the Twitter app. The world&#8217;s largest exchange also launched a challenge to reward followers. According to the tweet, all they need to win is to collect three of Binance&#8217;s #Binance10M badges and win a share of 10 million Satoshi. Binance continues to call for calm in the face of Reuter&#8217;s allegations. Changpeng Zhao &#8211; Binance CEO, has dismissed the reports as FUD. Replying to a tweet that the latest allegations seem sponsored, the CEO stated that FUD, although annoying, encourages growth. Also, he believes such reports will unite Binance supporters as they come together to align.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto sector has been a subject of divided opinions since the inception of Bitcoin and its meteoric rise. While the assets have benefits like fast transactions and decentralization, some risks include fraud and criminal activities.</p>

<p>More recently, during the crypto winter of 2022, some catastrophic events led to negativity among crypto users. The collapse of FTX – one of the world&#8217;s largest exchanges, was a pivot point sending shockwaves throughout the crypto world.</p>
<p>Since the event, individuals and bodies have called for crypto regulation. Some individuals now prefer to hold their tokens in personal wallets than leave them in the custody of an exchange. All crypto organizations are under scrutiny, with most governments determined to protect their citizens from fraud at all costs.</p>
<p>Binance, the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange by trading volume; is now facing a possible money laundering investigation. The case has been ongoing since 2018 and has gained popularity in light of recent happenings. Reuters has <a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/fintech-crypto-binance-doj-idTRNIKBN2SW0ZY" rel="nofollow">alleged</a> that Binance was employing different tactics to keep information away from public knowledge.</p>
<p>There have been divided opinions on how far the regulations can go. The prolonged case between Ripple Labs and the Security and Exchange Commission has led to fears for a possibly bleak future for crypto.</p>
<h2>Crypto Giant Binance Denies The Allegations</h2>
<p>Binance, in a series of <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1602287184400326656" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">tweets</a>, denied any wrongdoing citing it as an attack on their law enforcement team. According to the statement posted on Twitter, Binance made it clear that they have top-notch cyber investigators on their books. Also, the company said that it always cooperates during investigations.</p>
<p>Binance also went further to share its activities in combating ransomware and hacking cases with training organized in different locations. CEO of Binance Changpeng Zhao had <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1534245655497015297" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">tweeted earlier this year</a> on this issue. According to Zhao, the article by Reuters on money laundering is a waste of time.</p>

<p>He also labelled the story as fiction and stated that everyone makes mistakes, but the Reuters story was imbalanced.</p>
Binance Drums Up Praise For Followers
<p>Binance &#8211; the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange, had taken to <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance" rel="nofollow">Twitter</a> to celebrate having ten million followers on the Twitter app.</p>
<p>The world&#8217;s largest exchange also launched a challenge to reward followers. According to the tweet, all they need to win is to collect three of Binance&#8217;s <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance10M?src=hashtag_click" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">#Binance10M</a> badges and win a share of 10 million Satoshi.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-512198 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT_2022-12-13_12-42-00-860x499.png" alt="Crypto Exchange Binance Refutes Allegations Of Money Laundering" width="860" height="499" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT_2022-12-13_12-42-00-860x499.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT_2022-12-13_12-42-00-460x267.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT_2022-12-13_12-42-00-768x446.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT_2022-12-13_12-42-00-750x435.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT_2022-12-13_12-42-00.png 1116w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>Binance continues to call for calm in the face of Reuter&#8217;s allegations. Changpeng Zhao &#8211; Binance CEO, has dismissed the reports as FUD.</p>
<p>Replying to a <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance" rel="nofollow">twee</a><a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance" rel="nofollow">t</a> that the latest allegations seem sponsored, the CEO stated that FUD, although annoying, encourages growth. Also, he believes such reports will unite Binance supporters as they come together to align.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/cryptocurrency-gf7ef40e9c_1280-460x297.jpg" width="460" height="297" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>PancakeSwap (CAKE) Slides Below Range, Is This An Entry Point For Buyers?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/pancakeswap-cake-slides-below-range-is-this-an-entry-point-for-buyers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 17:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CAKEUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CAKEUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PancakeSwap]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512315</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[PancakeSwap (CAKE) has been trading against the broad market, especially when major market movers have rallied. The coin has lost 0.8% over the last 24 hours and still depicts no decisive price action on the chart. Despite the CPI data release, the coin has remained unaffected by that development. CAKE traders are still wary of the asset&#8217;s next price movement. The technical outlook for the coin has painted a bearish picture on the chart. Although that seems to be the case, there could be a scenario in which CAKE makes a comeback. After rangebound trading for weeks, the coin has finally broken below its lower band, indicating a chance of a price appreciation. This could prove beneficial for traders who are planning to log gains from the crypto. Risk-averse traders, however, should be careful about investing as the coin still continues to signify a further potential loss over the immediate trading sessions. The asset is still hovering around pockets of high liquidity, which could prove to be a negative point for traders. For CAKE to register further gains, the coin has to breach some vital trading levels. Related Reading: Dogecoin (DOGE) Climbs 2.58% In 24 Hours, Can It Reach $0.1 Before The Week Runs Out? PancakeSwap Price Analysis: One-Day Chart At press time, CAKE was exchanging hands for $3.80. The coin just fell below the lower band of the restricted price zone. CAKE was sandwiched between the $4.20 and $3.90 price bands, which represented increased selling. The coin&#8217;s immediate price ceiling was $4.08; a move above that could cause the coin to revisit $4.30. Breaching the $4.30 mark will clear the path for the altcoin to reach $4.90. Over the immediate trading sessions, however, the coin is expected to fall to $3.40 before it bounces back. The aforementioned level could act as an entry point for buyers. The amount of CAKE traded in the last session remained red, signifying bearish strength. CAKE Technical Analysis The coin has remained under the power of sellers for most of this month. The recent drop in price has pushed CAKE further into the selling zone. The Relative Strength Index was below 40, indicating a strong selling force. Further selling pressure could cause CAKE to fall below $3.40 and then to $4.30, resulting in a 26% rally. CAKE fell below the 20-Simple Moving Average line due to low buyer demand, indicating that sellers were driving the price momentum at press time. Corroborating that CAKE might start to register gains, the Parabolic SAR sided with the same observation. Parabolic SAR determines the price direction, and the dotted lines below the candlesticks reflect incoming bullishness for the coin. On the contrary, though, the Awesome Oscillator that exhibits price momentum turned red, marking a sell signal for the coin. The signal was, however, declining in strength. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Continues Decline, Sinks To 15th In Market Cap List]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>PancakeSwap (CAKE) has been trading against the broad market, especially when major market movers have rallied. The coin has lost 0.8% over the last 24 hours and still depicts no decisive price action on the chart. Despite the CPI data release, the coin has remained unaffected by that development. CAKE traders are still wary of the asset&#8217;s next price movement.</p>
<p>The technical outlook for the coin has painted a bearish picture on the chart. Although that seems to be the case, there could be a scenario in which CAKE makes a comeback. After rangebound trading for weeks, the coin has finally broken below its lower band, indicating a chance of a price appreciation. This could prove beneficial for traders who are planning to log gains from the crypto.</p>
<p>Risk-averse traders, however, should be careful about investing as the coin still continues to signify a further potential loss over the immediate trading sessions. The asset is still hovering around pockets of high liquidity, which could prove to be a negative point for traders. For CAKE to register further gains, the coin has to breach some vital trading levels.</p>

<h2>PancakeSwap Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-512317 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/CAKEUSD_2022-12-13_20-31-25.png" alt="PanCakeSwap" width="1816" height="782" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/CAKEUSD_2022-12-13_20-31-25.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/CAKEUSD_2022-12-13_20-31-25-460x198.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/CAKEUSD_2022-12-13_20-31-25-860x370.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/CAKEUSD_2022-12-13_20-31-25-768x331.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/CAKEUSD_2022-12-13_20-31-25-1536x661.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/CAKEUSD_2022-12-13_20-31-25-750x323.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/CAKEUSD_2022-12-13_20-31-25-1140x491.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>At press time, CAKE was exchanging hands for $3.80. The coin just fell below the lower band of the restricted price zone. CAKE was sandwiched between the $4.20 and $3.90 price bands, which represented increased selling. The coin&#8217;s immediate price ceiling was $4.08; a move above that could cause the coin to revisit $4.30.</p>
<p>Breaching the $4.30 mark will clear the path for the altcoin to reach $4.90. Over the immediate trading sessions, however, the coin is expected to fall to $3.40 before it bounces back. The aforementioned level could act as an entry point for buyers. The amount of CAKE traded in the last session remained red, signifying bearish strength.</p>
<h2>CAKE Technical Analysis</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-512318 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/CAKEUSD_2022-12-13_20-39-03.png" alt="PancakeSwap" width="1816" height="695" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/CAKEUSD_2022-12-13_20-39-03.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/CAKEUSD_2022-12-13_20-39-03-460x176.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/CAKEUSD_2022-12-13_20-39-03-860x329.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/CAKEUSD_2022-12-13_20-39-03-768x294.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/CAKEUSD_2022-12-13_20-39-03-1536x588.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/CAKEUSD_2022-12-13_20-39-03-750x287.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/CAKEUSD_2022-12-13_20-39-03-1140x436.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>The coin has remained under the power of sellers for most of this month. The recent drop in price has pushed CAKE further into the selling zone. The Relative Strength Index was below 40, indicating a strong selling force.</p>
<p>Further selling pressure could cause CAKE to fall below $3.40 and then to $4.30, resulting in a 26% rally. CAKE fell below the 20-Simple Moving Average line due to low buyer demand, indicating that sellers were driving the price momentum at press time.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-512319 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/CAKEUSD_2022-12-13_20-39-46.png" alt="PancakeSwap" width="1816" height="695" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/CAKEUSD_2022-12-13_20-39-46.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/CAKEUSD_2022-12-13_20-39-46-460x176.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/CAKEUSD_2022-12-13_20-39-46-860x329.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/CAKEUSD_2022-12-13_20-39-46-768x294.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/CAKEUSD_2022-12-13_20-39-46-1536x588.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/CAKEUSD_2022-12-13_20-39-46-750x287.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/CAKEUSD_2022-12-13_20-39-46-1140x436.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>Corroborating that CAKE might start to register gains, the Parabolic SAR sided with the same observation. Parabolic SAR determines the price direction, and the dotted lines below the candlesticks reflect incoming bullishness for the coin.</p>
<p>On the contrary, though, the Awesome Oscillator that exhibits price momentum turned red, marking a sell signal for the coin. The signal was, however, declining in strength.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/tangerine-newt-h3CLVcR1ppI-unsplash-460x460.jpg" width="460" height="460" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana Price Shows Signs Of A Breakout After CPI Data Release</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/solana-shows-signs-of-breakout-after-cpi-data-release/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 15:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512301</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Solana price is up by 6% over the last 24 hours. As the broader market secures upward price movement, most altcoins have followed suit. The release of the Consumer Price Index (CPI), which is an important measure of inflation, showed that U.S. inflation had slowed to 7.1%, down from 7.7% in the past month, as depicted by the numbers released by the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics. The data has revealed that consumer inflation has fallen, pushing stock futures to rise. Owing to this report, the crypto market has also shown signs of recovery. Solana, for instance, had been consolidating for the past few weeks; at press time, however, it has been eyeing a breakout on the upside. The technical outlook for the coin has begun to favor the bulls, indicating accumulation on the chart. As demand for the altcoin is making a recovery, buyers have started to show interest in the chart. Over the last week, the coin lost 1.6%, and the daily gains have managed to undo most of the coin&#8217;s loss. The market capitalization of Solana has also noted an increase, denoting bullish power in the market. It is, however, important for SOL to cross a couple of price barriers in order to continue its upward price trajectory. Related Reading: Bitcoin Long-Term Holder Supply Reclaims ATH, Return Of Conviction? Solana Price Analysis: One-Day Chart SOL was changing hands at $13.80 at the time of writing. The coin has been making intra-day gains after the U.S. CPI data release. The overhead resistance for Solana now awaits at $15, breaching which the coin could move over the $20 mark. Although buying strength needs to remain consistent in the market, a price pullback scenario is unlikely but not impossible, in which SOL would slip to $12 and then to $10. The amount of Solana traded in the last session demonstrated bullish strength, indicating increased buyers on the chart. Technical Analysis The price of the asset has depicted congestion for several weeks now. It has been trading along a descending trendline, but Solana price awaits a breakout now. If that happens, SOL will rise above the $23 price zone. This would mean a 64% price appreciation for the coin. The Relative Strength Index shot past the 40-mark and inched closer to the half-line, which depicted a considerable rise in buying strength. The indicator even formed a bullish divergence which usually reflects a rise in buying strength. In regards to the increase in accumulation, SOL moved above the 20-Simple Moving Average line, meaning that buyers were driving the price momentum in the market. Solana depicted buy signal on the one-day chart &#124; Source: SOLUSD on TradingView In correspondence with more buyers, SOL logged buy signals on the chart. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD), which measures price momentum, underwent a bullish crossover. This is good news for buyers, as it acts as an entry point for them to secure gains. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Breaks Above $18,200 – CPI Data Comes In Better Than Expected The Directional Movement Index (DMI) was yet to reflect positive price action as the -DI (orange) line was above the +DI (blue) line. The Average Directional Index (red) was just below 40, marking strength in the bullish price movement.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Solana price is up by 6% over the last 24 hours. As the broader market secures upward price movement, most altcoins have followed suit.</p>
<p>The release of the Consumer Price Index (CPI), which is an important measure of inflation, showed that U.S. inflation had slowed to 7.1%, down from 7.7% in the past month, as depicted by the numbers released by the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics.</p>
<p>The data has revealed that consumer inflation has fallen, pushing stock futures to rise. Owing to this report, the crypto market has also shown signs of recovery.</p>
<p>Solana, for instance, had been consolidating for the past few weeks; at press time, however, it has been eyeing a breakout on the upside. The technical outlook for the coin has begun to favor the bulls, indicating accumulation on the chart.</p>
<p>As demand for the altcoin is making a recovery, buyers have started to show interest in the chart. Over the last week, the coin lost 1.6%, and the daily gains have managed to undo most of the coin&#8217;s loss.</p>
<p>The market capitalization of Solana has also noted an increase, denoting bullish power in the market. It is, however, important for SOL to cross a couple of price barriers in order to continue its upward price trajectory.</p>

<h2>Solana Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-512305 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSD_2022-12-13_19-22-46.png" alt="Solana Price" width="1816" height="695" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSD_2022-12-13_19-22-46.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSD_2022-12-13_19-22-46-460x176.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSD_2022-12-13_19-22-46-860x329.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSD_2022-12-13_19-22-46-768x294.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSD_2022-12-13_19-22-46-1536x588.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSD_2022-12-13_19-22-46-750x287.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSD_2022-12-13_19-22-46-1140x436.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>SOL was changing hands at $13.80 at the time of writing. The coin has been making intra-day gains after the U.S. CPI data release. The overhead resistance for Solana now awaits at $15, breaching which the coin could move over the $20 mark.</p>
<p>Although buying strength needs to remain consistent in the market, a price pullback scenario is unlikely but not impossible, in which SOL would slip to $12 and then to $10. The amount of Solana traded in the last session demonstrated bullish strength, indicating increased buyers on the chart.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-512306 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSD_2022-12-13_19-26-24.png" alt="Solana Price" width="1816" height="695" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSD_2022-12-13_19-26-24.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSD_2022-12-13_19-26-24-460x176.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSD_2022-12-13_19-26-24-860x329.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSD_2022-12-13_19-26-24-768x294.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSD_2022-12-13_19-26-24-1536x588.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSD_2022-12-13_19-26-24-750x287.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSD_2022-12-13_19-26-24-1140x436.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>The price of the asset has depicted congestion for several weeks now. It has been trading along a descending trendline, but Solana price awaits a breakout now. If that happens, SOL will rise above the $23 price zone. This would mean a 64% price appreciation for the coin.</p>
<p>The Relative Strength Index shot past the 40-mark and inched closer to the half-line, which depicted a considerable rise in buying strength. The indicator even formed a bullish divergence which usually reflects a rise in buying strength.</p>
<p>In regards to the increase in accumulation, SOL moved above the 20-Simple Moving Average line, meaning that buyers were driving the price momentum in the market.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-512307 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSD_2022-12-13_19-27-09.png" alt="Solana Price" width="1816" height="695" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSD_2022-12-13_19-27-09.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSD_2022-12-13_19-27-09-460x176.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSD_2022-12-13_19-27-09-860x329.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSD_2022-12-13_19-27-09-768x294.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSD_2022-12-13_19-27-09-1536x588.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSD_2022-12-13_19-27-09-750x287.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSD_2022-12-13_19-27-09-1140x436.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" /></p>

<p>In correspondence with more buyers, SOL logged buy signals on the chart. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD), which measures price momentum, underwent a bullish crossover. This is good news for buyers, as it acts as an entry point for them to secure gains.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/bitcoin-price-breaks-above-18200-cpi-data-comes-in-better-than-expected/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin Price Breaks Above $18,200 – CPI Data Comes In Better Than Expected</a></p>
<p>The Directional Movement Index (DMI) was yet to reflect positive price action as the -DI (orange) line was above the +DI (blue) line. The Average Directional Index (red) was just below 40, marking strength in the bullish price movement.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/engin-akyurt-7aWvQdR36Y0-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Charges SBF Of Allegedly Conducting Fraud Schemes</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/sec-charges-sbf-of-allegedly-conducting-fraud-schemes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ana N.]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 15:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Breaking News Ticker]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTTUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512238</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The crypto community was left shell-shocked in November 2022 when FTX – one of the leading crypto exchange platforms, filed for bankruptcy. Pessimism towards crypto is at an all-time high, with famous investors like Warren Buffet seemingly right about the risks involved. Investigations into the exchange uncovered gross financial misappropriation and abuse of users&#8217; funds. The disastrous event left many investors seething and funds lost. Related Reading: Bitcoin Drops Below $17,000 Pre-CPI And FOMC – Scenarios To Prepare For This Week According to reports, FTX had allegedly acted unprofessionally and blurred corporate lines between FTX and sister corporation Alameda. The firm supposedly had borrowed funds illicitly from the exchange and sparked an outcry for regulating crypto exchanges. The revelation led to a negative trend in the cryptocurrency market, with exchanges treading cautiously. In recent events, Sam Bankman-Fried has been arrested in the Bahamas and is facing the possibility of prosecution for fraud. SBF Arrest And Charges According to CNN reports, Sam Bankman-Fried, the founder and ex-CEO of FTX, was arrested in the Bahamas on Monday at his apartment. This arrest comes on the heels of criminal charges against him. According to U.S. attorney Damian Williams, Samuel Bankman-Fried was arrested at the request of the U.S. Government. This arrest resulted from a sealed indictment filed by the SDNY. His arrests occurred around 6 pm ET on Monday, and he will likely face a Nassau court today, as detailed by the Royal Bahamas Police force. The Security and Exchange Commission also stated it had created separate charges for SBF for violating securities laws. Charges against SBF include wire fraud, security fraud, securities fraud, and money laundering. Related Reading: Upcoming FOMC Meeting Is The Most Important Ever For Bitcoin – Watch Out For The Dot Plot SBF faces the possibility of extradition to face his charges. According to the United States extradition treaty with the Bahamas, U.S. prosecutors can return defendants to American soil. The condition for the extradition is that the offense must be considered punishable by at least one-year imprisonment in both countries. SBF was to appear before the House Committee today to shed light on recent events. However, due to his arrest on Monday, the new CEO of FTX &#8211; John J. Ray III, will reveal his findings to the House. What&#8217;s Next For FTX Token Holders? The FTT token lost most of its value in the heat of the FTX saga that saw investors liquidate positions in droves. It is now unclear if investors will truly get compensation for their losses. The token price has plummeted, with the SBF arrest set to unfold another chapter in this saga. The former CEO might face prosecution and possible jail time.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto community was left shell-shocked in November 2022 when FTX – one of the leading crypto exchange platforms, filed for bankruptcy. Pessimism towards crypto is at an all-time high, with famous investors like <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/warren-buffett-just-said-doesn-220000034.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Warren Buffet</a> seemingly right about the risks involved.</p>
<p>Investigations into the exchange uncovered gross financial misappropriation and abuse of users&#8217; funds. The disastrous event left many investors seething and funds lost.</p>

<p>According to reports, FTX had allegedly acted unprofessionally and blurred corporate lines between FTX and sister corporation Alameda. The firm supposedly had borrowed funds illicitly from the exchange and sparked an outcry for regulating crypto exchanges. The revelation led to a negative trend in the cryptocurrency market, with exchanges treading cautiously.</p>
<p>In recent events, Sam Bankman-Fried has been arrested in the Bahamas and is facing the possibility of prosecution for fraud.</p>
<h2>SBF Arrest And Charges</h2>
<p>According to CNN reports, Sam Bankman-Fried, the founder and ex-CEO of FTX, was arrested in the Bahamas on Monday at his apartment. This arrest comes on the heels of criminal charges against him.</p>
<p>According to U.S. attorney Damian Williams, Samuel Bankman-Fried was arrested at the request of the U.S. Government. This arrest resulted from a sealed indictment filed by the SDNY.</p>
<p>His <a href="https://twitter.com/BitcoinMagazine/status/1602447620068499457" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">arrests</a> occurred around 6 pm ET on Monday, and he will likely face a Nassau court today, as detailed by the Royal Bahamas Police force.</p>
<p>The Security and Exchange Commission also <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2022-219" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">stated</a> it had created separate charges for SBF for violating securities laws.</p>
<p>Charges against SBF include wire fraud, security fraud, securities fraud, and money laundering.</p>

<p>SBF faces the possibility of extradition to face his charges. According to the United States extradition treaty with the Bahamas, U.S. prosecutors can return defendants to American soil.</p>
<p>The condition for the extradition is that the offense must be considered punishable by at least one-year imprisonment in both countries.</p>
<p>SBF was to appear before the House Committee today to shed light on recent events. However, due to his arrest on Monday, the new CEO of FTX &#8211; John J. Ray III, will reveal his findings to the House.</p>
<h2>What&#8217;s Next For FTX Token Holders?</h2>
<p>The FTT token lost most of its value in the heat of the FTX saga that saw investors liquidate positions in droves.</p>
<p>It is now unclear if investors will truly get compensation for their losses. The token price has plummeted, with the SBF arrest set to unfold another chapter in this saga. The former CEO might face prosecution and possible jail time.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-512242 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/FTTUSDT_2022-12-13_16-35-31-860x499.png" alt="SBF Seeks A Chance At Redemption With New Business Plan To Repay FTX Victims" width="860" height="499" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/FTTUSDT_2022-12-13_16-35-31-860x499.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/FTTUSDT_2022-12-13_16-35-31-460x267.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/FTTUSDT_2022-12-13_16-35-31-768x446.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/FTTUSDT_2022-12-13_16-35-31-750x435.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/FTTUSDT_2022-12-13_16-35-31.png 1116w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/money-g7e8c9ad0c_1280-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin (DOGE) Climbs 2.58% In 24 Hours, Can It Reach $0.1 Before The Week Runs Out?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/dogecoin-2/dogecoin-doge-climbs-2-58-in-24-hours-can-it-reach-0-1-before-the-week-runs-out/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE performance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doge price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusdt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512259</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE) has seen some positive movement in the last day despite the market onslaught. The meme coin was able to see more than 2.5% gains at a time when the majority of the crypto market was struggling price-wise. Currently, DOGE is still standing at a good short-term level but $0.1 remains the level to beat for the digital asset. Dogecoin Gains Momentum The last 24 hours have seen Dogecoin establish some much-needed momentum in the market. It saw an increase in its price in the early hours of Tuesday, which pushed the digital asset right above the $0.099 price level. DOGE has now continued to trend along this line for the better part of the morning, although the increased momentum shows that it may be able to maintain it for much longer. During this time, the trading volume of Dogecoin had also risen to a peak above $600 million for the 24-hour period. This showed where the uptick in price had been generated from as well. It represented a 48% increase in trading volume, which was largely driven by whale transactions. Related Reading: Cardano Community Expects ADA To Jump 50% By End Of Year, Is This Possible? Accumulation has also been persistent for the digital asset as the market eagerly awaits more developments from Elon Musk’s takeover of Twitter. Likewise, the market cap of the meme coin was pushed towards $12 billion, enabling it to hold on to its spot as the 8th largest cryptocurrency by market cap. DOGE price at $0.089 &#124; Source: DOGEUSD on TradingView.com Can DOGE Claim $0.1? With the bear market, the price outlook for cryptocurrencies including Dogecoin has been adjusted. Instead, the level to beat for DOGE has now been moved to $0.1 where the bears continue to mount significant resistance. This makes DOGE’s recovery above $0.09 all the more important since it puts it one step closer to testing this critical level. If DOGE were to successfully break above $0.1, it would put it comfortably above its 50-day moving average. Naturally, this would mark a bullish trend for the digital asset, even if just for the short term, and the next critical level would lie above $0.12. Related Reading: Why The GBTC Discount Could Lead To A Bitcoin Sell-Off DOGE’s most recent recovery has also turned indicators toward buy, especially in the short term. This means there is now support for the cryptocurrency at 0.08, which is expected to hold through the end of the week. If it doesn’t, then the next critical support lies at $0.075, a treacherous point for the digital asset given its previous performances. DOGE is trading at $0.089 at the time of this writing. Although it is in the green on the daily chart, the meme coin is still down more than 10% in the last seven days.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Dogecoin (DOGE) has seen some positive movement in the last day despite the market onslaught. The meme coin was able to see more than 2.5% gains at a time when the majority of the crypto market was struggling price-wise. Currently, DOGE is still standing at a good short-term level but $0.1 remains the level to beat for the digital asset.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Dogecoin Gains Momentum</h2>
<p class="p2">The last 24 hours have seen Dogecoin <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/dogecoin/" rel="nofollow">establish</a> some much-needed momentum in the market. It saw an increase in its price in the early hours of Tuesday, which pushed the digital asset right above the $0.099 price level. DOGE has now continued to trend along this line for the better part of the morning, although the increased momentum shows that it may be able to maintain it for much longer.</p>
<p class="p2">During this time, the trading volume of Dogecoin had also risen to a peak above $600 million for the 24-hour period. This showed where the uptick in price had been generated from as well. It represented a 48% increase in trading volume, which was largely driven by whale transactions.</p>

<p class="p2">Accumulation has also been persistent for the digital asset as the market eagerly awaits more developments from Elon Musk’s takeover of Twitter. Likewise, the market cap of the meme coin was pushed towards $12 billion, enabling it to hold on to its spot as the 8th largest cryptocurrency by market cap.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/4WKqwTRx/" alt="Dogecoin (DOGE) price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1760" /></p>

<h2 class="p2">Can DOGE Claim $0.1?</h2>
<p class="p2">With the bear market, the price outlook for cryptocurrencies including Dogecoin has been adjusted. Instead, the level to beat for DOGE has now been moved to $0.1 where the bears continue to mount significant resistance. This makes DOGE’s recovery above $0.09 all the more important since it puts it one step closer to testing this critical level.</p>
<p class="p2">If DOGE were to successfully break above $0.1, it would put it comfortably above its 50-day moving average. Naturally, this would mark a bullish trend for the digital asset, even if just for the short term, and the next critical level would lie above $0.12.</p>

<p class="p2">DOGE’s most recent recovery has also turned indicators toward buy, especially in the short term. This means there is now support for the cryptocurrency at 0.08, which is expected to hold through the end of the week. If it doesn’t, then the next critical support lies at $0.075, a treacherous point for the digital asset given its previous performances.</p>
<p class="p2">DOGE is trading at $0.089 at the time of this writing. Although it is in the green on the daily chart, the meme coin is still down more than 10% in the last seven days.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Dogecoin-460x256.jpeg" width="460" height="256" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Continues Decline, Sinks To 15th In Market Cap List</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-decline-sinks-15th-market-cap-list/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 14:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Bearish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Market Cap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512209</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu has declined by more than 6% in the last week, and as a result, has lost its place in the market as the 14th largest coin to Tron (TRX). Meme Coin Shiba Inu Has Continued To Struggle In Recent Days More than one month following the FTX collapse, SHIB has continued its struggle as the meme coin has been unable to put together any bullish momentum. While the rest of the market was also hit hard by the crash, other top coins have been nonetheless able to show at least a little recovery. Shiba Inu, on the other hand, has moved virtually sideways since then, and thus still finds itself down almost 30% in the period. Related Reading: Peter Schiff And Jim Cramer Present Their Doom Scenarios For Bitcoin, Cardano, XRP, Dogecoin At the time of writing, SHIB is trading around $0.00000887, down 0.5% in the last 24 hours. Here is a chart that shows the trend in the meme coin&#8217;s value during the past month: The value of the crypto seems to have mostly consolidated during this period &#124; Source: SHIBUSD on TradingView As you can see in the above graph, Shiba Inu has taken a hit during the last few days, breaking the monotonous sideways trend a bit. After this decline, the meme coin&#8217;s monthly returns now stand at around -8%. For comparison, rival Dogecoin is up almost 1% in the same period, while Bitcoin has seen profits amounting to 4%. SHIB Slips Further Down The Market Cap List A consequence of SHIB&#8217;s recent poor performance has been a change in its standing among the wider cryptocurrency sector. Just last month, Shiba Inu was the 13th largest coin based on the market cap, but the meme coin declining while its competitors have shown better strength has led to it first losing its spot to Litecoin (LTC), and now being overtaken by Tron (TRX). Related Reading: Bitcoin NVT Golden Cross Still In “Overbought” Region, Volatility To Follow? The below table shows how the 12th to 17th-placed cryptos have performed recently. SHIB has now fallen down to the 15th rank on the top crypto list &#124; Source: CoinMarketCap The current market cap of Shiba Inu is around $4.8 billion, which is actually only slightly lower than Tron&#8217;s almost $4.9 billion cap. This means that with only a little uptick in price, the crypto can possibly retake the 14th spot on the list. However, it&#8217;s also true that the next-placed asset, Solana, is only minimally behind SHIB now, suggesting that if the meme coin continues to do poorly, it will easily tumble further down the list. Dogecoin has also been struggling recently, but despite its 10% decline in the past week, the coin is still comfortably sitting at the 8th position in the list, with more than double the market cap of SHIB.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu has declined by more than 6% in the last week, and as a result, has lost its place in the market as the 14th largest coin to Tron (TRX).</p>
<h2>Meme Coin Shiba Inu Has Continued To Struggle In Recent Days</h2>
<p>More than one month following the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/ftx-crash-triggers-major-selloff-in-solana-price-how-deep-will-sol-dive/">FTX collapse</a>, SHIB has continued its struggle as the meme coin has been unable to put together any bullish momentum. While the rest of the market was also hit hard by the crash, other top coins have been nonetheless able to show at least a little recovery. <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/company/is-it-too-late-to-buy-shiba-inu-what-is-the-industry-saying-about-it/">Shiba Inu</a>, on the other hand, has moved virtually sideways since then, and thus still finds itself down almost 30% in the period.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/experts-present-doom-scenarios-for-bitcoin-ada-xrp-doge/"> Peter Schiff And Jim Cramer Present Their Doom Scenarios For Bitcoin, Cardano, XRP, Dogecoin</a></p>
<p>At the time of writing, SHIB is trading around $0.00000887, down 0.5% in the last 24 hours. Here is a chart that shows the trend in the meme coin&#8217;s value during the past month:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-512223 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-15-460x255.png" alt="Shiba Inu Price Chart" width="460" height="255" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-15-460x255.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-15-860x477.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-15-768x426.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-15-750x416.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-15.png 972w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p>As you can see in the above graph, Shiba Inu has taken a hit during the last few days, breaking the monotonous sideways trend a bit. After this decline, the meme coin&#8217;s monthly returns now stand at around -8%. For comparison, rival <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/dogecoin-price-plunges-0-0865/">Dogecoin</a> is up almost 1% in the same period, while Bitcoin has seen profits amounting to 4%.</p>
<h2>SHIB Slips Further Down The Market Cap List</h2>
<p>A consequence of SHIB&#8217;s recent poor performance has been a change in its standing among the wider cryptocurrency sector. Just last month, Shiba Inu was the 13th largest coin based on the market cap, but the meme coin declining while its competitors have shown better strength has led to it first losing its spot to Litecoin (LTC), and now being overtaken by Tron (TRX).</p>

<p>The below table shows how the 12th to 17th-placed cryptos have performed recently.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-512224 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/data-460x151.png" alt="Shiba Inu Market Cap" width="460" height="151" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/data-460x151.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/data-860x283.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/data-768x253.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/data-750x247.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/data-1140x375.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/data.png 1267w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p>The current market cap of Shiba Inu is around $4.8 billion, which is actually only slightly lower than Tron&#8217;s almost $4.9 billion cap. This means that with only a little uptick in price, the crypto can possibly retake the 14th spot on the list.</p>
<p>However, it&#8217;s also true that the next-placed asset, Solana, is only minimally behind SHIB now, suggesting that if the meme coin continues to do poorly, it will easily tumble further down the list.</p>
<p>Dogecoin has also been struggling recently, but despite its 10% decline in the past week, the coin is still comfortably sitting at the 8th position in the list, with more than double the market cap of SHIB.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ferhat-deniz-fors-YOCDD-D4oOM-unsplash-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Breaks Above $18,200 &#8211; CPI Data Comes In Better Than Expected</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/bitcoin-price-breaks-above-18200-cpi-data-comes-in-better-than-expected/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 13:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Breaking News Ticker]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CPI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FOMC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[S&P500]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512280</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The first of two key events in a historic week for Bitcoin and financial markets worldwide is in the books. While the CPI release was today at 8:30 ET, the last FOMC meeting of the year is scheduled to take place tomorrow featuring a new dot plot. CPI and FOMC coincide this week for the first time in a while, making it blockbuster week for Bitcoin. And drum roll! The Bureau of Labor Statistics released the November figures for the Consumer Price Index (CPI) and Core CPI a few minutes ago. The expectation for CPI was 7.3% CPI (0.3% MoM), up from 7.7% (0.4% MoM) in October. Core CPI was expected at 6.1% (0.3% MoM), and was 6.3% (0.3% MoM) the previous month. Related Reading: JPMorgan Says S&#38;P 500 Can Soar Over 10% Today – Will Bitcoin Follow? The new numbers for November read as follows: CPI fell 0.6% and was 7.1% in November. Thus, the CPI comes in 0.2% better than expected. Core CPI was 6.0 % in November, falling by 0.3% from the previous month. Compared to the prediction, Core CPI is 0.1% below expectation. Inflation dropping. US November CPI +7.1% y/y vs +7.3% expected. Send it all. &#8212; The Wolf Of All Streets (@scottmelker) December 13, 2022 Already in the run-up to the print, the bulls pushed the Bitcoin price up in anticipation of positive data. The price stood at around $17,550 before the announcement. After the release, the price reacted extremely bullish to the news along with the S&#38;P 500. The latter is currently breaking out of a year-long downtrend. S&#38;P breaking out of its year-long downtrend? pic.twitter.com/tWUKtCQlhg &#8212; Will Clemente (@WClementeIII) December 13, 2022 At press time, BTC was up almost 6% within the last 24 hours and was trading at $17,907. With a local high of $18,209, the price was rejected at the 2-month high of November 11 for the moment being. What Will The Federal Reserve Do With The Data? Prior to the CPI data release, the market was forecasting a rate hike of 50 bps with a 72% probability, according to the CME FedWatch tool. This is compared to a 28% probability of a 75 bps hike. Within the next few hours, it remains to be seen how this rate will shift due to the CPI print. At press time, however, the probability of a 50 basis point jumped significantly to 79.4%, according to the CME FedWatch tool. Today&#8217;s CPI print has thus further increased the probability for 50 bps tomorrow. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Key Indicators Suggest Strengthening Case For Upside Break As NewsBTC reported, JP Morgan published an analysis before releasing the CPI data, according to which it gave the highest probability (50%) of a CPI print of 7.2% to 7.4%. As it turns out, JP Morgan was almost spot on with this assessment. JP Morgan assigned only a 15% chance to the 7.1% outcome and predicted that this could mean increases of 4% to 5% for the S&#38;P 500. Goldman Sachs forecasts that today&#8217;s CPI print could mean a 2% to 3% increase for the S&#38;P 500. However, ultimately the FED will decide tomorrow what to do with the CPI data. As NewsBTC reported, it will also publish the dot plot, which reflects the central bank&#8217;s long-term expectations and outlook. So whether the rally will find a continuation or abruptly stop will depend on whether the FED plays along.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The first of two key events in a historic week for Bitcoin and financial markets worldwide is in the books.</p>
<p>While the CPI release was today at 8:30 ET, the last FOMC meeting of the year is scheduled to take place tomorrow featuring a new dot plot. CPI and FOMC coincide this week for the first time in a while, making it blockbuster week for Bitcoin.</p>
<p>And drum roll! The Bureau of Labor Statistics released the November figures for the Consumer Price Index (CPI) and Core CPI a few minutes ago.</p>
<p>The expectation for CPI was 7.3% CPI (0.3% MoM), up from 7.7% (0.4% MoM) in October. Core CPI was expected at 6.1% (0.3% MoM), and was 6.3% (0.3% MoM) the previous month.</p>

<p>The new numbers for November read as follows: CPI fell 0.6% and was 7.1% in November. Thus, the CPI comes in 0.2% better than expected.</p>
<p>Core CPI was 6.0 % in November, falling by 0.3% from the previous month. Compared to the prediction, Core CPI is 0.1% below expectation.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Inflation dropping. </p>
<p>US November CPI +7.1% y/y vs +7.3% expected.</p>
<p>Send it all.</p>
<p>&mdash; The Wolf Of All Streets (@scottmelker) <a href="https://twitter.com/scottmelker/status/1602659304292712450?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">December 13, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>Already in the run-up to the print, the bulls pushed the Bitcoin price up in anticipation of positive data. The price stood at around $17,550 before the announcement.</p>
<p>After the release, the price reacted extremely bullish to the news along with the S&amp;P 500. The latter is currently breaking out of a year-long downtrend.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">S&amp;P breaking out of its year-long downtrend? <a href="https://t.co/tWUKtCQlhg" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/tWUKtCQlhg</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Will Clemente (@WClementeIII) <a href="https://twitter.com/WClementeIII/status/1602662236685848577?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">December 13, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>At press time, BTC was up almost 6% within the last 24 hours and was trading at $17,907. With a local high of $18,209, the price was rejected at the 2-month high of November 11 for the moment being.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-512288 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-13_14-37-58.png" alt="Bitcoin BTC USD 2022-12-13" width="2962" height="1611" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-13_14-37-58.png 2962w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-13_14-37-58-460x250.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-13_14-37-58-860x468.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-13_14-37-58-768x418.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-13_14-37-58-1536x835.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-13_14-37-58-2048x1114.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-13_14-37-58-750x408.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-13_14-37-58-1140x620.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2962px) 100vw, 2962px" />
<h2>What Will The Federal Reserve Do With The Data?</h2>
<p>Prior to the CPI data release, the market was forecasting a rate hike of 50 bps with a 72% probability, according to the CME FedWatch tool. This is compared to a 28% probability of a 75 bps hike.</p>
<p>Within the next few hours, it remains to be seen how this rate will shift due to the CPI print. At press time, however, the probability of a 50 basis point jumped significantly to 79.4%, according to the CME FedWatch tool.</p>
<p>Today&#8217;s CPI print has thus further increased the probability for 50 bps tomorrow.</p>

<p>As NewsBTC <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/jp-morgan-says-sp-500-can-soar-10-today-bitcoin-too/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a>, JP Morgan published an analysis before releasing the CPI data, according to which it gave the highest probability (50%) of a CPI print of 7.2% to 7.4%. As it turns out, JP Morgan was almost spot on with this assessment.</p>
<p>JP Morgan assigned only a 15% chance to the 7.1% outcome and predicted that this could mean increases of 4% to 5% for the S&amp;P 500.</p>
<p>Goldman Sachs forecasts that today&#8217;s CPI print could mean a 2% to 3% increase for the S&amp;P 500.</p>
<p>However, ultimately the FED will decide tomorrow what to do with the CPI data. As NewsBTC reported, it will also publish the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/upcoming-fomc-meeting-is-the-most-important-ever-for-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">dot plot</a>, which reflects the central bank&#8217;s long-term expectations and outlook.</p>
<p>So whether the rally will find a continuation or abruptly stop will depend on whether the FED plays along.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/business-and-cpi-consumer-price-index-concept-text-cpi-consumer-price-picture-id1414898813-1-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/

Object Caching 206/212 objects using apc
Page Caching using disk: enhanced (Page is feed) 
Database Caching 41/47 queries in 0.008 seconds using memcached

Served from: newsbtc.com @ 2022-12-13 22:15:32 by W3 Total Cache
-->