<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 10:49:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>This Under-The-Radar Coin Just Beat The Top 100 Cryptocurrencies With 120% Explosion</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/all/cryptocurrencies-this-coin-soars-120/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 10:35:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto casino]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[RLB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rollbit]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543073</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies and the gaming industry have a new contender in Rollbit, and it has been making headlines over the past few days thanks to a slew of improvements to its blockchain technology. In a recent development, Rollbit disclosed its most current changes to the platform&#8217;s blockchain technology, propelling it to the forefront of the market. Notably, the company has started offering strong support for its own native cryptocurrency, Rollbit Coin (RLB), giving customers access to better ecosystem functionality and advantages. Related Reading: Elon Musk Fires Another Tweet – But Did It Lift Dogecoin Price? Based on crypto market tracker Coingecko figures, this lesser-known RLB coin has skyrocketed by more than 120% in the last seven days. At the time of writing, RLB was trading at $0.1224, up 24% over the previous 24 hours. Source: Coingecko RLB is a crucial part of the Rollbit lottery system, which decided to airdrop RLB tokens to their current Rollbit.com gaming and trading platform customers rather than holding an initial coin offering (ICO). RLB seven-day price action. Source: Coingecko Despite being a relatively new platform, Rollbit has quickly become one of the top competitors in crypto casinos. Rollbit has established itself as a dominant and significant power in the business, with an average monthly wagering volume above $1 billion. RLB has a market valuation of $357,728,046 with a 24-hour trading volume of $15,311,290. There are 3.3 billion coins in circulation. The highest transaction for RLB today was $0.1248. Its current price is over 14% less than its previous peak. As of today, cryptocurrencies have a market cap of $1.16 trillion. Chart: TradingView.com The Unstoppable Growth Of Cryptocurrencies And Bitcoin Casinos One of the newest trends in the cryptocurrencies and gaming sector, crypto casinos, could change the face of the industry as we know it. Some of the biggest Bitcoin casinos on the market now have thousands of active players worldwide, thanks to their numerous advantages over conventional casinos, including quicker payments, better security, and greater transparency. According to Casinos Blockchain, the global crypto casino market will be worth nearly $280 billion this year, with a $250 million gambling market. Over the years, cryptocurrency has accounted for 4% of all gambling, which is quickly rising. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Encounters Familiar Resistance, Prompting Concerns About Bull Run By the end of 2030, Straits Research projects that the global industry for online cryptocurrency gambling will be worth $153 billion, expanding at a CAGR of about 12%. Meanwhile, based on Captain Altcoin&#8217;s research, Rollbit (RLB) earns an astounding annualized revenue of $498,582,700 by collecting almost $1.36 million daily. This revenue exceeds that of Ethereum, a cryptocurrency with 2,000 times the value of Rollbit. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from BitcoinChaser]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrencies and the gaming industry have a new contender in Rollbit, and it has been making headlines over the past few days thanks to a slew of improvements to its blockchain technology.</p>
<p>In a recent development, Rollbit disclosed its most current changes to the platform&#8217;s blockchain technology, propelling it to the forefront of the market.</p>
<p>Notably, the company has started offering strong support for its own native cryptocurrency, Rollbit Coin (RLB), giving customers access to better ecosystem functionality and advantages.</p>

<p>Based on crypto market tracker Coingecko figures, this lesser-known RLB coin has <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/?page=2" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">skyrocketed by more than 120%</a> in the last seven days. At the time of writing, RLB was trading at $0.1224, up 24% over the previous 24 hours.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-543077" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-114.png" alt="" width="1146" height="71" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-114.png 1146w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-114-460x28.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-114-860x53.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-114-768x48.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-114-1140x71.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-114-750x46.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1146px) 100vw, 1146px"/></p>

<p>RLB is a crucial part of the Rollbit lottery system, which decided to airdrop RLB tokens to their current Rollbit.com gaming and trading platform customers rather than holding an initial coin offering (ICO).</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-543085" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-115.png" alt="" width="849" height="547" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-115.png 849w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-115-460x296.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-115-768x495.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-115-750x483.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 849px) 100vw, 849px"/></p>

<p>Despite being a relatively new platform, Rollbit has quickly become one of the top competitors in crypto casinos. Rollbit has established itself as a dominant and significant power in the business, with an average monthly wagering volume above $1 billion.</p>
<p>RLB has a market valuation of $357,728,046 with a 24-hour trading volume of $15,311,290. There are 3.3 billion coins in circulation.</p>
<p>The highest transaction for RLB today was $0.1248. Its current price is over 14% less than its previous peak.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/93hfSPLk/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>

<h2><strong>The Unstoppable Growth Of Cryptocurrencies And Bitcoin Casinos</strong></h2>
<p>One of the newest trends in the cryptocurrencies and gaming sector, crypto casinos, could change the face of the industry as we know it.</p>
<p>Some of the biggest Bitcoin casinos on the market now have thousands of active players worldwide, thanks to their numerous advantages over conventional casinos, including quicker payments, better security, and greater transparency.</p>
<p>According to Casinos Blockchain, the global crypto casino market will be worth nearly <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/elon-musk-fires-another-tweet/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$280 billion this year</a>, with a $250 million gambling market. Over the years, cryptocurrency has accounted for 4% of all gambling, which is quickly rising.</p>

<p>By the end of 2030, Straits Research projects that the global industry for online cryptocurrency gambling will be worth $153 billion, expanding at a CAGR of about 12%.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, based on Captain Altcoin&#8217;s research, Rollbit (RLB) earns an astounding <a href="https://captainaltcoin.com/could-this-rollbits-next-move-ignite-an-ultimate-rlb-price-explosion/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">annualized revenue</a> of $498,582,700 by collecting almost $1.36 million daily. This revenue exceeds that of Ethereum, a cryptocurrency with 2,000 times the value of Rollbit.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from BitcoinChaser</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-116-460x275.png" width="460" height="275" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BTC Price Analysis: Why Is Bitcoin Down Today?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/btc-price-analysis-why-is-bitcoin-down-today/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 08:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543045</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin price has fallen to the lower end of its almost one-month trading range between $29,800 and $31,300. Already yesterday, BTC briefly fell to as low as $29,704, only to recover to $30,306 within a few hours. At press time, BTC was again moving towards the $30,000 mark, and another fall and liquidity grab seems likely. While this week the macro data releases are pretty quiet, it&#8217;s worth taking a look at what&#8217;s happening in the Bitcoin market itself. Why Is Bitcoin Down Today? Swissblock Insights observed a peculiar calm in the market when Bitcoin reached a new yearly high of $31.840 last week. However, the momentum quickly faded, and selling pressure increased, causing BTC to drop to the low $30ks. They highlight the narrow Bollinger Bands, stating, &#8220;The Bollinger Bands are very narrow, with only a 4.2% value difference separating the upper and lower bands. A move is brewing.&#8221; Moreover, the analysts emphasize the need for a significant catalyst to inject life into the current lackluster scenario: Volatility is expected to appear on the scene, although, in the short term, we are in no man’s land; liquidity remains low, open interest is still flat and shorts are nowhere to be seen. There’s no command in the direction we are going, and only a significant catalyst can spice things up in this dull scenario we are in. According to the analysts, a breakdown of the $29.650 support level would invalidate a long setup. On the other hand, a bullish leg up $31.500 could reignite momentum and surge the price to $33,000. But for this to happen, spot demand needs to reignite strongly and longs need to enter the market, “otherwise momentum will continue to fading.&#8221; Related Reading: This Bitcoin Continuation Pattern Points To 3-6 Months Of Uptrend Ahead Glassnode, an on-chain data provider, further illuminates the current state of the Bitcoin market. Despite the temporary yearly high, they describe the market as &#8220;extremely quiet&#8221;, also pointing to the Bollinger Bands. This compression in volatility signals a market reminiscent of the calm observed in early January, as NewsBTC reported yesterday. Furthermore, Glassnode’s analysis reveals a slow but steady inflow of capital into Bitcoin. The Realized Cap currently sits just shy at $396 billion. After hitting a cycle low at $380 billion, the metric indicates that a slow but steady stream of capital is entering the market throughout 2023. Glasnode also emphasizes that investors remain unwilling to part with their held supply, resulting in choppy market conditions similar to those seen in 2016 and 2019-20 periods. Total realized profit and loss resembles the historic trend: If we take a ratio between total realized profit and loss, [&#8230;] we can also note that a lower high in this ratio was set this week. If sustained, it may allude to similar choppy market conditions seen in both 2019-20, and again in the second half of 2021. The analysis also highlights the profit-locking behavior among Bitcoin holders, with the majority of both short-term (88%) and long-term holders&#8217; balances (73%) held in profit. However, short-term holders are the primary entities that are active in the market. Related Reading: Big Bitcoin Move Ahead: Bollinger Bands See Extreme Squeeze Out of the total 39.600 BTC in daily exchange inflows, 78% of this is associated with the STH cohort. This means that short term holders may have to trim their profits for the time being before selling pressure eases and the bulls can take the upper hand again. GreekLive, an options expert, explains that the Bitcoin market is still losing liquidity, which makes it highly susceptible to spikes and V-shaped recoveries: Cryptocurrencies encountered a V-shaped market today, with BTC falling below $29,700 and ETH below $1,875, before rebounding in a V-shaped during Asian trading hours to regain the round number of points, but the options market barely reacted to this. The analysis advises sellers to focus on static protection and have risk control plans for holding options until expiration. For buyers, timely profit-taking and using futures to hedge options are recommended risk management strategies. At press time, BTC traded at $30,064. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin price has fallen to the lower end of its almost one-month trading range between $29,800 and $31,300. Already yesterday, BTC briefly fell to as low as $29,704, only to recover to $30,306 within a few hours. At press time, BTC was again moving towards the $30,000 mark, and another fall and liquidity grab seems likely.</p>
<p>While this week the macro data releases are pretty quiet, it&#8217;s worth taking a look at what&#8217;s happening in the Bitcoin market itself.</p>
<h2>Why Is Bitcoin Down Today?</h2>
<p>Swissblock Insights <a href="https://swissblock.substack.com/p/no-mans-land" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">observed</a> a peculiar calm in the market when Bitcoin reached a new yearly high of $31.840 last week. However, the momentum quickly faded, and selling pressure increased, causing BTC to drop to the low $30ks. They highlight the narrow Bollinger Bands, stating, &#8220;The Bollinger Bands are very narrow, with only a 4.2% value difference separating the upper and lower bands. A move is brewing.&#8221;</p>
<p>Moreover, the analysts emphasize the need for a significant catalyst to inject life into the current lackluster scenario:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>Volatility is expected to appear on the scene, although, in the short term, we are in no man’s land; liquidity remains low, open interest is still flat and shorts are nowhere to be seen. There’s no command in the direction we are going, and only a significant catalyst can spice things up in this dull scenario we are in.</strong></p></blockquote>
<p>According to the analysts, a breakdown of the $29.650 support level would invalidate a long setup. On the other hand, a bullish leg up $31.500 could reignite momentum and surge the price to $33,000. But for this to happen, spot demand needs to reignite strongly and longs need to enter the market, “otherwise momentum will continue to fading.&#8221;</p>

<p>Glassnode, an on-chain data provider, further <a href="https://insights.glassnode.com/the-week-onchain-week-29-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">illuminates</a> the current state of the Bitcoin market. Despite the temporary yearly high, they describe the market as &#8220;extremely quiet&#8221;, also pointing to the Bollinger Bands. This compression in volatility signals a market reminiscent of the calm observed in early January, as NewsBTC <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/big-bitcoin-move-ahead-bollinger-bands-see-extreme-squeeze/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">reported</a> yesterday.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Glassnode’s analysis reveals a slow but steady inflow of capital into Bitcoin. The Realized Cap currently sits just shy at $396 billion. After hitting a cycle low at $380 billion, the metric indicates that a slow but steady stream of capital is entering the market throughout 2023.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-543060 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/01_RealizedCap.png" alt="Bitcoin Realized Cap" width="2400" height="1382" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/01_RealizedCap.png 2400w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/01_RealizedCap-460x265.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/01_RealizedCap-860x495.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/01_RealizedCap-768x442.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/01_RealizedCap-1536x884.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/01_RealizedCap-2048x1179.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/01_RealizedCap-750x432.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/01_RealizedCap-1140x656.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2400px) 100vw, 2400px"/>
<p>Glasnode also emphasizes that investors remain unwilling to part with their held supply, resulting in choppy market conditions similar to those seen in 2016 and 2019-20 periods. Total realized profit and loss resembles the historic trend:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>If we take a ratio between total realized profit and loss, [&#8230;] we can also note that a lower high in this ratio was set this week. If sustained, it may allude to similar choppy market conditions seen in both 2019-20, and again in the second half of 2021.</strong></p></blockquote>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-543059 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/03_RealizedPnLRatio.png" alt="Bitcoin Realized PnL Ratio" width="2400" height="1382" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/03_RealizedPnLRatio.png 2400w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/03_RealizedPnLRatio-460x265.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/03_RealizedPnLRatio-860x495.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/03_RealizedPnLRatio-768x442.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/03_RealizedPnLRatio-1536x884.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/03_RealizedPnLRatio-2048x1179.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/03_RealizedPnLRatio-750x432.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/03_RealizedPnLRatio-1140x656.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2400px) 100vw, 2400px"/>
<p>The analysis also highlights the profit-locking behavior among Bitcoin holders, with the majority of both short-term (88%) and long-term holders&#8217; balances (73%) held in profit. However, short-term holders are the primary entities that are active in the market.</p>

<p>Out of the total 39.600 BTC in daily exchange inflows, 78% of this is associated with the STH cohort. This means that short term holders may have to trim their profits for the time being before selling pressure eases and the bulls can take the upper hand again.</p>
<p>GreekLive, an options expert, <a href="https://twitter.com/GreeksLive/status/1681118606451707904" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">explains</a> that the Bitcoin market is still losing liquidity, which makes it highly susceptible to spikes and V-shaped recoveries:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>Cryptocurrencies encountered a V-shaped market today, with BTC falling below $29,700 and ETH below $1,875, before rebounding in a V-shaped during Asian trading hours to regain the round number of points, but the options market barely reacted to this.</strong></p></blockquote>
<p>The analysis advises sellers to focus on static protection and have risk control plans for holding options until expiration. For buyers, timely profit-taking and using futures to hedge options are recommended risk management strategies.</p>
<p>At press time, BTC traded at $30,064.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-543061 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-18_09-14-59.png" alt="Bitcoin price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-18_09-14-59.png 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-18_09-14-59-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-18_09-14-59-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-18_09-14-59-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-18_09-14-59-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-18_09-14-59-2048x944.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-18_09-14-59-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-18_09-14-59-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3628px) 100vw, 3628px"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1410473489-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk Fires Another Tweet &#8211; But Did It Lift Dogecoin Price?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/elon-musk-fires-another-tweet/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 06:43:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doge price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543048</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Elon Musk has consistently proven to be a pivotal figure in cryptocurrencies, particularly Dogecoin (DOGE), his crypto of choice. His influence on DOGE has been nothing short of remarkable, with any mention or action from him causing significant fluctuations in its price. In the digital currency landscape, where DOGE has struggled to keep pace with its counterparts despite the recent positive sentiment surrounding cryptocurrencies, any movement on the meme coin carries a heightened significance. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Encounters Familiar Resistance, Prompting Concerns About Bull Run Enthusiasts eagerly await every word uttered by Musk, recognizing the potential impact his statements can have on the price and overall market sentiment. Given this context, what did Elon Musk, the Tesla and SpaceX top honcho and Twitter owner, say this time, and how did it reverberate within the DOGE community? Elon Musk ‘Doges’ Preference Boosts Dogecoin Price Musk recently responded to a question on a popular social media platform. The question was about his preference between cats and dogs, and the enigmatic billionaire, promptly answered, &#8220;Doges.&#8221; This seemingly innocuous response had an immediate impact on the price of the meme coin. Doges — Elon Musk (@elonmusk) July 17, 2023 Following Musk&#8217;s endorsement, Dogecoin experienced a surge in its price on Monday, with a notable 3% gain. Its trading value climbed from $0.07 to $0.073, reflecting the enthusiastic market response to Musk&#8217;s statement. The sudden price increase further solidified the significance of Musk&#8217;s influence on Dogecoin and the broader cryptocurrency market. DOGE to USD gets a little boost. Source: CoinMarketCap However, as of the time of writing, the initial excitement has subsided, and DOGE’s price on Coingecko has adjusted to $0.070024. Despite the slight dip from the peak, the meme coin still managed to record a modest increase of 0.5% within the last 24 hours. Over seven days, Dogecoin showcased a more promising rally, with a substantial gain of 8.2%. Source: Coingecko Crypto Trading Expert Foresees DOGE Breakout Meanwhile, crypto trading expert Ali Martinez recently took to Twitter to share his prediction that Dogecoin is on the brink of a breakout, presenting an opportunity for investors. Leveraging an analysis of critical resistance levels and historical data on address accumulation, Martinez foresees a potential 10% price surge if DOGE surpasses the significant $0.75 supply wall. #Dogecoin is trying to break out! Slicing through the $0.75 supply wall will trigger a 10% upswing to $0.85, where 176,000 addresses had previously purchased over 12.34 billion $DOGE. pic.twitter.com/RJw7v7q30X — Ali (@ali_charts) July 15, 2023 His insightful analysis suggests that breaking through the $0.75 supply wall can catalyze a notable upswing in Dogecoin&#8217;s price, propelling it toward the $0.85 mark. DOGE market cap nearing the $10 billion level. Chart: TradingView.com Related Reading: Polkadot (DOT) Price Momentum Builds As Open Interest Climbs – Details This specific price level holds particular significance because of the presence of approximately 176,000 addresses that had previously acquired a substantial amount of over 12.34 billion DOGE. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Doha News]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Elon Musk has consistently proven to be a pivotal figure in cryptocurrencies, particularly Dogecoin (DOGE), his crypto of choice. His influence on DOGE has been nothing short of remarkable, with any mention or action from him causing significant fluctuations in its price.</p>
<p>In the digital currency landscape, where DOGE has struggled to keep pace with its counterparts despite the recent positive sentiment surrounding cryptocurrencies, any movement on the meme coin carries a heightened significance.</p>

<p>Enthusiasts eagerly await every word uttered by Musk, recognizing the potential impact his statements can have on the price and overall market sentiment.</p>
<p>Given this context, what did Elon Musk, the Tesla and SpaceX top honcho and Twitter owner, say this time, and how did it reverberate within the DOGE community?</p>
<h2><strong>Elon Musk ‘Doges’ Preference Boosts Dogecoin Price</strong></h2>
<p>Musk recently responded to a question on a popular social media platform. The question was about his preference between cats and dogs, and the enigmatic billionaire, <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1680815158157877248" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">promptly answered, &#8220;Doges.&#8221;</a> This seemingly innocuous response had an immediate impact on the price of the meme coin.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Doges</p>
<p>— Elon Musk (@elonmusk) <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1680815158157877248?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Following Musk&#8217;s endorsement, Dogecoin experienced a surge in its price on Monday, with a notable 3% gain. Its trading value climbed from $0.07 to $0.073, reflecting the enthusiastic market response to Musk&#8217;s statement. </p>
<p>The sudden price increase further solidified the significance of Musk&#8217;s influence on Dogecoin and the broader cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-543049" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-110.png" alt="" width="745" height="336" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-110.png 745w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-110-460x207.png 460w" sizes="(max-width: 745px) 100vw, 745px"/></p>

<p>However, as of the time of writing, the initial excitement has subsided, and <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1680815158157877248" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">DOGE’s price on Coingecko</a> has adjusted to $0.070024. Despite the slight dip from the peak, the meme coin still managed to record a modest increase of 0.5% within the last 24 hours. </p>
<p>Over seven days, Dogecoin showcased a more promising rally, with a substantial gain of 8.2%.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-543051" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-111.png" alt="" width="943" height="70" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-111.png 943w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-111-460x34.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-111-860x64.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-111-768x57.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-111-750x56.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 943px) 100vw, 943px"/></p>

<h2><strong>Crypto Trading Expert Foresees DOGE Breakout</strong></h2>
<p>Meanwhile, crypto trading expert Ali Martinez recently took<a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1680141210122371072" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> to Twitter</a> to share his prediction that Dogecoin is on the brink of a breakout, presenting an opportunity for investors. </p>
<p>Leveraging an analysis of critical resistance levels and historical data on address accumulation, Martinez foresees a potential 10% price surge if DOGE surpasses the significant $0.75 supply wall.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Dogecoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Dogecoin</a> is trying to break out!</p>
<p>Slicing through the $0.75 supply wall will trigger a 10% upswing to $0.85, where 176,000 addresses had previously purchased over 12.34 billion <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24DOGE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$DOGE</a>. <a href="https://t.co/RJw7v7q30X" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/RJw7v7q30X</a></p>
<p>— Ali (@ali_charts) <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1680141210122371072?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>His insightful analysis suggests that breaking through the $0.75 supply wall can catalyze a notable upswing in Dogecoin&#8217;s price, propelling it toward the $0.85 mark. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/GxipMy2U/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>


<p>This specific price level holds particular significance because of the presence of approximately 176,000 addresses that had previously acquired a substantial amount of over 12.34 billion DOGE.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Doha News</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-112-460x258.png" width="460" height="258" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>LINK Price Prediction: Chainlink Rallies Over 7% As The Bulls Aim $8.8</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/link/link-price-prediction-chainlink-to-8-8/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 04:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LINK]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chainlink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Link]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LINKUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[linkusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543042</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Chainlink’s LINK price is gaining pace above $7.00. The price could rise further if it clears the $7.35 and $7.50 resistance levels. Chainlink token price is showing positive signs and rising from $6.50 against the US dollar. The price is trading above the $7.00 level and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $6.65 on the 4-hour chart of the LINK/USD pair (data source from Kraken). The price could gain bullish momentum above the $7.35 resistance zone. Chainlink (LINK) Price Eyes More Gains After a short-term downside correction, LINK price found support near the $6.45 level against the US Dollar. A low was formed near $6.458 and the price started a fresh increase, unlike Bitcoin and Ethereum. There was a clear move above the $6.65 and $6.90 resistance levels. The price climbed above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $7.36 swing high to the $6.458 low. LINK price is now trading above the $7.00 level and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support near $6.65 on the 4-hour chart of the LINK/USD pair. The pair is now facing resistance near the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $7.36 swing high to the $6.458 low. Source: LINKUSD on TradingView.com The first major resistance is near the $7.35 zone. A clear break above $7.35 may possibly start a fresh increase toward the $7.50 and $7.85 levels. The next major resistance is near the $8.00 level, above which the price could revisit $8.80. Dips Supported? If Chainlink’s price fails to climb above the $7.35 resistance level, there could be a downside correction. Initial support on the downside is near the $6.90 level. The next major support is near the $6.65 level and the trend line zone, below which the price might test the $6.45 level. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $6.00 level in the near term. Technical Indicators 4 hours MACD – The MACD for LINK/USD is gaining momentum in the bullish zone. 4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LINK/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $6.90 and $6.65. Major Resistance Levels – $7.35 and $8.00.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Chainlink’s LINK price is gaining pace above $7.00. The price could rise further if it clears the $7.35 and $7.50 resistance levels.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Chainlink token price is showing positive signs and rising from $6.50 against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is trading above the $7.00 level and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $6.65 on the 4-hour chart of the LINK/USD pair (data source from Kraken).</li>
<li>The price could gain bullish momentum above the $7.35 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Chainlink (LINK) Price Eyes More Gains</h2>
<p>After a short-term downside correction, LINK price found support near the $6.45 level against the US Dollar. A low was formed near $6.458 and the price started a fresh increase, unlike <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-30500-fresh-rally/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a> and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-downsides-1900/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum</a>.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above the $6.65 and $6.90 resistance levels. The price climbed above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $7.36 swing high to the $6.458 low. LINK price is now trading above the $7.00 level and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support near $6.65 on the 4-hour chart of the LINK/USD pair. The pair is now facing resistance near the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $7.36 swing high to the $6.458 low.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-543043" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chainlink-LINK.png" alt="LINK Price Prediction" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chainlink-LINK.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chainlink-LINK-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chainlink-LINK-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chainlink-LINK-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chainlink-LINK-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chainlink-LINK-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chainlink-LINK-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LINKUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">LINKUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $7.35 zone. A clear break above $7.35 may possibly start a fresh increase toward the $7.50 and $7.85 levels. The next major resistance is near the $8.00 level, above which the price could revisit $8.80.</p>
<h2>Dips Supported?</h2>
<p>If Chainlink’s price fails to climb above the $7.35 resistance level, there could be a downside correction. Initial support on the downside is near the $6.90 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $6.65 level and the trend line zone, below which the price might test the $6.45 level. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $6.00 level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LINK/USD is gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LINK/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $6.90 and $6.65.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $7.35 and $8.00.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/shutterstock_309774656-460x311.jpg" width="460" height="311" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Indicators Suggest A Strong Case For More Downsides</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-downsides-1900/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 03:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543039</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum price corrected further lower below the $1,900 level against the US Dollar. ETH is showing bearish signs and might decline further toward $1,825. Ethereum extended its decline and tested the $1,875 level. The price is trading below $1,930 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,910 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could decline further if it stays below the $1,910 and $1,940 resistance levels. Ethereum Price Could Extend Losses Ethereum’s price made a fresh attempt to start a decent increase above the $1,950 resistance. However, ETH struggled to gain strength for a move above $1,950. A high was formed near $1,943 and the price reacted to the downside. There was a break below the $1,900 support zone. A new weekly low is formed near $1,875 and the price is now attempting a fresh increase. It broke the $1,890 and $1,900 levels. There was a move above the 50% Fib retracement level recent decline from the $1,943 swing high to the $1,875 low. Ether is now trading below $1,930 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $1,910 level. There is also a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,910 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. The trend line is near the 61.8% Fib retracement level recent decline from the $1,943 swing high to the $1,875 low. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com The first major resistance is near the $1,950 zone, above which the price could rise toward the $1,985 resistance zone. The next major resistance is near the $2,030 level. Any more gains could send Ether toward the $2,120 resistance or even $2,200. More Losses in ETH? If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,910 resistance, it could start a fresh decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,890 level. The first major support is near the $1,875 level, below which the price could extend its decline. The next major support is near the $1,825 support level. Any more losses could send Ether toward the $1,780 support level in the near term. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is losing momentum in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is now below the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,875 Major Resistance Level – $1,910]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum price corrected further lower below the $1,900 level against the US Dollar. ETH is showing bearish signs and might decline further toward $1,825.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum extended its decline and tested the $1,875 level.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $1,930 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</li>
<li>There is a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,910 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could decline further if it stays below the $1,910 and $1,940 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Could Extend Losses</h2>
<p>Ethereum’s price made a fresh attempt to start a decent increase above the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-move-1900/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$1,950 resistance</a>. However, ETH struggled to gain strength for a move above $1,950.</p>
<p>A high was formed near $1,943 and the price reacted to the downside. There was a break below the $1,900 support zone. A new weekly low is formed near $1,875 and the price is now attempting a fresh increase. It broke the $1,890 and $1,900 levels.</p>
<p>There was a move above the 50% Fib retracement level recent decline from the $1,943 swing high to the $1,875 low. Ether is now trading below $1,930 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-breaks-2000/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100-hourly Simple Moving Average</a>.</p>
<p>On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $1,910 level. There is also a connecting bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,910 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. The trend line is near the 61.8% Fib retracement level recent decline from the $1,943 swing high to the $1,875 low.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-543040" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-11.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-11.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-11-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-11-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-11-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-11-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-11-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-11-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $1,950 zone, above which the price could rise toward the $1,985 resistance zone. The next major resistance is near the $2,030 level. Any more gains could send Ether toward the $2,120 resistance or even $2,200.</p>
<h2>More Losses in ETH?</h2>
<p>If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,910 resistance, it could start a fresh decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,890 level.</p>
<p>The first major support is near the $1,875 level, below which the price could extend its decline. The next major support is near the $1,825 support level. Any more losses could send Ether toward the $1,780 support level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is losing momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,875</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,910</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/shutterstock_481530088-460x314.jpg" width="460" height="314" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Needs To Clear $30,500 For Hopes of a Fresh Rally</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-30500-fresh-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 03:20:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543036</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is again moving lower toward the $29,200 level. BTC must surpass $30,500 to attempt a fresh increase in the near term. Bitcoin is showing bearish signs and trading well below the $30,500 zone. The price is trading below $30,300 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,200 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could continue to move down if it stays below the $30,500 resistance. Bitcoin Price Extends Decline Bitcoin price attempted a fresh increase above the $30,250 level but failed to gain bullish momentum. BTC stayed below the key $30,500 resistance zone. A high was formed near $30,447 before the price dropped below $30,000. It traded to a new weekly low at $29,669 and is currently correcting losses. It broke the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $30,447 swing high to the $29,669 low. The price was able to climb above the $30,000 level. Bitcoin price is now trading below $30,300 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. Immediate resistance is near the $30,200 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,200 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. The trend line is near the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $30,447 swing high to the $29,669 low. The first major resistance is near $30,265. The main resistance is now forming near the $30,450 and $30,500 levels. A close above the $30,500 level might start a fresh increase. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The next major resistance is near the $30,850 level. Any more gains could open the doors for a move toward the $31,500 resistance zone. More Losses in BTC? If Bitcoin fails to clear the $30,500 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $29,850 level. The next major support is near the $29,550 level, below which there could be a drop toward the $29,200 support zone. Any more losses might send the price toward the $28,750 level in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now near the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $29,850, followed by $29,200. Major Resistance Levels – $30,200, $30,265, and $30,500.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is again moving lower toward the $29,200 level. BTC must surpass $30,500 to attempt a fresh increase in the near term.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is showing bearish signs and trading well below the $30,500 zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $30,300 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,200 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move down if it stays below the $30,500 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Extends Decline</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price attempted a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-aims-31k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">fresh increase above the $30,250 level</a> but failed to gain bullish momentum. BTC stayed below the key $30,500 resistance zone.</p>
<p>A high was formed near $30,447 before the price dropped below $30,000. It traded to a new weekly low at $29,669 and is currently correcting losses. It broke the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $30,447 swing high to the $29,669 low.</p>
<p>The price was able to climb above the $30,000 level. Bitcoin price is now trading below $30,300 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-attempts-to-follow-xrp/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>. Immediate resistance is near the $30,200 level.</p>
<p>There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,200 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. The trend line is near the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent decline from the $30,447 swing high to the $29,669 low.</p>
<p>The first major resistance is near $30,265. The main resistance is now forming near the $30,450 and $30,500 levels. A close above the $30,500 level might start a fresh increase.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-543037" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-11.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-11.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-11-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-11-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-11-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-11-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-11-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-11-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $30,850 level. Any more gains could open the doors for a move toward the $31,500 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>More Losses in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin fails to clear the $30,500 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $29,850 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $29,550 level, below which there could be a drop toward the $29,200 support zone. Any more losses might send the price toward the $28,750 level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now near the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $29,850, followed by $29,200.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $30,200, $30,265, and $30,500.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/shutterstock_1363186970-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Four Straight Days Down: Bullish Or Bearish?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-four-straight-days-down-bullish-or-bearish/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[dbthequant]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 02:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543011</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[While most crypto market watchers remain focused on Bitcoin&#8217;s ongoing struggle with $31,000, Ethereum recently closed above the psychologically important $2000 level for the first time in weeks. Now poised to close lower for four straight days, let&#8217;s take an evidence-based approach and determine whether four consecutive days lower for Ether is historically bullish or bearish going forward. Let&#8217;s dive in! Ethereum&#8217;s Close Above $2000 Followed By Pullback After closing at an impressive multi-week high and back above the $2000 level on July 13th, Ether has pulled back for four consecutive sessions, one of the conditions we&#8217;ll test momentarily. To better add context to the test, we&#8217;ll also add two more conditions requiring that [1] Ether is above its 200ma and that [2] its 200ma is rising. Why? The 200ma and its slope both act as simple filters to help determine market regime. For example, this latest four day pullback in Ether occurs in an improving market in which ETH is above the rising 200ma. If the current four day pullback were occurring in a down trending market regime, we would require that ETH be below its declining 200ma. Ethereum daily chart  &#124; ETHUSD on TradingView.com What does this pullback in Ethereum suggest for its price? To find out, we&#8217;ll look at all signals since inception, and also compare those signals to a simple &#8220;buy and hold&#8221; approach. This will provide us with a baseline to better understand today&#8217;s test results. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Breaks $2,000 As The Bulls Take Over Crypto Market Four Days Down Compared To Buy And Hold The holding time graphic below shows historical results for Ether&#8217;s current technical setup on top with a simple &#8220;buy and hold&#8221; approach on the bottom. In other words, we&#8217;ll show hypothetical results using various holding times solely for when Ethereum has closed lower for four straight days while above its rising 200ma on top. The bottom results will act as a baseline, assuming a hypothetical purchase of ETHUSD with no conditions whatsoever and an exit n-days later. Average Trade Comparison  &#124; SOURCE: REKTelligence, Tableau While both approaches show positive average trade results over every exit we tested from 7 days through 90 days, our baseline &#8220;buy and hold&#8221; actually outperforms the current technical setup of four days down. The single exception is the &#8220;exit in 90 days&#8221; in which the current setup slightly outpaces the historical average &#8220;buy and hold&#8221; trade, beating it 62.1% to 59.4%. But while the average trade statistic remains important, it does not always tell the whole story. When looking at a comparison of the largest hypothetical losses for both approaches using the same conditions described earlier, note that the largest losses (i.e., worst trades) for the current four days down setup are far lower than for a simple &#8220;buy and hold&#8221; approach. This largest loss comparison indicates that while the current setup may not beat &#8220;buy and hold&#8221; in terms of average trade, Ethereum may currently have a lower than usual risk exposure &#8211; something most experienced traders will appreciate. Largest Loss Comparison  &#124; SOURCE: REKTelligence, Tableau Related Reading: Tradecurve Unique Set Of Features Has Ethereum Holders Excited While the past doesn&#8217;t predict future, based on our analysis, Ethereum looks poised for potential upside mostly in line with typical &#8220;buy and hold&#8221; expectations. In other words, not overly exciting and apparently lacking any meaningful edge at the moment. That said, risk also appears lower than usual relative to the &#8220;buy and hold&#8221; largest loss stats. Traders take note. Ethereum may now be offering its typical return profile based on its current technical setup, but with a lower overall risk exposure. DB the Quant is the author of the REKTelligence Report newsletter on Substack. Follow @REKTelligence on Twitter for evidence-based crypto market research and analysis. Important Note: This content is strictly educational in nature and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from nadia_snopek/Adobe Stock. Charts from TradingView.com.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While most crypto market watchers remain focused on Bitcoin&#8217;s ongoing struggle with $31,000, Ethereum recently closed above the psychologically important $2000 level for the first time in weeks. Now poised to close lower for four straight days, let&#8217;s take an evidence-based approach and determine whether four consecutive days lower for Ether is historically bullish or bearish going forward. Let&#8217;s dive in!</p>
<h2><strong>Ethereum&#8217;s Close Above $2000 Followed By Pullback</strong></h2>
<p>After closing at an impressive multi-week high and back above the $2000 level on July 13th, Ether has pulled back for four consecutive sessions, one of the conditions we&#8217;ll test momentarily. To better add context to the test, we&#8217;ll also add two more conditions requiring that [1] Ether is above its 200ma and that [2] its 200ma is rising. Why? The 200ma and its slope both act as simple filters to help determine market regime. For example, this latest four day pullback in Ether occurs in an improving market in which ETH is above the rising 200ma. If the current four day pullback were occurring in a down trending market regime, we would require that ETH be below its declining 200ma.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-543013 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-SETUP-460x370.png" alt="" width="460" height="370" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-SETUP-460x370.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-SETUP-860x692.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-SETUP-768x618.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-SETUP-750x603.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-SETUP.png 987w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>
<p style="text-align: center">Ethereum daily chart  | ETHUSD on TradingView.com</p>
<p>What does this pullback in Ethereum suggest for its price? To find out, we&#8217;ll look at all signals since inception, and also compare those signals to a simple &#8220;buy and hold&#8221; approach. This will provide us with a baseline to better understand today&#8217;s test results.</p>

<h2><strong>Four Days Down Compared To Buy And Hold</strong></h2>
<p>The holding time graphic below shows historical results for Ether&#8217;s current technical setup on top with a simple &#8220;buy and hold&#8221; approach on the bottom. In other words, we&#8217;ll show hypothetical results using various holding times solely for when Ethereum has closed lower for four straight days while above its rising 200ma on top. The bottom results will act as a baseline, assuming a hypothetical purchase of ETHUSD with no conditions whatsoever and an exit n-days later.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-543017 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AVG-TRADE-Comparison2-436x460.png" alt="" width="436" height="460" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AVG-TRADE-Comparison2-436x460.png 436w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AVG-TRADE-Comparison2.png 738w" sizes="(max-width: 436px) 100vw, 436px"/></p>
<p style="text-align: center">Average Trade Comparison  | SOURCE: REKTelligence, Tableau</p>
<p>While both approaches show positive average trade results over every exit we tested from 7 days through 90 days, our baseline &#8220;buy and hold&#8221; actually outperforms the current technical setup of four days down. The single exception is the &#8220;exit in 90 days&#8221; in which the current setup slightly outpaces the historical average &#8220;buy and hold&#8221; trade, beating it 62.1% to 59.4%.</p>
<p>But while the average trade statistic remains important, it does not always tell the whole story. When looking at a comparison of the largest hypothetical losses for both approaches using the same conditions described earlier, note that the largest losses (i.e., worst trades) for the current four days down setup are far lower than for a simple &#8220;buy and hold&#8221; approach. This largest loss comparison indicates that while the current setup may not beat &#8220;buy and hold&#8221; in terms of average trade, Ethereum may currently have a lower than usual risk exposure &#8211; something most experienced traders will appreciate.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-543018 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/WORST-LOSS-comparison2-460x434.png" alt="" width="460" height="434" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/WORST-LOSS-comparison2-460x434.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/WORST-LOSS-comparison2-768x724.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/WORST-LOSS-comparison2-750x707.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/WORST-LOSS-comparison2.png 827w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>
<p style="text-align: center">Largest Loss Comparison  | SOURCE: REKTelligence, Tableau</p>




While the past doesn&#8217;t predict future, based on our analysis, Ethereum looks poised for potential upside mostly in line with typical &#8220;buy and hold&#8221; expectations. In other words, not overly exciting and apparently lacking any meaningful edge at the moment. That said, risk also appears lower than usual relative to the &#8220;buy and hold&#8221; largest loss stats. Traders take note. Ethereum may now be offering its typical return profile based on its current technical setup, but with a lower overall risk exposure.
<p>DB the Quant is the author of the <a href="https://rektelligence.substack.com/" rel="nofollow">REKTelligence Report</a> newsletter on Substack. Follow <a href="https://twitter.com/rektelligence?s=21&amp;t=MTrDR-nCiRRkbzbRMFRc0Q" rel="nofollow">@REKTelligence</a> on Twitter for evidence-based crypto market research and analysis. Important Note: This content is strictly educational in nature and should not be considered investment advice.</p>
<p>Featured image from nadia_snopek/Adobe Stock. Charts from TradingView.com.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-113-460x288.png" width="460" height="288" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>USDC Market Cap Drops As Redemptions Climb To $1.4 Billion</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/stablecoin/usdc-market-cap-drops-as-1-4-billion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 01:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[circle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Circle USDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542984</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As one of the biggest stablecoins, USDC is one of the major players in the crypto industry. However, the stablecoins have seen better days, as the stablecoin has seen its market cap drop drastically over the past few months. Related Reading: 29% Of Bitcoin’s Circulating Supply Is Now Presumed Lost Forever The second-largest stablecoin has seen its market cap drop by over $1.4 billion in just the last few days thanks to a surge in redemptions.  $1.4 Billion Redeemed In One Week The stablecoin market was rocked this week by a massive redemption of USDC. According to Circle and data obtained from Coinmarketcap, the supply of USDC decreased by $1.4 billion in just seven days as Circle&#8217;s rate of token burning outnumbered the rate of new token creations. This led to a market cap drop from $27.4 billion to $26.9 billion in a 7-day timeframe. This comes as the overall supply of USDC has been on a steep decline since the beginning of the year, plummeting from $45 billion to its present level of $26 billion. The worst drop in USDC’s market cap this year came during the height of Silicon Valley Bank&#8217;s shutdown.  USDC market cap plunges &#124; Source: Glassnode According to Nansen, Circle burned $1.6 billion in USDC in a single day. During this period, Circle’s market cap fell by more than $10 billion. This came as investors rushed to redeem USDC due to Circle having cash reserves in the failed bank. What Does This Mean For USDC? The rush to redeem USDC over the course of the past year has prompted doubts about the reserves underpinning the stablecoin. But the stablecoin market appears to be doing just fine in terms of maintaining its peg to the US dollar. Circle also maintains that the USDC cryptocurrency is backed 1:1 by cash and other monetary equivalents.  USDC market cap sitting at $27.25 billion &#124; Source: Market Cap USDC on Tradingview.com In March of this year, Circle switched to short-term maturity bonds. This means that the USDC reserve is now held 80% in short-dated US treasuries and 20% in cash deposits within the US banking system. Given this, there are worries among investors as redemptions at this scale could strain the reserves if they’re invested in less liquid assets. This would explain the high volume of redemptions over this time. Related Reading: XRP Crosses 1 Million Trades Per Minute Following Court Ruling The cryptocurrency market is known for its volatility, but stablecoins have become one of the backbones of the industry due to their ability to offer more stability. Overall, most of the stablecoin market remains split between USDT and USDC, making up more than 83% of the total stablecoin market cap.  For now, USDT has the higher momentum. While USDC’s market cap has slipped throughout the year, data shows USDT has added over $15 billion to its market cap. Featured image from Cryptonomist, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As one of the biggest stablecoins, USDC is one of the major players in the crypto industry. However, the stablecoins have seen better days, as the stablecoin has seen its market cap drop drastically over the past few months. </p>

<p>The second-largest stablecoin has seen its market cap drop by over $1.4 billion in just the last few days thanks to a surge in redemptions. </p>
<h2>$1.4 Billion Redeemed In One Week</h2>
<p>The stablecoin market was rocked this week by a massive redemption of USDC. According to Circle and data obtained from Coinmarketcap, the supply of USDC decreased by $1.4 billion in just seven days as Circle&#8217;s rate of token burning outnumbered the rate of new token creations. This led to a market cap drop from $27.4 billion to $26.9 billion in a 7-day timeframe.</p>
<p>This comes as the overall supply of USDC has been on a steep decline since the beginning of the year, plummeting from $45 billion to its present level of $26 billion. The worst drop in USDC’s market cap this year came during the height of Silicon Valley Bank&#8217;s shutdown. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-543007 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/USDC-460x259.png" alt="USDC" width="460" height="259" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/USDC-460x259.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/USDC.png 512w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>

<p>According to Nansen, Circle burned $1.6 billion in USDC in a single day. During this period, Circle’s market cap fell by more than $10 billion. This came as investors rushed to redeem USDC due to Circle having cash reserves in the failed bank.</p>
<h2>What Does This Mean For USDC?</h2>
<p>The rush to redeem USDC over the course of the past year has prompted doubts about the reserves underpinning the stablecoin. But the stablecoin market appears to be doing just fine in terms of maintaining its peg to the US dollar. Circle also maintains that the USDC cryptocurrency is backed 1:1 by cash and other monetary equivalents. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/pDurkiSi/" alt="Total USDC market cap chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>

<p>In March of this year, Circle switched to short-term maturity bonds. This means that the USDC reserve is now held 80% in short-dated US treasuries and 20% in cash deposits within the US banking system. Given this, there are worries among investors as redemptions at this scale could strain the reserves if they’re invested in less liquid assets. This would explain the high volume of redemptions over this time.</p>

<p>The cryptocurrency market is known for its volatility, but stablecoins have become one of the backbones of the industry due to their ability to offer more stability. Overall, most of the stablecoin market remains split between USDT and USDC, making up more than 83% of the total stablecoin market cap. </p>
<p>For now, USDT has the higher momentum. While USDC’s market cap has slipped throughout the year, data shows USDT has added over $15 billion to its market cap.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/USDC-460x242.jpeg" width="460" height="242" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bearish Signal: BNB Open Interest Skyrockets To New Highs</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/bnb/bnb-open-interest-new-highs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 23:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnbusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=542965</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Binance has been the subject of intense regulatory scrutiny over the last few months and BNB has suffered as a result. Even now, as it seems the crypto exchange is beginning to find its footing once more amid regulatory wolves circling, its native token is still under immense selling pressure. This is evidenced by the BNB open interest, which has now skyrocketed to new all-time highs. BNB Open Interest Reaches New All-Time High In an interesting turn of events, BNB shorts are ramping up even at a time when the crypto market seems to be on a recovery trend. According to a Twitter post by analyst Dylan LeClair, this has caused the open interest in the digital asset to rise exponentially. Related Reading: Crypto Liquidations Cross $300 Million Amid Massive Market Recovery The chart shared by LeClair shows that BNB&#8217;s open interest is now sitting at $400 million. This is over four times higher than the previous all-time high for the digital asset which was $50 million back in 2020. And unlike then, the surge in open interest right now is more bearish than it is bullish. Hmmm, some interesting flow in $BNB futures: &#8211; Perpetual futures open interest is seeing new highs as funding rates have gone deeply negative (-200% APR for next funding period) (Chart #1) &#8211; looks as if someone is getting ahead of some bad news flow. &#8211; The last time BNB… pic.twitter.com/1B27OkjvPx — Dylan LeClair 🟠 (@DylanLeClair_) July 17, 2023 This current increase has seen funding rates move above negative 200% and yet traders continue to short the altcoin. The fact that traders are choosing this route despite the high cost to do so points to the expectations of a massive crash coming for the digital asset. As LeClair points out, this could mean that the United States Department of Justice (DoJ) is finally leveling charges against the crypto exchange. “And people in the know are positioning accordingly.” Will The Altcoin Survive a DoJ Lawsuit? As already demonstrated by the Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) lawsuit against the Binance crypto exchange, a lawsuit from regulators would have an adverse impact on the price of BNB. When the SEC sued the exchange in early June, the price of BNB plummeted by over 20% over a few days period.  BNB price continues to hold above $240 &#124; Source: BNBUSD on TradingView.com Given such a response, a lawsuit from the DoJ would be even worse because of its implications. And if this were to happen this week, then another 20% decline from here would see the digital asset lose its footing above $200. Related Reading: Polygon Upgrade Proposal Pushes Price Over 5%, Is It Too Late To Buy? For right now, the price of BNB is still holding up nicely above $240. One reason for this could be the Arkham sale being carried out on the Binance launchpad. As this sale requires BNB for subscriptions to participate, it has provided temporary buy pressure for investors to participate. However, once the sale ends on July 18, this temporary plug would be eliminated and the cryptocurrency will likely fall back to the $230 territory. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from Currency.com, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Crypto exchange Binance has been the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/fud-or-real-binance-selling-bitcoin-to-prop-up-bnb/">subject</a> of intense regulatory scrutiny over the last few months and BNB has suffered as a result. Even now, as it seems the crypto exchange is beginning to find its footing once more amid regulatory wolves circling, its native token is still under immense selling pressure. This is evidenced by the BNB open interest, which has now skyrocketed to new all-time highs.</p>
<h2 class="p2">BNB Open Interest Reaches New All-Time High</h2>
<p class="p2">In an interesting turn of events, BNB shorts are ramping up even at a time when the crypto market seems to be on a recovery trend. According to a Twitter <a href="https://twitter.com/DylanLeClair_/status/1680749844170784769?s=20" rel="nofollow">post</a> by analyst Dylan LeClair, this has caused the open interest in the digital asset to rise exponentially.</p>

<p class="p2">The chart shared by LeClair shows that BNB&#8217;s open interest is now sitting at $400 million. This is over four times higher than the previous all-time high for the digital asset which was $50 million back in 2020. And unlike then, the surge in open interest right now is more bearish than it is bullish.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Hmmm, some interesting flow in <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BNB&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$BNB</a> futures:</p>
<p>&#8211; Perpetual futures open interest is seeing new highs as funding rates have gone deeply negative (-200% APR for next funding period) (Chart #1) &#8211; looks as if someone is getting ahead of some bad news flow.</p>
<p>&#8211; The last time BNB… <a href="https://t.co/1B27OkjvPx" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/1B27OkjvPx</a></p>
<p>— Dylan LeClair <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f7e0.png" alt="🟠" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@DylanLeClair_) <a href="https://twitter.com/DylanLeClair_/status/1680749844170784769?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p class="p2">This current increase has seen funding rates move above negative 200% and yet traders continue to short the altcoin. The fact that traders are choosing this route despite the high cost to do so points to the expectations of a massive crash coming for the digital asset.</p>
<p class="p2">As LeClair points out, this could mean that the United States Department of Justice (DoJ) is finally leveling charges against the crypto exchange. “And people in the know are positioning accordingly.”</p>
<h2 class="p2">Will The Altcoin Survive a DoJ Lawsuit?</h2>
<p class="p2">As already <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/bnb/bnb-market-cap-down-by-25-in-june-amidst-binance-regulatory-pressure/">demonstrated</a> by the Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) lawsuit against the Binance crypto exchange, a lawsuit from regulators would have an adverse impact on the price of BNB. When the SEC sued the exchange in early June, the price of BNB plummeted by over 20% over a few days period.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/iwSP16O4/" alt="Binance Coin (BNB) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>

<p class="p2">Given such a response, a lawsuit from the DoJ would be even worse because of its implications. And if this were to happen this week, then another 20% decline from here would see the digital asset lose its footing above $200.</p>

<p class="p2">For right now, the price of BNB is still holding up nicely above $240. One reason for this could be the Arkham sale being carried out on the Binance launchpad. As this sale requires BNB for subscriptions to participate, it has provided temporary buy pressure for investors to participate. However, once the sale ends on July 18, this temporary plug would be eliminated and the cryptocurrency will likely fall back to the $230 territory.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BNB-1-460x268.jpeg" width="460" height="268" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Bitcoin Continuation Pattern Points To 3-6 Months Of Uptrend Ahead</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/this-bitcoin-continuation-pattern-points-to-3-6-months-of-uptrend-ahead/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 22:19:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543029</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is pulling back after a strong finish in the crypto market last week. However, this past Sunday night’s weekend close was also the close of the 4-week BTCUSD chart, which has potentially confirmed a high timeframe continuation pattern. If the continuation pattern is indeed valid, it could point to 3-6 months of an extended uptrend, making 2023 an extremely bullish year in the end. Here is everything you need to know about the bullish continuation pattern and what it could mean for the crypto market. Bullish Candlestick Continuation Pattern To Light Up Second Half Of 2023 2023 has been an interesting year in the cryptocurrency market. Bitcoin has been mostly bullish, but nothing compared to what we’ve witnessed in the past — as recently as 2020. Meanwhile, altcoins have been long suffering an onslaught from the US SEC. This has kept Bitcoin further at bay against the US Dollar, while eating up altcoin capital on the BTC pair. Despite an important week for the industry and BTCUSD setting a new high for the year, Bitcoin lost some momentum and is now trading below $30,000 per coin. However, before the correction happened, the 4-week BTCUSD candle also closed on Sunday night. Related Reading: Perfect Storm: Why Bitcoin &#38; Crypto Are Poised For A Dramatic Recovery The 4-week timeframe is slightly more sensitive than the monthly at between 2 to 3 days less, sometimes offering unique signals from the 1-month. Sunday night’s close forever marked the chart with the last candle necessary for a completed Rising Three Method pattern. The Rising Three Method is a bullish Japanese candlesticks continuation pattern. It consists of a large white candle, followed by three small-bodied candles in a row. After the period of consolidation, a large white candle closes above the trio of black candles, engulfing them all. The Rising Three Method pattern &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com Bitcoin Buyers Make A Statement: Rising Three Method Pattern Completes The pattern shows that after a pause, buyers resume control. By making this statement, bulls could gain control of Bitcoin over the next 3 to 6 months. The reason for the timing, is due to the length of each candle’s session. After a Japanese candlestick pattern confirms, its expected results should appear within the next 3-5 candlesticks. 3-5 sessions of 4 weeks total, equals roughly 12 to 20 weeks, or around 3-5 months. That timing would take any potential bull rally through the end of the year. For further validation of the fact upside should appear within 3-5 candles after a confirmed signal, we can see that a morning star pattern completed during the first candlestick close of the year. The second candle of the year was a doji, then this bullish continuation pattern formed. All of this combined tells a possible story of a continued bull market for the rest of the calendar year. Related Reading: The One Ingredient Missing From A Full-Bore Bitcoin Bull Run The Japanese candlestick continuation pattern also comes with plenty of confluence through a confirmed bullish crossover of the LMACD. The technical indicator suggests a momentum shift supportive of more upside in Bitcoin. Will this continuation pattern result in a strong bull market breakout? This chart originally appeared in issue #12 of CoinChartist (VIP) alongside a dozen exclusive XRP, Bitcoin, and other charts. Subscribe for free. Tony is the author of the CoinChartist (VIP) newsletter. Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter. Or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price is pulling back after a strong finish in the crypto market last week. However, this past Sunday night’s weekend close was also the close of the 4-week BTCUSD chart, which has potentially confirmed a high timeframe continuation pattern.</p>
<p>If the continuation pattern is indeed valid, it could point to 3-6 months of an extended uptrend, making 2023 an extremely bullish year in the end. Here is everything you need to know about the bullish continuation pattern and what it could mean for the crypto market.</p>
<h2>Bullish Candlestick Continuation Pattern To Light Up Second Half Of 2023</h2>
<p>2023 has been an interesting year in the cryptocurrency market. Bitcoin has been mostly bullish, but nothing compared to what we’ve witnessed in the past — as recently as 2020. Meanwhile, altcoins have been long suffering an onslaught from the US SEC. This has kept Bitcoin further at bay against the US Dollar, while eating up altcoin capital on the BTC pair.</p>
<p>Despite an important week for the industry and BTCUSD setting a new high for the year, Bitcoin lost some momentum and is now trading below $30,000 per coin. However, before the correction happened, the 4-week BTCUSD candle also closed on Sunday night.</p>

<p>The 4-week timeframe is slightly more sensitive than the monthly at between 2 to 3 days less, sometimes offering unique signals from the 1-month. Sunday night’s close forever marked the chart with the last candle necessary for a completed <a href="https://coinchartist.io/rising-three-methods/education/japanese-candlesticks/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Rising Three Method</a> pattern.</p>
<p>The Rising Three Method is a bullish Japanese candlesticks continuation pattern. It consists of a large white candle, followed by three small-bodied candles in a row. After the period of consolidation, a large white candle closes above the trio of black candles, engulfing them all.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-543031 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1489EC1D-BBB8-450B-8189-3D6E41ECBF54-860x535.png" alt="Bitcoin Rising Three Method" width="860" height="535" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1489EC1D-BBB8-450B-8189-3D6E41ECBF54-860x535.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1489EC1D-BBB8-450B-8189-3D6E41ECBF54-460x286.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1489EC1D-BBB8-450B-8189-3D6E41ECBF54-768x478.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1489EC1D-BBB8-450B-8189-3D6E41ECBF54-1536x955.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1489EC1D-BBB8-450B-8189-3D6E41ECBF54-2048x1274.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1489EC1D-BBB8-450B-8189-3D6E41ECBF54-750x466.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1489EC1D-BBB8-450B-8189-3D6E41ECBF54-1140x709.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<h2>Bitcoin Buyers Make A Statement: Rising Three Method Pattern Completes</h2>
<p>The pattern shows that after a pause, buyers resume control. By making this statement, bulls could gain control of Bitcoin over the next 3 to 6 months. The reason for the timing, is due to the length of each candle’s session. After a Japanese candlestick pattern confirms, its expected results should appear within the next 3-5 candlesticks. 3-5 sessions of 4 weeks total, equals roughly 12 to 20 weeks, or around 3-5 months.</p>
<p>That timing would take any potential bull rally through the end of the year. For further validation of the fact upside should appear within 3-5 candles after a confirmed signal, we can see that a morning star pattern completed during the first candlestick close of the year. The second candle of the year was a doji, then this bullish continuation pattern formed. All of this combined tells a possible story of a continued bull market for the rest of the calendar year.</p>

<p>The Japanese candlestick continuation pattern also comes with plenty of confluence through a confirmed bullish crossover of the LMACD. The technical indicator suggests a momentum shift supportive of more upside in Bitcoin.</p>
<p>Will this continuation pattern result in a strong bull market breakout?</p>
<p>This chart originally appeared in <a href="https://coinchartist.substack.com/p/issue-12-patience-for-the-grand-finale" rel="nofollow">issue #12 of CoinChartist (VIP)</a> alongside a dozen exclusive XRP, Bitcoin, and other charts. Subscribe for <a href="https://coinchartist.substack.com/p/issue-12-patience-for-the-grand-finale" rel="nofollow">free</a>.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/C9D0C50F-7BB5-4547-9DBB-0ECAE62360FF-460x330.jpeg" width="460" height="330" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
