<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 03:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Key Indicators Suggest A Strengthening Case For Rally To $32K</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-rally-to-32k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 03:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540422</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is still struggling to clear the $31,000 resistance. BTC is showing strength and might soon rally toward the $32,000 resistance. Bitcoin is trading in a range below the $31,000 resistance zone. The price is trading above $30,400 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There was a break above a key declining channel with resistance near $30,210 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $30,750 resistance zone. Bitcoin Price Aims Higher Bitcoin price corrected lower below the $30,500 support zone. BTC even spiked below the $30,000 level but downsides were limited. A low is formed near $29,834 and the price is again rising. There was a move above the $30,000 and $30,200 resistance levels. The price climbed above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $31,008 swing high to the $29,834 low. Besides, there was a break above a key declining channel with resistance near $30,210 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Bitcoin price is now trading above $30,400 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. It is also trading above the $30,550 pivot level. Immediate resistance is near the $30,750 level. It is close to the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $31,008 swing high to the $29,834 low. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The first major resistance is near the $31,000 level, above which the price gain bullish momentum. The next major resistance is near the $31,450 level. An upside break above the $31,450 resistance might send BTC toward $32,000. Any more gains could open the doors for a move toward the $32,500 resistance zone. Another Dip in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $30,750 resistance, it could start another decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $30,420 level and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. The next major support is near the $30,000 level, below which there could be a drop toward the $29,550 support. Any more losses might send the price toward the $29,000 zone in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $30,420, followed by $30,000. Major Resistance Levels – $30,750, $31,000, and $31,450.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is still struggling to clear the $31,000 resistance. BTC is showing strength and might soon rally toward the $32,000 resistance.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is trading in a range below the $31,000 resistance zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $30,400 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There was a break above a key declining channel with resistance near $30,210 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $30,750 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Aims Higher</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price corrected lower below the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-31k-resistance/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$30,500 support zone</a>. BTC even spiked below the $30,000 level but downsides were limited. A low is formed near $29,834 and the price is again rising.</p>
<p>There was a move above the $30,000 and $30,200 resistance levels. The price climbed above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $31,008 swing high to the $29,834 low. Besides, there was a break above a key declining channel with resistance near $30,210 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is now trading above $30,400 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-consolidates-below-31k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>. It is also trading above the $30,550 pivot level. Immediate resistance is near the $30,750 level. It is close to the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $31,008 swing high to the $29,834 low.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-540423" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-21.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-21.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-21-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-21-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-21-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-21-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-21-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-21-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $31,000 level, above which the price gain bullish momentum. The next major resistance is near the $31,450 level. An upside break above the $31,450 resistance might send BTC toward $32,000. Any more gains could open the doors for a move toward the $32,500 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Another Dip in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $30,750 resistance, it could start another decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $30,420 level and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $30,000 level, below which there could be a drop toward the $29,550 support. Any more losses might send the price toward the $29,000 zone in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $30,420, followed by $30,000.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $30,750, $31,000, and $31,450.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/shutterstock_350833328-460x325.jpg" width="460" height="325" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum/Bitcoin Futures Ratio Launch Could Threaten ETH Price? Expert Forecasts</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-bitcoin-futures-ratio-launch-could-threaten-eth-price-expert-forecasts/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 02:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540407</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The two largest cryptocurrencies by market capitalization, Ethereum and Bitcoin, slowed down on their rally. Following a surge above critical resistance, the cryptocurrencies could retrace and return to critical support levels. Related Reading: Cardano Shows Signs of Recovery: When Will it Reach $0.30? As of this writing, Ethereum (ETH) trades at $1,840 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. Over the past week, ETH has recorded a 2% loss except for Bitcoin (BTC) and Solana (SOL), the crypto top 10 by market cap trades in the red. Trouble Ahead For Ethereum? Earlier today, the Chicago Mercantile Exchange (CME) announced the launch of a new product. The platform will roll out an Ethereum (ETH/USD) to Bitcoin (BTC/USD) ratio futures contract. The financial product will follow the price of these cryptocurrencies and their correlation. In that way, traders can gain exposure to both cryptocurrencies by holding a single futures contract. According to an official announcement, The product aims to create more opportunities for traders in the nascent industry. However, in the short term, the CME launch hints at a potential downside for the two largest assets in the crypto market. CME Product Could Trigger This Effect In the past, whenever the CME rolled out a Bitcoin or Ethereum-based contract, the price of either asset trended to the downside. A pseudonym analyst forecasted issues for ETH and BTC, probably driven by a “buy the rumor, sell the news” effect. Via Twitter, the analyst stated, reacting to the news: If this has an effect similar to the $BTC &#38; $ETH futures back in the day then the release of this instrument could form a pivot for the ETH/BTC pair. Maybe more down into the release and then a reversal around the end of July? Let&#8217;s see. In response to the forecast, another analyst stated that a “buy the rumor, sell the news effect” will cause ETH’s price to rally into the event. Therefore, ETH could profit as the CME prepares to roll out their new contracts and anticipation around the spot Bitcoin Exchange Traded Funds (ETFs) applications continues. Related Reading: Bitcoin Bulls Battle Against Miners’ $128 Million Move: Is The Bull Run In Danger? The analyst stated: Wouldn&#8217;t make more sense a buy the rumor, sell the news event? So we pump before end of July Everything is exhausted right now. If BTC pumps through resistance, maybe ETH could catch up. Cover image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>The two largest cryptocurrencies by market capitalization, Ethereum and Bitcoin, slowed down on their rally. Following a surge above critical resistance, the cryptocurrencies could retrace and return to critical support levels. </strong></p>

<p>As of this writing, Ethereum (ETH) trades at $1,840 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. Over the past week, ETH has recorded a 2% loss except for Bitcoin (BTC) and Solana (SOL), the crypto top 10 by market cap trades in the red.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-540410 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-860x410.png" alt="Ethereum ETH ETHUSDT" width="860" height="410" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-860x410.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-460x219.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-768x366.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-1536x732.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-750x357.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-1140x543.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT.png 1759w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<h2>Trouble Ahead For Ethereum?</h2>
<p>Earlier today, the Chicago Mercantile Exchange (CME) <a href="https://seekingalpha.com/pr/19384891-cme-group-to-launch-ether-bitcoin-ratio-futures-on-july-31" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced</a> the launch of a new product. The platform will roll out an Ethereum (ETH/USD) to Bitcoin (BTC/USD) ratio futures contract.</p>
<p>The financial product will follow the price of these cryptocurrencies and their correlation. In that way, traders can gain exposure to both cryptocurrencies by holding a single futures contract.</p>
<p>According to an official announcement, The product aims to create more opportunities for traders in the nascent industry. However, in the short term, the CME launch hints at a potential downside for the two largest assets in the crypto market.</p>
CME Product Could Trigger This Effect
<p>In the past, whenever the CME rolled out a Bitcoin or Ethereum-based contract, the price of either asset trended to the downside. A pseudonym analyst forecasted issues for ETH and BTC, probably driven by a “buy the rumor, sell the news” effect.</p>
<p>Via Twitter, the analyst <a href="https://twitter.com/DaanCrypto/status/1674463455720484884" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">stated</a>, reacting to the news:</p>
<blockquote><p>If this has an effect similar to the $BTC &amp; $ETH futures back in the day then the release of this instrument could form a pivot for the ETH/BTC pair. Maybe more down into the release and then a reversal around the end of July? Let&#8217;s see.</p></blockquote>
<p>In response to the forecast, another analyst stated that a “buy the rumor, sell the news effect” will cause ETH’s price to rally into the event. Therefore, ETH could profit as the CME prepares to roll out their new contracts and anticipation around the spot Bitcoin Exchange Traded Funds (ETFs) applications continues.</p>

<p>The analyst <a href="https://twitter.com/silver_bits/status/1674464475397738496" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">stated</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>Wouldn&#8217;t make more sense a buy the rumor, sell the news event? So we pump before end of July Everything is exhausted right now. If BTC pumps through resistance, maybe ETH could catch up.</p></blockquote>
<p>Cover image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin Bull Case Grows Stronger As Hashrate Touches New All Time-High</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/litecoin-bull-case-grows-stronger-as-hashrate-touches-new-all-time-high/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin hashrate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc/usd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540322</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Litecoin (LTC) has been one of the most bullish coins for the year 2023 with anticipation around its forthcoming halving event. This has propelled the digital asset toward price increases higher than the market average. And now, once again, the bull case for the digital asset is even stronger as its hashrate has risen rapidly to a new peak. Litecoin Hashrate Touches New All-Time High As the halving event draws closer, more attention is being paid to the Litecoin network. This has led to an increase in the hashrate of the network as more miners are joining the network. Most of the month of June has seen large spikes in hashrate following the rise in the mining difficulty. Related Reading: The Blessing Of July: Can Bitcoin Climb To $36,000 In The Coming Month? The rise in mining difficulty means that it is harder to find a block and as such, miners have to bring more machines online to increase their chances, leading to a spike in the hashrate. And as more miners are brought online, the Litecoin hashrate has touched its highest level yet. According to data from CoinWarz, the Litecoin hashrate reached 958.36 terahashes per second (TH/s), on Wednesday, June 28, 2023. This is a new all-time high for the network whose previous all-time high had data just above 800 TH/s. Litecoin hashrate reaches new all-time high &#124; Source: CoinWarz The hashrate has seen a decline and is now sitting at 735.71 TH/s for the global hashrate. However, the spike points toward a more positive development for its network and its native token LTC. LTC Could Surge Upon Halving Event The Litecoin halving which will cut block rewards down from 12.5 LTC per mined block to 6.25 LTC per mined block is now less than two months away. As halving events have been known to impose a level of scarcity on a digital asset, a surge in the price of LTC is expected as the event draws closer. LTC price sitting above $85 support &#124; Source: LTCUSD on TradingView.com This scarcity would see supply reduce and if demand continues to rise, then LTC is poised to break $100 by the time the halving is done. If this happens, it could also trigger a reasonable rally in the crypto market as positive sentiment and profits from LTC spills over into the rest of the crypto market. Related Reading: Bitcoin Investor Sentiment Suggests BTC Rally Is Far From Over Litecoin’s rise in hashrate already shows that miners are preparing for the halving, indicating renewed fate in the digital asset. As the next few weeks leading up to the event roll by, investors can expect LTC to trade in the green despite market bearishness. At the time of writing, LTC is trading at a price of $85.40 per coin, down 3.08% in the past week. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Litecoin (LTC) has been one of the most bullish coins for the year 2023 with anticipation around its forthcoming halving event. This has propelled the digital asset toward price increases higher than the market average. And now, once again, the bull case for the digital asset is even stronger as its hashrate has risen rapidly to a new peak.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Litecoin Hashrate Touches New All-Time High</h2>
<p class="p2">As the halving event draws closer, more attention is being paid to the Litecoin network. This has led to an increase in the hashrate of the network as more miners are joining the network. Most of the month of June has seen large spikes in hashrate following the rise in the mining difficulty.</p>

<p class="p2">The rise in mining difficulty means that it is harder to find a block and as such, miners have to bring more machines online to increase their chances, leading to a spike in the hashrate. And as more miners are brought online, the Litecoin hashrate has touched its highest level yet.</p>
<p class="p2">According to data from CoinWarz, the Litecoin hashrate reached 958.36 terahashes per second (TH/s), on Wednesday, June 28, 2023. This is a new all-time high for the network whose previous all-time high had data just above 800 TH/s.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-540324 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-2023-06-29-at-12.30.51-460x195.png" alt="Litecoin hashrate" width="460" height="195" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-2023-06-29-at-12.30.51-460x195.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-2023-06-29-at-12.30.51-860x364.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-2023-06-29-at-12.30.51-768x325.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-2023-06-29-at-12.30.51-1536x651.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-2023-06-29-at-12.30.51-2048x867.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-2023-06-29-at-12.30.51-750x318.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-2023-06-29-at-12.30.51-1140x483.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>

<p class="p2">The hashrate has seen a decline and is now sitting at 735.71 TH/s for the global hashrate. However, the spike points toward a more positive development for its network and its native token LTC.</p>
<h2 class="p2">LTC Could Surge Upon Halving Event</h2>
<p class="p2">The Litecoin <a href="https://www.litecoinhalving.com/" rel="nofollow">halving</a> which will cut block rewards down from 12.5 LTC per mined block to 6.25 LTC per mined block is now less than two months away. As halving events have been known to impose a level of scarcity on a digital asset, a surge in the price of LTC is expected as the event draws closer.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/iV2mzetC/" alt="Litecoin price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1724"/></p>

<p class="p2">This scarcity would see supply reduce and if demand continues to rise, then LTC is poised to break $100 by the time the halving is done. If this happens, it could also trigger a reasonable rally in the crypto market as positive sentiment and profits from LTC spills over into the rest of the crypto market.</p>

<p class="p2">Litecoin’s rise in hashrate already shows that miners are preparing for the halving, indicating renewed fate in the digital asset. As the next few weeks leading up to the event roll by, investors can expect LTC to trade in the green despite market bearishness.</p>
<p class="p2">At the time of writing, LTC is trading at a price of $85.40 per coin, down 3.08% in the past week.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/michael-fortsch-I1PywtFZY6s-unsplash-460x285.jpg" width="460" height="285" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dawn For Bitcoin: $5 Billion In Options Expire And Could Push Price Towards $31,000</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/dawn-for-bitcoin-5-billion-in-options-expire-and-could-push-price-towards-31000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 22:11:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540412</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Still recording some green on small timeframes, the price of Bitcoin has remained above $30,400. Despite the recent selling pressure across the sector, the support around this level held, providing bulls a chance to fight back. Related Reading: Bitcoin Bulls Battle Against Miners’ $128 Million Move: Is The Bull Run In Danger? As of this writing, Bitcoin trades at $30,458 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. The previous week, the number one crypto by market cap recorded similar price action while other cryptocurrencies experienced losses. Bitcoin About To Explode? Data from crypto options platform Deribit, shared by analyst Tom Dunleavy, shows that over $7 billion in these contracts will expire today, Friday 29th. In other words, today, option holders can exercise their right or obligation to buy/sell BTC and other assets at a specific price, depending on their contract. Over $5 billion of the options contracts are based on Bitcoin, while the rest are based on Ethereum, as seen in the chart below. However, option holders could choose to “roll over” their contracts to a later date. As a result, according to Dunleavy, spot prices could see a spike in buying pressure as major option players hedge their positions. This increased buying pressure could see BTC soaring above the $31,000 mark. Via Twitter, the analyst stated: Big options expiration date for both ETH and BTC tomorrow ETH: ~$2B notional BTC: ~$5B notional If these are rolled into more calls we should see spot buying from dealers to hedge their books; puts opposite story. Either way expect some vol (volatility). As Dunleavy claims, the crypto market is poised for volatility, whichever direction. The chart above shows the Max Pain price for BTC options, which is $26,500. Max Pain is the price Bitcoin must trade to deny most options traders from booking profits. In that sense, the BTC price will likely turn to the downside with a spike in volatility. Beyond $31,000, What’s Next For BTC? Analysis and crypto education firm Blofin recently posted a report on BTC&#8217;s short- and long-term risks and scenarios. The firm claims the recent rally was driven by a “hunger for positive news” and a “rebalancing” of internal liquidity. In other words, crypto investors got bullish and took money from altcoins into BTC. However, there is still a liquidity issue within the sector that could limit any rally, but there is a silver lining in this scenario. Related Reading: Cardano Shows Signs of Recovery: When Will it Reach $0.30? Blofin stated: The decline in the price of BTC will be more limited, with a relatively small probability of falling below $28k, while the upward space is relatively large, and there is even hope for a rebound to $35k and above. Cover image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Still recording some green on small timeframes, the price of Bitcoin has remained above $30,400. Despite the recent selling pressure across the sector, the support around this level held, providing bulls a chance to fight back. </strong></p>

<p>As of this writing, Bitcoin trades at $30,458 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. The previous week, the number one crypto by market cap recorded similar price action while other cryptocurrencies experienced losses.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-540416 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-2-860x410.png" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT" width="860" height="410" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-2-860x410.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-2-460x219.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-2-768x366.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-2-1536x732.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-2-750x358.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-2-1140x543.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-2.png 1758w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<h2>Bitcoin About To Explode?</h2>
<p>Data from crypto options platform Deribit, shared by analyst Tom Dunleavy, shows that over $7 billion in these contracts will expire today, Friday 29th. In other words, today, option holders can exercise their right or obligation to buy/sell BTC and other assets at a specific price, depending on their contract.</p>
<p>Over $5 billion of the options contracts are based on Bitcoin, while the rest are based on Ethereum, as seen in the chart below. However, option holders could choose to “roll over” their contracts to a later date.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-540415 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-1-860x430.jpg" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT Chart 2" width="860" height="430" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-1-860x430.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-1-460x230.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-1-768x384.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-1-360x180.jpg 360w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-1-750x375.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-1-1140x570.jpg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-1.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>As a result, according to Dunleavy, spot prices could see a spike in buying pressure as major option players hedge their positions. This increased buying pressure could see BTC soaring above the $31,000 mark.</p>
<p>Via Twitter, the analyst <a href="https://twitter.com/dunleavy89/status/1674386107893522433" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">stated</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>Big options expiration date for both ETH and BTC tomorrow ETH: ~$2B notional BTC: ~$5B notional If these are rolled into more calls we should see spot buying from dealers to hedge their books; puts opposite story. Either way expect some vol (volatility).</p></blockquote>
<p>As Dunleavy claims, the crypto market is poised for volatility, whichever direction. The chart above shows the Max Pain price for BTC options, which is $26,500.</p>
<p>Max Pain is the price Bitcoin must trade to deny most options traders from booking profits. In that sense, the BTC price will likely turn to the downside with a spike in volatility.</p>
Beyond $31,000, What’s Next For BTC?
<p>Analysis and crypto education firm Blofin recently <a href="https://insights.deribit.com/industry/flow-insights-meteor/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">posted</a> a report on BTC&#8217;s short- and long-term risks and scenarios. The firm claims the recent rally was driven by a “hunger for positive news” and a “rebalancing” of internal liquidity.</p>
<p>In other words, crypto investors got bullish and took money from altcoins into BTC. However, there is still a liquidity issue within the sector that could limit any rally, but there is a silver lining in this scenario.</p>

<p>Blofin stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>The decline in the price of BTC will be more limited, with a relatively small probability of falling below $28k, while the upward space is relatively large, and there is even hope for a rebound to $35k and above.</p></blockquote>
<p>Cover image from Unsplash, chart from Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1-460x315.jpg" width="460" height="315" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano Shows Signs of Recovery: When Will it Reach $0.30?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-shows-signs-of-recovery-when-will-it-reach-0-30/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 20:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[adausd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ta]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540391</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) has shown signs of recovery in recent trading sessions, although its price continues to linger near a significant resistance level. In the past 24 hours, ADA witnessed a modest 2% increase, but weekly gains have been erased, resulting in a 7% depreciation on the weekly chart. Related Reading: Slovakian Lawmakers Pass Amendment Lowering Cryptocurrency Taxation The technical outlook has yet to present bullish signals, with both demand and accumulation remaining relatively low. Bitcoin dominance increased while trading within the $30,000 price range. Major altcoins also experienced minor gains in the past few days. Although Bitcoin displayed a bullish trend, its price fluctuated, and other altcoins followed similar patterns. For the Cardano price to experience upward movement, Bitcoin must exhibit another surge from its current price level. If ADA manages to sustain above the current support line with the support of BTC, the altcoin may soon attempt to break through immediate price resistance. The decrease in ADA&#8217;s market capitalization indicates the continued influence of bearish sentiment in the market. Cardano Price Analysis: One-Day Chart At the time of writing, ADA was observed to be trading at $0.27, a significant resistance point for the altcoin. Previous price action has indicated that the bulls have faced rejection at this level in the past. Additionally, consolidation has been observed around this price mark. If ADA continues its upward movement, it may attempt to trade near or even surpass the $0.30 level. However, in the case of extended consolidation, ADA could experience a dip towards its support line at $0.26. Notably, the $0.26 level has acted as a bullish order block for the coin, indicating a price reversal and subsequent upward movement after reaching this level. This observation suggests the possibility of incoming bullishness for ADA. Technical Analysis Despite an increase in buying strength, the overall demand for ADA has remained low. This is evident from the Relative Strength Index (RSI) failing to move above the half-line, indicating that sellers have maintained a strong presence in the market. However, there is an expectation for a potential resurgence in demand if the price manages to surpass the $0.27 zone. Similarly, the price falling below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line indicates that sellers have been driving the price momentum in the market. ADA has exhibited buy signals that suggest a potential price reversal in the near future. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) has formed green histograms, which are tied to buy signals for the coin. This indicates positive momentum for ADA and suggests a potential upward movement in price. Related Reading: Dogecoin Faces Downward Pressure – Will DOGE Bulls Avert A Further Slide? Additionally, the Bollinger Bands, which provide insights into price volatility and fluctuation, have constricted. This tightening of the bands indicates that the trading range has become tight. Therefore, there is a possibility of a price breakout. Featured image from UnSplash, charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cardano (ADA) has shown signs of recovery in recent trading sessions, although its price continues to linger near a significant resistance level. In the past 24 hours, ADA witnessed a modest 2% increase, but weekly gains have been erased, resulting in a 7% depreciation on the weekly chart.</p>

<p>The technical outlook has yet to present bullish signals, with both demand and accumulation remaining relatively low. Bitcoin dominance increased while trading within the $30,000 price range. Major altcoins also experienced minor gains in the past few days. Although Bitcoin displayed a bullish trend, its price fluctuated, and other altcoins followed similar patterns.</p>
<p>For the Cardano price to experience upward movement, Bitcoin must exhibit another surge from its current price level. If ADA manages to sustain above the current support line with the support of BTC, the altcoin may soon attempt to break through immediate price resistance. The decrease in ADA&#8217;s market capitalization indicates the continued influence of bearish sentiment in the market.</p>
<h2>Cardano Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-540395 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSD_2023-06-29_23-56-28.png" alt="Cardano" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSD_2023-06-29_23-56-28.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSD_2023-06-29_23-56-28-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSD_2023-06-29_23-56-28-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSD_2023-06-29_23-56-28-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSD_2023-06-29_23-56-28-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSD_2023-06-29_23-56-28-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSD_2023-06-29_23-56-28-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>At the time of writing, ADA was observed to be trading at $0.27, a significant resistance point for the altcoin. Previous price action has indicated that the bulls have faced rejection at this level in the past. Additionally, consolidation has been observed around this price mark.</p>
<p>If ADA continues its upward movement, it may attempt to trade near or even surpass the $0.30 level. However, in the case of extended consolidation, ADA could experience a dip towards its support line at $0.26.</p>
<p>Notably, the $0.26 level has acted as a bullish order block for the coin, indicating a price reversal and subsequent upward movement after reaching this level. This observation suggests the possibility of incoming bullishness for ADA.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-540396 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSD_2023-06-29_23-57-20.png" alt="Cardano" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSD_2023-06-29_23-57-20.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSD_2023-06-29_23-57-20-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSD_2023-06-29_23-57-20-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSD_2023-06-29_23-57-20-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSD_2023-06-29_23-57-20-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSD_2023-06-29_23-57-20-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSD_2023-06-29_23-57-20-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>Despite an increase in buying strength, the overall demand for ADA has remained low. This is evident from the Relative Strength Index (RSI) failing to move above the half-line, indicating that sellers have maintained a strong presence in the market.</p>
<p>However, there is an expectation for a potential resurgence in demand if the price manages to surpass the $0.27 zone. Similarly, the price falling below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line indicates that sellers have been driving the price momentum in the market.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-540397 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSD_2023-06-29_23-57-50.png" alt="Cardano" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSD_2023-06-29_23-57-50.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSD_2023-06-29_23-57-50-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSD_2023-06-29_23-57-50-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSD_2023-06-29_23-57-50-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSD_2023-06-29_23-57-50-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSD_2023-06-29_23-57-50-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSD_2023-06-29_23-57-50-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>ADA has exhibited buy signals that suggest a potential price reversal in the near future. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) has formed green histograms, which are tied to buy signals for the coin. This indicates positive momentum for ADA and suggests a potential upward movement in price.</p>

<p>Additionally, the Bollinger Bands, which provide insights into price volatility and fluctuation, have constricted. This tightening of the bands indicates that the trading range has become tight. Therefore, there is a possibility of a price breakout.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/traxer-MnWFs31CPEk-unsplash-2-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Slovakian Lawmakers Pass Amendment Lowering Cryptocurrency Taxation</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/slovakian-pass-lowering-crypto-taxation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 17:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto tax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto tax regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Slovakia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540365</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Lawmakers in Slovakia have approved new legislation, with a resounding 112-2 vote in favor, aimed at reducing taxes associated with the sale of crypto or digital assets. In addition to the aforementioned tax-cutting law, members of the National Council of the Slovak Republic, the country&#8217;s parliament, have further endorsed additional measures that impact cryptocurrency holders. The National Council of the Slovak Republic passed the amendment that will result in a reduction of personal income tax on profits derived from the sale of cryptocurrencies. This tax reduction specifically applies to individuals who have held the cryptocurrencies for a minimum period of one year. The recent vote marked the third reading of the bill in the National Council. According to reports, the Ministry of Finance in Slovakia has projected that the amendment, once implemented, will have a financial impact of approximately 30 million euros per year. Related Reading: Solana Faces Resistance Yet Traders May Find Buying Opportunities Here In a significant development, the Slovakian parliament recently passed another amendment to the constitution. This amendment specifically codifies the right of citizens to utilize cash as a recognized payment method. This action comes in response to discussions surrounding the potential introduction of a digital euro. The government aims to ensure that citizens retain the freedom to choose their preferred form of payment. Citizens will be able to choose cash payment after it has been implemented within the constitution. Drastic Reduction In Crypto Tax Rates Under the new legislation, the tax rate on profits gained from the sale of cryptocurrencies will be reduced to 7%. This marks a significant decrease compared to the current sliding scale tax rates of 19% or 25%. Moreover, the bill includes a provision that exempts payments received in cryptocurrencies up to 2,400 euros ($2,600) from taxation. Furthermore, the bill also addresses the issue of health insurance contributions. It specifically excludes income derived from cryptocurrencies from being subject to a health insurance contribution of 14%. As a member state of the European Union, Slovakia, like other EU countries, has the freedom to establish its own tax regulations and policies concerning cryptocurrencies. Related Reading: Analyst’s Forecast: Bitcoin (BTC) To Hit $310,000 If This Happens This autonomy allows Slovakia to create tax rules. And it can formulate rules that are conducive to promoting the popularity and adoption of cryptocurrencies within its jurisdiction. Slovakia is among the 27 member states that demonstrate a proactive approach to monitoring the advancements within the cryptocurrency industry across the region. EU Takes Initiative In Forming Guidelines The European Union (EU) recently enacted the Markets in Crypto-Assets (MiCA) regulations into law. This landmark set of regulations aims to establish Europe as a prominent hub for digital asset activities. In contrast to the European Union&#8217;s proactive approach, other major markets like the United States have not yet implemented comprehensive guidelines for the cryptocurrency industry. Related Reading: FTX Puts Sale Of $500 Million Stake In AI Firm Anthropic On Hold While the US remains an important player in the crypto space, there is an ongoing discussion of potential regulations. However, United States Republican lawmakers have proposed the Digital Asset Market Structure bill, which is under review. Featured image from UnSplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lawmakers in Slovakia have<a href="https://e.dennikn.sk/minuta/3447018" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> approved</a> new legislation, with a resounding 112-2 vote in favor, aimed at reducing taxes associated with the sale of crypto or digital assets.</p>
<p>In addition to the aforementioned tax-cutting law, members of the National Council of the Slovak Republic, the country&#8217;s parliament, have further endorsed additional measures that impact cryptocurrency holders.</p>
<p>The National Council of the Slovak Republic passed the amendment that will result in a reduction of personal income tax on profits derived from the sale of cryptocurrencies. This tax reduction specifically applies to individuals who have held the cryptocurrencies for a minimum period of one year.</p>
<p>The recent vote marked the third reading of the bill in the National Council. According to reports, the Ministry of Finance in Slovakia has projected that the amendment, once implemented, will have a financial impact of approximately 30 million euros per year.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/solana/solana-faces-resistance-yet-traders-may-find-buying-opportunities-here/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Solana Faces Resistance Yet Traders May Find Buying Opportunities Here</a></p>
<p>In a significant development, the Slovakian parliament recently passed another amendment to the constitution. This amendment specifically codifies the right of citizens to utilize cash as a recognized payment method.</p>
<p>This action comes in response to discussions surrounding the potential introduction of a digital euro. The government aims to ensure that citizens retain the freedom to choose their preferred form of payment. Citizens will be able to choose cash payment after it has been implemented within the constitution.</p>
<h2>Drastic Reduction In Crypto Tax Rates</h2>
<p>Under the new legislation, the tax rate on profits gained from the sale of cryptocurrencies will be reduced to 7%. This marks a significant decrease compared to the current sliding scale tax rates of 19% or 25%.</p>
<p>Moreover, the bill includes a provision that exempts payments received in cryptocurrencies up to 2,400 euros ($2,600) from taxation.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the bill also addresses the issue of health insurance contributions. It specifically excludes income derived from cryptocurrencies from being subject to a health insurance contribution of 14%.</p>
<p>As a member state of the European Union, Slovakia, like other EU countries, has the freedom to establish its own tax regulations and policies concerning cryptocurrencies.</p>

<p>This autonomy allows Slovakia to create tax rules. And it can formulate rules that are conducive to promoting the popularity and adoption of cryptocurrencies within its jurisdiction.</p>
<p>Slovakia is among the 27 member states that demonstrate a proactive approach to monitoring the advancements within the cryptocurrency industry across the region.</p>
<h2>EU Takes Initiative In Forming Guidelines</h2>
<p>The European Union (EU) recently enacted the Markets in Crypto-Assets (MiCA) regulations into law. This landmark set of regulations aims to establish Europe as a prominent hub for digital asset activities.</p>
<p>In contrast to the European Union&#8217;s proactive approach, other major markets like the United States have not yet implemented comprehensive guidelines for the cryptocurrency industry.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/ftx/ftx-puts-sale-of-500-million-stake-in-ai-firm-anthropic-on-hold/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">FTX Puts Sale Of $500 Million Stake In AI Firm Anthropic On Hold</a></p>
<p>While the US remains an important player in the crypto space, there is an ongoing discussion of potential regulations. However, United States Republican lawmakers have proposed the Digital Asset Market Structure bill, which is under review.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-540374 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-29_20-58-17.png" alt="Crypto" width="1817" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-29_20-58-17.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-29_20-58-17-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-29_20-58-17-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-29_20-58-17-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-29_20-58-17-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-29_20-58-17-750x343.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD_2023-06-29_20-58-17-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/jon-tyson-qAQsVsSxp_w-unsplash-345x460.jpg" width="345" height="460" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Bulls Battle Against Miners&#8217; $128 Million Move: Is The Bull Run In Danger?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-bulls-battle-against-miners-128-million-move-is-the-bull-run-in-danger/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 16:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540370</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin&#8217;s (BTC) recent performance has been a source of concern for its investors, as the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency struggles to maintain its upward trajectory. While the currency recently recorded a 12-month high slightly above $31,000, it is now facing potential profit-taking as miners signal a massive $128 Million move. Bitcoin Bulls Brace For Impact According to Yan Allemann, co-founder of Glassnode, the miner&#8217;s transfer could lead to significant sell-off pressure in the market. This could cause friction in the current bull run, which has already seen Bitcoin struggle to hold steady at the crucial $30,000 support line. Adding to the uncertainty is that Bollinger Bands, a technical analysis tool used to measure volatility, remains tight despite the low volatility. This has been shown to lead to abrupt market moves in the past, which could cause further complications for Bitcoin bulls. Related Reading: Altcoin Whales Show Highly Active Day, Volatility Incoming? The support at $30,000 is crucial for the revival of the uptrend, and investors are now anxiously watching to see how the market reacts to the miner&#8217;s move. While Bitcoin has faced similar challenges in the past and managed to overcome them, the current situation is causing some concern among market observers. Furthermore, Bitcoin&#8217;s current price stagnation is reflected in its Average Directional Index (ADX) on the daily chart, which is set to spike downward.  This ADX movement suggests that Bitcoin&#8217;s trend for the next 10 days could be to the downside. This development raises the possibility that Bitcoin might either consolidate for the next week-and-a-half, revisit the $29,600 support line, or even drop further to the $28,300 level if the downside movement persists. Either way, it has been a common price action for Bitcoin for the majority of the year to experience periods of correction or consolidation before taking another uptrend. The current ADX movement and potential downside trend are no exception to this pattern, as seen in the chart above. As Bitcoin corrects or consolidates, the liquidity of late-long positions taken from these levels is likely to be absorbed. This is a natural part of market cycles, and it is not unusual for Bitcoin to experience this type of price action. Once the correction or consolidation phase passes and the late longs liquidity is taken from these levels, Bitcoin may be poised to begin another uptrend. This could potentially result in a 6,000-point uptrend, which has been seen in previous cycles. BTC Faces Further Decline Yan Allemann also pointed out other technical indicators that suggest a short-term reversal in Bitcoin&#8217;s price. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) peaked at 72.92 over the weekend, which is within the limit of overbought territory. The RSI has since remained in the upper and lower levels, which indicates a possible decrease in buying pressure. Furthermore, the double-top pattern and the Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) also suggest that a short-term reversal in Bitcoin&#8217;s price may be imminent. The MACD being overbought, along with the RSI at the top level, adds to this likelihood. Related Reading: Compound (COMP) Surges Nearly 10% In The Past Day, Here’s Why However, there are also positive indicators for Bitcoin&#8217;s price. The funding rates remain positive, reflecting bullish sentiment among investors. Additionally, Bitcoin mining stocks have been moving higher, suggesting the potential catalyst for the next major move in Bitcoin&#8217;s price. As of now, BTC trades at $30,500, slightly up by 0.5% in the last 24 hours but failing to conquer the $31,000 mark.  Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s (BTC) recent performance has been a source of concern for its investors, as the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency struggles to maintain its upward trajectory. While the currency recently recorded a 12-month high slightly above $31,000, it is now facing potential profit-taking as miners signal a massive $128 Million move.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Bulls Brace For Impact</h2>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/Negentropic_/status/1674363526159237122?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to Yan Allemann, co-founder of Glassnode, the miner&#8217;s transfer could lead to significant sell-off pressure in the market. This could cause friction in the current bull run, which has already seen Bitcoin struggle to hold steady at the crucial $30,000 support line.</p>
<p>Adding to the uncertainty is that Bollinger Bands, a technical analysis tool used to measure volatility, remains tight despite the low volatility. This has been shown to lead to abrupt market moves in the past, which could cause further complications for Bitcoin bulls.</p>

<p>The support at $30,000 is crucial for the revival of the uptrend, and investors are now anxiously watching to see how the market reacts to the miner&#8217;s move. While Bitcoin has faced similar challenges in the past and managed to overcome them, the current situation is causing some concern among market observers.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Bitcoin&#8217;s current price stagnation is reflected in its Average Directional Index (ADX) on the daily chart, which is set to spike downward. </p>
<p>This ADX movement suggests that Bitcoin&#8217;s trend for the next 10 days could be to the downside. This development raises the possibility that Bitcoin might either consolidate for the next week-and-a-half, revisit the $29,600 support line, or even drop further to the $28,300 level if the downside movement persists.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/WaCl02FJ/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Either way, it has been a common price action for Bitcoin for the majority of the year to experience periods of correction or consolidation before taking another uptrend. The current ADX movement and potential downside trend are no exception to this pattern, as seen in the chart above.</p>
<p>As Bitcoin corrects or consolidates, the liquidity of late-long positions taken from these levels is likely to be absorbed. This is a natural part of market cycles, and it is not unusual for Bitcoin to experience this type of price action.</p>
<p>Once the correction or consolidation phase passes and the late longs liquidity is taken from these levels, Bitcoin may be poised to begin another uptrend. This could potentially result in a 6,000-point uptrend, which has been seen in previous cycles.</p>
BTC Faces Further Decline
<p>Yan Allemann also <a href="https://twitter.com/Negentropic_/status/1674099292770820096?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">pointed </a>out other technical indicators that suggest a short-term reversal in Bitcoin&#8217;s price. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) peaked at 72.92 over the weekend, which is within the limit of overbought territory. The RSI has since remained in the upper and lower levels, which indicates a possible decrease in buying pressure.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-540371" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_6-860x494.jpg" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="494" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_6-860x494.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_6-460x264.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_6-768x441.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_6-750x430.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_6.jpg 941w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>Furthermore, the double-top pattern and the Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) also suggest that a short-term reversal in Bitcoin&#8217;s price may be imminent. The MACD being overbought, along with the RSI at the top level, adds to this likelihood.</p>

<p>However, there are also positive indicators for Bitcoin&#8217;s price. The funding rates remain positive, reflecting bullish sentiment among investors. Additionally, Bitcoin mining stocks have been moving higher, suggesting the potential catalyst for the next major move in Bitcoin&#8217;s price.</p>
<p>As of now, BTC trades at $30,500, slightly up by 0.5% in the last 24 hours but failing to conquer the $31,000 mark. </p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-186295282-1-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Analyst’s Forecast: Bitcoin (BTC) To Hit $310,000 If This Happens</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/analysts-forecast-bitcoin-btc-to-hit-310000-if-this-happens/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 15:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540342</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The crypto community is currently in a state of constant speculation as renowned analyst Willy Woo sets forth a prediction suggesting Bitcoin could potentially scale up to a price of $310,000 under a specific set of circumstances. Woo&#8217;s hypothesis, which has sparked a flurry of discussions in the crypto community, is hinged on an assumption that notable institutional players might decide to designate a fraction of their assets under management (AUM) to the largest digital currency, Bitcoin. The Theoretical Path To $310,000 Bitcoin Woo breaks down his perspective, detailing that a significant augmentation in Bitcoin&#8217;s market cap, coupled with a corresponding increase in its realized cap, could set the stage for this quantum leap in price. However, he underscores that the timing of these potential institutional inflows would significantly determine the trajectory of Bitcoin&#8217;s price. Related Reading: Crypto Analyst Predicts: Bitcoin (BTC) To Reach $69,000 And Above In 2023 Woo noted: It [BTC potential to $310,000] would really depend on whether they [institutional players] deploy in a bearish or bullish phase of the market but the range would be between $128,000 &#8211; $398,000. Right now it&#8217;s $310,000. According to Woo, if such investment decisions take place during a bearish market phase, Bitcoin may dip to around $128,000. On the flip side, a bullish market condition could propel BTC to $400,000. Woo’s projections, albeit well-reasoned, were met with a fair share of skepticism, particularly concerning the assumption of institutional asset reallocation towards Bitcoin. Reacting to the doubts, Woo emphasized the hypothetical nature of his argument, stressing that the ultimate control of asset allocation rests with the investors and not the institutions. Investor Decisions VS Wealth Manager Discretion Splitting wealth management into two distinct categories &#8211; investor-driven decisions and wealth manager discretion &#8211; Woo explained that any large-scale movement toward Bitcoin would likely necessitate the approval of the individual investors represented by these institutions. Tweeting about his analysis, Woo stated that If these institutions &#8220;allocated 5% of AUM into BTC,&#8221; his calculations project above $300,000 per coin and could vary significantly to below it. However, currently, the estimate stands at $310,000, based on a methodology measuring market cap increase versus realized cap increase. Meanwhile, at the time of writing, Bitcoin currently trades above $30,000 after trading below that price range earlier this month due to its bloodbath from the United States Security and Exchange Commission (SEC) lawsuit on the two largest crypto exchanges, Binance and Coinbase. However, following financial giants such as BlackRock expressed acceptance of the crypto market, Bitcoin has seen significant growth up by more than 20% in the past two weeks. Notably, over the past 14 days, more than $100 billion has been added to the crypto market cap. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price On Shaky Ground: Market Analysts Warn Of Potential Fall To $20,000 Level This surge comes amid BlackRock and other financial giants&#8217; recent filing of a Bitcoin Exchange-traded fund (ETF) and the launch of EDX Markets, a digital-asset exchange supported by esteemed traditional finance giants such as Citadel Securities, Fidelity Digital Assets, and Charles Schwab Corp. Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto community is currently in a state of constant speculation as renowned analyst Willy Woo sets forth a <a href="https://twitter.com/woonomic/status/1674010721225691136?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">prediction</a> suggesting Bitcoin could potentially scale up to a price of $310,000 under a specific set of circumstances. </p>
<p>Woo&#8217;s hypothesis, which has sparked a flurry of discussions in the crypto community, is hinged on an assumption that notable institutional players might decide to designate a fraction of their assets under management (AUM) to the largest digital currency, Bitcoin.</p>
<h2>The Theoretical Path To $310,000 Bitcoin</h2>
<p>Woo breaks down his perspective, detailing that a significant augmentation in Bitcoin&#8217;s market cap, coupled with a corresponding increase in its realized cap, could set the stage for this quantum leap in price. However, he underscores that the timing of these potential institutional inflows would significantly determine the trajectory of Bitcoin&#8217;s price.</p>

<p>Woo noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>It [BTC potential to $310,000] would really depend on whether they [institutional players] deploy in a bearish or bullish phase of the market but the range would be between $128,000 &#8211; $398,000. Right now it&#8217;s $310,000.</p></blockquote>
<p>According to Woo, if such investment decisions take place during a bearish market phase, Bitcoin may dip to around $128,000. On the flip side, a bullish market condition could <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/crypto-analyst-predicts-bitcoin-to-reach-above-in-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">propel BTC to $400,000</a>.</p>
<p>Woo’s projections, albeit well-reasoned, were met with a fair share of skepticism, particularly concerning the assumption of institutional asset reallocation towards <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-price-on-shaky-ground-market-analysts-warn-potential-fall/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a>. Reacting to the doubts, Woo emphasized the hypothetical nature of his argument, stressing that the ultimate control of asset allocation rests with the investors and not the institutions.</p>
<h2>Investor Decisions VS Wealth Manager Discretion</h2>
<p>Splitting wealth management into two distinct categories &#8211; investor-driven decisions and wealth manager discretion &#8211; Woo explained that any large-scale movement toward Bitcoin would likely necessitate the approval of the individual investors represented by these institutions.</p>
<p>Tweeting about his analysis, Woo stated that If these institutions &#8220;allocated 5% of AUM into BTC,&#8221; his calculations project above $300,000 per coin and could vary significantly to below it. However, currently, the estimate stands at $310,000, based on a methodology measuring market cap increase versus realized cap increase.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ZJc5Ahpt/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC)’s price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<p>Meanwhile, at the time of writing, Bitcoin currently trades above $30,000 after trading below that price range earlier this month due to its bloodbath from the United States Security and Exchange Commission (SEC) lawsuit on the two largest crypto exchanges, Binance and Coinbase.</p>
<p>However, following <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/blackrock-inches-closer-to-launching-bitcoin-etf-impact-on-btc-price/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">financial giants such as BlackRock</a> expressed acceptance of the crypto market, Bitcoin has seen significant growth up by more than 20% in the past two weeks. Notably, over the past 14 days, more than $100 billion has been added to the crypto market cap.</p>

<p>This surge comes amid BlackRock and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/btc-uptrend-fidelity-to-submit-bitcoin-spot-etf-filing/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">other financial giants&#8217; recent filing of a Bitcoin Exchange-traded fund (ETF)</a> and the launch of EDX Markets, a digital-asset exchange supported by esteemed traditional finance giants such as Citadel Securities, Fidelity Digital Assets, and Charles Schwab Corp.</p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-1.jpg" width="350" height="250" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Altcoin Whales Show Highly Active Day, Volatility Incoming?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/altcoin-whales-highly-active-day-volatility-incoming/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 14:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin Volatility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin Whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540337</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that altcoin whales have been highly active recently, something that could lead to volatility in the prices of these assets. Altcoin Whales Have Displayed One Of The Most Active Days Of 2023 According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, several altcoins have seen transfers worth more than $10 million in value in a single day. Generally, besides centralized platforms like exchanges, only whale investors are capable of moving such a large amount of tokens with individual transactions. Whales are an important part of any cryptocurrency&#8217;s ecosystem, as the sheer number of coins that they hold means that they can sometimes have the power to influence the market. Related Reading: Stablecoin Cap Shows Early Sign Of Reversal, Why This Could Benefit Bitcoin Naturally, only a couple of whales making a few sizeable, but still relatively small transfers likely won&#8217;t actually produce visible fluctuations on the market, but a few massive transfers may do so. Thus, whenever the whales are highly active (that is, a number of them are making multiple large transactions), the price of the asset that they are trading can become more likely to display volatility. Now, here is a chart from Santiment that shows how the scale of whale activity has recently looked like for the various altcoins in the sector: Many different assets seem to have observed high levels of whale activity recently &#124; Source: Santiment on Twitter As highlighted in the above graph, the whales of several altcoins moved around a large volume of tokens yesterday. Many of these alts saw major transactions crossing the $10 million mark, making the day the third most active of the year. These large transactions have come while these alts have registered some amount of fluctuations during the past week. It would appear that this market activity has raised the interest of the whales in trading these assets. As mentioned before, whales making such large multiple transactions can result in higher volatility for the prices of these cryptocurrencies. So far, however, since these large transfers have taken place, some of these coins have noticed some volatile price action, while the others have continued to move sideways. From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that Polygon (MATIC) in particular saw extreme amounts moved by the whales, but the asset has still only moved 1% in the past day. Nonetheless, it&#8217;s possible that volatility could still be coming soon for the asset, so it may be worth keeping an eye on the cryptocurrency. Related Reading: Bitcoin Rally Stalls As Short-Term Holder Exchange Inflows Intensify Interestingly, the Tether (USDT) whales have also been quite active recently, suggesting that some large shifts have been taking place. It&#8217;s unknown whether these moves are for buying or selling, but if they are a sign of whales exchanging the stablecoin for buying into the other cryptocurrencies, then their prices may feel a bullish effect. MATIC Price At the time of writing, Polygon is trading around $0.63, up 6% in the last week. Looks like MATIC has been struggling recently &#124; Source: MATICUSD on TradingView Featured image from Vivek Kumar on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Santiment.net]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows that altcoin whales have been highly active recently, something that could lead to volatility in the prices of these assets.</p>
<h2>Altcoin Whales Have Displayed One Of The Most Active Days Of 2023</h2>
<p>According to data from the on-chain analytics firm <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1674104719864918018" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Santiment</a>, several altcoins have seen transfers worth more than $10 million in value in a single day. Generally, besides centralized platforms like exchanges, only <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/whale-trades-link-and-bnb-for-pepe-and-eth/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">whale</a> investors are capable of moving such a large amount of tokens with individual transactions.</p>
<p>Whales are an important part of any cryptocurrency&#8217;s ecosystem, as the sheer number of coins that they hold means that they can sometimes have the power to influence the market.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/stablecoin-cap-early-signs-of-reversal-why-goodr-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Stablecoin Cap Shows Early Sign Of Reversal, Why This Could Benefit Bitcoin</a></p>
<p>Naturally, only a couple of whales making a few sizeable, but still relatively small transfers likely won&#8217;t actually produce visible fluctuations on the market, but a few massive transfers may do so.</p>
<p>Thus, whenever the whales are highly active (that is, a number of them are making multiple large transactions), the price of the asset that they are trading can become more likely to display <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-realized-loss-low-despite-volatility-what-mean/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">volatility</a>.</p>
<p>Now, here is a chart from Santiment that shows how the scale of whale activity has recently looked like for the various altcoins in the sector:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FzucRNpaAAEZux9?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Image" loading="lazy"/></p>

<p>As highlighted in the above graph, the whales of several altcoins moved around a large volume of tokens yesterday. Many of these alts saw major transactions crossing the $10 million mark, making the day the third most active of the year.</p>
<p>These large transactions have come while these alts have registered some amount of fluctuations during the past week. It would appear that this market activity has raised the interest of the whales in trading these assets.</p>
<p>As mentioned before, whales making such large multiple transactions can result in higher volatility for the prices of these cryptocurrencies. So far, however, since these large transfers have taken place, some of these coins have noticed some volatile price action, while the others have continued to move sideways.</p>
<p>From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/matic-analysis/matic-price-prediction-polygon-0-75/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Polygon (MATIC)</a> in particular saw extreme amounts moved by the whales, but the asset has still only moved 1% in the past day. Nonetheless, it&#8217;s possible that volatility could still be coming soon for the asset, so it may be worth keeping an eye on the cryptocurrency.</p>

<p>Interestingly, the Tether (USDT) whales have also been quite active recently, suggesting that some large shifts have been taking place. It&#8217;s unknown whether these moves are for buying or selling, but if they are a sign of whales exchanging the stablecoin for buying into the other cryptocurrencies, then their prices may feel a bullish effect.</p>
<h2>MATIC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Polygon is trading around $0.63, up 6% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/b7foU1JA/" alt="Polygon Price Chart" width="1534" height="911"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/vivek-kumar-fs283LESUtc-unsplash-460x267.jpg" width="460" height="267" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Compound (COMP) Surges Nearly 10% In The Past Day, Here’s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/compound-comp-surges-nearly-10-in-the-past-day/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 13:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[comp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[compound]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540316</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As the crypto world continues to evolve with increased volatility, unique patterns emerge, attracting the interest of investors and analysts alike. One such way has been observed in the recent trading activity of Compound (COMP), the governance token tied to the Compound protocol. The asset experienced a significant surge, registering a nearly 10% growth within the past day. Over the last 7 days, COMP has been in an uptrend, and the 10% single-day rise forms part of a larger appreciation pattern. This escalation is noteworthy as the token&#8217;s price soared over 50% within just a week. Whale Activity Fuels Price Momentum Blockchain analytics firm Lookonchain earlier today shed some light on the reason behind the recent COMP price surge. The firm disclosed on Twitter that a possible whale or institutional investor appears to have made substantial COMP transactions. Related Reading: Over 167 Million BAT Utilized In DeFi Mainly In Compound, Aave And Uniswap According to Lookonchain, &#8220;Wallet &#8216;0x0D5&#8217; transferred 3 million USDT to Binance on June 26 and extracted 50,000 COMP, equating to around $2.26 million, 16 hours ago.&#8221; The same entity reportedly withdrew an additional 120,000 COMP, valued at approximately $5.53 million from Binance shortly after. The whale/institution withdrew another 120K $COMP ($5.53M) from #Binance just now. So the rise in the price of $COMP may have something to do with this whale/institution.https://t.co/6LfmjMxaRZ pic.twitter.com/Deh4v260qt — Lookonchain (@lookonchain) June 29, 2023 Such considerable transfers often signify bullish behavior and could contribute to the increase in COMP&#8217;s price, given their potential influence on the token&#8217;s supply and demand dynamics. Compound (COMP) Latest Price Action COMP token price has increased in the past few days, with the governance token breaking multiple resistance levels. COMP is currently trading above $46, up 51.7% over the past week. The token currently has a market capitalization of $321 million, making it rank 109th among the largest cryptocurrency by market cap. Meanwhile, over the past 24 hours, the asset has seen an upward trend of nearly 10% in price. COMP has also added more than $100 million to its market cap in the past weeks. The asset market capitalization has surged from a low of below $200 million in the past few days to as high as $321 million as of today. COMP&#8217;s daily trading volume has also recorded a significant surge from the $10 million volume seen earlier this month to stand above $90 million in the past 24 hours. COMP currently has a 24-hour low of $38.82 and a 24-hour high of $47.39. Related Reading: Compound Prepares For A Major Rally To $80, Here Is Why Notably, the token&#8217;s performance is not limited to the past day or week. When viewed over a two-week span, COMP has recorded a substantial growth pattern, registering a 70% gain. At the beginning of the month, COMP was trading at a low of $25 per token. At the time of writing, however, the token stands tall, commanding a price of $46.94. Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As the crypto world continues to evolve with increased volatility, unique patterns emerge, attracting the interest of investors and analysts alike. One such way has been observed in the recent trading activity of Compound (COMP), the governance token tied to the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/defi/over-167-million-bat-utilized-in-defi-mainly-in-compound-aave-and-uniswap/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Compound protocol</a>. The asset experienced a significant surge, registering a nearly 10% growth within the past day.</p>
<p>Over the last 7 days, COMP has been in an uptrend, and the 10% single-day rise forms part of a larger appreciation pattern. This escalation is noteworthy as the token&#8217;s price soared over 50% within just a week.</p>
<h2>Whale Activity Fuels Price Momentum</h2>
<p>Blockchain analytics firm Lookonchain earlier today <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1674343743774937089?s=20" rel="nofollow">shed some light</a> on the reason behind the recent COMP price surge. The firm disclosed on Twitter that a possible whale or institutional investor appears to have made substantial COMP transactions.</p>

<p>According to Lookonchain, &#8220;Wallet &#8216;0x0D5&#8217; transferred 3 million USDT to Binance on June 26 and extracted 50,000 COMP, equating to around $2.26 million, 16 hours ago.&#8221; The same entity reportedly withdrew an additional 120,000 COMP, valued at approximately $5.53 million from Binance shortly after.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">The whale/institution withdrew another 120K <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24COMP&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$COMP</a> ($5.53M) from <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Binance</a> just now.</p>
<p>So the rise in the price of <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24COMP&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$COMP</a> may have something to do with this whale/institution.<a href="https://t.co/6LfmjMxaRZ" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/6LfmjMxaRZ</a> <a href="https://t.co/Deh4v260qt" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/Deh4v260qt</a></p>
<p>— Lookonchain (@lookonchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1674343743774937089?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 29, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Such considerable transfers often signify bullish behavior and could contribute to the increase in COMP&#8217;s price, given their potential influence on the token&#8217;s supply and demand dynamics.</p>
<h2>Compound (COMP) Latest Price Action</h2>
<p>COMP token price has increased in the past few days, with the governance token breaking multiple resistance levels. COMP is currently <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/compound-prepares-for-a-major-rally-to-80-here-is-why/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">trading above $46, up 51.7%</a> over the past week. The token currently has a market capitalization of $321 million, making it rank 109th among the largest cryptocurrency by market cap.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, over the past 24 hours, the asset has seen an upward trend of nearly 10% in price. COMP has also added more than $100 million to its market cap in the past weeks. The <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/defi-coins/compound-comp-outruns-top-defi-tokens-as-tvl-closes-above-2b/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">asset market capitalization</a> has surged from a low of below $200 million in the past few days to as high as $321 million as of today.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/PbblLtoI/" alt="Compound (COMP) price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<p>COMP&#8217;s daily trading volume has also recorded a significant surge from the $10 million volume seen earlier this month to stand above $90 million in the past 24 hours. COMP currently has a 24-hour low of $38.82 and a 24-hour high of $47.39.</p>

<p>Notably, the token&#8217;s performance is not limited to the past day or week. When viewed over a two-week span, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/compound-finance-suffers-bug/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">COMP</a> has recorded a substantial growth pattern, registering a 70% gain. At the beginning of the month, COMP was trading at a low of $25 per token. At the time of writing, however, the token stands tall, commanding a price of $46.94.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Mining-460x272.jpg" width="460" height="272" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
