<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 22:35:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>XRP Bulls Try To Break Consolidation At $0.4 To Conquer New Levels</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/ripple/xrp-consolidation-04-to-conquer-new-levels/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 00:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517678</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[XRP bulls are trying to ride the wave along with Bitcoin to reclaim previously lost territory. The bulls are targeting new annual highs. Related Reading: XRP Whales Accumulate Massive Tokens – Is A Bull Run Coming? XRP has been trading in the green zone since the beginning of the year with a strong recovery and bullish sentiment from its investors. At press time, XRP is trading at $04.96, representing a gain of 0.78% in the last 24 hours. The token is auctioning 34% below its 2018 high of $3.40. Can XRP Sustain Its Bull Streak? XRP started the year with a spike in volatility that characterized the market and has been able to profit 11.85% in the last 30 days, pushing its market cap to $20.6 billion.  In addition, the trading volume that XRP has experienced in recent days and weeks and the profitable trend of XRP shows that market makers are involved in the project. According to a recent report from NewsBTC, it&#8217;s possible to assume that  XRP whales are once again buying and accumulating the token.  This increase in activity in the XRP Ledger&#8217;s native token suggests that more wallets are being created with large amounts of XRP. While the perspective of many investors may be bullish, we can also find traces that lead us to consider a bearish scenario.  XRP can break the trend line that touches three key levels and continue its bullish trend to find a position in the following challenge represented by $0.5. XRP Heaven or Hell Levels Despite the breach of previous target zones, there are strong signals that XRP&#8217;s bullish days may be numbered. The current market scenario, where some tokens are consolidating or forming a range price, suggests that the price action can explode in any direction. As with any pivotal moment in the market, this leaves XRP with two scenarios, which are explained in the following chart: XRP can break the trend line that touches three key levels and continue its bullish momentum to find a position in the following challenge represented by $0.5. On the daily chart above, XRP has formed a bearish divergence, which may represent a significant pullback for the token. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) sits at 42.51, approaching oversold territory, but for XRP, there needs to be a correction in the daily time frame before the price action can follow the RSI indicator. If this is confirmed, XRP could significantly retreat to the $0.36 support level. If the bulls cannot stop this hypothetical scenario, the token may also lose territory and test the $0.288 level.  In short, XRP needs to find its momentum before a significant correction of the token and the cryptocurrency market, with Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) forming bearish divergences on the daily charts. Related Reading: Ethereum Hovers Above $1,600, What’s The Next Move? Confirmation of the bearish divergences for XRP will be complete when the price action breaks below $0.379. In that case, bears may find themselves in the perfect scenario to ride down the hill to visit lower prices. If XRP&#8217;s downturn continues, it could retest $0.33, the following primary support line for the token.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>XRP bulls are trying to ride the wave along with Bitcoin to reclaim previously lost territory. The bulls are targeting new annual highs.</p>

<p>XRP has been trading in the green zone since the beginning of the year with a strong recovery and bullish sentiment from its investors. At press time, XRP is trading at $04.96, representing a gain of 0.78% in the last 24 hours. The token is auctioning 34% below its 2018 high of $3.40.</p>
<h2><b>Can XRP Sustain Its Bull Streak?</b></h2>
<p>XRP started the year with a spike in volatility that characterized the market and has been able to profit 11.85% in the last 30 days, pushing its market cap to $20.6 billion. </p>
<p>In addition, the trading volume that XRP has experienced in recent days and weeks and the profitable trend of XRP shows that market makers are involved in the project. According to a recent <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-whales-accumulate-massive-tokens-is-a-bull-run-coming/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">report from NewsBTC</a>, it&#8217;s possible to assume that  XRP whales are once again buying and accumulating the token. </p>
<p>This increase in activity in the XRP Ledger&#8217;s native token suggests that more wallets are being created with large amounts of XRP. While the perspective of many investors may be bullish, we can also find traces that lead us to consider a bearish scenario. </p>
<p>XRP can break the trend line that touches three key levels and continue its bullish trend to find a position in the following challenge represented by $0.5.</p>
<b>XRP Heaven or Hell Levels</b>
<p>Despite the breach of previous target zones, there are strong signals that XRP&#8217;s bullish days may be numbered. The current market scenario, where some tokens are consolidating or forming a range price, suggests that the price action can explode in any direction.</p>
<p>As with any pivotal moment in the market, this leaves XRP with two scenarios, which are explained in the following chart:</p>
<p>XRP can break the trend line that touches three key levels and continue its bullish momentum to find a position in the following challenge represented by $0.5.</p>
<img class="wp-image-517679 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT_2023-01-26_14-42-10_623eb-860x407.png" alt="XRP XRPUSDT" width="860" height="407" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT_2023-01-26_14-42-10_623eb-860x407.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT_2023-01-26_14-42-10_623eb-460x218.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT_2023-01-26_14-42-10_623eb-768x363.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT_2023-01-26_14-42-10_623eb-1536x727.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT_2023-01-26_14-42-10_623eb-750x355.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT_2023-01-26_14-42-10_623eb-1140x539.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT_2023-01-26_14-42-10_623eb.png 1814w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>On the daily chart above, XRP has formed a bearish divergence, which may represent a significant pullback for the token. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) sits at 42.51, approaching oversold territory, but for XRP, there needs to be a correction in the daily time frame before the price action can follow the RSI indicator.</p>
<p>If this is confirmed, XRP could significantly retreat to the $0.36 support level. If the bulls cannot stop this hypothetical scenario, the token may also lose territory and test the $0.288 level. </p>
<p>In short, XRP needs to find its momentum before a significant correction of the token and the cryptocurrency market, with Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) forming bearish divergences on the daily charts.</p>



<p>Confirmation of the bearish divergences for XRP will be complete when the price action breaks below $0.379. In that case, bears may find themselves in the perfect scenario to ride down the hill to visit lower prices. If XRP&#8217;s downturn continues, it could retest $0.33, the following primary support line for the token.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/iStock-933090786-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin (DOGE) Soars 8%, But An Uptick In This Metric Suggests A Pullback</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/dogecoin-doge-8-metric-pullback/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 22:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Breaking News Ticker]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517663</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE) and other altcoins are stealing some of Bitcoin’s shine as the benchmark crypto stalls at its current levels. However, the recent rally could spell trouble for optimistic traders and investors waiting for a continuation of the trend. Related Reading: Cardano Adds 50,000 New Wallets As ADA Market Cap Surges As of this writing, Dogecoin (DOGE) trades at $0.08 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. Over the previous seven days, the meme coin still records an 8% profit. In the crypto top 10, DOGE stands amongst the best performers, surpassed only by Cardano (ADA) and Polygon (MATIC). Dogecoin’s Rally Stirs The Crowds, Is A Retrace Imminent? Data from Coingecko indicates positive development for meme coins. The sector records around $20 billion in total market cap, a 2% increase in 24 hours, and $1 billion in trading volume over the same period. In addition to Dogecoin, Shiba Inu (SHIB), Baby Dogecoin, and Bonk have captured the attention of crypto investors. The second of these assets experience a 23% rally in the past week alone, hinting at the increase in risk appetite from digital asset enthusiasts. The Bitcoin rally deep into the $20,000 territory has flipped the crypto market’s sentiment. As a result, Dogecoin and other meme coins are resurging and outperforming more significant digital assets. Additional data from analytics firm Santiment registered increased levels of positive interaction across social media platforms. This suggests that users are more willing to take long positions, swelling the liquidity to the downside. In other words, people are experiencing fear of missing out (FOMO), as recorded by Santiment, increasing the chances of a pullback. Market makers could squeeze long positions before resuming the bullish momentum. As seen in the chart below, the altcoin sector has recently seen important growth. Tokens such as APTOS and LCX saw around 40% of weekly profits. Related Reading: XRP Whales Accumulate Massive Tokens – Is A Bull Run Coming? Santiment wrote: Altcoins are on another impressive run, with several notable assets up 20% or more. After a 5-day crypto dip, prices are seeing little resistance. Social spikes &#38; FOMO may cause a top, or traders will scoff at this run (allowing rallies to continue).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Dogecoin (DOGE) and other altcoins are stealing some of Bitcoin’s shine as the benchmark crypto stalls at its current levels. However, the recent rally could spell trouble for optimistic traders and investors waiting for a continuation of the trend. </strong></p>

<p>As of this writing, Dogecoin (DOGE) trades at $0.08 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. Over the previous seven days, the meme coin still records an 8% profit. In the crypto top 10, DOGE stands amongst the best performers, surpassed only by Cardano (ADA) and Polygon (MATIC).</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-517676 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-860x394.png" alt="Dogecoin DOGE DOGEUSDT" width="860" height="394" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-860x394.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-460x211.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-768x352.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-1536x704.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-750x344.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-1140x522.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT.png 1814w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<h2><strong>Dogecoin’s Rally Stirs The Crowds, Is A Retrace Imminent? </strong></h2>
<p>Data from Coingecko indicates positive development for meme coins. The sector records around $20 billion in total market cap, a 2% increase in 24 hours, and $1 billion in trading volume over the same period.</p>
<p>In addition to Dogecoin, Shiba Inu (SHIB), Baby Dogecoin, and Bonk have captured the attention of crypto investors. The second of these assets experience a 23% rally in the past week alone, hinting at the increase in risk appetite from digital asset enthusiasts.</p>
<p>The Bitcoin rally deep into the $20,000 territory has flipped the crypto market’s sentiment. As a result, Dogecoin and other meme coins are resurging and outperforming more significant digital assets.</p>
<p>Additional <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1618372704612257799" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from analytics firm Santiment registered</a> increased levels of positive interaction across social media platforms. This suggests that users are more willing to take long positions, swelling the liquidity to the downside.</p>
<p>In other words, people are experiencing fear of missing out (FOMO), as recorded by Santiment, increasing the chances of a pullback. Market makers could squeeze long positions before resuming the bullish momentum.</p>
<p>As seen in the chart below, the altcoin sector has recently seen important growth. Tokens such as APTOS and LCX saw around 40% of weekly profits.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-517675 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-860x546.jpeg" alt="Dogecoin DOGE DOGEUSDT" width="860" height="546" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-860x546.jpeg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-460x292.jpeg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-768x487.jpeg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-1536x975.jpeg 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-2048x1300.jpeg 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-750x476.jpeg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-DOGE-DOGEUSDT-1140x724.jpeg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />

<p>Santiment wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>Altcoins are on another impressive run, with several notable assets up 20% or more. After a 5-day crypto dip, prices are seeing little resistance. Social spikes &amp; FOMO may cause a top, or traders will scoff at this run (allowing rallies to continue).</p></blockquote>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-460x274.png" width="460" height="274" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano Adds 50,000 New Wallets As ADA Market Cap Surges</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-50k-wallets-ada-market-cap-surges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 20:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Djed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517669</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Cardano ecosystem has the potential for further growth. The network has grown tremendously in various sectors, including decentralized finance (DeFi) and nonfungible tokens (NFTs). The blockchain has recorded massive adoption over the past months emerging as the third most active blockchain in development activity. According to data from Cardano Blockchain Insights, this blockchain&#8217;s ecosystem has added more than 50,000 new wallets since the beginning of the year. From 3,842,867 recorded on January 1 to 3,894,735 wallets registered as of January 25, a total of 51,868 wallets were added to the network.  In the past 25 days, an average of 2,075 new wallets have been created daily, indicating a rising interest and activity from potential new investors on the Cardano blockchain. Related Reading: Cardano (ADA) Continues To Shine With 15% Gains In the Last Week ADA Market Cap Surges Nearly 50% Following the increasing interest from potential buyers, Cardano&#8217;s (ADA) market capitalization has recorded new monthly highs. From the $8.48 billion seen late last year, the ADA market cap has surged to over $13 billion, up by 43% in the previous 30 days.  The asset has gained traction and recognition from notable firms. Earlier this week, crypto analytics platform StockTwits ranked ADA as the most trending cryptocurrency, surpassing Bitcoin (BTC), which attained the second position below ADA. CoinGecko and Coinmarketcap have ranked ADA as eighth regarding top cryptocurrencies with the highest market capitalization. Alongside its cryptocurrency market cap surge, ADA has also rallied in the past weeks, appearing among the top gainers among cryptocurrencies with large market caps. Over the past 30 days, ADA has surged from the $0.25 price tag seen late last year to above $0.35 at the time of writing. Its trading volume has also changed significantly from $161 million recorded at the beginning of the year to $489 million in the last 24 hours.  Cardano&#8217;s Most Anticipated Catalyst Though ADA&#8217;s recent rally seems based on the crypto market&#8217;s ubiquitous bullish trend, a catalyst such as the Djed stablecoin could also be a part of the asset’s increasing attraction. Djed is Cardano’s first ADA-backed stablecoin powered by COTI Network. It is an over-collateralized stablecoin with a collateral rate between 400%-800%, according to the description on adapulse.io. Related Reading: Cardano’s Aggressive Development Activity Will Withstand Bear Assault At $0.3? Although it&#8217;ll be launched soon, Djed has received a lot of interest from non-ADA investors and potential Cardano buyers. Rick McCracken, a Cardano supporter, and owner of the ADA staking pool, DIGI, celebrated and confirmed the launch of Djed on mainnet. Featured image from Bitcoinist, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Cardano ecosystem has the potential for further growth. The network has grown tremendously in various sectors, including decentralized finance (DeFi) and nonfungible tokens (NFTs). The blockchain has recorded massive adoption over the past months emerging as the third most active blockchain in development activity.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://datastudio.google.com/u/0/reporting/3136c55b-635e-4f46-8e4b-b8ab54f2d460/page/p_a6behjl6oc" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a> from Cardano Blockchain Insights, this blockchain&#8217;s ecosystem has added more than 50,000 new wallets since the beginning of the year. From 3,842,867 recorded on January 1 to 3,894,735 wallets registered as of January 25, a total of 51,868 wallets were added to the network. </p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-517670 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-wallets.jpg" alt="Cardano wallets | Source: Cardano Blockchain Insights" width="414" height="355" />
<p>In the past 25 days, an average of 2,075 new wallets have been created daily, indicating a rising interest and activity from potential new investors on the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-top-trending-crypto-list/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Cardano</a> blockchain.</p>

<h2>ADA Market Cap Surges Nearly 50%</h2>
<p>Following the increasing interest from potential buyers, Cardano&#8217;s (ADA) market capitalization has recorded new monthly highs. From the $8.48 billion seen late last year, the ADA market cap has surged to over $13 billion, up by 43% in the previous 30 days. </p>
<p>The asset has gained traction and recognition from notable firms. Earlier this week, crypto analytics platform StockTwits ranked <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-top-trending-crypto-list/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ADA as the most trending cryptocurrency</a>, surpassing Bitcoin (BTC), which attained the second position below ADA.</p>
<p>CoinGecko and Coinmarketcap have ranked ADA as eighth regarding top cryptocurrencies with the highest market capitalization. Alongside its cryptocurrency market cap surge, <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-up-30-since-december/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ADA</a> has also rallied in the past weeks, appearing among the top gainers among cryptocurrencies with large market caps.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/uO4eIpli/" alt="ADA price chart on TradingView" width="1562" height="753" />
<p>Over the past 30 days, ADA has <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-ada-up-nearly-20/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">surged</a> from the $0.25 price tag seen late last year to above $0.35 at the time of writing. Its trading volume has also changed significantly from $161 million recorded at the beginning of the year to $489 million in the last 24 hours. </p>
<h2>Cardano&#8217;s Most Anticipated Catalyst</h2>
<p>Though ADA&#8217;s recent rally seems based on the crypto market&#8217;s ubiquitous bullish trend, a catalyst such as the Djed stablecoin could also be a part of the asset’s increasing attraction. Djed is Cardano’s first ADA-backed stablecoin powered by COTI Network. It is an over-collateralized stablecoin with a collateral rate between 400%-800%, according to the description on <a href="https://adapulse.io/djed-a-stablecoin-in-cardano-deep-dive-part-1/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">adapulse.io</a>.</p>

<p>Although it&#8217;ll be launched soon, Djed has received a lot of interest from non-ADA investors and potential Cardano buyers. Rick McCracken, a Cardano supporter, and owner of the ADA staking pool, DIGI, celebrated and <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/cardano/launch-for-djed-cardano-stablecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">confirmed</a> the launch of Djed on mainnet.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-1-460x230.jpeg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Whales Accumulate Massive Tokens &#8211; Is A Bull Run Coming?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-whales-accumulate-massive-tokens-is-a-bull-run-coming/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli Dambell]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stuart Alderoty]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517546</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The XRP price dipped in 2022 during the crypto winter, and the back-and-forth legal exchange between Ripple Labs and the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission has not helped matters. However, the token is still attracting interest from whales and institutional investors. XRP still has a chance of recovery, which seems to be the motivation behind the whale mass acquisition of the token. Related Reading: MakerDAO Passes Proposal To Deploy $100 Million USDC In Yearn Finance Vault Whales Seize The Dip WhaleAlert reported that whales had moved 128 million-plus XRP worth close to $53 million in the last day. The largest whale activity recorded in that period was the movement of 35 million XRP worth around $15 million to the Bitstamp exchange.  According to the data, whales have purchased up to 69 million XRP tokens in 24 hours. The first accumulation noted by Whale Alert is the addition of 33 million XRP (approx worth above $13 million) to a Bitstamp address. 🚨 33,000,000 #XRP (13,274,704 USD) transferred from unknown wallet to #Bitstamphttps://t.co/YZirFauiLJ &#8212; Whale Alert (@whale_alert) January 24, 2023 Another large whale accumulation was 36 million tokens sent to a Bitstamp address worth 14,972,855 USD at the time of the transaction. 🚨 36,000,000 #XRP (14,972,855 USD) transferred from unknown wallet to #Bitstamphttps://t.co/QK23u7luIM &#8212; Whale Alert (@whale_alert) January 25, 2023 Whalestats also reports that XRP was the most traded token among the top 100 BSC whales. The top 100 whales on this list currently hold more than $28.6 million worth of XRP, which accounts for 2.5% of their entire portfolio. Over the past few days, there has been increased whale activity on the XRP network. WhaleAlert reported massive transfers exceeding 600 million XRP tokens between anonymous whale addresses. The whale transfers come amid rising crypto inflows from investors since the beginning of the year. A single transaction, as reported by WhaleAlert, carried 254,594,795 XRP, which amounted to $107,778,830 between two unnamed whale addresses. Another was about 221,500,500 XRP worth $89,110,472 from an unknown whale address to a Bittrex-linked wallet. Each of the transfers occurred in single transactions. Ripple Versus SEC: Is The End In Sight? The ongoing legal drama between Ripple Labs, Ripple (XRP) developers, and the SEC will likely end in 2023. Brad Garlinghouse, head of Ripple Labs, said he hopes for a conclusion in the ongoing saga in the first half of 2023. The SEC sued Ripple Labs in 2020 for selling XRP tokens to the public, which it says were unregistered securities. The SEC has repeatedly classified XRP as securities, with the Ripple defense team objecting to the idea. Garlinghouse stated that the judgment would take some time, but his confidence in Ripple&#8217;s chances of a victory is high. Related Reading: Cardano’s Aggressive Development Activity Will Withstand Bear Assault At $0.3? However, he emphasized that a settlement is unlikely since SEC chairman Gary Gensler has labeled all cryptos as securities. Both parties have completed the final step in their motion for summary judgment and are now anticipating the court&#8217;s decision. Meanwhile, the lead counsel to the defendant in the XRP case, Stuart Alderoty, said the lawsuit&#8217;s outcome would define what tokens are securities in the crypto space. He added that the ruling would impact crypto asset regulations in the industry. Featured Image From Pixabay/ vjkombajn, Charts From Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The XRP price dipped in 2022 during the crypto winter, and the back-and-forth legal exchange between Ripple Labs and the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission has not helped matters.</p>
<p>However, the token is still attracting interest from whales and institutional investors. XRP still has a chance of recovery, which seems to be the motivation behind the whale mass acquisition of the token.</p>

<h2><b>Whales Seize The Dip</b></h2>
<p><a href="https://whale-alert.io/transaction/ripple/0CEA08F26020E762B8DFF1EB1F586DF877A07C562E4964C12FBC22B5A83340EC" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">WhaleAlert</a> reported that whales had moved 128 million-plus XRP worth close to $53 million in the last day. The largest whale activity recorded in that period was the movement of 35 million XRP worth around $15 million to the Bitstamp exchange. </p>
<p>According to the data, whales have purchased up to 69 million XRP tokens in 24 hours. The first accumulation noted by Whale Alert is the <a href="https://whale-alert.io/transaction/ripple/0CEA08F26020E762B8DFF1EB1F586DF877A07C562E4964C12FBC22B5A83340EC" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">addition of 33 million XRP</a> (approx worth above $13 million) to a Bitstamp address.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />  33,000,000 <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/XRP?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#XRP</a> (13,274,704 USD) transferred from unknown wallet to <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitstamp?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#Bitstamp</a><a href="https://t.co/YZirFauiLJ" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">https://t.co/YZirFauiLJ</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Whale Alert (@whale_alert) <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1618027256802168832?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 24, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>Another <a href="https://whale-alert.io/transaction/ripple/88D41905A1DB54D50718841D3D5DDB6A3526D7578AEFDB07E8770006F217D209" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">large whale accumulation</a> was 36 million tokens sent to a Bitstamp address worth 14,972,855 USD at the time of the transaction.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />  36,000,000 <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/XRP?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#XRP</a> (14,972,855 USD) transferred from unknown wallet to <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitstamp?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#Bitstamp</a><a href="https://t.co/QK23u7luIM" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">https://t.co/QK23u7luIM</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Whale Alert (@whale_alert) <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1618384880399749125?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 25, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>Whalestats also reports that XRP was the most traded token among the top 100 BSC whales. The top 100 whales on this list currently hold more than $28.6 million worth of XRP, which accounts for 2.5% of their entire portfolio.</p>
<p>Over the past few days, there has been increased whale activity on the XRP network. WhaleAlert reported massive transfers exceeding 600 million XRP tokens between anonymous whale addresses. The whale transfers come amid rising crypto inflows from investors since the beginning of the year.</p>
<p>A single transaction, as <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1617495287211204608%7Ctwgr%5E0da4641d66746e7444b0c6da088c60e3d35e3358%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fu.today%2Fhundreds-of-millions-of-xrp-wired-as-xrp-sees-large-inflows-this-year" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">reported</a> by WhaleAlert, carried 254,594,795 XRP, which amounted to $107,778,830 between two unnamed whale addresses. Another was about <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1617258352492400640?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1617258352492400640%7Ctwgr%5E0da4641d66746e7444b0c6da088c60e3d35e3358%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fu.today%2Fhundreds-of-millions-of-xrp-wired-as-xrp-sees-large-inflows-this-year" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">221,500,500 XRP</a> worth $89,110,472 from an unknown whale address to a Bittrex-linked wallet. Each of the transfers occurred in single transactions.</p>
<h2><strong>Ripple Versus SEC: Is The End In Sight?</strong></h2>
<p>The ongoing <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/18/ripple-ceo-optimistic-crypto-firm-will-get-sec-xrp-lawsuit-ruling-soon.html?utm_term=Autofeed&amp;utm_medium=Social&amp;utm_content=Main&amp;utm_source=Twitter#Echobox=1674054943" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">legal drama</a> between Ripple Labs, Ripple (XRP) developers, and the SEC will likely end in 2023. Brad Garlinghouse, head of Ripple Labs, said he hopes for a conclusion in the ongoing saga in the first half of 2023.</p>
<p>The SEC sued Ripple Labs in 2020 for selling XRP tokens to the public, which it says were unregistered securities. The SEC has repeatedly classified XRP as securities, with the Ripple defense team objecting to the idea. Garlinghouse stated that the judgment would take some time, but his confidence in Ripple&#8217;s chances of a victory is high.</p>

<p>However, he emphasized that a settlement is unlikely since SEC chairman Gary Gensler has labeled all cryptos as securities. Both parties have completed the final step in their motion for summary judgment and are now anticipating the court&#8217;s decision.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-517554 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT_2023-01-26_09-45-49-860x499.png" alt="XRP Whales Accumulate Almost 60.2 Million Tokens, Is A Bull Run Coming?" width="860" height="499" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT_2023-01-26_09-45-49-860x499.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT_2023-01-26_09-45-49-460x267.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT_2023-01-26_09-45-49-768x446.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT_2023-01-26_09-45-49-750x435.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT_2023-01-26_09-45-49.png 1116w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>Meanwhile, the lead counsel to the defendant in the XRP case, <a href="https://twitter.com/s_alderoty/status/1615498088311066624?cxt=HHwWgMDUkfe8s-ssAAAA" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Stuart Alderoty</a>, said the lawsuit&#8217;s outcome would define what tokens are securities in the crypto space. He added that the ruling would impact crypto asset regulations in the industry.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/coin-g3c12cb5cb_1280-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Hovers Above $1,600, What&#8217;s The Next Move?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-hovers-above-1600/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jammy Hunts]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 17:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517643</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The general crypto market has increased in market cap in 24 hours, up by 2.89%. Ethereum (ETH), the second-largest crypto project, is also trading in the green in the same time period. Despite being so early in 2023, ETH has recorded significant price gains in the crypto market. Ethereum is still off its all-time high value, but its price shows resilience with the current upsurge.  Related Reading: This Is How The Bitcoin Price Will Be Affected By Macro: Charles Edwards What Is Driving Ethereum’s Rally? The recent gains recorded could be attributed to the notable projects hosted on the Ethereum network. The Ethereum blockchain remains the most popular blockchain for NFTs. The blockchain is also the pioneer of smart contracts, which is now the widely adopted technology in crypto. These smart contracts enable crypto users to interact seamlessly and securely on the blockchain. Ethereum Name Service (ENS) is one of the innovations on the Ethereum network. ENS is a distributed naming system that helps to shorten a cryptocurrency address by assigning readable names to eliminate confusion. Also, ETH is the second-largest cryptocurrency project by market cap and the first altcoin. Its innovative proof-of-stake system is more energy efficient and attracts increased participation from the crypto community. The network is renowned as a developer’s hub with numerous Web3 and Metaverse projects.  What Next For Ethereum As It Crosses $1,600? ETH recovered from the general market pullback yesterday, trading at $1,605, an increase of 3.81%. The candlesticks on the chart show that ETH has been in an uptrend in the past few days. However, it is currently in a sideways trend and is poised to resume its ascent on the price charts. ETH&#8217;s price correlates to bitcoin&#8217;s price, just like most cryptocurrencies, increasing whenever BTC is bullish. ETH is now trading above its 50-day and 200-day Simple Moving Average (SMA). This is a bullish signal for the asset, so there could be an increase in ETH&#8217;s price in the coming days. The support levels are $1,452.32, $1,495.32, and $1,560.14, and its resistance levels are $1,667.95, $1,710.67, and $1,775.77. Ethereum has sufficient momentum in the market today and will likely surpass the closest resistance level of $1,667.95. Related Reading: CryptoQuant’s Bitcoin PnL Index Forms Bullish Crossover The Relative Strength Index (RSI) is currently at 67.12, close to the overbought region of 70. However, it shows signs of a possible retracement, implying that a reversal in the coming days is still possible. The Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) is above its signal line but showing convergence. It also reflects the possibility of a downtrend occurring in the short term. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">general crypto market</a> has increased in market cap in 24 hours, up by 2.89%. Ethereum (ETH), the second-largest crypto project, is also trading in the green in the same time period. </p>
<p>Despite being so early in 2023, ETH has recorded significant price gains in the crypto market. Ethereum is still off its all-time high value, but its price shows resilience with the current upsurge. </p>

<h2><b>What Is Driving Ethereum’s Rally?</b></h2>
<p>The recent gains recorded could be attributed to the <a href="https://twitter.com/ethereum" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">notable projects</a> hosted on the Ethereum network. The <a href="https://github.com/ethereum/ethereum-org-website/issues/9090" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Ethereum blockchain</a> remains the most popular blockchain for NFTs. The blockchain is also the pioneer of smart contracts, which is now the widely adopted technology in crypto. These smart contracts enable crypto users to interact seamlessly and securely on the blockchain.</p>
<p><a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/alexandria/article/what-is-ens" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Ethereum Name Service</a> (ENS) is one of the innovations on the Ethereum network. ENS is a distributed naming system that helps to shorten a cryptocurrency address by assigning readable names to eliminate confusion.</p>
<p>Also, ETH is the second-largest cryptocurrency project by market cap and the first altcoin. Its innovative proof-of-stake system is more energy efficient and attracts increased participation from the crypto community. The network is renowned as a <a href="https://twitter.com/ethdotorg/status/1612441409247744000" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">developer’s hub</a> with numerous Web3 and Metaverse <a href="https://twitter.com/ethdotorg/status/1615752521049600000" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">projects</a>. </p>
<img loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-517650" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-26_19-54-04.png" alt="ETHUSD" width="856" height="538" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-26_19-54-04.png 856w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-26_19-54-04-460x289.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-26_19-54-04-768x483.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSD_2023-01-26_19-54-04-750x471.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 856px) 100vw, 856px" />
<h2><b>What Next For Ethereum As It Crosses $1,600?</b></h2>
<p>ETH <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?app=desktop&amp;v=AeH3OiTtnKs" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">recovered</a> from the general market pullback yesterday, trading at $1,605, an increase of 3.81%. The candlesticks on the chart show that ETH has been in an uptrend in the past few days. However, it is currently in a sideways trend and is poised to resume its ascent on the price charts. ETH&#8217;s price correlates to bitcoin&#8217;s price, just like most cryptocurrencies, increasing whenever BTC is bullish.</p>
<p>ETH is now trading above its 50-day and 200-day Simple Moving Average (SMA). This is a bullish signal for the asset, so there could be an increase in ETH&#8217;s price in the coming days.</p>
<p> The support levels are $1,452.32, $1,495.32, and $1,560.14, and its resistance levels are $1,667.95, $1,710.67, and $1,775.77. Ethereum has sufficient momentum in the market today and will likely surpass the closest resistance level of $1,667.95.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/cryptoquant-bitcoin-pnl-bullish-crossover/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CryptoQuant’s Bitcoin PnL Index Forms Bullish Crossover</a></p>
<p>The Relative Strength Index (RSI) is currently at 67.12, close to the overbought region of 70. However, it shows signs of a possible retracement, implying that a reversal in the coming days is still possible. The Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) is above its signal line but showing convergence. It also reflects the possibility of a downtrend occurring in the short term.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ethereum-2-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin Whale Transactions Set New 2023 High, Bullish Signal?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/litecoin-whale-transactions-2023-high-bullish/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 16:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin Bullish Signal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin Whale Transactions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin Whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc/usd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517612</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows Litecoin whale transactions have jumped to new highs for 2023 recently. Here&#8217;s how this may impact the crypto&#8217;s price. Litecoin Transactions Valued Higher Than $1 Million Have Surged According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, the last two spikes led to significant rises in the price. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;whale transaction count,&#8221; which measures the total number of Litecoin transactions taking place on the blockchain that involve coins worth at least $1 million. When the value of this metric is high, it means there are a large number of whale transactions happening on the network right now. Such a trend suggests these humongous holders are actively trading currently. As the volume of coins involved in transfers like these is very sizeable, a high amount of whale transactions can sometimes cause noticeable effects on the market. Thus, whenever the indicator&#8217;s value is high, LTC is likely to see more volatility than usual. Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Litecoin whale transaction counts over the last few months: The value of the metric seems to have been quite high in recent days &#124; Source: Santiment on Twitter As displayed in the above graph, the Litecoin whale transaction count has recently spiked and hit the highest values observed since December 28. This would suggest that whales have become active again. Related Reading: CryptoQuant’s Bitcoin PnL Index Forms Bullish Crossover In the chart, Santiment has also marked the trends that the price of LTC followed the last couple of times this cohort showed elevated activity. It looks like the most recent instance was last month when LTC&#8217;s price was observing some high volatility. Following these large number of whale transactions, Litecoin soon formed a local bottom and went on to rally around 33%. Another instance of this trend was during the collapse of the crypto exchange FTX, where once again high values of the metric accompanied significant volatility in the value of LTC. After this instance as well, the crypto enjoyed some sharp uptrend as the price rose to 37% over the next few weeks. Since the Litecoin whales are active right now, the crypto could soon witness similarly high volatility. Though, which way this volatility may ultimately take the coin&#8217;s price is uncertain, as while these whales could be buying right now (which would be bullish), they could just as well be selling with these transactions (naturally a bearish factor). Related Reading: Bitcoin Short-Term Holder Profit-Taking Spikes, Will BTC Price Recover? However, if the last two occurrences of this pattern are anything to go by, Litecoin might just go on to see runs similar to those that followed these previous instances. In some other news, the LTC mining hashrate (a measure of the total amount of computing power connected by the miners to the network) hit a new all-time high earlier today, which may also prove to be constructive for the price. Litecoin&#39;s Hashrate hit an all time high today! ⚡798.43 TH/s⚡ &#8212; Litecoin (@litecoin) January 26, 2023 LTC Price At the time of writing, Litecoin is trading around $89, up 11% in the last week. Looks like the value of the asset has gone stale in the last few days &#124; Source: LTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Santiment.net]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows Litecoin whale transactions have jumped to new highs for 2023 recently. Here&#8217;s how this may impact the crypto&#8217;s price.</p>
<h2>Litecoin Transactions Valued Higher Than $1 Million Have Surged</h2>
<p>According to data from the on-chain analytics firm <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1618453883029970945" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Santiment</a>, the last two spikes led to significant rises in the price. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;<a href="https://newsbtc.com/altcoin/quant-biggest-whale-transactions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">whale transaction count</a>,&#8221; which measures the total number of Litecoin transactions taking place on the blockchain that involve coins worth at least $1 million.</p>
<p>When the value of this metric is high, it means there are a large number of <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/dogecoin-whale-5m-doge-coinbase-bearish/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">whale</a> transactions happening on the network right now. Such a trend suggests these humongous holders are actively trading currently.</p>
<p>As the volume of coins involved in transfers like these is very sizeable, a high amount of whale transactions can sometimes cause noticeable effects on the market. Thus, whenever the indicator&#8217;s value is high, LTC is likely to see more volatility than usual.</p>
<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Litecoin whale transaction counts over the last few months:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FnXmwWUaEAIP33G?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Litecoin Whale Transactions" width="2913" height="1816" /></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the Litecoin whale transaction count has recently spiked and hit the highest values observed since December 28. This would suggest that whales have become active again.</p>

<p>In the chart, Santiment has also marked the trends that the price of LTC followed the last couple of times this cohort showed elevated activity. It looks like the most recent instance was last month when LTC&#8217;s price was observing some high <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-realized-volatility-drops-rare/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">volatility</a>.</p>
<p>Following these large number of whale transactions, Litecoin soon formed a local bottom and went on to rally around 33%. Another instance of this trend was during the collapse of the crypto exchange FTX, where once again high values of the metric accompanied significant volatility in the value of LTC. After this instance as well, the crypto enjoyed some sharp uptrend as the price rose to 37% over the next few weeks.</p>
<p>Since the Litecoin whales are active right now, the crypto could soon witness similarly high volatility. Though, which way this volatility may ultimately take the coin&#8217;s price is uncertain, as while these whales could be buying right now (which would be bullish), they could just as well be selling with these transactions (naturally a bearish factor).</p>

<p>However, if the last two occurrences of this pattern are anything to go by, Litecoin might just go on to see runs similar to those that followed these previous instances.</p>
<p>In some other news, the LTC <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-hashrate-not-out-of-the-woods/">mining hashrate</a> (a measure of the total amount of computing power connected by the miners to the network) hit a new all-time high earlier today, which may also prove to be constructive for the price.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Litecoin&#39;s Hashrate hit an all time high today!</p>
<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/26a1.png" alt="⚡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />798.43 TH/s<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/26a1.png" alt="⚡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>&mdash; Litecoin (@litecoin) <a href="https://twitter.com/litecoin/status/1618407087704510464?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 26, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<h2>LTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Litecoin is trading around $89, up 11% in the last week.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-517634 size-large aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-41-860x316.png" alt="Litecoin Price Chart" width="860" height="316" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-41-860x316.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-41-460x169.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-41-768x282.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-41-750x275.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-41.png 978w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/kanchanara-HxCc28pFRLo-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polkadot Hints At Price Recovery &#8211; Can DOT Go Past 15% Weekly Ceiling?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/polkadot-hints-price-rebound/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 16:12:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOT Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polkadot]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot Social Metrics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517635</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Polkadot (DOT) is in the green (see image below) and going steady. Could this hint at price recovery? Even though Polkadot’s funding rate plunged for a while, it is showing some improvement at the time of writing. Here&#8217;s a quick look at DOT price movement:  Polkadot price is up by 14.9% in the weekly  DOT low in market cap dominance  DOT shows a spike in development activity According to Coingecko, DOT price has skyrocketed by 4% in the last 24 hours, and trading at $6.50 as of press time. Polkadot Eco-Friendliness To Drive Positive Momentum January was phenomenal for most cryptocurrencies that are enjoying a price rally, but DOT was seen struggling and was unable to reach its pre-FTX levels.  On a positive note, DOT was the only asset that consumed the least electricity when pitted against other cryptocurrencies. This eco-friendly quality of DOT can drive positive momentum for the coin. POLKADOT &#8211; THE ECO-FRIENDLY BLOCKCHAIN Thanks to CCRI Report 2022, we found @Polkadot was ranked #2, only followed by US Household in terms of the total yearly electricity consumption 🚀 Let&#8217;s see more details below 👇#Polkadot $DOT #AVAX #ALGO #BTC #ETH #SOL #ADA pic.twitter.com/S5WxxvJSA0 — Polkadot Insider (@PolkadotInsider) January 25, 2023 Even though the weighted sentiment on Polkadot remained to be negative last December, its low electricity consumption can drive a change in public sentiment, switching it to positive which is great news for Polkadot. Image: Santiment Related Reading: Aptos (APT) Price Snowballs 147% As On-Chain Development Shoots Up The low trading volumes suggest that the bears may have the upper hand. This action has the potential to push DOT prices below the $6.154 support level, putting the brakes on the recent uptrend in DOT. DOT is predicted to spike in terms of development activity which could tick developer interest this year. In addition, DOT is said to potentially tip its pre-FTX levels in the next couple of days or weeks.   &#160; DOT total market cap at $7.3 billion on the daily chart &#124; Chart: TradingView.com In the event that this positive pattern persists, DOT&#8217;s pace of rebound is estimated to climb, which would enable bulls to charge beyond the resistance located at $6.845 and $7.235, which is the range that existed before the crypto turmoil broke out around late November. Social Metrics Up For DOT The number of people staking DOT has also increased by over 6.2% as seen in the past month which also hints at a positive streak for the asset. More so, social metrics have also increased for DOT. Social mentions spiked by 7.6% with engagements shooting over 26K. Interestingly, DOT has been increasingly popular as more people are interested in and talking about it. Polkadot social mentions. Image: LunarCrush Additionally, there are upcoming referendums in line with runtime and governance upgrades that could increase the attractiveness of the coin to investors. Meanwhile, the market sentiment enveloping DOT still has that air of uncertainty considering its shrinking market cap and high volatility. Featured image from Freepik]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Polkadot (DOT) is in the green (see image below) and going steady. Could this hint at price recovery? Even though Polkadot’s funding rate plunged for a while, it is showing some improvement at the time of writing.</p>
<p>Here&#8217;s a quick look at DOT price movement:</p>
<ul>
<li>  Polkadot price is up by 14.9% in the weekly</li>
<li>  DOT low in market cap dominance</li>
<li>  DOT shows a spike in development activity</li>
</ul>
<p>According to Coingecko, DOT price has skyrocketed by 4% in the last 24 hours, and trading at <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">$6.50</a> as of press time.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-517637 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-79.png" alt="" width="784" height="78" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-79.png 784w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-79-460x46.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-79-768x76.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-79-750x75.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 784px) 100vw, 784px" /></p>
<h2><b>Polkadot Eco-Friendliness To Drive Positive Momentum</b></h2>
<p>January was phenomenal for most cryptocurrencies that are enjoying a price rally, but DOT was seen struggling and was unable to reach its<a href="https://ambcrypto.com/polkadots-dot-recovery-is-likely-can-bulls-target-pre-ftx-levels/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> pre-FTX levels</a>. </p>
<p>On a positive note, DOT was the only asset that consumed the least electricity when pitted against other cryptocurrencies. This eco-friendly quality of DOT can drive positive momentum for the coin.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">POLKADOT &#8211; THE ECO-FRIENDLY BLOCKCHAIN</p>
<p>Thanks to CCRI Report 2022, we found <a href="https://twitter.com/Polkadot?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@Polkadot</a> was ranked #2, only followed by US Household in terms of the total yearly electricity consumption <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>Let&#8217;s see more details below <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f447.png" alt="👇" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Polkadot?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#Polkadot</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24DOT&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$DOT</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/AVAX?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#AVAX</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ALGO?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#ALGO</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BTC?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#BTC</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ETH?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#ETH</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/SOL?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#SOL</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ADA?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#ADA</a> <a href="https://t.co/S5WxxvJSA0" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/S5WxxvJSA0</a></p>
<p>— Polkadot Insider (@PolkadotInsider) <a href="https://twitter.com/PolkadotInsider/status/1618074803742687233?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 25, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Even though the weighted sentiment on Polkadot remained to be negative last December, its low electricity consumption can drive a change in public sentiment, switching it to positive which is great news for Polkadot.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-517662 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-82.png" alt="" width="666" height="223" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-82.png 666w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-82-460x154.png 460w" sizes="(max-width: 666px) 100vw, 666px" /></p>



<p>The low trading volumes suggest that the bears may have the upper hand. This action has the potential to push DOT prices below the $6.154 support level, putting the brakes on the recent uptrend in DOT.</p>
<p>DOT is predicted to spike in terms of development activity which could tick developer interest this year. In addition, DOT is said to potentially tip its pre-FTX levels in the next couple of days or weeks.  </p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/k0RzkhQ6/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>

<p>In the event that this positive pattern persists, DOT&#8217;s pace of rebound is estimated to climb, which would enable bulls to charge beyond the resistance located at $6.845 and $7.235, which is the range that existed before the crypto turmoil broke out around late November.</p>
<h2><b>Social Metrics Up For DOT</b></h2>
<p>The number of people staking DOT has also increased by over 6.2% as seen in the past month which also hints at a positive streak for the asset. More so, social metrics have also increased for DOT. </p>
<p><a href="https://lunarcrush.com/coins/dot/polkadot?metric=social_volume" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Social mentions</a> spiked by 7.6% with engagements shooting over 26K. Interestingly, DOT has been increasingly popular as more people are interested in and talking about it.</p>

<p>Additionally, there are upcoming referendums in line with runtime and <a href="https://polkadot.network/blog/gov2-polkadots-next-generation-of-decentralised-governance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">governance upgrades</a> that could increase the attractiveness of the coin to investors.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the market sentiment enveloping DOT still has that air of uncertainty considering its shrinking market cap and high volatility.</p>
<p><em>Featured image from Freepik</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-84-460x315.png" width="460" height="315" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Continues To Shine With 15% Gains In the Last Week</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-shines-with-13-gains/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jammy Hunts]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 15:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[adausd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517626</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cardano’s native coin ADA has seen many rallies since the start of this year. The token owes its performance to the improving economic condition in the market and the ongoing developments on the Cardano Network. Over the past seven days, ADA has observed more than a 15% price gain in 7 days and an over 17% 14-day gain. But what are the possible reasons for ADA&#8217;s impressive performance? Related Reading: CryptoQuant’s Bitcoin PnL Index Forms Bullish Crossover What Is Contributing To ADA’s Price Rally? The hype around the upcoming Djed stablecoin launch, among others, has played a part in driving ADA price up over the past weeks in January. According to COTI developers, the network behind the Djed stablecoins, ADA holders would receive extra rewards when they mint Djed by staking their ADA coins. This information might spur users to buy more ADA and could further push the coin price. Also, the Cardano community is anticipating upcoming launches that would enhance the network and Smart Contract capabilities. Furthermore, Cardano has received a new improvement proposal known as CIP-30. This improvement proposal would allow the integration of web-based wallet bridges that would promote interaction between Cardano wallets and Web2 platforms like Amazon. It would allow ADA more use cases and adoptions and ensure increased growth for Cardano, positioning it to meet more market needs. This development could be among the factors fuelling ADA&#8217;s price gain.  Another new development on the Cardano network that might be fuelling the ADA price rally is the eTukTuk automotive project launch. According to the announcement, the Cardano blockchain would be hosting the project.  The project allows users to earn rewards using the eTukTuk electric vehicle charging infrastructure. Users can access the service using TUK, eTukTuk native token, but they need to hold ADA since the project anchors on Cardano. That also could be boosting ADA prices upward. ADA Price Outlook The Cardano cryptocurrency, ADA, has gained over 6% in the last 24 hours. ADA hit an eleven-week high of $0.384 on January 22 before taking a hit over the past 48 hours. Its price dropped 6.4% on the day while retracing its support levels. However, ADA is currently trading at $0.3833 with a 24-hour high of $0.3866 and a low of $0.354580 after declining over the last six hours. The reversal could present a chance for the bulls to accumulate tokens in anticipation of Djed launch, which might push the ADA price forward. From the technical view, ADA is showing a buy signal. The oscillators fluctuate between neutral and buy, and the Moving Averages show a strong buy signal. The token&#8217;s price is currently hovering at $0.3833, representing a 6.43 % increase in its value in 24 hours. It has broken above its 50-day Simple Moving Average, indicating a short-term bullish sentiment for Cardano. However, it is below its 200-day SMA, meaning the asset price can become bearish in the coming weeks. The current support levels are $0.324253, $0.335986, and $0.354289, while the resistance levels are $0.384326, $0.396059, and $0.414363. ADA will likely not surpass the $0.384326 level in the coming days since the bears are sustaining their charge. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) is at 68.39, close to the overbought zone. However, a retracement can occur anytime soon. The Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) is above its signal line but shows convergence, which is a bearish signal. Expect the price of ADA to record slight gains before retracing to the $0.36 price level in the coming days. Related Reading: Aptos (APT) Price Snowballs 147% As On-Chain Development Shoots Up But note that altcoins are volatile and sometimes deviate from predicted trends. Also, an altcoin that loses half its value (50%) must rally to (100%) to return to its original value. Traders with risk management techniques for volatile markets can utilize the opportunities to profit. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cardano’s native coin ADA has seen many rallies since the start of this year. The token owes its performance to the improving economic condition in the market and the ongoing developments on the Cardano Network.</p>
<p>Over the past seven days, ADA has observed more than a <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/cardano" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">15% price gain</a> in 7 days and an over 17% 14-day gain. But what are the possible reasons for ADA&#8217;s impressive performance?</p>

<h2><b>What Is Contributing To ADA’s Price Rally?</b></h2>
<p>The hype around the upcoming <a href="https://twitter.com/COTInetwork/status/1617952207357509632" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Djed stablecoin launch</a>, among others, has played a part in driving ADA price up over the past weeks in January. According to COTI developers, the network behind the Djed stablecoins, ADA holders would receive extra rewards when they mint Djed by staking their ADA coins. This information might spur users to buy more ADA and could further push the coin price.</p>
<p>Also, the Cardano community is anticipating upcoming launches that would enhance the network and Smart Contract capabilities. Furthermore, Cardano has received a new improvement proposal known as <a href="https://cips.cardano.org/cips/cip30/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CIP-30</a>. This improvement proposal would allow the integration of web-based wallet bridges that would promote interaction between Cardano wallets and Web2 platforms like Amazon.</p>
<p>It would allow ADA more use cases and adoptions and ensure increased growth for Cardano, positioning it to meet more market needs. This development could be among the factors fuelling ADA&#8217;s price gain. </p>
<p>Another new development on the Cardano network that might be fuelling the ADA price rally is the <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/feed/post/176803" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">eTukTuk automotive project launch</a>. According to <a href="https://mobile.twitter.com/etuktukio" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">the announcement</a>, the Cardano blockchain would be hosting the project. </p>
<p>The project allows users to earn rewards using the eTukTuk electric vehicle charging infrastructure. Users can access the service using TUK, eTukTuk native token, but they need to hold ADA since the project anchors on Cardano. That also could be boosting ADA prices upward.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-517630" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSD_2023-01-26_18-57-08.png" alt="ADAUSD" width="856" height="538" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSD_2023-01-26_18-57-08.png 856w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSD_2023-01-26_18-57-08-460x289.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSD_2023-01-26_18-57-08-768x483.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSD_2023-01-26_18-57-08-750x471.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 856px) 100vw, 856px" />
<b>ADA Price Outlook</b>
<p>The Cardano cryptocurrency, ADA, has gained over 6% in the last 24 hours. ADA hit an eleven-week high of $0.384 on January 22 before taking a hit over the past 48 hours. Its price dropped 6.4% on the day while retracing its support levels.</p>
<p>However, ADA is currently trading at $0.3833 with a 24-hour high of $0.3866 and a low of $0.354580 after declining over the last six hours. The reversal could present a chance for the bulls to accumulate tokens in anticipation of Djed launch, which might push the ADA price forward.</p>
<p>From the technical view, ADA is showing a buy signal. The oscillators fluctuate between neutral and buy, and the Moving Averages show a strong buy signal.</p>
<p>The token&#8217;s price is currently hovering <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/cardano" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">at $0.3833</a>, representing a 6.43 % increase in its value in 24 hours. It has broken above its 50-day Simple Moving Average, indicating a short-term bullish sentiment for Cardano. However, it is below its 200-day SMA, meaning the asset price can become bearish in the coming weeks.</p>
<p>The current support levels are $0.324253, $0.335986, and $0.354289, while the resistance levels are $0.384326, $0.396059, and $0.414363. ADA will likely not surpass the $0.384326 level in the coming days since the bears are sustaining their charge.</p>
<p>The Relative Strength Index (RSI) is at 68.39, close to the overbought zone. However, a retracement can occur anytime soon. The Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) is above its signal line but shows convergence, which is a bearish signal. Expect the price of ADA to record slight gains before retracing to the $0.36 price level in the coming days.</p>

<p>But note that altcoins are volatile and sometimes deviate from predicted trends. Also, an altcoin that loses half its value (50%) must rally to (100%) to return to its original value. Traders with risk management techniques for volatile markets can utilize the opportunities to profit.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/cardano-4-460x307.png" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Is How The Bitcoin Price Will Be Affected By Macro: Charles Edwards</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-price-affected-by-macro-edwards/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 14:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charles Edwards]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macro]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517606</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a new interview, Charles Edwards of Capriole Investments shared his Bitcoin theses for 2023. Looking back at the past few months, the renowned expert said those have put the market in a position where Bitcoin offers &#8220;a great position for long-term investors.&#8221; As Edwards noted, almost every sentiment metric imaginable fell into the &#8220;biggest or second-biggest bearish&#8221; range in macro, equities, and crypto. &#8220;Pretty much anyone would have said on Twitter last year that we are in a recession or it&#8217;s coming to a recession,&#8221; the analyst continued. While Edwards acknowledged that the risk of a recession is far from gone, many key metrics have come back quite a bit. Among them is the housing market, which is slowing and often leads the overall economy. &#8220;So there are a number of metrics which suggest things are slowing down a bit. You got all the big tech names laying off employees and you see this in crypto as well. 10% to 20% cuts have not been unusual in the last months,&#8221; the founder of Capriole Investments asserted. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Resumes Increase as The Bulls Aim Larger Rally To $25K Furthermore, he pointed out an interesting fact: every time inflation peaked above 5% and then fell by more than 20%, the U.S. central bank pivoted. This observation holds true for the last 60 years. &#8220;So I think there is a high probability the Fed stops raising rates or reducing rates,&#8221; Edwards concluded and further said: And then we have this deep value situation in crypto which has been playing out the last 3 or 4 months. [&#8230;] And all that sets up a great opportunity for long-term investors in crypto and equities, as well, risk assets in general. Fed Pivot Will Propel Bitcoin Upwards Within 6 Months In general, it is difficult to predict when there will be a regime change at the Fed. However, Edwards believes it will happen within the next 3-6 months. After the forced liquidations in the Bitcoin market over the past 12 months, there is currently no longer any significant selling pressure. Therefore, according to the Capriole Investments founder, there will be a liquidity crisis on the sell side once larger amounts of Bitcoin buyers return to the market, leading to a squeeze to the upside. &#8220;And we saw that kind of short-squeeze play out in the first weeks of January.&#8221; As for the Fed pivot, investors should keep an eye on specific data. While the consensus now seems to be that the Fed will change monetary policy, there are still some risks. Edwards pointed to history in this regard, warning that inflation could rise again. In the 1970s inflation went through a roller coaster ride and that could be the case for the next 5 to 10 years as well. But I do think the base case for me is at least a rate pause this year, at some point in the coming months. Related Reading: Banking Giant Goldman Sachs Ranks Bitcoin As World Best Performing Asset Moreover, investors should be cautious when employment remains very high. This is &#8220;probably the single most important factor leading to recessions.&#8221; While this data point is still incredibly strong currently, it could change &#8220;any month now&#8221; given the layoffs in the big tech sector, according to Edwards. Equities are also worth considering, he said. If they hit new highs, or if earnings are very strong, if manufacturing picks up and inflation is still at 5% to 6%, then the Fed might think it can keep going because everything is still fine. However, Edwards&#8217;s base case looks different: I think 2023 will generally be a positive year because the Bitcoin price will probably be higher at the end of the year [&#8230;], but there will be a lot of volatility. At press time, Bitcoin traded at $23.115. Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a new interview, Charles Edwards of Capriole Investments shared his Bitcoin theses for 2023. Looking back at the past few months, the renowned expert said those have put the market in a position where Bitcoin offers &#8220;a great position for long-term investors.&#8221;</p>
<p>As Edwards <a href="https://youtu.be/xHREec9gVR4" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">noted</a>, almost every sentiment metric imaginable fell into the &#8220;biggest or second-biggest bearish&#8221; range in macro, equities, and crypto. &#8220;Pretty much anyone would have said on Twitter last year that we are in a recession or it&#8217;s coming to a recession,&#8221; the analyst continued.</p>
<p>While Edwards acknowledged that the risk of a recession is far from gone, many key metrics have come back quite a bit. Among them is the housing market, which is slowing and often leads the overall economy.</p>
<p>&#8220;So there are a number of metrics which suggest things are slowing down a bit. You got all the big tech names laying off employees and you see this in crypto as well. 10% to 20% cuts have not been unusual in the last months,&#8221; the founder of Capriole Investments asserted.</p>

<p>Furthermore, he pointed out an interesting fact: every time inflation peaked above 5% and then fell by more than 20%, the U.S. central bank pivoted. This observation holds true for the last 60 years. &#8220;So I think there is a high probability the Fed stops raising rates or reducing rates,&#8221; Edwards concluded and further said:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>And then we have this deep value situation in crypto which has been playing out the last 3 or 4 months. [&#8230;] And all that sets up a great opportunity for long-term investors in crypto and equities, as well, risk assets in general.</strong></p></blockquote>
<h2>Fed Pivot Will Propel Bitcoin Upwards Within 6 Months</h2>
<p>In general, it is difficult to predict when there will be a regime change at the Fed. However, Edwards believes it will happen within the next 3-6 months. After the forced liquidations in the Bitcoin market over the past 12 months, there is currently no longer any significant selling pressure.</p>
<p>Therefore, according to the Capriole Investments founder, there will be a liquidity crisis on the sell side once larger amounts of Bitcoin buyers return to the market, leading to a squeeze to the upside. &#8220;And we saw that kind of short-squeeze play out in the first weeks of January.&#8221;</p>
<p>As for the Fed pivot, investors should keep an eye on specific data. While the consensus now seems to be that the Fed will change monetary policy, there are still some risks. Edwards pointed to history in this regard, warning that inflation could rise again.</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>In the 1970s inflation went through a roller coaster ride and that could be the case for the next 5 to 10 years as well. But I do think the base case for me is at least a rate pause this year, at some point in the coming months.</strong></p></blockquote>

<p>Moreover, investors should be cautious when employment remains very high. This is &#8220;probably the single most important factor leading to recessions.&#8221; While this data point is still incredibly strong currently, it could change &#8220;any month now&#8221; given the layoffs in the big tech sector, according to Edwards.</p>
<p>Equities are also worth considering, he said. If they hit new highs, or if earnings are very strong, if manufacturing picks up and inflation is still at 5% to 6%, then the Fed might think it can keep going because everything is still fine. However, Edwards&#8217;s base case looks different:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>I think 2023 will generally be a positive year because the Bitcoin price will probably be higher at the end of the year [&#8230;], but there will be a lot of volatility.</strong></p></blockquote>
<p>At press time, Bitcoin traded at $23.115.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-517615 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-26_14-05-39.png" alt="Bitcoin price BTC USD" width="2962" height="1605" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-26_14-05-39.png 2962w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-26_14-05-39-460x249.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-26_14-05-39-860x466.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-26_14-05-39-768x416.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-26_14-05-39-1536x832.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-26_14-05-39-2048x1110.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-26_14-05-39-750x406.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-26_14-05-39-1140x618.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2962px) 100vw, 2962px" />

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/iStock-1314199360-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>CryptoQuant&#8217;s Bitcoin PnL Index Forms Bullish Crossover</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/cryptoquant-bitcoin-pnl-bullish-crossover/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 13:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bullish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bullish Crossover]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin PnL Index]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptoquant]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CryptoQuant PnL Index]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=517596</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CryptoQuant&#8217;s Bitcoin on-chain PnL index has surged above its 365-day MA recently, a crossover that has historically signaled early bull markets. Bitcoin On-Chain PnL Index Has Formed A Bullish Crossover As per data from the on-chain analytics firm CryptoQuant, the index is indicating a buy signal for BTC right now. The &#8220;CryptoQuant on-chain PnL index&#8221; is a metric that combines three different indicators into one to point out tops, bottoms, and cyclical shifts in the price of Bitcoin. The first of the metrics that the PnL index uses is the &#8220;MVRV ratio,&#8221; which is a model that checks whether BTC is currently overvalued or undervalued by comparing the crypto&#8217;s market cap with a fair value model called the &#8220;realized cap.&#8221; The second relevant indicator here is the &#8220;NUPL,&#8221; which tells us whether the Bitcoin market as a whole is currently carrying an unrealized profit or an unrealized loss. This metric can provide hints about whether there is a buying or selling motive among investors right now. Finally, there is the Spent Output Profit Ratio (SOPR), which tracks whether the average holder is selling at a loss or a profit at the moment. The SOPR shouldn&#8217;t be confused with the NUPL, as the quantity being measured by the NUPL is the &#8220;unrealized&#8221; profit/loss, which is the profit or loss that investors have accumulated but are yet to harvest (or &#8220;realize&#8221;) as they are still to sell their coins. There are actually two SOPR metrics of interest here; the version specifically for the short-term holders (STHs) and that for the long-term holders (LTHs). The entire Bitcoin market can be divided into these two groups, with the criteria being that holders who bought within the last 155 days fall into the former cohort, while those who bought before that fall into the latter. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Declines 6%, Gets Flipped By Litecoin In Market Cap Again Now, here is the data for the CryptoQuant on-chain PnL index, which takes all these different Bitcoin indicators and combines them into one model for the crypto: Looks like the value of the metric has shot up &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As displayed in the above graph, the CryptoQuant on-chain PnL index has sharply risen out of the historical bottom zone recently. The chart also includes the curve for the 365-day moving average (MA) of the metric, and it&#8217;s clear that the index has crossed above this MA with the latest surge. Historically, such a crossover during bearish periods has signaled a transition toward an early bull market. If this pattern holds true this time as well, then the current breakout could be good news for the ongoing rally. Related Reading: Bitcoin Short-Term Holder Profit-Taking Spikes, Will BTC Price Recover? However, back in 2015, an initial breakout like the current one did end up failing, and it was only later that a successful transition took place. Nonetheless, CryptoQuant notes &#8220;although it is still possible for the index to fall back below, the CryptoQuant PnL Index has issued a definitive buy signal for BTC.&#8221; BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $22,900, up 11% in the last week. BTC seems to be showing stale price action &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Hans Eiskonen on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CryptoQuant&#8217;s Bitcoin on-chain PnL index has surged above its 365-day MA recently, a crossover that has historically signaled early bull markets.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin On-Chain PnL Index Has Formed A Bullish Crossover</h2>
<p>As per data from the on-chain analytics firm <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/quicktake/63d185c7a01cee57d52ca5e2-CryptoQuant-PnL-Index-Confirms-Ealy-Bull-Market-For-Now" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CryptoQuant</a>, the index is indicating a buy signal for BTC right now. The &#8220;CryptoQuant on-chain PnL index&#8221; is a metric that combines three different indicators into one to point out tops, bottoms, and cyclical shifts in the price of Bitcoin.</p>
<p>The first of the metrics that the PnL index uses is the &#8220;<a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-mvrv-ratio-falls-to-3-year-lows/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MVRV ratio</a>,&#8221; which is a model that checks whether BTC is currently overvalued or undervalued by comparing the crypto&#8217;s market cap with a fair value model called the &#8220;<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-long-term-holders-own-80-realized-cap/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">realized cap</a>.&#8221;</p>
<p>The second relevant indicator here is the &#8220;<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/quant-explains-bitcoin-nupl-cycles-less-volatile/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NUPL</a>,&#8221; which tells us whether the Bitcoin market as a whole is currently carrying an unrealized profit or an unrealized loss. This metric can provide hints about whether there is a buying or selling motive among investors right now.</p>
<p>Finally, there is the Spent Output Profit Ratio (SOPR), which tracks whether the average holder is selling at a loss or a profit at the moment. The SOPR shouldn&#8217;t be confused with the NUPL, as the quantity being measured by the NUPL is the &#8220;unrealized&#8221; profit/loss, which is the profit or loss that investors have accumulated but are yet to harvest (or &#8220;realize&#8221;) as they are still to sell their coins.</p>
<p>There are actually two SOPR metrics of interest here; the version specifically for the short-term holders (STHs) and that for the long-term holders (LTHs). The entire Bitcoin market can be divided into these two groups, with the criteria being that holders who bought within the last 155 days fall into the former cohort, while those who bought before that fall into the latter.</p>

<p>Now, here is the data for the CryptoQuant on-chain PnL index, which takes all these different Bitcoin indicators and combines them into one model for the crypto:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/4/quicktake/XMy6I_57c9dd595beaaa82db12355725a83bfab6d66b11d518476d9793796e54289ec2.png" alt="Bitcoin CryptoQuant PnL Index" width="1090" height="537" /></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the CryptoQuant on-chain PnL index has sharply risen out of the historical bottom zone recently. The chart also includes the curve for the 365-day moving average (MA) of the metric, and it&#8217;s clear that the index has crossed above this MA with the latest surge.</p>
<p>Historically, such a crossover during bearish periods has signaled a transition toward an early bull market. If this pattern holds true this time as well, then the current breakout could be good news for the ongoing rally.</p>

<p>However, back in 2015, an initial breakout like the current one did end up failing, and it was only later that a successful transition took place. Nonetheless, CryptoQuant notes &#8220;although it is still possible for the index to fall back below, the CryptoQuant PnL Index has issued a definitive buy signal for BTC.&#8221;</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $22,900, up 11% in the last week.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-517608 size-large aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-40-860x315.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="860" height="315" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-40-860x315.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-40-460x169.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-40-768x281.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-40-750x275.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-40.png 980w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/hans-eiskonen-wn57cSQ7VzI-unsplash-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/

Object Caching 227/230 objects using apc
Page Caching using disk: enhanced (Page is feed) 
Database Caching 22/45 queries in 0.009 seconds using memcached

Served from: newsbtc.com @ 2023-01-26 22:13:32 by W3 Total Cache
-->