<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 01:58:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Kava (KAVA) Price Rallies 10% In 7 Days &#8211; Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/kava-kava-price-rallies-10-in-7-days-heres-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olowoporoku Adeniyi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 02:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kava]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kava analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kava price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535272</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[KAVA, the native token associated with the Kava platform, has experienced a whirlwind week regarding its price swing. The token, which began the week trading around $1.03, surged to $1.23 on May 23, driven by positive news within its ecosystem.  However, the bull momentum was short-lived, with the token recently experiencing a significant price correction. Nevertheless, at the time of writing, KAVA is up 10% and is one of the top gainers in the crypto market within this period.  What’s Behind The Recent Spike In Kava? However, it is important to analyze the factors behind this rally to assess its sustainability. Cryptocurrencies are known for their price volatility, and sudden reversals are not uncommon. In the case of KAVA, the token experienced a swift downturn following the initial surge, raising concerns about the solidity of the upward movement.  Related Reading: Bullish Case For Litecoin Grows Stronger As LTC Halving Draws Close This pattern is often observed when a rapid rise lacks strong fundamental support, leading to a correction as the market adjusts itself. In terms of recent developments, it was reported that the Digital Asset Exchange Association (DAXA) in South Korea removed investment warnings on KAVA and WAVES, the latter being another digital asset associated with the Waves platform.  The warnings had been issued due to concerns about stablecoins linked to these assets, which were found to be &#8220;not normally linked to 1 dollar”. However, after a thorough review, DAXA determined that the risks associated with KAVA and WAVES had been resolved, allowing South Korean exchanges to resume deposit services for these tokens. This news likely contributed to the positive sentiment surrounding KAVA and may have played a role in the recent price rally. In addition, the launch of the Kava 13 mainnet and the introduction of GameFi (Game Finance) and non-fungible tokens (NFTs) to the Kava ecosystem have also contributed to the positive momentum for the KAVA token. These developments have attracted attention and interest from users, investors, and traders, potentially driving the token&#8217;s price higher. What’s Next For KAVA? The price surge experienced by KAVA stands out as an outlier within the broader context of the cryptocurrency market. Considering the overall outlook, such gains may not be sustainable, and a subsequent correction could erase the entirety of the upward movement. Related Reading: Upcoming Interest Rate Hikes Could Be The Next Big Challenge For Bitcoin, Here’s Why If the current levels near $1.20 fail to provide sufficient support, KAVA/USD might retreat towards the support level at $1.10 or even lower. However, on the other hand, if there is an overall uptick in the market sentiment or if there is fresh, positive news specific to KAVA, it could potentially lead to renewed buying interest and push the price toward a retest of the recent highs. At press time, KAVA sells at $1.134 per token with a slight 0.9% 24-hour increase. -Featured image from Kava.io, charts from tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>KAVA, the native token associated with the Kava platform, has experienced a whirlwind week regarding its price swing. The token, which began the week trading around $1.03, surged to $1.23 on May 23, driven by positive news within its ecosystem. </p>
<p>However, the bull momentum was short-lived, with the token recently experiencing a significant price correction. Nevertheless, at the time of writing, KAVA is up 10% and is one of the top gainers in the crypto market within this period. </p>
<img decoding="async" class="size-medium wp-image-535274" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-40-21-460x254.png" alt="Kava has experienced a significant price correction this week; source @tradingview" width="460" height="254" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-40-21-460x254.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-40-21-860x474.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-40-21-768x424.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-40-21-750x414.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-40-21-1140x629.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-40-21.png 1479w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" loading="lazy"/>
<h2>What’s Behind The Recent Spike In Kava?</h2>
<p>However, it is important to analyze the factors behind this rally to assess its sustainability. Cryptocurrencies are known for their price volatility, and sudden reversals are not uncommon. In the case of KAVA, the token experienced a swift downturn following the initial surge, raising concerns about the solidity of the upward movement. </p>
<p><b>Related Reading:</b> <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/ltc/bullish-case-for-litecoin-grows-stronger-as-ltc-halving-draws-close/">Bullish Case For Litecoin Grows Stronger As LTC Halving Draws Close</a></p>
<p>This pattern is often observed when a rapid rise lacks strong fundamental support, leading to a correction as the market adjusts itself. In terms of recent developments, it was reported that the Digital Asset Exchange Association (DAXA) in South Korea removed investment warnings on KAVA and WAVES, the latter being another digital asset associated with the Waves platform. </p>
<p>The warnings had been issued due to concerns about stablecoins linked to these assets, which were found to be &#8220;not normally linked to 1 dollar”. However, after a thorough review, DAXA determined that the risks associated with KAVA and WAVES had been resolved, allowing South Korean exchanges to resume deposit services for these tokens. This news likely contributed to the positive sentiment surrounding KAVA and may have played a role in the recent price rally.</p>
<p>In addition, the launch of the Kava 13 mainnet and the introduction of GameFi (Game Finance) and non-fungible tokens (NFTs) to the Kava ecosystem have also contributed to the positive momentum for the KAVA token. These developments have attracted attention and interest from users, investors, and traders, potentially driving the token&#8217;s price higher.</p>
<h2>What’s Next For KAVA?</h2>
<p>The price surge experienced by KAVA stands out as an outlier within the broader context of the cryptocurrency market. Considering the overall outlook, such gains may not be sustainable, and a subsequent correction could erase the entirety of the upward movement.</p>
<p><b>Related Reading:</b> <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/upcoming-interest-rate-hikes-could-be-the-next-big-challenge-for-bitcoin-heres-why/">Upcoming Interest Rate Hikes Could Be The Next Big Challenge For Bitcoin, Here’s Why</a></p>
<p>If the current levels near $1.20 fail to provide sufficient support, KAVA/USD might retreat towards the support level at $1.10 or even lower.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-535275 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-52-29-860x432.png" alt="Kava currently trading below the $1.20 resistance mark: source @tradingview" width="860" height="432" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-52-29-860x432.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-52-29-460x231.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-52-29-768x386.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-52-29-360x180.png 360w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-52-29-750x377.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-52-29-1140x573.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/KAVAUSDT_2023-05-27_15-52-29.png 1479w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>However, on the other hand, if there is an overall uptick in the market sentiment or if there is fresh, positive news specific to KAVA, it could potentially lead to renewed buying interest and push the price toward a retest of the recent highs. At press time, KAVA sells at $1.134 per token with a slight 0.9% 24-hour increase.</p>
<p><em>-Featured image from Kava.io, charts from tradingview.com</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/kava-1140x641-1-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Revisits $0.47 &#8211; What Can Be Expected For Short-Term Price Movement?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-revisits-0-47-what-can-be-expected-for-short-term-price-movement/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 01:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535287</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[XRP has shown recent gains on its price chart, allowing the altcoin to surpass a significant resistance level. Although the 1% increase over the past 24 hours may not be substantial, it has helped maintain bullish momentum. However, on a weekly chart, XRP has experienced minimal movement. Despite this, the technical outlook for the coin indicates bullish strength in the market. Buying strength has risen, and both demand and accumulation have turned positive, contributing to this technical outlook. The performance of XRP on its chart may be influenced by the movement of Bitcoin. Related Reading: Bullish Case For Litecoin Grows Stronger As LTC Halving Draws Close If Bitcoin continues to appreciate and reaches the $27,000 range, XRP may attempt to break through its immediate resistance. With buying strength recovering and demand potentially supporting the bulls, their position in the market could strengthen. However, if the price remains stagnant at its current level, demand might start to decline, causing the bulls to lose momentum. The increase in the altcoin&#8217;s market capitalization over the past 24 hours suggests that buyers have gained control over sellers. XRP Price Analysis: One-Day Chart At the time of writing, XRP was trading at $0.47. In recent trading sessions, the altcoin successfully surpassed the resistance level of $0.45. Sustaining this positive momentum, the next resistance level for XRP is expected to be at $0.48. If this level is cleared, it could fuel a rally towards the $0.50 mark. However, if the price retreats from its current level, it may invite bearish pressure, potentially causing the price to settle around $0.43. Notably, the volume of XRP traded in the last session was relatively high, indicating a lower selling strength in the market. Technical Analysis During the recent trading sessions, the altcoin not only made progress in its price movement but also saw a notable recovery in buying strength. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) being above the half-line suggests that buyers have taken control of the price action in the market. Additionally, XRP moved above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, indicating that buyers were driving the price momentum. This shift in momentum was supported by an increased demand for XRP in the market. In line with other technical indicators, the altcoin has started to exhibit buy signals on the chart. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD), a tool used to assess price momentum and potential reversals, displayed green histograms associated with buy signals. This suggests that there is a possibility of the altcoin attempting to break through its overhead resistance level. Related Reading: When Is A Token Coming For Coinbase’s Base L2? Here’s What The Roadmap Says Furthermore, the Bollinger Bands, which indicate price volatility and fluctuations, remained parallel and wide. This indicates that the XRP price action is not expected to be constricted or range-bound. The upper band of the Bollinger Bands intersected at $0.48, highlighting this level as an important resistance level or price ceiling for the altcoin to overcome. -Featured Image From iStock, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>XRP has shown recent gains on its price chart, allowing the altcoin to surpass a significant resistance level. Although the 1% increase over the past 24 hours may not be substantial, it has helped maintain bullish momentum. However, on a weekly chart, XRP has experienced minimal movement.</p>
<p>Despite this, the technical outlook for the coin indicates bullish strength in the market. Buying strength has risen, and both demand and accumulation have turned positive, contributing to this technical outlook. The performance of XRP on its chart may be influenced by the movement of Bitcoin.</p>

<p>If Bitcoin continues to appreciate and reaches the $27,000 range, XRP may attempt to break through its immediate resistance. With buying strength recovering and demand potentially supporting the bulls, their position in the market could strengthen.</p>
<p>However, if the price remains stagnant at its current level, demand might start to decline, causing the bulls to lose momentum. The increase in the altcoin&#8217;s market capitalization over the past 24 hours suggests that buyers have gained control over sellers.</p>
<h2>XRP Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-535291 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-04.png" alt="XRP" width="1816" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-04.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-04-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-04-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-04-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-04-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-04-750x343.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-04-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>






<p>At the time of writing, XRP was trading at $0.47. In recent trading sessions, the altcoin successfully surpassed the resistance level of $0.45. Sustaining this positive momentum, the next resistance level for XRP is expected to be at $0.48.</p>
<p>If this level is cleared, it could fuel a rally towards the $0.50 mark. However, if the price retreats from its current level, it may invite bearish pressure, potentially causing the price to settle around $0.43.</p>
<p>Notably, the volume of XRP traded in the last session was relatively high, indicating a lower selling strength in the market.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-535292 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-41.png" alt="" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-41.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-41-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-41-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-41-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-41-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-41-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-51-41-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>
<p>During the recent trading sessions, the altcoin not only made progress in its price movement but also saw a notable recovery in buying strength. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) being above the half-line suggests that buyers have taken control of the price action in the market.</p>
<p>Additionally, XRP moved above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, indicating that buyers were driving the price momentum. This shift in momentum was supported by an increased demand for XRP in the market.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-535293 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-52-05.png" alt="XRP" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-52-05.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-52-05-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-52-05-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-52-05-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-52-05-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-52-05-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSD_2023-05-28_01-52-05-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>In line with other technical indicators, the altcoin has started to exhibit buy signals on the chart. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD), a tool used to assess price momentum and potential reversals, displayed green histograms associated with buy signals. This suggests that there is a possibility of the altcoin attempting to break through its overhead resistance level.</p>

<p>Furthermore, the Bollinger Bands, which indicate price volatility and fluctuations, remained parallel and wide. This indicates that the XRP price action is not expected to be constricted or range-bound.</p>
<p>The upper band of the Bollinger Bands intersected at $0.48, highlighting this level as an important resistance level or price ceiling for the altcoin to overcome.</p>







]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/istockphoto-1323355582-612x612-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Whales Flock To XRP, Accumulate 52 Million Tokens In Just 3 Weeks &#8211; Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/whales-flock-to-xrp-accumulating-52-million-tokens/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 01:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535286</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the world of crypto, the actions of large investors, known as whales, can often provide valuable insights into the market sentiment surrounding a particular digital asset. Recent data has revealed a common trend in the XRP market, as whales have been actively accumulating millions of tokens over a short period, particularly in the last three weeks. This surge in whale activity has sparked intrigue and speculation among crypto enthusiasts, suggesting a strong bullish sentiment toward Ripple&#8217;s remittance token. Whales Show Bullishness On XRP According to data shared by renowned crypto analyst Ali on Twitter, whales are making significant moves in the XRP market. Utilizing behavior analytics resource Santiment&#8217;s data, Ali highlighted the noteworthy accumulation of XRP by whales, which indicates their strong belief in the future prospects of the token. Related Reading: XRP Emerges As Top Performing Crypto With 55% Surge – Messari Report Over the past three weeks alone, these prominent investors have acquired 52 million XRP, representing an estimated value of over $22 million. Notably, the accumulation trend has been primarily observed among XRP whales, specifically addresses holding 10 million to 100 million XRP. This period of intense accumulation began on May 7, following a notable selloff pressure that occurred on April 12. During the selloff phase, Ripple&#8217;s token experienced a prolonged consolidation period, stemming from the temporary exhaustion of the rally before the latest move. However, the selloff eventually subsided, paving the way for the current accumulation trend witnessed among whales. What Drives The Accumulation  The sudden surge in XRP accumulation by whales has raised questions about what factors could be driving this bullish sentiment. While individual motivations may vary, several plausible explanations shed light on the underlying dynamics at play. One significant factor could be the anticipation of positive developments within the Ripple ecosystem, such as new partnerships or advancements in the adoption of Ripple&#8217;s token for cross-border transactions.  Last month, Ripple (XRP), Cardano (ADA), and several other cryptocurrencies received an adoption boost through a recently announced partnership between Binance Pay and CoinGate. This collaboration enables users of Binance Pay to make crypto payments to merchants powered by CoinGate. In turn, CoinGate merchants can facilitate Binance Pay payments during the checkout process. This new feature, which will be automatically activated, caters to various digital assets available on the Binance Pay platform, including Ripple (XRP), Cardano (ADA), and many others. Notably, such developments often drive demand for Ripple&#8217;s token, prompting investors to accumulate the token in anticipation of future price appreciation. Furthermore, the recent regulatory clarity surrounding Ripple&#8217;s legal battle with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) may have also contributed to the increased confidence among whales. Related Reading: XRP Bears Prevail As Asset Retreats From Recent Highs As Ripple continues to make progress in the legal proceedings, the resolution of the case could potentially remove a major overhang on XRP&#8217;s market sentiment, paving the way for renewed optimism and investment. Meanwhile, following the accumulation of whales, XRP has shown an upcoming uptick. Over the past 24 hours, Ripple&#8217;s token has seen a 1% gain. The asset currently trades at $0.47, at the time of writing. -Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the world of crypto, the actions of large investors, known as whales, can often provide valuable insights into the market sentiment surrounding a particular digital asset. Recent <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1662215112659456000?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a> has revealed a common trend in the XRP market, as whales have been actively accumulating millions of tokens over a short period, particularly in the last three weeks. </p>
<p>This surge in whale activity has sparked intrigue and speculation among crypto enthusiasts, suggesting a strong bullish sentiment toward <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-emerges-as-top-performing-crypto-with-55-surge-messari-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ripple&#8217;s remittance token</a>.</p>
<h2>Whales Show Bullishness On XRP</h2>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">According to data shared by renowned crypto analyst Ali on Twitter, whales are making significant moves in the XRP market. Utilizing behavior analytics resource Santiment&#8217;s data, Ali highlighted the noteworthy accumulation of XRP by whales, which indicates their strong belief in the future prospects of the token.</p>

<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Over the past three weeks alone, these prominent investors have acquired 52 million XRP, representing an estimated value of over $22 million.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Notably, the accumulation trend has been primarily observed among XRP whales, specifically addresses holding 10 million to 100 million XRP. This period of intense accumulation began on May 7, following a notable selloff pressure that occurred on April 12. </p>
<p dir="ltr">During the selloff phase, Ripple&#8217;s token experienced a prolonged consolidation period, stemming from the temporary exhaustion of the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-ledger-on-fire-daily-transactions-skyrocket-10-7-in-q1-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">rally</a> before the latest move. However, the selloff eventually subsided, paving the way for the current accumulation trend witnessed among whales.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What Drives The Accumulation </h2>
<p>The sudden surge in XRP accumulation by whales has raised questions about what factors could be driving this bullish sentiment. While individual motivations may vary, several plausible explanations shed light on the underlying dynamics at play. </p>
<p>One significant factor could be the anticipation of positive <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ripple/ripple-xrp-legal-defender-lauds-judge-torres-ruling-as-a-victory-for-the-people/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">developments</a> within the Ripple ecosystem, such as new partnerships or advancements in the adoption of Ripple&#8217;s token for cross-border transactions. </p>
<p>Last month, Ripple (XRP), Cardano (ADA), and several other cryptocurrencies received an adoption boost through a recently <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/payment/binance-pay-is-even-more-versatile-thanks-to-our-coingate-partnership-3983097682377001190#:~:text=What%20Does%20the%20New%20Partnership,the%20service%20on%20and%20off." target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced</a> partnership between Binance Pay and CoinGate. This collaboration enables users of Binance Pay to make crypto payments to merchants powered by CoinGate. In turn, CoinGate merchants can facilitate Binance Pay payments during the checkout process.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">This new feature, which will be automatically activated, caters to various digital assets available on the Binance Pay platform, including <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-bears-prevail-as-asset-retreats-from-recent-highs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ripple (XRP)</a>, Cardano (ADA), and many others.</p>
<p>Notably, such developments often drive demand for Ripple&#8217;s token, prompting investors to accumulate the token in anticipation of future price appreciation. Furthermore, the recent regulatory clarity surrounding Ripple&#8217;s legal battle with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) may have also contributed to the increased confidence among whales.</p>

<p>As Ripple continues to make progress in the legal proceedings, the resolution of the case could potentially remove a major overhang on XRP&#8217;s market sentiment, paving the way for renewed optimism and investment.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/DkZLSED7/" alt="XRP price chart on TradingView" width="2768" height="1556"/>
<p>Meanwhile, following the accumulation of whales, XRP has shown an upcoming uptick. Over the past 24 hours, Ripple&#8217;s token has seen a 1% gain. The asset currently <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-aims-for-0-50-hinges-on-breaking-through-this-price-level/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">trades at $0.47</a>, at the time of writing.</p>
<p><em>-Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/XRP-2-460x329.jpeg" width="460" height="329" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bullish Case For Litecoin Grows Stronger As LTC Halving Draws Close</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/ltc/bullish-case-for-litecoin-grows-stronger-as-ltc-halving-draws-close/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 23:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc/usd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535158</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Litecoin (LTC) is still trending low like the rest of the cryptocurrency market but one thing that separates the altcoin from the others is its obvious bullish case. Unlike the rest of the market, Litecoin looks set for another rally which will likely be propelled forward by the next halving. Litecoin Halving Presents Bullish Scenario Just like Bitcoin, the Litecoin halving happens every four years and cuts block rewards by 50%. The aim of this halving is to reduce the amount of new supply flowing into the market. And as demand rises, there is less supply to meet this demand, thus leading to scarcity and a surge in prices. Related Reading: When Is A Token Coming For Coinbase’s Base L2? Here’s What The Roadmap Says The next Litecoin halving is now around the corner with only about three months left to go. This halving, like the ones before it, carries the same promise of a rally for the digital asset. The last halving in 2019 saw LTC’s price bottom out around $62 and then rally to a local peak of $80 in the same month. LTC halving will happen in August &#124; Source: Nicehash If this year’s halving stays true to this trend, then the digital asset should be seeing some upside in the coming months. This could result in LTC clearing the $100 level once more as investors prep for the next leg-up. A 20% upside is attainable at this point, especially with the halving expected to happen in early August. So more than likely, the buyers will dominate the market for the next two months, leading to rising prices for Litecoin. LTC Outlook For 2023 Presently, the crypto market is seeing muted momentum as investors remain indecisive. For Litecoin, the upcoming halving remains a bullish event but the prospects for the months following the halving event do not look good given historical performances. Previous performance paint bull case for LTC &#124; Source: LTCUSD on TradingView.com After each halving, LTC has seen a reversal in sentiment following the initial surge and the subsequent crashes have been more brutal than the uptrends. For example in 2019, LTC’s price crashed almost 50% in the month of September, one month after the halving was completed. This was because the bull market was yet to begin and the cryptocurrency fell back into lockstep with the rest of the market again. Related Reading: Elon Musk Reveals Reason Behind Dogecoin Investment, But Why Is DOGE Down? Going by this historical performance, it would seem the best time to take profits would be toward the end of August after the asset has rallied around 30%. The window of opportunity closes with the month of September which has historically been a bearish month for cryptocurrencies. At the time of writing, LTC is trading at $87.11, up 3.22% in the last day. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Litecoin (LTC) is still trending low like the rest of the cryptocurrency market but one thing that separates the altcoin from the others is its obvious bullish case. Unlike the rest of the market, Litecoin looks set for another rally which will likely be propelled forward by the next halving.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Litecoin Halving Presents Bullish Scenario</h2>
<p class="p2">Just like Bitcoin, the Litecoin halving happens every four years and cuts block rewards by 50%. The aim of this halving is to reduce the amount of new supply flowing into the market. And as demand rises, there is less supply to meet this demand, thus leading to scarcity and a surge in prices.</p>

<p class="p2">The next Litecoin halving is now around the corner with only about three months left to go. This halving, like the ones before it, carries the same promise of a rally for the digital asset. The last halving in 2019 saw LTC’s price bottom out around $62 and then rally to a local peak of $80 in the same month.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-535162 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-26-at-15.31.53-460x364.png" alt="Litecoin halving" width="460" height="364" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-26-at-15.31.53-460x364.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-26-at-15.31.53-860x681.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-26-at-15.31.53-768x608.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-26-at-15.31.53-1536x1216.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-26-at-15.31.53-750x594.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-26-at-15.31.53-1140x903.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-26-at-15.31.53.png 1902w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>

<p class="p2">If this year’s halving stays true to this trend, then the digital asset should be seeing some upside in the coming months. This could result in LTC clearing the $100 level once more as investors prep for the next leg-up.</p>
<p class="p2">A 20% upside is attainable at this point, especially with the halving expected to happen in early August. So more than likely, the buyers will dominate the market for the next two months, leading to rising prices for Litecoin.</p>
<h2 class="p2">LTC Outlook For 2023</h2>
<p class="p2">Presently, the crypto market is seeing muted momentum as investors remain indecisive. For Litecoin, the upcoming halving remains a bullish event but the prospects for the months following the halving event do not look good given historical performances.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/gn8HyO6h/" alt="Litecoin price chart from TradingView.com" width="2882" height="1724"/></p>

<p class="p2">After each halving, LTC has seen a reversal in sentiment following the initial surge and the subsequent crashes have been more brutal than the uptrends. For example in 2019, LTC’s price crashed almost 50% in the month of September, one month after the halving was completed. This was because the bull market was yet to begin and the cryptocurrency fell back into lockstep with the rest of the market again.</p>

<p class="p2">Going by this historical performance, it would seem the best time to take profits would be toward the end of August after the asset has rallied around 30%. The window of opportunity closes with the month of September which has historically been a bearish month for cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p class="p2">At the time of writing, LTC is trading at $87.11, up 3.22% in the last day.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1015828796-1-460x263.jpg" width="460" height="263" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Upcoming Interest Rate Hikes Could Be The Next Big Challenge For Bitcoin, Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/upcoming-interest-rate-hikes-could-be-the-next-big-challenge-for-bitcoin-heres-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 22:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535219</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin&#8217;s (BTC) current sideways price action has left investors wondering what the future holds for the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency. The upcoming interest rate hikes by the Federal Reserve (Fed) may pose the next big challenge for Bitcoin, according to the crypto market analysis firm Blofin Academy. Related Reading: Arbitrum (ARB) Fallout: 70% Price Drop, But These Charts Reveal Its True Value Is Bitcoin Ready For The Heat Of Interest Rate Hikes? The US economy has shown considerable resilience in recent months, prompting the Fed to consider raising interest rates to prevent inflation. However, this could be bad news for the crypto market, as higher interest rates tend to make traditional investments more attractive, potentially leading to a decrease in demand for Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies. The correlation between interest rates and Bitcoin&#8217;s price action has been observed in the past. When interest rates rise, investors tend to move their money into traditional investment vehicles such as stocks and bonds, leading to a decrease in demand for cryptocurrencies. However, it&#8217;s worth noting that Bitcoin has often been viewed as a hedge against inflation, which means that it could still hold some appeal for investors during times of economic uncertainty.  The next scheduled Fed meeting is set to take place on June 14, 2023, where the central bank will likely discuss the possibility of raising interest rates in response to the current state of the US economy.  Macro Determinants Leave Crypto Traders Waiting Noelle Acheson, owner of the &#8220;Crypto Is Macro Now&#8221; newsletter, has cautioned against investors piling into the crypto market at this time. While the upside potential for Bitcoin remains significant, Acheson suggests that there is currently no compelling reason for investors to take on additional risk. According to Acheson, there are few macro determinants at the moment, such as debt limit negotiations and Fed rate policy, which are leaving investors waiting for more clarity before making any major investment decisions. As a result, there is a sense of caution in the market as traders wait to see how these macro factors will play out. Despite the lack of clarity, Acheson notes that there is not much reason for existing crypto holders to sell their holdings. This suggests that the current wait-and-see period is not necessarily a sign of bearish sentiment in the market, but rather a period of caution as investors await more information. Acheson also notes that there may be some downside movement in the near term, but the belief in a potential rally is not strong enough to warrant the possibility of missing out on any potential gains. As a result, there has been some buying and selling in the market, but not enough to significantly increase volatility despite low volumes and liquidity. At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading at $26,700, reflecting a 1.2% increase over the last 24 hours. However, the 50-day Moving Average (MA) has placed the largest cryptocurrency in a narrow range between $26,200 and $26,800. This means that Bitcoin may struggle to surpass its current trading range in the near term, as the 50-day MA is currently situated at the upper end of this range on the 1-hour chart, making it a challenging level to breach. While Bitcoin has experienced some upside movements in recent weeks, the current trading range suggests that further gains may be limited until there is a significant shift in market sentiment or the emergence of a bullish catalyst. Related Reading: Why This Signal Means Uniswap’s Bear Run Is Almost Over Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s (BTC) current sideways price action has left investors wondering what the future holds for the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency. The upcoming interest rate hikes by the Federal Reserve (Fed) may pose the next big challenge for Bitcoin, <a href="https://twitter.com/Blofin_Academy/status/1661745585215655939?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">according </a>to the crypto market analysis firm Blofin Academy.</p>

<h2>Is Bitcoin Ready For The Heat Of Interest Rate Hikes?</h2>
<p>The US economy has shown considerable resilience in recent months, prompting the Fed to consider raising interest rates to prevent inflation. However, this could be bad news for the crypto market, as higher interest rates tend to make traditional investments more attractive, potentially leading to a decrease in demand for Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>The correlation between interest rates and Bitcoin&#8217;s price action has been observed in the past. When interest rates rise, investors tend to move their money into traditional investment vehicles such as stocks and bonds, leading to a decrease in demand for cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>However, it&#8217;s worth noting that Bitcoin has often been viewed as a hedge against inflation, which means that it could still hold some appeal for investors during times of economic uncertainty. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-535223" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Fw-zrzNaQAIJXmG.png" alt="Bitcoin " width="799" height="349" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Fw-zrzNaQAIJXmG.png 799w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Fw-zrzNaQAIJXmG-460x201.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Fw-zrzNaQAIJXmG-768x335.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Fw-zrzNaQAIJXmG-750x328.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 799px) 100vw, 799px"/>
<p>The next scheduled Fed meeting is set to take place on June 14, 2023, where the central bank will likely discuss the possibility of raising interest rates in response to the current state of the US economy. </p>
Macro Determinants Leave Crypto Traders Waiting
<p>Noelle Acheson, owner of the &#8220;Crypto Is Macro Now&#8221; newsletter, has <a href="https://noelleacheson.substack.com/p/friday-may-26-2023" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">cautioned </a>against investors piling into the crypto market at this time. While the upside potential for Bitcoin remains significant, Acheson suggests that there is currently no compelling reason for investors to take on additional risk.</p>
<p>According to Acheson, there are few macro determinants at the moment, such as debt limit negotiations and Fed rate policy, which are leaving investors waiting for more clarity before making any major investment decisions. As a result, there is a sense of caution in the market as traders wait to see how these macro factors will play out.</p>
<p>Despite the lack of clarity, Acheson notes that there is not much reason for existing crypto holders to sell their holdings. This suggests that the current wait-and-see period is not necessarily a sign of bearish sentiment in the market, but rather a period of caution as investors await more information.</p>
<p>Acheson also notes that there may be some downside movement in the near term, but the belief in a potential rally is not strong enough to warrant the possibility of missing out on any potential gains. As a result, there has been some buying and selling in the market, but not enough to significantly increase volatility despite low volumes and liquidity.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading at $26,700, reflecting a 1.2% increase over the last 24 hours. However, the 50-day Moving Average (MA) has placed the largest cryptocurrency in a narrow range between $26,200 and $26,800. This means that Bitcoin may struggle to surpass its current trading range in the near term, as the 50-day MA is currently situated at the upper end of this range on the 1-hour chart, making it a challenging level to breach.</p>
<p>While Bitcoin has experienced some upside movements in recent weeks, the current trading range suggests that further gains may be limited until there is a significant shift in market sentiment or the emergence of a bullish catalyst.</p>

<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/gtqg4P95/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1813" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-877508718-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will This Political Deal In The US Save Bitcoin and Crypto?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/all/will-this-political-deal-in-the-us-save-bitcoin-and-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 21:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Interest rate hike]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Treasury Department]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[united states]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535217</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Politicians in the United States will likely strike a deal and raise the government’s $31.4 trillion debt ceiling for two more years. Amid this debate, the price of Bitcoin is firm but lower, tracking below the psychological $30,000 level as bulls recover after posting sharp losses mid-this week. The Debt Ceiling Debate There are reports that there will be more discretionary spending on the military and veterans with the reduction of other sectors. Moreover, there are unconfirmed reports that the Biden administration will likely not fund the Internal Revenue Service (IRS) to boost collection, as laid out earlier. Instead, the immediate focus will be to hire more auditors and target wealthy citizens. Related Reading: Bitcoin Up After Fed Rate Reveal, Correlation With Stocks Over? There are concerns that the Treasury Department and the United States government will default on their obligation as soon as the first half of June 2023. Even though highly unlikely, as the Treasury Department has said it will liquidate $119 billion of debt on that day, the market is watching how discussions pan out. Bitcoin is firming up after losses on May 24. As a deal is reportedly struck and consensus reached, politicians would once again lift the debt ceiling, sending mixed signals to the economy. Unlike in previous years when top cryptocurrencies were decoupled from the mainstream economy, things have changed as Bitcoin’s prominence rises. Will Bitcoin Benefit? BTC prices will likely rally if there is an instance of default brought about by politicians disagreeing on the way forward. On the reverse side, a deal that addresses concerns brought by the negotiating parties could signal confidence in the economy despite more debt on the table. This averts a crisis and keeps operations running, removing uncertainty and stabilizing the economy. In that case, the USD could strengthen, possibly reversing gains by Bitcoin bulls in the last two trading days. Still, the crypto community remains bullish on Bitcoin considering macroeconomic events and next year’s halving. After months of steady interest rate hikes, the United States Federal Reserve could slow down rate increments in the next meeting in mid-June. Their action could support the commodities and securities markets. Related Reading: Nigeria’s Federal Executive Council Approves Blockchain Policy At the same time, the expected supply shock following the halving of Bitcoin miner rewards could make BTC scarcer, driving prices even higher. Miners are special nodes tasked with confirming transactions and decentralizing the network. If past price action can be used to predict future formations, BTC&#8217;s prospects look positive. Before the rally of 2020 to 2021, BTC prices bottomed up in 2018 and rose in 2019 before the halving event 2020. The same pattern may be repeated through to 2024 when Bitcoin halving occurs. Feature Image From Canva, Chart From TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Politicians in the United States will likely strike a deal and raise the government’s $31.4 trillion debt ceiling for two more years. Amid this debate, the price of Bitcoin is firm but lower, tracking below the psychological $30,000 level as bulls recover after posting sharp losses mid-this week.</p>
<h2>The Debt Ceiling Debate</h2>
<p>There are reports that there will be more discretionary spending on the military and veterans with the reduction of other sectors. </p>
<p>Moreover, there are unconfirmed <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/white-house-republicans-seek-close-us-debt-ceiling-deal-deadline-nears-2023-05-25/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reports</a> that the Biden administration will likely not fund the Internal Revenue Service (IRS) to boost collection, as laid out earlier. </p>
<p>Instead, the immediate focus will be to hire more auditors and target wealthy citizens.</p>

<p>There are concerns that the Treasury Department and the United States government will default on their obligation as soon as the first half of June 2023.</p>
<p> Even though highly unlikely, as the Treasury Department has said it will liquidate $119 billion of debt on that day, the market is watching how discussions pan out.</p>
<p>Bitcoin is firming up after losses on May 24. </p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/j0bJ66FA/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/j0bJ66FA/" alt="Bitcoin Price On May 26| Source: BTCUSDT On Binance, TradingView" width="1225" height="595"/></a>
<p>As a deal is reportedly struck and consensus reached, politicians would once again lift the debt ceiling, sending mixed signals to the economy. </p>
<p>Unlike in previous years when top cryptocurrencies were decoupled from the mainstream economy, things have changed as Bitcoin’s prominence rises.</p>
<h2>Will Bitcoin Benefit?</h2>
<p>BTC prices will likely rally if there is an instance of default brought about by politicians disagreeing on the way forward. </p>
<p>On the reverse side, a deal that addresses concerns brought by the negotiating parties could signal confidence in the economy despite more debt on the table. </p>
<p>This averts a crisis and keeps operations running, removing uncertainty and stabilizing the economy. </p>
<p>In that case, the USD could strengthen, possibly reversing gains by Bitcoin bulls in the last two trading days.</p>
<p>Still, the crypto community remains bullish on Bitcoin considering macroeconomic events and next year’s halving. </p>
<p>After months of steady interest rate hikes, the United States Federal Reserve could slow down rate increments in the next meeting in mid-June. Their action could support the commodities and securities markets.</p>

<p>At the same time, the expected supply shock following the halving of Bitcoin miner rewards could make BTC scarcer, driving prices even higher. </p>
<p>Miners are special nodes tasked with confirming transactions and decentralizing the network. </p>
<p>If past price action can be used to predict future formations, BTC&#8217;s prospects look positive. Before the rally of 2020 to 2021, BTC prices bottomed up in 2018 and rose in 2019 before the halving event 2020. </p>
<p>The same pattern may be repeated through to 2024 when Bitcoin halving occurs.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/US-Debt-Ceiling-Bitcoin-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Arbitrum (ARB) Fallout: 70% Price Drop, But These Charts Reveal Its True Value</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/arb/arbitrum-arb-fallout-70-price-drop-but-these-charts-reveal-its-true-value/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 20:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ARB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitrum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitrum (ARB)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ARBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535207</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Arbitrum (ARB) has been making waves in the crypto world as it recently became the 4th largest ecosystem in the market. Despite experiencing a sharp decline of 70% since its airdrop, Arbitrum’s native token has continued to gain attention from investors, currently trading around $1.158, down from $1.1808 on April 18th. Related Reading: Toncoin (TON) Continues Downward Trend As Bears Maintain Control Arbitrum Defies The Odds According to the Decentralized Finance (DeFi) researcher Deebs, Arbitrum has emerged as a major player in the crypto market, with its Total Value Locked (TVL) soaring to an impressive $2.3 billion. This puts it in 4th position by TVL, surpassing many of its competitors.  Additionally, since the launch of Arbitrum, the value of stablecoins has grown by over $500 million in just two months. At its peak, the network&#8217;s active user base reached over 600,000, surpassing Optimism (OP), a fast, stable, and scalable L2 blockchain built by Ethereum developers, and nearly overtaking the blockchain platform designed to host decentralized, scalable applications Solana (SOL).  Despite these impressive metrics, ARB’s price has experienced a significant drop of 70% since its airdrop and has had very little positive price action since. However, DeFi researcher Deebs believes that this dip in price may be a sign of a hidden gem in the crypto market. One of the main factors that make Arbitrum an attractive investment opportunity is its high TVL, user base, and liquidity. In fact, since its launch, Arbitrum has maintained the highest liquidity of all Layer 2 (L2) networks and is the third highest of all chains on DeFi Llama. Furthermore, while many other chains have a market capitalization to TVL ratio above 1, Arbitrum boasts one of the smallest ratios at 0.6. This means that the potential price upside for ARB is significantly higher than its competitors, making it an enticing investment opportunity for those looking for long-term gains. Additionally, ARB&#8217;s technology has been praised for its ability to address some of the key issues facing the crypto industry, such as scalability and high transaction fees. ARB&#8217;s use of cutting-edge technology such as Optimistic Rollups provides a solution to these problems, making it an attractive option for investors looking for a reliable network with great potential. Another positive sign for ARB is the amount of support it has received from major players in the crypto industry. This includes partnerships with well-known crypto projects such as Uniswap, Aave, and Chainlink. These collaborations demonstrate that the industry recognizes the value of ARB&#8217;s technology and the potential it holds for the future of decentralized finance. Related Reading: JPMorgan Predicts Bitcoin (BTC) To Revisit $45,000, Here’s Why Overall, despite the recent drop in price, ARB&#8217;s strong fundamentals and growing network usage suggest that it is a hidden gem in the crypto market. Its partnerships with major players in the industry, as well as its innovative technology, make it a promising investment opportunity for those looking to capitalize on the potential of decentralized finance. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Arbitrum (ARB) has been making waves in the crypto world as it recently became the 4th largest ecosystem in the market. Despite experiencing a sharp decline of 70% since its airdrop, Arbitrum’s native token has continued to gain attention from investors, currently trading around $1.158, down from $1.1808 on April 18th.</p>

<h2>Arbitrum Defies The Odds</h2>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/Deebs_DeFi/status/1662065395212378112?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to the Decentralized Finance (DeFi) researcher Deebs, Arbitrum has emerged as a major player in the crypto market, with its Total Value Locked (TVL) soaring to an impressive $2.3 billion. This puts it in 4th position by TVL, surpassing many of its competitors. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-535209" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FxDXrGbacAAIUQ8.png" alt="Arbitrum" width="777" height="534" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FxDXrGbacAAIUQ8.png 777w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FxDXrGbacAAIUQ8-460x316.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FxDXrGbacAAIUQ8-768x528.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FxDXrGbacAAIUQ8-750x515.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 777px) 100vw, 777px"/>
<p>Additionally, since the launch of Arbitrum, the value of stablecoins has grown by over $500 million in just two months. At its peak, the network&#8217;s active user base reached over 600,000, surpassing Optimism (OP), a fast, stable, and scalable L2 blockchain built by Ethereum developers, and nearly overtaking the blockchain platform designed to host decentralized, scalable applications Solana (SOL). </p>
<p>Despite these impressive metrics, ARB’s price has experienced a significant drop of 70% since its airdrop and has had very little positive price action since. However, DeFi researcher Deebs believes that this dip in price may be a sign of a hidden gem in the crypto market.</p>
<p>One of the main factors that make Arbitrum an attractive investment opportunity is its high TVL, user base, and liquidity. In fact, since its launch, Arbitrum has maintained the highest liquidity of all Layer 2 (L2) networks and is the third highest of all chains on DeFi Llama.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-535210" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FxDXsbwaIAAwKEi.png" alt="Arbitrum" width="775" height="545" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FxDXsbwaIAAwKEi.png 775w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FxDXsbwaIAAwKEi-460x323.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FxDXsbwaIAAwKEi-768x540.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FxDXsbwaIAAwKEi-750x527.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 775px) 100vw, 775px"/>
<p>Furthermore, while many other chains have a market capitalization to TVL ratio above 1, Arbitrum boasts one of the smallest ratios at 0.6. This means that the potential price upside for ARB is significantly higher than its competitors, making it an enticing investment opportunity for those looking for long-term gains.</p>
<p>Additionally, ARB&#8217;s technology has been praised for its ability to address some of the key issues facing the crypto industry, such as scalability and high transaction fees. ARB&#8217;s use of cutting-edge technology such as Optimistic Rollups provides a solution to these problems, making it an attractive option for investors looking for a reliable network with great potential.</p>
<p>Another positive sign for ARB is the amount of support it has received from major players in the crypto industry. This includes partnerships with well-known crypto projects such as Uniswap, Aave, and Chainlink. These collaborations demonstrate that the industry recognizes the value of ARB&#8217;s technology and the potential it holds for the future of decentralized finance.</p>

<p>Overall, despite the recent drop in price, ARB&#8217;s strong fundamentals and growing network usage suggest that it is a hidden gem in the crypto market. Its partnerships with major players in the industry, as well as its innovative technology, make it a promising investment opportunity for those looking to capitalize on the potential of decentralized finance.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/bAMMmILE/" alt="Arbitrum" width="1813" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/engin-akyurt-RFIpITqnaZw-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why This Signal Means Uniswap&#8217;s Bear Run Is Almost Over</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/uniswap/why-this-signal-means-uniswaps-bear-run-is-almost-over/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 19:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uniswap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Base]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UNI]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535198</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The price of Uniswap, the largest decentralized exchange by trading volume, is down roughly 35% from Q1 2023 peaks. Even so, on-chain data from Etherscan shows that there has been a steady increase in the number of UNI holders in the past two days. As of May 13, there were 369,646 UNI holders. Since then, the number has increased to over 370,100 as of May 26. During this time, UNI prices have remained stable but relatively high. Based on the UNIUSDT chart, the prices have found support around $4.9. However, prices have increased by approximately 10% over the past two weeks, rising to $5.4. Although the number of UNI holders may not directly affect the prices, there is a clear correlation between the demand for UNI and the increase in token prices. Related Reading: Toncoin (TON) Continues Downward Trend As Bears Maintain Control Several factors could have provided tailwinds for UNI, the governance token of Uniswap.  Apple Jail Break On May 23, Uniswap’s mobile wallet was released from what Uniswap Labs, the team maintaining Uniswap, said was “Apple jail.”  With this jailbreak, users can download the Uniswap Wallet, that’s non-custodial like MetaMask.  Through this wallet, users can buy and sell various supported cryptocurrencies.  This announcement is bullish because as more users opt for Uniswap Wallet, the demand for the decentralized exchange could rise, increasing its dominance and stature.  While MetaMask remains the most dominant Ethereum and Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) wallet enabling the storing and trading of various tokens, even using processors like PayPal, the popularity of Uniswap could see Uniswap Wallet gnaw market share.  Presently, Uniswap Labs said their wallet could support the trading of tokens across Ethereum, Polygon, Optimism, and Arbitrum. Uniswap To Launch On Base? Earlier on, the Uniswap contributors proposed the deployment of the DEX v3 on Coinbase’s Base.  Among supporters of this proposal is GFX Labs, one of the largest UNI holders and supporters of Uniswap’s expansion to other chains. Recently, GFX Labs voted for the launch of the DEX on BNB Smart Chain (BSC) and MoonBeam.  Even so, before voting starts, the proposal will undergo a “temperature check-up” to gauge community support. If there is majority support, it will proceed to the next step. Uniswap v3 is the latest iteration of the DEX, introducing the concept of concentrated liquidity for higher capital efficiency and more return on investment (ROI) for liquidity providers.  Base is a layer-2, open-source, and EVM-compatible platform by Coinbase, one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges. Related Reading: JPMorgan Predicts Bitcoin (BTC) To Revisit $45,000, Here’s Why It is unclear whether the above-spurred demand for UNI, pushed the number of holders higher in the last week.  However, this could suggest that the project is generating interest, which may support future token prices. Feature Image From Canva, Chart From TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price of Uniswap, the largest decentralized exchange by trading volume, is down roughly 35% from Q1 2023 peaks. Even so, on-chain data from Etherscan <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://etherscan.io/token/0x1f9840a85d5af5bf1d1762f925bdaddc4201f984#balances" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shows</a> that there has been a steady increase in the number of UNI holders in the past two days.</p>
<p>As of May 13, there were 369,646 UNI holders. Since then, the number has increased to over 370,100 as of May 26. During this time, UNI prices have remained stable but relatively high.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/BdcOvyWi/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/BdcOvyWi/" alt="Uniswap Price On May 6| Source: UNIUSDT On Binance, TradingView" width="1225" height="595"/></a>
<p>Based on the UNIUSDT chart, the prices have found support around $4.9. However, prices have increased by approximately 10% over the past two weeks, rising to $5.4. Although the number of UNI holders may not directly affect the prices, there is a clear correlation between the demand for UNI and the increase in token prices.</p>

<p>Several factors could have provided tailwinds for UNI, the governance token of Uniswap. </p>
<h2>Apple Jail Break</h2>
<p>On May 23, Uniswap’s mobile wallet was <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/uniswap-wallet/id6443944476" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">released</a> from what Uniswap Labs, the team maintaining Uniswap, said was “Apple jail.” </p>
<p>With this jailbreak, users can download the Uniswap Wallet, that’s non-custodial like MetaMask. </p>
<p>Through this wallet, users can buy and sell various supported cryptocurrencies. </p>
<p>This announcement is bullish because as more users opt for Uniswap Wallet, the demand for the decentralized exchange could rise, increasing its dominance and stature. </p>
<p>While MetaMask remains the most dominant Ethereum and Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) wallet enabling the storing and trading of various tokens, even using processors like PayPal, the popularity of Uniswap could see Uniswap Wallet gnaw market share. </p>
<p>Presently, Uniswap Labs said their wallet could support the trading of tokens across Ethereum, Polygon, Optimism, and Arbitrum.</p>
<h2>Uniswap To Launch On Base?</h2>
<p>Earlier on, the Uniswap contributors <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://gov.uniswap.org/t/deploy-uniswap-v3-on-base/21249" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">proposed</a> the deployment of the DEX v3 on Coinbase’s Base. </p>
<p>Among supporters of this proposal is GFX Labs, one of the largest UNI holders and supporters of Uniswap’s expansion to other chains. Recently, GFX Labs voted for the launch of the DEX on BNB Smart Chain (BSC) and MoonBeam. </p>
<p>Even so, before voting starts, the proposal will undergo a “temperature check-up” to gauge community support. If there is majority support, it will proceed to the next step.</p>
<p>Uniswap v3 is the latest iteration of the DEX, introducing the concept of concentrated liquidity for higher capital efficiency and more return on investment (ROI) for liquidity providers. </p>
<p>Base is a layer-2, open-source, and EVM-compatible platform by Coinbase, one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges.</p>

<p>It is unclear whether the above-spurred demand for UNI, pushed the number of holders higher in the last week.  However, this could suggest that the project is generating interest, which may support future token prices.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/PancakeSwap-CAKE-Uniswap-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Toncoin (TON) Continues Downward Trend As Bears Maintain Control</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/toncoin-ton-continues-downward-trend-as-bears-maintain-control/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli Dambel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 17:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bears]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Toncoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535167</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Toncoin (TON) has experienced a negative price decline, resulting in a bearish sentiment among investors of the altcoin. TON has been exhibiting a bearish strength on a monthly timeframe, based on data from CoinMarketCap.  Within the last 30-Day trading session, the asset is down by 15,67%, indicating a high bearish strength with low buying pressure. Related Reading: Bitcoin Bearish Signal: NUPL Finds Rejection At Long-Term Resistance As of the time of writing, the asset is experiencing a decline in value, as it’s down today by 2.76%. This downward trend has resulted in the asset, TON, reaching a low point of $1.91.  The decrease in value reflects a temporary setback in the market, indicating a decrease in investor confidence. It also detects a shift in the supply and demand dynamics surrounding the asset. Toncoin (TON) Bears Maintained Their Positions Toncoin (TON) witnessed a sharp price decline on May 23, from $2.03 to its present value of $1.89. This price decline represents a loss of 6.89%. This decline reflects the dominance of bearish sentiment in the market, which shows a lack of investor confidence and a shift in the supply and demand dynamics. According to the market sentiment indicator, the current market sentiment is bearish, while the Fear &#38; Greed index value is a neutral 49. Notably, a Fear &#38; Greed index value below 50 points to an increase in bearish momentum. Conversely, an important resistance level is noted at $2.080, representing a significant hurdle for potential upward movement.  Toncoin trades below the 50-day and 200-day Simple Moving Average (SMA). The SMAs formed a Death Cross in the TON market on May 21, 2023.  This confirms the bearish sentiment present in the market, indicating a potential sell signal and further price decline. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) momentum oscillator value is 40.98 and points downwards. RSI is a popular indicator showing whether a cryptocurrency is oversold or overbought.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Hangs At $26,200: Why This Is A Crucial Support Level If TON RSI drops below 30, it may ignite high selling pressure and further price decline. TON Demand Index and Bollinger Bands Signals Bearish Activities The TON/USDT trading pair demand index is at -0.449, suggesting relatively weak demand for the asset in the market. Note that a demand index below zero is generally considered a lack of buying pressure. It also indicates that the selling pressure outweighs the buying interest. In addition, the asset is heading toward the lower part of the Bollinger Bands indicator. This suggests an increase in selling pressure and high bearish momentum. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Toncoin (TON) has experienced a negative price decline, resulting in a bearish sentiment among investors of the altcoin. TON has been exhibiting a bearish strength on a monthly timeframe, based on data from CoinMarketCap. </p>
<p>Within the last 30-Day trading session, the asset is down by 15,67%, indicating a high bearish strength with low buying pressure.</p>

<p>As of the time of writing, the asset is experiencing a decline in value, as it’s down today by 2.76%. This downward trend has resulted in the asset, TON, reaching a low point of $1.91. </p>
<p>The decrease in value reflects a temporary setback in the market, indicating a decrease in investor confidence. It also detects a shift in the supply and demand dynamics surrounding the asset.</p>
<h2>Toncoin (TON) Bears Maintained Their Positions</h2>
<p>Toncoin (TON) witnessed a sharp price decline on May 23, from $2.03 to its <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/toncoin/historical_data#panel" rel="nofollow">present value</a> of $1.89. This price decline represents a loss of 6.89%.</p>
<p>This decline reflects the dominance of bearish sentiment in the market, which shows a lack of investor confidence and a shift in the supply and demand dynamics.</p>
<p>According to the market sentiment indicator, the current market sentiment is bearish, while the Fear &amp; Greed index value is a neutral 49. Notably, a Fear &amp; Greed index value below 50 points to an increase in bearish momentum.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-535175 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/TONUSDT_2023-05-26_20-17-40-860x470.png" alt="Toncoin (TON) Continues Downward Trend As Bears Maintain Control" width="860" height="470" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/TONUSDT_2023-05-26_20-17-40-860x470.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/TONUSDT_2023-05-26_20-17-40-460x252.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/TONUSDT_2023-05-26_20-17-40-768x420.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/TONUSDT_2023-05-26_20-17-40-750x410.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/TONUSDT_2023-05-26_20-17-40-1140x624.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/TONUSDT_2023-05-26_20-17-40.png 1530w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>Conversely, an important resistance level is noted at $2.080, representing a significant hurdle for potential upward movement. </p>
<p>Toncoin trades below the 50-day and 200-day Simple Moving Average (SMA). The SMAs formed a Death Cross in the TON market on May 21, 2023. </p>
<p>This confirms the bearish sentiment present in the market, indicating a potential sell signal and further price decline.</p>
<p>The Relative Strength Index (RSI) momentum oscillator value is 40.98 and points downwards. RSI is a popular indicator showing whether a cryptocurrency is oversold or overbought. </p>

<p>If TON RSI drops below 30, it may ignite high selling pressure and further price decline.</p>
TON Demand Index and Bollinger Bands Signals Bearish Activities
<p>The TON/USDT trading pair demand index is at -0.449, suggesting relatively weak demand for the asset in the market.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-535172 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-26-201543.png" alt="Toncoin (TON) Continues Downward Trend As Bears Maintain Control" width="777" height="343" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-26-201543.png 777w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-26-201543-460x203.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-26-201543-768x339.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-26-201543-750x331.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 777px) 100vw, 777px"/></p>
<p>Note that a demand index below zero is generally considered a lack of buying pressure. It also indicates that the selling pressure outweighs the buying interest.</p>
<p>In addition, the asset is heading toward the lower part of the Bollinger Bands indicator. This suggests an increase in selling pressure and high bearish momentum.</p>
<p>Featured image from Pixabay and chart from Tradingview.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/pexels-pixabay-158109-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>JPMorgan Predicts Bitcoin (BTC) To Revisit $45,000, Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/jpmorgan-predicts-bitcoin-btc-to-revisit-45000-heres-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 16:20:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[JP Morgan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=535161</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a recent note, JPMorgan strategists have made a prediction, suggesting that Bitcoin (BTC) could soar and revisit its former trading price of $45,000 due to the rising price of gold. This prediction comes amid Bitcoin&#8217;s price action of a blend of bulls and bears in the past week. Meanwhile, over the past 24 hours, BTC has seen a 2.1% gain with a current trading price above $26,000. The current surge comes after Bitcoin previously fall that dropped its price below its previously ranging market price of $28,000. Bitcoin And Gold: A Correlation Bitcoin and gold have often been regarded as alternative investments by investors, and their prices have displayed a tendency to move in tandem. Given this, JPMorgan analysts note that the current gold price, hovering near $2,000 per ounce, implies a Bitcoin price of $45,000. This assumption is based on the idea that BTC will reach a similar standing as gold in the portfolios of private investors. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Struggles To Recover and Remains Vulnerable To Fresh Decline JP Morgan wrote in a note: With the gold price rising above $2,000, the value of gold held for investment purposes outside central banks is currently valued at around [$3 trillion]. In turn, this implies a $45,000 price for bitcoin under the assumption that bitcoin equalizes gold in private investors&#8217; portfolios in risk capital or [volume]-adjusted terms. One key factor contributing to JPMorgan&#8217;s optimistic prediction is the upcoming Bitcoin halving event, scheduled to take place between April and May 2024. The halving mechanism reduces the rate at which new Bitcoins are produced, effectively doubling the production cost. The JPMorgan strategists believe this event will push Bitcoin&#8217;s production cost to approximately $40,000, acting as a lower bound and potentially driving the price upward. Drawing from historical data, JPMorgan highlights the bullish trajectory observed during previous halving events in 2016 and 2020. These events were accompanied by significant surges in Bitcoin prices, indicating the potential for a similar outcome following the next halving. As a result, JPMorgan sets an upper limit of $45,000 for BTC, indicating limited potential beyond the increase driven by the doubling of production costs. Reflecting On Ethereum (ETH) While Bitcoin takes the spotlight in JPMorgan&#8217;s prediction, the bank suggests that Ethereum (ETH) may face some selling pressure in the near term, extending beyond the Shanghai upgrade until mid-year. JPMorgan expects Ethereum to &#8220;somewhat underperform&#8221; BTC during this period. However, it&#8217;s essential to note that Ethereum&#8217;s performance is subject to a range of factors, including market dynamics and technological developments. Related Reading: The Best Decision Is To ‘Buy Bitcoin (BTC),’ Robert Kiyosaki Urges Meanwhile, regardless of JPMorgan&#8217;s prediction, BTC is currently in a bullish trend recording an uptick. Over the past 24 hours, Bitcoin has seen more than a 2% gain, while the past seven days have seen a dip of 1.2%. At the time of writing, the top crypto currently trades at $26,823. Bitcoin’s trading volume has, however, ranged around $20 billion in the past 7 days, indicating a possible accumulation. Bitcoin currently has a trading volume of $13.1 billion in the past 24 hours. Featured image from Shutterstock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a recent note, JPMorgan strategists have made a <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/232334/bitcoin-price-45k-jpmorgan-gold" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">prediction</a>, suggesting that Bitcoin (BTC) could soar and revisit its former trading price of $45,000 due to the rising price of gold. This prediction comes amid Bitcoin&#8217;s price action of a blend of bulls and bears in the past week.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, over the past 24 hours, BTC has seen a 2.1% gain with a current trading price above $26,000. The current surge comes after Bitcoin previously fall that dropped its price below its previously ranging market price of $28,000.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin And Gold: A Correlation</h2>
<p>Bitcoin and gold have often been regarded as alternative investments by investors, and their prices have displayed a tendency to move in tandem. </p>
<p>Given this, JPMorgan analysts note that the current gold price, hovering near $2,000 per ounce, implies a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-struggles-26650/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin price</a> of $45,000. This assumption is based on the idea that BTC will reach a similar standing as gold in the portfolios of private investors.</p>

<p>JP Morgan wrote in a note:</p>
<blockquote><p>With the gold price rising above $2,000, the value of gold held for investment purposes outside central banks is currently valued at around [$3 trillion]. In turn, this implies a $45,000 price for bitcoin under the assumption that bitcoin equalizes gold in private investors&#8217; portfolios in risk capital or [volume]-adjusted terms.</p></blockquote>
<p>One key factor contributing to JPMorgan&#8217;s optimistic prediction is the upcoming <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/best-decision-is-to-buy-bitcoin-btc-robert-kiyosaki-urges/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a> halving event, scheduled to take place between April and May 2024. The halving mechanism reduces the rate at which new Bitcoins are produced, effectively doubling the production cost. </p>
<p>The JPMorgan strategists believe this event will push Bitcoin&#8217;s production cost to approximately $40,000, acting as a lower bound and potentially driving the price upward.</p>
<p>Drawing from historical data, JPMorgan highlights the bullish trajectory observed during previous halving events in 2016 and 2020. These events were accompanied by significant surges in Bitcoin prices, indicating the potential for a similar outcome following the next halving. </p>
<p>As a result, JPMorgan sets an upper limit of $45,000 for BTC, indicating limited potential beyond the increase driven by the doubling of production costs.</p>
<h2>Reflecting On Ethereum (ETH)</h2>
<p>While Bitcoin takes the spotlight in JPMorgan&#8217;s prediction, the bank suggests that Ethereum (ETH) may face some selling pressure in the near term, extending beyond the Shanghai upgrade until mid-year. JPMorgan expects Ethereum to &#8220;somewhat underperform&#8221; BTC during this period. </p>
<p>However, it&#8217;s essential to note that Ethereum&#8217;s performance is subject to a range of factors, including market dynamics and technological developments.</p>

<p>Meanwhile, regardless of JPMorgan&#8217;s prediction, BTC is currently in a bullish trend recording an uptick. Over the past 24 hours, Bitcoin has seen more than a 2% gain, while the past seven days have seen a dip of 1.2%.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/paVvpyKA/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC)’s price chart on TradingView" width="2768" height="1556"/>
<p>At the time of writing, the<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-exchange-inflows-loss-weak-hands-exiting/" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> top crypto</a> currently<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-bears-aim-25000/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> trades at $26,823</a>. Bitcoin’s trading volume has, however, ranged around $20 billion in the past 7 days, indicating a possible accumulation. Bitcoin currently has a trading volume of $13.1 billion in the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>Featured image from Shutterstock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-1.jpg" width="350" height="250" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
