<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 06:50:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Crystal Ball &#8211; What Happens To BTC After Christmas 2022?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin-price-on-the-checklist-what-happens-to-btc-after-christmas-2022/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 06:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto winter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[federal reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FOMC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[inflation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512412</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin and the broader crypto market rapidly reversed course in response to the U.S. Federal Reserve&#8217;s announcement of a 50-basis-point increase in interest rates, erasing any gains made before the disclosure. The Federal Reserve has been steadily raising interest rates in an effort to ease the economy and rein in inflation, which has driven prices to record highs. Yesterday, the Bitcoin price reached a one-month high and had a brief recovery of positive momentum, but a conservative report from the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) and remarks from Fed chair Jerome Powell drove BTC to an intraday low of $17,659. Related Reading: LINK Still On ETH Whales’ Shopping Cart Despite Dismal Performance In Last 7 Days A Whipsaw For Bitcoin After Fed Disclosure According to TradingView data, the BTC price saw a bit of a whipsaw in response to the central bank announcement, rising to an intraday high of $18,377 before falling to a low of $17,663 in a few of hours before bulls pushed it back up above the $17,800 support. Prior to Powell&#8217;s announcement, the key indexes were in the green zone; however, they plunged into the red zone after his announcement. At the close of trading, the Dow Jones, Nasdaq, and S&#38;P were all in the red. Powell told members of the press on Wednesday afternoon that &#8220;we have more work to do&#8221; and that &#8220;inflation risks are on the upside.&#8221; Coingecko statistics indicates at the time of writing that Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) values have fallen by more than 2.7% in the last hour and are presently trading at $17,717 and $1,292 apiece. In the past 24 hours, the market capitalization of all cryptocurrencies declined 1.42 percent to $857.98 billion, representing a decline of $85.72 billion. The overall crypto market volume during the past 24 hours has decreased by 14.40%, reaching $45.67 billion, based on latest data. BTC total market cap at $341 billion. Chart: TradingView.com Related Reading: How Litecoin (LTC) Outperforms Other Top Cryptocurrencies In This Department What The Experts Predict For BTC Price In its Crypto Outlook For 2023 report by Forbes Advisor, it predicts that Bitcoin&#8217;s price could decline to $13,560 in 2023, given that crypto&#8217;s reputation has been severely damaged by the problems and scandals of 2022 and that broader markets are suffering. Jim Wyckoff, a senior technical analyst at Kitco, has a different take: he said that Bitcoin&#8217;s surge to $18,377 was a five-week high, which actually signals optimism in the crypto&#8217;s price trajectory. The markets fell from $20K to $15.6K due to the FTX collapse. We&#8217;re currently trading at $18K, slightly higher than the low in June. I understand the bearish thesis, but this is honestly a sign of strength for #Bitcoin. — Michaël van de Poppe (@CryptoMichNL) December 14, 2022 According to Wyckoff, this week&#8217;s price action has created a bullish &#8220;upside breakout&#8221; from a &#8220;choppy and sideways trading range&#8221; on the daily chart, indicating the emergence of a price upswing. Other renowned analysts say that the market has already reached its bottom and that a Bitcoin relief bounce is in the offing. The question that arises now is whether the current market turmoil will persist into the new year, and if so &#8212; when the crypto winter&#8217;s frozen edges might begin to thaw.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin and the broader crypto market rapidly reversed course in response to the U.S. Federal Reserve&#8217;s announcement of a 50-basis-point increase in interest rates, erasing any gains made before the disclosure.</p>
<p>The Federal Reserve has been steadily raising interest rates in an effort to ease the economy and rein in inflation, which has driven prices to record highs.</p>
<p>Yesterday, the Bitcoin price reached a one-month high and had a brief recovery of positive momentum, but a conservative report from the Federal Open Market Committee<a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fed-preview-central-bank-set-to-slow-rate-hikes-at-final-meeting-of-2022-194812853.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> (FOMC)</a> and remarks from Fed chair Jerome Powell drove BTC to an intraday low of $17,659.</p>

<h2>A Whipsaw For Bitcoin After Fed Disclosure</h2>
<p>According to TradingView data, the BTC price saw a bit of a whipsaw in response to the central bank announcement, rising to an intraday high of $18,377 before falling to a low of $17,663 in a few of hours before bulls pushed it back up above the $17,800 support.</p>
<p>Prior to Powell&#8217;s announcement, the key indexes were in the green zone; however, they plunged into the red zone after his announcement. At the close of trading, the Dow Jones, Nasdaq, and S&amp;P were all in the red.</p>
<p><a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/federal-reserve-hikes-rate-by-50bps-fomc-signals-rate-to-rise-to-5-1-next-year/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Powell</a> told members of the press on Wednesday afternoon that &#8220;we have more work to do&#8221; and that &#8220;inflation risks are on the upside.&#8221;</p>
<p>Coingecko <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">statistics</a> indicates at the time of writing that Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) values have fallen by more than 2.7% in the last hour and are presently trading at $17,717 and $1,292 apiece.</p>
<p>In the past 24 hours, the market capitalization of all cryptocurrencies declined 1.42 percent to $857.98 billion, representing a decline of $85.72 billion. The overall crypto market volume during the past 24 hours has decreased by 14.40%, reaching $45.67 billion, based on latest data.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/oHIAl2UE/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>


<h2>What The Experts Predict For BTC Price</h2>
<p>In its Crypto Outlook For 2023 report by <a href="https://www.forbes.com/advisor/ca/investing/cryptocurrency/crypto-outlook-for-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Forbes</a> Advisor, it predicts that Bitcoin&#8217;s price could decline to $13,560 in 2023, given that crypto&#8217;s reputation has been severely damaged by the problems and scandals of 2022 and that broader markets are suffering.</p>
<p>Jim Wyckoff, a senior technical analyst at Kitco, has a different take: he said that Bitcoin&#8217;s surge to $18,377 was a five-week high, which actually signals optimism in the crypto&#8217;s price trajectory.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">The markets fell from $20K to $15.6K due to the FTX collapse.</p>
<p>We&#8217;re currently trading at $18K, slightly higher than the low in June.</p>
<p>I understand the bearish thesis, but this is honestly a sign of strength for <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p>— Michaël van de Poppe (@CryptoMichNL) <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1603049392541683712?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">December 14, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p>According to Wyckoff, this week&#8217;s price action has created a bullish &#8220;upside breakout&#8221; from a &#8220;choppy and sideways trading range&#8221; on the daily chart, indicating the emergence of a price upswing.</p>
<p>Other renowned analysts say that the market has already reached its bottom and that a Bitcoin relief bounce is in the offing.</p>
<p>The question that arises now is whether the current market turmoil will persist into the new year, and if so &#8212; when the crypto winter&#8217;s frozen edges might begin to thaw.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-12-460x307.png" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tron Price Prediction: Why TRX Could Outperform BTC and ETH</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/trx/tron-price-prediction-trx-0-06/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 05:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[TRON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tron price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trxusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRXUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512403</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tron price is up over 5% and showing positive signs above $0.055 against the US Dollar. TRX could outperform bitcoin and rise further towards $0.060. Tron price is trading in a positive zone well above the $0.0520 pivot level against the US dollar. The price is showing positive signs above $0.055 and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.0530 on the 4-hours chart of the TRX/USD pair (data source from Kraken). The pair is likely to start a fresh increase above the $0.0562 and $0.0575 resistance levels. Tron Price Jumps 5% In the past few days, tron price remained strong above the $0.0520 level against the US Dollar, outperforming bitcoin and ethereum. TRX gained pace for a clear move above the $0.055 resistance and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours). The price traded to a new weekly high at $0.0575 and it is currently correcting gains. There was a move below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent rally from the $0.0519 low to $0.0575 high. Trx price is now trading above $0.055 and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours). It is also above the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent rally from the $0.0519 low to $0.0575 high. On the upside, an initial resistance is near the $0.0562 level. Source: TRXUSD on TradingView.com The next major resistance is near the $0.0575 level, above which the bulls are likely to aim a larger increase towards the key $0.0600 zone in the coming sessions. Any more gains could set the pace for a move towards the $0.0645 level. Dips Likely to be Limited in TRX If TRX price fails to clear the $0.0575 barrier, it could correct lower. An initial support on the downside is near the $0.0550 zone, where the bulls are currently taking a stand. The next major support is near the $0.0540 level and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours). The main support is near the trend line and $0.0530, below which there is a risk of a move towards the $0.050 support. Technical Indicators 4-hours MACD – The MACD for TRX/USD is gaining momentum in the bullish zone. 4-hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for TRX/USD is currently above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $0.0550, $0.0542 and $0.0530. Major Resistance Levels – $0.0562, $0.0575 and $0.0600.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Tron price is up over 5% and showing positive signs above $0.055 against the US Dollar. TRX could outperform bitcoin and rise further towards $0.060.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Tron price is trading in a positive zone well above the $0.0520 pivot level against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is showing positive signs above $0.055 and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bullish trend line forming with support near $0.0530 on the 4-hours chart of the TRX/USD pair (data source from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair is likely to start a fresh increase above the $0.0562 and $0.0575 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Tron Price Jumps 5%</h2>
<p>In the past few days, tron price remained strong above the $0.0520 level against the US Dollar, outperforming <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-retreats-18k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bitcoin</a> and <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-resilience-pause-1350/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ethereum</a>. TRX gained pace for a clear move above the $0.055 resistance and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours).</p>
<p>The price traded to a new weekly high at $0.0575 and it is currently correcting gains. There was a move below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent rally from the $0.0519 low to $0.0575 high. Trx price is now trading above $0.055 and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours).</p>
<p>It is also above the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent rally from the $0.0519 low to $0.0575 high. On the upside, an initial resistance is near the $0.0562 level.</p>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Tron-TRX.png"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-512404" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Tron-TRX.png" alt="Tron Price TRX" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Tron-TRX.png 1834w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Tron-TRX-460x212.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Tron-TRX-860x396.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Tron-TRX-768x354.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Tron-TRX-1536x708.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Tron-TRX-750x346.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Tron-TRX-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/TRXUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">TRXUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $0.0575 level, above which the bulls are likely to aim a larger increase towards the key $0.0600 zone in the coming sessions. Any more gains could set the pace for a move towards the $0.0645 level.</p>
<h2>Dips Likely to be Limited in TRX</h2>
<p>If TRX price fails to clear the $0.0575 barrier, it could correct lower. An initial support on the downside is near the $0.0550 zone, where the bulls are currently taking a stand.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $0.0540 level and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours). The main support is near the trend line and $0.0530, below which there is a risk of a move towards the $0.050 support.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>4-hours MACD – The MACD for TRX/USD is gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4-hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for TRX/USD is currently above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $0.0550, $0.0542 and $0.0530.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $0.0562, $0.0575 and $0.0600.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/shutterstock_584552989-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Resilience Gives us Pause, but Not out of Woods Yet</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-resilience-pause-1350/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 04:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512398</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum jumped and tested the $1,350 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH corrected lower, but the bulls are active near the $1,280 support. Ethereum was able to clear the $1,300 and $1,320 resistance levels. The price is now trading near $1,290 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $1,285 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could start a fresh increase unless there is a clear move below the $1,280 support. Ethereum Price Tops Near $1,350 Ethereum price gained pace for a steady move above the $1,300 resistance zone. ETH even surpassed the $1,320 level and settled well above the 100 hourly simple moving average. However, the bears were active near the $1,350 zone. There were two attempts to clear the $1,350 resistance, but the bulls failed. As a result, there was a bearish reaction from $1,350, similar to bitcoin. Ether price declined below the $1,320 and $1,300 levels. There was a clear move below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1,240 swing low to $1,350 swing high. The price is now trading near $1,290 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $1,285on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. The pair seems to be stable above the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1,240 swing low to $1,350 swing high. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com An immediate resistance on the upside is near the $1,300 level. The first major resistance is near the $1,318 and $1,320 levels. A close above the $1,320 resistance might start a fresh increase. The next major resistance could be $1,350. Any more gains might send the price towards the $1,400 resistance zone. More Losses in ETH? If ethereum fails to climb above the $1,320 resistance, it could continue to move down. An initial support on the downside is near the $1,285 level and the trend line. The next major support is near the $1,280 level, below which the price could gain bearish momentum towards the $1,240 support. Any more losses could lead the price towards the $1,200 support. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now gaining momentum in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is now below the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,280 Major Resistance Level – $1,320]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum jumped and tested the $1,350 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH corrected lower, but the bulls are active near the $1,280 support.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum was able to clear the $1,300 and $1,320 resistance levels.</li>
<li>The price is now trading near $1,290 and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $1,285 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a fresh increase unless there is a clear move below the $1,280 support.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Tops Near $1,350</h2>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-aim-big-1400/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum price gained pace</a> for a steady move above the $1,300 resistance zone. ETH even surpassed the $1,320 level and settled well above the 100 hourly simple moving average.</p>
<p>However, the bears were active near the $1,350 zone. There were two attempts to clear the $1,350 resistance, but the bulls failed. As a result, there was a bearish reaction from $1,350, similar to <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-retreats-18k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bitcoin</a>. Ether price declined below the $1,320 and $1,300 levels.</p>
<p>There was a clear move below the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1,240 swing low to $1,350 swing high. The price is now trading near $1,290 and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</p>
<p>There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $1,285on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. The pair seems to be stable above the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1,240 swing low to $1,350 swing high.</p>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-10.png"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-512400" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-10.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-10.png 1834w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-10-460x212.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-10-860x396.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-10-768x354.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-10-1536x708.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-10-750x346.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-10-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>An immediate resistance on the upside is near the $1,300 level. The first major resistance is near the $1,318 and $1,320 levels. A close above the $1,320 resistance might start a fresh increase. The next major resistance could be $1,350. Any more gains might send the price towards the $1,400 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>More Losses in ETH?</h2>
<p>If ethereum fails to climb above the $1,320 resistance, it could continue to move down. An initial support on the downside is near the $1,285 level and the trend line.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $1,280 level, below which the price could gain bearish momentum towards the $1,240 support. Any more losses could lead the price towards the $1,200 support.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is now gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,280</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,320</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/iStock-1383710952-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Retreats After Fed Decision But 100 SMA Is The Key</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-retreats-18k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 02:29:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512394</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price climbed higher towards $18,400 before there was a bearish reaction. BTC is now trading near a major support at $17,550 and might bounce back. Bitcoin broke the $18,000 resistance zone before there was a downside correction. The price is trading above $17,500 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $17,580 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could start a fresh increase unless it trades below the 100 hourly SMA. Bitcoin Price Remains Supported Bitcoin price extended its increase above the $17,800 resistance zone. BTC even climbed above the $18,000 resistance zone and settled well above the 100 hourly simple moving average. The price traded as high as $18,387 before there was a bearish reaction. The Fed increased interest rates by 0.5%, sparking sharp moves in the market. BTC price reacted the downside and traded below the $18,000 support zone. There was a clear move below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $16,880 low to $18,387 high. However, bitcoin price is trading above $17,500 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. It is holding the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $16,880 low to $18,387 high. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $17,580 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $17,900 level. The first major resistance is near the $18,000 zone, above which the price may perhaps revisit the $18,400 zone. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The next major resistance is near $18,500, above which the price might gain pace and rise towards the $19,200 zone in the near term. Downside Break in BTC? If bitcoin fails to clear the $18,000 resistance, there could be more downsides. An immediate support on the downside is near the $17,580 level and the trend line support. The next major support is near the $17,400 zone and the 100 hourly simple moving average. A downside break below the $17,400 support might call more losses. In the stated case, the price could decline towards the $16,800 support in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now below the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $17,580, followed by $17,400. Major Resistance Levels – $17,900, $18,000 and $18,500.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price climbed higher towards $18,400 before there was a bearish reaction. BTC is now trading near a major support at $17,550 and might bounce back.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin broke the $18,000 resistance zone before there was a downside correction.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $17,500 and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $17,580 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a fresh increase unless it trades below the 100 hourly SMA.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Remains Supported</h2>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-reversal-18k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin price extended its increase</a> above the $17,800 resistance zone. BTC even climbed above the $18,000 resistance zone and settled well above the 100 hourly simple moving average.</p>
<p>The price traded as high as $18,387 before there was a bearish reaction. The Fed increased interest rates by 0.5%, sparking sharp moves in the market. BTC price reacted the downside and traded below the $18,000 support zone. There was a clear move below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $16,880 low to $18,387 high.</p>
<p>However, bitcoin price is trading above $17,500 and the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-ready-17-5k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">100 hourly simple moving average</a>. It is holding the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $16,880 low to $18,387 high.</p>
<p>There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $17,580 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $17,900 level. The first major resistance is near the $18,000 zone, above which the price may perhaps revisit the $18,400 zone.</p>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-11.png"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-512396" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-11.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-11.png 1834w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-11-460x212.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-11-860x396.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-11-768x354.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-11-1536x708.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-11-750x346.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-11-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>

<p>The next major resistance is near $18,500, above which the price might gain pace and rise towards the $19,200 zone in the near term.</p>
<h2>Downside Break in BTC?</h2>
<p>If bitcoin fails to clear the $18,000 resistance, there could be more downsides. An immediate support on the downside is near the $17,580 level and the trend line support.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $17,400 zone and the 100 hourly simple moving average. A downside break below the $17,400 support might call more losses. In the stated case, the price could decline towards the $16,800 support in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $17,580, followed by $17,400.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $17,900, $18,000 and $18,500.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/shutterstock_1363186970-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Volatility Explodes Around $18K Level, As Fed Reveals 50 Basis Point Rate Increase</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-volatility-explodes-fed-reveals-50-basis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony Spilotro]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 20:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcud]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512390</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price touched a high of nearly $18,400 in anticipation of today’s Federal Reserve meeting, where the US central bank was expected to raise interest rates by 50 basis points. Volatility picked up as the Fed meeting commenced, with Bitcoin suffering a sudden pullback to $17,700. Here’s what you need to know about the last Fed meeting of the year.  No Pivot: Fed Hikes Rates 50 Basis Points All eyes were on today’s Fed meeting and if Fed Chair Jerome Powell would follow through and soften interest rate hikes from the previously aggressive 75-basis points, to a more tolerable 50-basis points increase.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Prediction: What Elliott Wave Theory Suggests Is Next For BTC Although Powell’s speech was the most dovish in nearly twelve months of meetings, the end result was still an increase in rates, with no true pivot in sight.  What this means for risk assets like crypto or the stock market, remains to be seen.  Explosive volatility struck BTC ahead of the Fed meeting &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com Bitcoin Pulls Back Promptly As FOMC Meeting Begins November CPI data came in lower than expected yesterday, prompting Bitcoin to front run today’s Fed meeting slightly.  In the hours leading up to the meeting. Bitcoin climbed to close to $18,400 at the daily high. The moment the meeting began the top brass cryptocurrency by market cap plunged by $700 in one five-minute candle.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Fundamental Expert Breaks Down Why The Bottom Is In The move could have been investors in slight profit selling the news, or potentially a shakeout ahead of a larger breakout. Bitcoin has been entrenched in an arduous downtrend for more than a year and counting and sellers could also be taking an opportunity to exit at each sign of a rally.  Bitcoin will need to reclaim today’s high of $18,400 and push through the $20,000 range before considering a potential bottom in the crypto market.  A slightly softer Fed stance is certainly a good sign.  Featured image from iStock, charts from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-fundamental-expert-bottom/">Bitcoin price</a> touched a high of nearly $18,400 in anticipation of today’s Federal Reserve meeting, where the US central bank was expected to raise interest rates by 50 basis points.</p>
<p>Volatility picked up as the Fed meeting commenced, with Bitcoin suffering a sudden pullback to $17,700. Here’s what you need to know about the last Fed meeting of the year. </p>
<h2>No Pivot: Fed Hikes Rates 50 Basis Points</h2>
<p>All eyes were on today’s Fed meeting and if Fed Chair Jerome Powell would follow through and soften interest rate hikes from the previously aggressive 75-basis points, to a more tolerable 50-basis points increase. </p>

<p>Although Powell’s speech was the most dovish in nearly twelve months of meetings, the end result was still an increase in rates, with no true pivot in sight.  What this means for risk assets like crypto or the stock market, remains to be seen. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-large wp-image-512392 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT_2022-12-14_15-52-03-860x362.png" alt="BTCUSDT_2022-12-14_15-52-03" width="860" height="362" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT_2022-12-14_15-52-03-860x362.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT_2022-12-14_15-52-03-460x194.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT_2022-12-14_15-52-03-768x324.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT_2022-12-14_15-52-03-1536x647.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT_2022-12-14_15-52-03-2048x863.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT_2022-12-14_15-52-03-750x316.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT_2022-12-14_15-52-03-1140x480.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>

<h2>Bitcoin Pulls Back Promptly As FOMC Meeting Begins</h2>
<p>November CPI data came in lower than expected yesterday, prompting Bitcoin to front run today’s Fed meeting slightly. </p>
<p>In the hours leading up to the meeting. Bitcoin climbed to close to $18,400 at the daily high. The moment the <a href="https://www.federalreserve.gov/monetarypolicy/fomccalendars.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">meeting</a> began the top brass cryptocurrency by market cap plunged by $700 in one five-minute candle. </p>

<p>The move could have been investors in slight profit selling the news, or potentially a shakeout ahead of a larger breakout.</p>
<p>Bitcoin has been entrenched in an arduous downtrend for more than a year and counting and sellers could also be taking an opportunity to exit at each sign of a rally. </p>
<p>Bitcoin will need to reclaim today’s high of $18,400 and push through the $20,000 range before considering a potential bottom in the crypto market. </p>
<p>A slightly softer Fed stance is certainly a good sign. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/iStock-1434336064-460x460.jpeg" width="460" height="460" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Ethereum’s Rejection At $1,350 Says About The Cryptocurrency</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/what-ethereums-rejection-at-1350-says-about-the-cryptocurrency/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 20:28:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#ETHLDN]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512385</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum saw an increase in its price on Tuesday along with the rest of the crypto market following the positive CPI data release. The jump in price saw Ethereum finally beat the $1,300 price point after hovering around $1,200 coming out of the weekend. However, the digital asset had met significant resistance at the $1,350 price level, which could end up being a bearish development for the cryptocurrency. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Aim Big After Recent Breakout Above $1,300 Ethereum Trades Are Wary Currently, Ethereum traders are still very on edge regarding the cryptocurrency. Even the Tuesday recovery has not done much to actually instill faith in buyers, especially given the Fed’s announcement that is expected to happen on Wednesday. Expectations remain narrow because even though inflation saw a slowdown, it still remains high at 7.1%. Given this, traders are still being conservative in their positions and are not placing too much emphasis on ETH at this time. This is expected to continue through much of the midweek trading day until Powell’s announcement is live. There are also expectations to follow depending on what stance the Fed takes this time around. Over the last couple of months, the Fed had been hawkish due to the rising inflation in the country. But given that inflation had actually come out lower this time around, it could see the Fed soften its stance. If not, then a continuous hawkish stance from the Fed would no doubt see a retracement in the crypto market, which could see Ethereum lose all of its gains from Tuesday. Binance FUD Affects ETH Over the last couple of days, the Binance crypto exchange had been the target to crypto users’ ire as questions about its reserves were raised. As a result, there was massive withdrawals from the exchange, with Binance Ethereum withdrawals accounting for the majority of ETH withdrawals from centralized exchanges over the past week. As it is now, there are still rumors that the exchange may be insolvent and some are beginning to prepare for another FTX-level event if Binance were to fall.  Naturally, this has led to caution among investors who expect a downtrend if such a thing were to happen. Related Reading: BNB Price Prediction: Breaking This Barrier Could Spark a Significant Surge Alternatively, the withdrawals from centralized exchanges could also point towards accumulation among ETH holders. The reduced volume on centralized exchanges could mean a bottom for the digital asset, and if the Fed announcement turns out to be positive, ETH is likely to see $1,400 before the close of day.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum saw an increase in its price on Tuesday along with the rest of the crypto market following the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/bitcoin-price-breaks-above-18200-cpi-data-comes-in-better-than-expected/">positive CPI data release</a>. The jump in price saw Ethereum finally beat the $1,300 price point after hovering around $1,200 coming out of the weekend. However, the digital asset had met significant resistance at the $1,350 price level, which could end up being a bearish development for the cryptocurrency.</p>

<h2>Ethereum Trades Are Wary</h2>
<p>Currently, Ethereum traders are still very on edge regarding the cryptocurrency. Even the Tuesday recovery has not done much to actually instill faith in buyers, especially given the Fed’s announcement that is expected to happen on Wednesday. Expectations remain narrow because even though inflation saw a slowdown, it still remains high at 7.1%.</p>
<p>Given this, traders are still being conservative in their positions and are not placing too much emphasis on ETH at this time. This is expected to continue through much of the midweek trading day until Powell’s announcement is live.</p>
<p>There are also expectations to follow depending on what stance the Fed takes this time around. Over the last couple of months, the Fed had been hawkish due to the rising inflation in the country. But given that inflation had actually come out lower this time around, it could see the Fed soften its stance. If not, then a continuous hawkish stance from the Fed would no doubt see a retracement in the crypto market, which could see Ethereum lose all of its gains from Tuesday.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-512387 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-860x376.png" alt="Ethereum ETH ETHUSDT" width="860" height="376" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-860x376.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-460x201.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-768x336.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-1536x671.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-750x328.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-1140x498.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT.png 1814w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
Binance FUD Affects ETH
<p>Over the last couple of days, the Binance crypto exchange had been the target to crypto users’ ire as questions about its reserves were raised. As a result, there was massive withdrawals from the exchange, with Binance Ethereum withdrawals accounting for the majority of ETH withdrawals from centralized exchanges over the past week.</p>
<p>As it is now, there are still rumors that the exchange may be insolvent and some are beginning to prepare for another FTX-level event if Binance were to fall.  Naturally, this has led to caution among investors who expect a downtrend if such a thing were to happen.</p>

<p>Alternatively, the <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnodealerts/status/1602891130768707584?s=20&amp;t=ZszuWs9ZeMXVRTi1elxhxA" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">withdrawals from centralized exchanges</a> could also point towards accumulation among ETH holders. The reduced volume on centralized exchanges could mean a bottom for the digital asset, and if the Fed announcement turns out to be positive, ETH is likely to see $1,400 before the close of day.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/ETH-COIN-460x345.jpeg" width="460" height="345" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FUD Intensifies: Can Binance Survive Or Is This The End?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/fud-intensifies-can-binance-survive-or-is-this-the-end/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 20:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnbusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512379</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Binance, the largest crypto exchange in the world by trading volume, has been the target of massive FUD (Fear, Uncertainty, and Doubt, for the uninitiated) over the last couple of days. After FTX collapsed, users in the space began to question if exchanges actually held enough in their reserves to honor all customers. Given what happened to FTX, is it possible for Binance to come out of this unscathed? Related Reading: Why Goldman Sachs Expects This Asset Class To Outperform Bitcoin Binance Withdrawals Intensify As the FUD spread across social media platforms, Binance users had taken to withdrawing their deposits from the exchange en masse. Data aggregator platform reported on Tuesday that Binance’s withdrawals had crossed $1.9 billion, and by the end of the day, reports were that the withdrawals were eventually higher than $3 billion in a single day. According to the data released, the withdrawals were one of the highest single-day volume for the crypto exchange, which understandably had users at the edge of their seats. However, Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao had come out to quell fears, explaining that it was nowhere near the highest single-day withdrawals the exchange had processed. Zhao explained that Binance had seen higher volumes when the LUNA cryptocurrency had collapsed, as well as during the FTX implosion. Most of the FUD had stemmed from the ‘audit’ report from Mazars which had drawn criticism from some experts in the industry. The multiple tweets saying that the Mazars report did not qualify as an audit had gained traction, leading to the current situation. Can The Crypto Exchange Survive? So far, Binance has been able to wade through the enormous FUD without much of a problem. Reports on social media say that despite the large withdrawal volumes, the crypto exchange continues to honor all of them in a timely manner. Also, data on Nansen show that deposits into the crypto exchange has been high during this time, offsetting the outflows to a significant degree. This tweet retweeted by “CZ” includes a screenshot of Nansen’s dashboard that showed Binance inflows were almost as high as outflows, resulting in negative net flows of only $378 million for the 24-hour period. CEO Zhao has referred to the current FUD as a “stress test” that “helps to build the credibility for exchanges that passes the test.” Haters: Omg omg!! #binance saw over 6 bn in withdrawals yesterday!!But these fudders did not tell that it got more deposits (6.56B) than withdrawals. The overall volume 12.6B $!! Many exchanges cannot even handle 100 M volume!!@cz_binance we support #Binance unconditionally!! pic.twitter.com/tIazDsLN0H &#8212; Spidey_ElonFan (@spideycyp_155) December 14, 2022 Related Reading: Dogecoin (DOGE) Climbs 2.58% In 24 Hours, Can It Reach $0.1 Before The Week Runs Out? At this time, there have been no obvious signs of struggle for the crypto exchange. Ki Young Ju, CEO of CryptoQuant, also took to Twitter to publicly state that there are no “shady on-chain activities” on the part of the exchange.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance, the largest crypto exchange in the world by trading volume, has been the target of massive FUD (Fear, Uncertainty, and Doubt, for the uninitiated) over the last couple of days. After FTX collapsed, users in the space began to question if exchanges actually held enough in their reserves to honor all customers. Given what happened to FTX, is it possible for Binance to come out of this unscathed?</p>

<h2><strong>Binance Withdrawals Intensify</strong></h2>
<p>As the FUD spread across social media platforms, Binance users had taken to withdrawing their deposits from the exchange en masse. Data aggregator platform reported on Tuesday that Binance’s withdrawals had crossed $1.9 billion, and by the end of the day, reports were that the withdrawals were eventually higher than $3 billion in a single day.</p>
<p>According to the data released, the withdrawals were one of the highest single-day volume for the crypto exchange, which understandably had users at the edge of their seats. However, Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao had come out to quell fears, explaining that it was nowhere near the highest single-day withdrawals the exchange had processed. Zhao explained that Binance had seen higher volumes when the LUNA cryptocurrency had collapsed, as well as during the FTX implosion.</p>
<p>Most of the FUD had stemmed from the ‘audit’ report from Mazars which had drawn criticism from some experts in the industry. The multiple tweets saying that the Mazars report did not qualify as an audit had gained traction, leading to the current situation.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-512383 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-BNB-BNBUSDT-860x376.png" alt="Binance BNB BNBUSDT" width="860" height="376" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-BNB-BNBUSDT-860x376.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-BNB-BNBUSDT-460x201.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-BNB-BNBUSDT-768x336.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-BNB-BNBUSDT-1536x671.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-BNB-BNBUSDT-750x328.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-BNB-BNBUSDT-1140x498.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-BNB-BNBUSDT.png 1814w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
Can The Crypto Exchange Survive?
<p>So far, Binance has been able to wade through the enormous FUD without much of a problem. Reports on social media say that despite the large withdrawal volumes, the crypto exchange continues to honor all of them in a timely manner.</p>
<p>Also, data on Nansen show that deposits into the crypto exchange has been high during this time, offsetting the outflows to a significant degree. This <a href="https://twitter.com/spideycyp_155/status/1602962197009010690?s=20&amp;t=xJKinDsncVmhoflgZxzQAA" rel="nofollow">tweet</a> retweeted by “CZ” includes a screenshot of Nansen’s dashboard that showed Binance inflows were almost as high as outflows, resulting in negative net flows of only $378 million for the 24-hour period. CEO Zhao has referred to the current FUD as a “stress test” that “helps to build the credibility for exchanges that passes the test.”</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Haters: Omg omg!! <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#binance</a> saw over 6 bn in withdrawals yesterday!!But these fudders did not tell that it got more deposits (6.56B) than withdrawals. The overall volume 12.6B $!! Many exchanges cannot even handle 100 M volume!!<a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@cz_binance</a> we support <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Binance</a> unconditionally!! <a href="https://t.co/tIazDsLN0H" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/tIazDsLN0H</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Spidey_ElonFan (@spideycyp_155) <a href="https://twitter.com/spideycyp_155/status/1602962197009010690?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">December 14, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>

<p>At this time, there have been no obvious signs of struggle for the crypto exchange. Ki Young Ju, CEO of CryptoQuant, also took to Twitter to publicly state that there are no “shady on-chain activities” on the part of the exchange.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-coin-460x383.jpeg" width="460" height="383" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Toncoin (TON) Shoots Up 50% In 7 Days &#8211; This Telegram Feature Cranks Up Demand</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/altcoin/toncoin-ton-shoots-up-50-in-7-days-this-telegram-feature-cranks-up-demand/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 19:48:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[telegram]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TON]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512408</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Toncoin (TON) is currently outperforming all other cryptocurrencies in the top 100 by market capitalization on a weekly basis. With a price increase of around 50% within the last seven days, the token is the undisputed leader, followed by Stacks (+16%) and Bitcoin SV (+14%). Over the last 24 hours, Toncoin is writing a whopping 21% gain. While it was trading at $1.86 on Sunday, the cryptocurrency was trading for $2.86 at press time. In the last 24 hours alone, the trading volume has skyrocketed 83%, to $95.4 million. On the daily chart, TON is thus approaching its all-time high of $3.26. A Reason For The Skyrocketing Price Of Toncoin The reason for the recent pump of the Toncoin could be a feature of Telegram, which was announced last week. Pavel Durov himself, the founder and head of the popular messenger, introduced a feature for Telegram that allows users to buy an anonymous phone number with the token and create an account with it. Related Reading: VanEck’s Bitcoin Prediction Stands At $10K-$12K By Q1 2023 On December 07, the Telegram Messenger team launched the sale of virtual numbers with the +888 prefix, which exist as collectible on the The Open Network blockchain. Users can log in to the Fragment platform with the TON blockchain-backed anonymous numbers and enjoy &#8220;ultimate privacy.&#8221; Fragment is a decentralized auction platform founded by Durov. It sells the anonymous numbers compatible only with Telegram. Purchases are transacted on the platform using The Open Network Telegram token. Related Reading: Senator Lummis Claims Pouring Retirement Funds In Bitcoin Is Still A Good Idea These numbers can then be used to chat completely anonymously, but not to call or register with third-party services. In addition, purchased numbers can be stored in a regular Toncoin wallet, transferred to other users, and offered for sale on marketplaces, just like any other NFT on the The Open Network blockchain. +888 8 888 Is The Most Popular Telegram Number Some numbers are so popular that they are auctioned on Fragment for over $100,000. The most popular number is +888 8 888, for which 38,290 TON, the equivalent of about $103,000, are currently being bid. The auction runs for a little more than six days. The Open Network is the brainchild of the Telegram development team, which was forced to abandon the blockchain solution due to pressure from the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in June 2020. The SEC forced Telegram to pay $1.2 billion in raised funds back to investors and pay an $18.5 million fine to settle the SEC charges. Since then, the TON ecosystem has evolved as a standalone ecosystem and regularly integrates innovations into the Telegram messenger.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Toncoin (TON) is currently outperforming all other cryptocurrencies in the top 100 by market capitalization on a weekly basis. With a price increase of around 50% within the last seven days, the token is the undisputed leader, followed by Stacks (+16%) and Bitcoin SV (+14%).</p>
<p>Over the last 24 hours, Toncoin is writing a whopping 21% gain. While it was<a href="https://newsbtc.com/toncoin-ton/toncoin-ton-leads-market-gains-with-over-27-in-a-week/"> trading</a> at $1.86 on Sunday, the cryptocurrency was trading for $2.86 at press time.</p>
<p>In the last 24 hours alone, the trading volume has skyrocketed 83%, to $95.4 million. On the daily chart, TON is thus approaching its all-time high of $3.26.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-512410 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TONUSDT_2022-12-14_13-50-42.png" alt="Toncoin/USDT on OKX" width="2957" height="1611" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TONUSDT_2022-12-14_13-50-42.png 2957w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TONUSDT_2022-12-14_13-50-42-460x251.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TONUSDT_2022-12-14_13-50-42-860x469.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TONUSDT_2022-12-14_13-50-42-768x418.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TONUSDT_2022-12-14_13-50-42-1536x837.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TONUSDT_2022-12-14_13-50-42-2048x1116.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TONUSDT_2022-12-14_13-50-42-750x409.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/TONUSDT_2022-12-14_13-50-42-1140x621.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2957px) 100vw, 2957px" />
<h2><b>A Reason For The Skyrocketing Price Of Toncoin</b></h2>
<p>The reason for the recent pump of the Toncoin could be a feature of Telegram, which was announced last week.</p>
<p>Pavel Durov himself, the founder and head of the popular messenger, introduced a feature for Telegram that allows users to buy an anonymous phone number with the token and create an account with it.</p>
<p>Related Reading:<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/vanecks-bitcoin-prediction-stands-at-10k-12k-by-q1-2023/"> VanEck’s Bitcoin Prediction Stands At $10K-$12K By Q1 2023</a></p>
<p>On December 07, the Telegram Messenger team launched the sale of virtual numbers with the +888 prefix, which exist as collectible on the The Open Network blockchain.</p>
<p>Users can log in to the Fragment platform with the TON blockchain-backed anonymous numbers and enjoy &#8220;ultimate privacy.&#8221;</p>
<p>Fragment is a decentralized auction platform founded by Durov. It sells the anonymous numbers compatible only with Telegram. Purchases are transacted on the platform using The Open Network Telegram token.</p>
<p>Related Reading:<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/senator-lummis-claims-pouring-retirement-funds-in-bitcoin-is-still-a-good-idea/"> Senator Lummis Claims Pouring Retirement Funds In Bitcoin Is Still A Good Idea</a></p>
<p>These numbers can then be used to chat completely anonymously, but not to call or register with third-party services.</p>
<p>In addition, purchased numbers can be stored in a regular Toncoin wallet, transferred to other users, and offered for sale on marketplaces, just like any other NFT on the The Open Network blockchain.</p>
<b>+888 8 888 Is The Most Popular Telegram Number</b>
<p>Some numbers are so popular that they are auctioned on Fragment for over $100,000. The most popular number is +888 8 888, for which 38,290 TON, the equivalent of about $103,000, are currently being bid.</p>
<p>The auction runs for a little more than six days.</p>
<p>The Open Network is the brainchild of the Telegram development team, which was forced to<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/company/goodbye-telegram-here-comes-secretum/"> abandon</a> the blockchain solution due to pressure from the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in June 2020.</p>
<p>The SEC forced Telegram to pay $1.2 billion in raised funds back to investors and pay an $18.5 million fine to settle the SEC charges.</p>
<p>Since then, the TON ecosystem has evolved as a standalone ecosystem and regularly integrates innovations into the Telegram messenger.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/telegram-ton-cryptocurrency-retail-trader-investor-shutterstock_1501389587-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BNB Price Prediction: Breaking This Barrier Could Spark a Significant Surge</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/bnb/bnb-price-prediction-surge-285/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 05:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnbusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512374</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[BNB price (Binance coin) found support near $255 against the US Dollar. BNB is rising and might gain pace if it clears the $285 resistance zone. Binance coin price started a recovery wave from the $255 support against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $280 and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $285 on the 4-hours chart of the BNB/USD pair (data source from Binance). The pair could start a fresh rally if it clears the $285 and $290 levels. Binance Coin Price Aims Upside Break After a steady decline, BNB price settled below the $280 level. It tested the $255 support zone and traded as low as $253.8. Recently, there was a recovery wave above the $260 level, similar to bitcoin and ethereum. The price climbed above the $265 and $268 resistance levels. There was a clear move above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the main decline from the $317 swing high to $253 swing low. However, bnb price is still trading below $280 and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours). On the upside, the $280 and $285 levels are immediate hurdles. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $285 on the 4-hours chart of the BNB/USD pair. Source: BNBUSD on TradingView.com The 50% Fib retracement level of the main decline from the $317 swing high to $253 swing low is also near $285. The next major resistance is near the $290 level, above which the price is likely to aim a test of the $320 level in the near term. Any more gains might send the price towards the $350 level. Fresh Decline in BNB? If BNB fails to clear the $285 resistance, it could start a fresh decline. An initial support on the downside is near the $268 and $265 levels. The first major support is near the $260 level. The next major support is near the $255 level. If there is a downside break below the $255 support, there could be an extended decline towards the $225 support. Technical Indicators 4-Hours MACD – The MACD for BNB/USD is gaining pace in the bullish zone. 4-Hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BNB/USD is currently near the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $265, $260 and $255. Major Resistance Levels – $285, $290 and $320.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>BNB price (Binance coin) found support near $255 against the US Dollar. BNB is rising and might gain pace if it clears the $285 resistance zone.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Binance coin price started a recovery wave from the $255 support against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $280 and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $285 on the 4-hours chart of the BNB/USD pair (data source from Binance).</li>
<li>The pair could start a fresh rally if it clears the $285 and $290 levels.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Binance Coin Price Aims Upside Break</h2>
<p>After a steady decline, BNB price settled below the $280 level. It tested the $255 support zone and traded as low as $253.8. Recently, there was a recovery wave above the $260 level, similar to <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-reversal-18k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bitcoin</a> and <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-aim-big-1400/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ethereum</a>.</p>
<p>The price climbed above the $265 and $268 resistance levels. There was a clear move above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the main decline from the $317 swing high to $253 swing low. However, bnb price is still trading below $280 and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours).</p>
<p>On the upside, the $280 and $285 levels are immediate hurdles. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $285 on the 4-hours chart of the BNB/USD pair.</p>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-Coin-BNB.png"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-512375" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-Coin-BNB.png" alt="Binance Coin Price BNB" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-Coin-BNB.png 1834w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-Coin-BNB-460x212.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-Coin-BNB-860x396.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-Coin-BNB-768x354.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-Coin-BNB-1536x708.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-Coin-BNB-750x346.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Binance-Coin-BNB-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BNBUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BNBUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The 50% Fib retracement level of the main decline from the $317 swing high to $253 swing low is also near $285. The next major resistance is near the $290 level, above which the price is likely to aim a test of the $320 level in the near term. Any more gains might send the price towards the $350 level.</p>
<h2>Fresh Decline in BNB?</h2>
<p>If BNB fails to clear the $285 resistance, it could start a fresh decline. An initial support on the downside is near the $268 and $265 levels.</p>
<p>The first major support is near the $260 level. The next major support is near the $255 level. If there is a downside break below the $255 support, there could be an extended decline towards the $225 support.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>4-Hours MACD – The MACD for BNB/USD is gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4-Hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BNB/USD is currently near the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $265, $260 and $255.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $285, $290 and $320.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Depositphotos_78872860_s-2019-460x293.jpg" width="460" height="293" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Aim Big After Recent Breakout Above $1,300</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-aim-big-1400/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 04:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=512369</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum gained pace for a move above the $1,300 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH is consolidating gains and might eye a fresh increase in the near term. Ethereum was able to clear the $1,280 and $1,300 resistance levels. The price is now trading above $1,280 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There was a break above a key contracting triangle with resistance near $1,275 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could correct lower, but the bulls might be active near $1,280 and $1,270. Ethereum Price Breaks Hurdle Ethereum price remained well bid above the $1,240 support zone. ETH formed a base above the $1,250 level and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There was a strong increase above the $1,280 resistance after the US CPI release, similar to bitcoin. Besides, there was a break above a key contracting triangle with resistance near $1,275 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. The pair even cleared the $1,300 resistance zone. Ether price traded as high as $1,349 before the bears appeared. Recently, there was a downside correction below the $1,320 level. The price declined below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent wave from the $1,240 swing low to $1,349 high. However, the bulls were active near the $1,300 support zone. It also stayed well above the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent wave from the $1,240 swing low to $1,349 high. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com An immediate resistance on the upside is near the $1,325 level. The first major resistance is near the $1,345 and $1,350 levels. A close above the $1,350 resistance might start a fresh increase. The next major resistance could be $1,400. Any more gains might send the price towards the $1,500 resistance zone. Dips Limited in ETH? If ethereum fails to climb above the $1,350 resistance, it could start another downside correction. An initial support on the downside is near the $1,295 level. The next major support is near the $1,280 level and the 100 hourly simple moving average, below which the price could even retest the $1,260 support. Any more losses could lead the price towards the $1,245 support. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now losing momentum in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is now well above the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,280 Major Resistance Level – $1,350]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum gained pace for a move above the $1,300 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH is consolidating gains and might eye a fresh increase in the near term.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum was able to clear the $1,280 and $1,300 resistance levels.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $1,280 and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</li>
<li>There was a break above a key contracting triangle with resistance near $1,275 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could correct lower, but the bulls might be active near $1,280 and $1,270.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Breaks Hurdle</h2>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-upside-break-1300/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum price remained well bid</a> above the $1,240 support zone. ETH formed a base above the $1,250 level and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</p>
<p>There was a strong increase above the $1,280 resistance after the US CPI release, similar to <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-reversal-18k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bitcoin</a>. Besides, there was a break above a key contracting triangle with resistance near $1,275 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. The pair even cleared the $1,300 resistance zone.</p>
<p>Ether price traded as high as $1,349 before the bears appeared. Recently, there was a downside correction below the $1,320 level. The price declined below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent wave from the $1,240 swing low to $1,349 high.</p>
<p>However, the bulls were active near the $1,300 support zone. It also stayed well above the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent wave from the $1,240 swing low to $1,349 high.</p>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-9.png"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-512370" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-9.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-9.png 1834w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-9-460x212.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-9-860x396.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-9-768x354.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-9-1536x708.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-9-750x346.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-9-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>An immediate resistance on the upside is near the $1,325 level. The first major resistance is near the $1,345 and $1,350 levels. A close above the $1,350 resistance might start a fresh increase. The next major resistance could be $1,400. Any more gains might send the price towards the $1,500 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Dips Limited in ETH?</h2>
<p>If ethereum fails to climb above the $1,350 resistance, it could start another downside correction. An initial support on the downside is near the $1,295 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $1,280 level and the 100 hourly simple moving average, below which the price could even retest the $1,260 support. Any more losses could lead the price towards the $1,245 support.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is now losing momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is now well above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,280</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,350</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Depositphotos_201447528_s-2019-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/

Object Caching 169/173 objects using apc
Page Caching using disk: enhanced (Page is feed) 
Database Caching 34/46 queries in 0.008 seconds using memcached

Served from: newsbtc.com @ 2022-12-15 01:56:36 by W3 Total Cache
-->