<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 02:50:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Indicators Suggest A Strengthening Case For Surge Above $1,850</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-surge-above-1850/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 02:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533701</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum price is still below the $1,840 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH could start a decent increase if it clears $1,840 and $1,850. Ethereum is currently facing a strong hurdle near the $1,850 resistance zone. The price is trading above $1,800 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,830 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could start a fresh increase if it clears the $1,840 and $1,850 resistance levels. Ethereum Price Could Rally Above $1,850 Ethereum’s price started a decent upward move from the $1,780 support zone. ETH moved above the $1,800 and $1,820 resistance levels, similar to Bitcoin. The price even spiked toward the $1,840 resistance where the bears emerged. A high is formed near $1,835 and the price is now consolidating gains. Ether is now trading above $1,800 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. It is also consolidating near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1,782 swing low to the $1,834 high. Immediate resistance is near the $1,830 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,830 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com The next resistance sits near $1,840, above which Ethereum could gain bullish momentum and rise toward $1,850.  If there is a move above the $1,880 resistance level, the price might rise toward the $1,920 level. Any more gains above the $1,920 resistance zone could start a decent increase toward the $2,000 resistance. Fresh Decline in ETH? If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,840 resistance, it could start a downside correction. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,815 level and 100 hourly SMA. The next major support is near the $1,800 zone or the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1,782 swing low to the $1,834 high. If there is a clear move below the $1,800 support, the price could gain bearish momentum. In the stated case, the price might drop toward the $1,780 support zone. Any more losses may perhaps take the price toward the $1,740 level in the near term. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is gaining momentum in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is above the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,800 Major Resistance Level – $1,850]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum price is still below the $1,840 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH could start a decent increase if it clears $1,840 and $1,850.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum is currently facing a strong hurdle near the $1,850 resistance zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $1,800 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,830 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a fresh increase if it clears the $1,840 and $1,850 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Could Rally Above $1,850</h2>
<p>Ethereum’s price started a decent upward move from the $1,780 support zone. ETH moved above the $1,800 and $1,820 resistance levels, similar to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-rally-28k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p>The price even spiked toward the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-recovery-fade-1850/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$1,840 resistance</a> where the bears emerged. A high is formed near $1,835 and the price is now consolidating gains. Ether is now trading above $1,800 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</p>
<p>It is also consolidating near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1,782 swing low to the $1,834 high. Immediate resistance is near the $1,830 level. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $1,830 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-11.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-533702" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-11.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1950" height="1109" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-11.png 1950w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-11-460x262.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-11-860x489.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-11-768x437.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-11-1536x874.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-11-750x427.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-11-1140x648.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1950px) 100vw, 1950px"/></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The next resistance sits near $1,840, above which Ethereum could gain bullish momentum and rise toward $1,850.  If there is a move above the $1,880 resistance level, the price might rise toward the $1,920 level. Any more gains above the $1,920 resistance zone could start a decent increase toward the $2,000 resistance.</p>
<h2>Fresh Decline in ETH?</h2>
<p>If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,840 resistance, it could start a downside correction. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,815 level and 100 hourly SMA.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $1,800 zone or the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $1,782 swing low to the $1,834 high. If there is a clear move below the $1,800 support, the price could gain bearish momentum. In the stated case, the price might drop toward the $1,780 support zone. Any more losses may perhaps take the price toward the $1,740 level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,800</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,850</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/shutterstock_584552989-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Close Above $28K Could Spark A Fresh Rally</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-rally-28k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 02:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533698</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is rising above $27,200. BTC might gain bullish momentum if it clears the key $28,000 resistance zone in the coming sessions. Bitcoin is moving higher above the $27,000 and $27,200 levels. The price is trading above $27,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There was a break above a connecting bearish trend line with resistance near $27,000 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could start a fresh rally if it clears the $27,550 and $28,000 resistance levels. Bitcoin Price Attempts Upside Break Bitcoin price started a fresh decline below the $26,800 level. BTC retested the $26,550 support zone and recently started a fresh increase. There was a decent upward move above the $27,000 resistance zone. Besides, there was a break above a connecting bearish trend line with resistance near $27,000 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Bitcoin price is now trading above $27,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. It is also above the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $27,677 swing high to the $26,550 low. Immediate resistance is now forming near the $27,420 level. The 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $27,677 swing high to the $26,550 low is also near the $27,420 level. The next major resistance is near the $27,550 level. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com A close above the $27,550 resistance might start a decent increase. The next key resistance is near $28,000, above which the price might gain bullish momentum and test the $29,200 resistance. Any more gains might send the price toward the $30,000 level. Fresh Decline in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $27,550 resistance, it could start a fresh decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $27,000 level and the 100 hourly SMA. The next major support is near the $26,800 zone, below which the price might struggle to recover. In the stated case, it could revisit the $26,550 level. Any more losses might take Bitcoin toward the $26,000 level in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $27,000, followed by $26,550. Major Resistance Levels – $27,420, $27,550, and $28,000.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is rising above $27,200. BTC might gain bullish momentum if it clears the key $28,000 resistance zone in the coming sessions.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is moving higher above the $27,000 and $27,200 levels.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $27,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There was a break above a connecting bearish trend line with resistance near $27,000 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a fresh rally if it clears the $27,550 and $28,000 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Attempts Upside Break</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price started a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-holds-support-28k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">fresh decline</a> below the $26,800 level. BTC retested the $26,550 support zone and recently started a fresh increase.</p>
<p>There was a decent upward move above the $27,000 resistance zone. Besides, there was a break above a connecting bearish trend line with resistance near $27,000 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Bitcoin price is now trading above $27,000 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-strong-27k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>.</p>
<p>It is also above the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $27,677 swing high to the $26,550 low. Immediate resistance is now forming near the $27,420 level.</p>
<p>The 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $27,677 swing high to the $26,550 low is also near the $27,420 level. The next major resistance is near the $27,550 level.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-13.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-533699" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-13.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1950" height="1109" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-13.png 1950w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-13-460x262.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-13-860x489.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-13-768x437.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-13-1536x874.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-13-750x427.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-13-1140x648.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1950px) 100vw, 1950px"/></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>A close above the $27,550 resistance might start a decent increase. The next key resistance is near $28,000, above which the price might gain bullish momentum and test the $29,200 resistance. Any more gains might send the price toward the $30,000 level.</p>
<h2>Fresh Decline in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $27,550 resistance, it could start a fresh decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $27,000 level and the 100 hourly SMA.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $26,800 zone, below which the price might struggle to recover. In the stated case, it could revisit the $26,550 level. Any more losses might take Bitcoin toward the $26,000 level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $27,000, followed by $26,550.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $27,420, $27,550, and $28,000.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/shutterstock_764448946-460x265.jpg" width="460" height="265" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chainlink Price Consolidation Persists: Will Bulls Front A Recovery Soon?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/chainlink/chainlink-price-consolidation-persists-will-bulls-front-a-recovery-soon/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 01:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Chainlink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chainlink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Link]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LINKUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[linkusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533681</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Chainlink price has been trading within a narrow range recently, leading to decreased investor interest. However, in the past 24 hours, the altcoin managed to experience a 1.5% increase, indicating sideways movement. On the weekly chart, LINK showed a 4% upward movement. Despite these gains, the technical analysis indicates that the bears still control the price action. Both demand and accumulation levels remain low, although there has been a slight increase in buying activity on the daily chart. Nonetheless, sellers still dominate the market. Related Reading: Dogecoin, Shiba Inu Whales Move Massive Amounts, Dumping Going On? The decline in Bitcoin&#8217;s price below $27,000 has caused uncertainty among altcoins, preventing them from making decisive moves on their respective charts. Following a period of consolidation, a price breakout is possible. While the technical outlook suggests bearish strength, there are also signals of a potential reversal. However, for LINK to initiate a price recovery, it will depend on broader market strength, as indicated by the decline in the LINK market capitalization, reflecting weak buying power. Chainlink Price Analysis: One-Day At the time of writing, the price of LINK was $6.78, as it attempted to break its sideways trading pattern while remaining below its resistance level of $6.90. A successful breakthrough above $6.90 could potentially trigger a rally toward $7.20. Conversely, if the price falls from its current level, it may decline to $6.30. A breach of the $6.30 support line could push the price below $6. On the other hand, as long as LINK remains above the local support line at $6.60, it has the potential to continue its recovery on the chart. The volume of Chainlink traded in the previous session was positive, indicating buyers were starting to reemerge in the market. Technical Analysis Following sustained selling pressure, LINK is now trying to attract buyers back into the market. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) has been trending upward, nearing the halfway point. However, at the present moment, sellers still outnumber buyers. Additionally, LINK is attempting to trade above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, indicating a renewed demand in the market. Despite the coin&#8217;s recovery attempts, sellers still drive the overall price momentum. A buy signal emerged as the price and buying strength of LINK aimed for recovery. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD), a tool that reflects price momentum and potential trend reversals, formed a green signal bar aligned with a buy signal. Related Reading: Citadel Strikes Back: Sues Crypto Executives Over Trading Secrets This indicated a potential for positive price movement. Additionally, the Bollinger Bands were wide and parallel, suggesting that the coin would likely attempt a breakout from its previous consolidated price action. Featured Image From Gadgets360, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Chainlink price has been trading within a narrow range recently, leading to decreased investor interest. However, in the past 24 hours, the altcoin managed to experience a 1.5% increase, indicating sideways movement.</p>
<p>On the weekly chart, LINK showed a 4% upward movement. Despite these gains, the technical analysis indicates that the bears still control the price action. Both demand and accumulation levels remain low, although there has been a slight increase in buying activity on the daily chart. Nonetheless, sellers still dominate the market.</p>

<p>The decline in Bitcoin&#8217;s price below $27,000 has caused uncertainty among altcoins, preventing them from making decisive moves on their respective charts. Following a period of consolidation, a price breakout is possible.</p>
<p>While the technical outlook suggests bearish strength, there are also signals of a potential reversal. However, for LINK to initiate a price recovery, it will depend on broader market strength, as indicated by the decline in the LINK market capitalization, reflecting weak buying power.</p>
<h2>Chainlink Price Analysis: One-Day</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-533689 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSD_2023-05-18_01-06-24.png" alt="Chainlink" width="1816" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSD_2023-05-18_01-06-24.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSD_2023-05-18_01-06-24-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSD_2023-05-18_01-06-24-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSD_2023-05-18_01-06-24-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSD_2023-05-18_01-06-24-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSD_2023-05-18_01-06-24-750x343.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSD_2023-05-18_01-06-24-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>
<p>At the time of writing, the price of LINK was $6.78, as it attempted to break its sideways trading pattern while remaining below its resistance level of $6.90. A successful breakthrough above $6.90 could potentially trigger a rally toward $7.20.</p>
<p>Conversely, if the price falls from its current level, it may decline to $6.30. A breach of the $6.30 support line could push the price below $6.</p>
<p>On the other hand, as long as LINK remains above the local support line at $6.60, it has the potential to continue its recovery on the chart. The volume of Chainlink traded in the previous session was positive, indicating buyers were starting to reemerge in the market.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-533690 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSD_2023-05-18_01-06-50-1.png" alt="Chainlink" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSD_2023-05-18_01-06-50-1.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSD_2023-05-18_01-06-50-1-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSD_2023-05-18_01-06-50-1-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSD_2023-05-18_01-06-50-1-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSD_2023-05-18_01-06-50-1-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSD_2023-05-18_01-06-50-1-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSD_2023-05-18_01-06-50-1-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>
<p>Following sustained selling pressure, LINK is now trying to attract buyers back into the market. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) has been trending upward, nearing the halfway point. However, at the present moment, sellers still outnumber buyers.</p>
<p>Additionally, LINK is attempting to trade above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, indicating a renewed demand in the market. Despite the coin&#8217;s recovery attempts, sellers still drive the overall price momentum.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-533691 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSD_2023-05-18_01-07-13.png" alt="Chainlink" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSD_2023-05-18_01-07-13.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSD_2023-05-18_01-07-13-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSD_2023-05-18_01-07-13-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSD_2023-05-18_01-07-13-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSD_2023-05-18_01-07-13-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSD_2023-05-18_01-07-13-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/LINKUSD_2023-05-18_01-07-13-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>
<p>A buy signal emerged as the price and buying strength of LINK aimed for recovery. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD), a tool that reflects price momentum and potential trend reversals, formed a green signal bar aligned with a buy signal.</p>

<p>This indicated a potential for positive price movement. Additionally, the Bollinger Bands were wide and parallel, suggesting that the coin would likely attempt a breakout from its previous consolidated price action.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/chainlink-coin-460x270.png" width="460" height="270" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Uniswap And Polkadot Join Forces To Boost Decentralized Trading Volume, Here&#8217;s How</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/uniswap/uniswap-and-polkadot-join-forces-to-boost-decentralized-trading-volume-heres-how/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 01:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uniswap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot (DOT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uniswap (UNI)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UNIUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533664</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Polkadot has announced that Uniswap, the most important decentralized exchange (DEX) in terms of daily traded volume, is coming to its ecosystem via the Moonbeam Network parachain. This development is expected to significantly increase volume and liquidity across the Polkadot ecosystem while providing users a trustless, permissionless, and non-custodial way to trade and access tokens. Related Reading: Crypto Assets Flow From Ethereum To BSC, Are Users Escaping High Gas Fees? Polkadot And Uniswap Partnership Signals New Era For DEX Uniswap&#8217;s arrival on Polkadot is a significant development for the decentralized finance (DeFi) space, as it adds visibility and momentum toward developing a new world of decentralized financial products and services on the Polkadot network. With Uniswap&#8217;s proven track record in the Ethereum ecosystem, the following opportunities will open up on the DeFi sector: Increased liquidity: Uniswap&#8217;s arrival on Polkadot is expected to increase liquidity across the ecosystem, as more users can trade a wider range of assets on the platform. This will likely attract more liquidity providers and traders to the ecosystem, further enhancing liquidity. Interoperability: Polkadot&#8217;s unique architecture enables the creation of customized blockchains, or parachains, that can be tailored to meet the specific needs of different applications. With Uniswap&#8217;s arrival on the Polkadot network, developers will have access to a proven DeFi infrastructure that can be leveraged to create new and innovative products. This is expected to stimulate innovation in the DeFi space while facilitating the seamless asset transfer between Ethereum and Polkadot. Trustless, permissionless, and non-custodial access to tokens: Uniswap provides users a trustless, permissionless, and non-custodial way to access tokens. Its arrival on Polkadot is expected to provide users with a more secure and decentralized way to access tokens, which will likely attract more users to the ecosystem. Improved scalability and security: Polkadot&#8217;s high performance, scalability, and security will benefit Uniswap&#8217;s users, who can trade on a more secure and scalable platform. Furthermore, according to Osama el-Sayed, Global Head of Growth &#38; BD at ParityTech: Polkadot is a strong fit for Uniswap, whose users can discover the network’s high performance, scalability, security, and interoperability. Polkadot’s DeFi ecosystem benefits from a marquee name in the space. What Is The Moonbeam Network? The Moonbeam Network is a Polkadot parachain that provides full Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) compatibility and native interoperability and prioritizes secure cross-chain integration solutions. It has seen impressive user growth over the last year, and the initiative to bring Uniswap to Polkadot and Moonbeam, led by the University of Michigan&#8217;s Blockchain Group, has successfully passed Moonbeam&#8217;s governance processes today following strong community support. Related Reading: Dogecoin, Shiba Inu Whales Move Massive Amounts, Dumping Going On? Adding Uniswap to the Polkadot ecosystem via the Moonbeam Network parachain is a significant development for the DeFi space. By increasing volume and liquidity across the Polkadot network and providing a trustless, permissionless, and non-custodial way to access tokens, Uniswap is expected to stimulate innovation and open up new opportunities for liquidity providers and traders.  Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Polkadot has <a href="https://twitter.com/Polkadot/status/1658820737384292352?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced </a>that Uniswap, the most important decentralized exchange (DEX) in terms of daily traded volume, is coming to its ecosystem via the Moonbeam Network parachain. This development is expected to significantly increase volume and liquidity across the Polkadot ecosystem while providing users a trustless, permissionless, and non-custodial way to trade and access tokens.</p>

<h2><b>Polkadot And Uniswap Partnership Signals New Era For DEX</b></h2>
<p>Uniswap&#8217;s arrival on Polkadot is a significant development for the decentralized finance (DeFi) space, as it adds visibility and momentum toward developing a new world of decentralized financial products and services on the Polkadot network.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">1/ <a href="https://twitter.com/Uniswap?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@Uniswap</a> &#8211; the most popular decentralized exchange by daily traded volume &#8211; is coming to Polkadot via the <a href="https://twitter.com/MoonbeamNetwork?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@MoonbeamNetwork</a> parachain, increasing volume &amp; liquidity across the ecosystem! <a href="https://t.co/lKaceLv6ce" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/lKaceLv6ce</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Polkadot (@Polkadot) <a href="https://twitter.com/Polkadot/status/1658820737384292352?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">May 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>With Uniswap&#8217;s proven track record in the Ethereum ecosystem, the following opportunities will open up on the DeFi sector:</p>
<ul>
<li>Increased liquidity: Uniswap&#8217;s arrival on Polkadot is expected to increase liquidity across the ecosystem, as more users can trade a wider range of assets on the platform. This will likely attract more liquidity providers and traders to the ecosystem, further enhancing liquidity.</li>
<li>Interoperability: Polkadot&#8217;s unique architecture enables the creation of customized blockchains, or parachains, that can be tailored to meet the specific needs of different applications. With Uniswap&#8217;s arrival on the Polkadot network, developers will have access to a proven DeFi infrastructure that can be leveraged to create new and innovative products. This is expected to stimulate innovation in the DeFi space while facilitating the seamless asset transfer between Ethereum and Polkadot.</li>
<li>Trustless, permissionless, and non-custodial access to tokens: Uniswap provides users a trustless, permissionless, and non-custodial way to access tokens. Its arrival on Polkadot is expected to provide users with a more secure and decentralized way to access tokens, which will likely attract more users to the ecosystem.</li>
<li>Improved scalability and security: Polkadot&#8217;s high performance, scalability, and security will benefit Uniswap&#8217;s users, who can trade on a more secure and scalable platform.</li>
</ul>
<p>Furthermore, according to Osama el-Sayed, Global Head of Growth &amp; BD at ParityTech: </p>
<blockquote><p>Polkadot is a strong fit for Uniswap, whose users can discover the network’s high performance, scalability, security, and interoperability. Polkadot’s DeFi ecosystem benefits from a marquee name in the space.</p></blockquote>
<b>What Is The Moonbeam Network?</b>
<p>The Moonbeam Network is a Polkadot parachain that provides full Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) compatibility and native interoperability and prioritizes secure cross-chain integration solutions. It has seen impressive user growth over the last year, and the initiative to bring Uniswap to Polkadot and Moonbeam, led by the University of Michigan&#8217;s Blockchain Group, has successfully passed Moonbeam&#8217;s governance processes today following strong community support.</p>

<p>Adding Uniswap to the Polkadot ecosystem via the Moonbeam Network parachain is a significant development for the DeFi space. By increasing volume and liquidity across the Polkadot network and providing a trustless, permissionless, and non-custodial way to access tokens, Uniswap is expected to stimulate innovation and open up new opportunities for liquidity providers and traders. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ZIQHzj8d/" alt="Uniswap" width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/nik-Geu-i5VvI1A-unsplash-308x460.jpg" width="308" height="460" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unveiling the Mystery: Trillions of SHIB Flow Into Accounts of Large Shiba Inu Holders</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/trillions-of-shib-flow-into-large-shiba-inu-holders/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[memecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533652</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the world of cryptocurrencies, strange and unexpected events are not uncommon. The latest puzzling development revolves around Shiba Inu (SHIB), as trillions of these tokens have mysteriously found their way into large holders&#8217; accounts, often called whales. The influx of SHIB tokens into these wallets has caught the attention of crypto enthusiasts and analysts, sparking curiosity and speculation about the motives behind these substantial transfers. Interestingly, regardless of this activity, SHIB has only continued to move in a downward trend.  Large Shiba Inu Holders Record Large Inflows According to data provided by the crypto intelligence portal IntoTheBlock, the past day has witnessed an unprecedented surge in the number of SHIB tokens flowing into the addresses of large Shiba Inu holders. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Faces Tough Resistance, Risk Of Uncharted Lows – Here’s Why The total inflow recorded amounts to a staggering 20.1 trillion SHIB tokens. To put this into perspective, this activity level has not been observed since March 23 and January of this year, suggesting that something significant may be unfolding within the Shiba Inu ecosystem. Interestingly, previous instances of such massive inflows were accompanied by similarly large outflows. The recent surge is no exception, as more than 20.16 trillion SHIB tokens were observed to flow out of these large wallets within the same 24-hour period. Though the exact reason behind these anomalous activities remains unclear, it is suggested that it could result from redistribution between exchange wallets. Meanwhile, renowned crypto tracking platform Whale Alert has also reported consecutive transactions involving five trillion SHIB tokens each, totaling $43.6 million. While the scale of these transfers might suggest internal transactions within a major crypto exchange, it is important to note that similar large SHIB transactions among Binance&#8217;s crypto wallets have been confirmed. SHIB Remains In Red Despite the intriguing influx of SHIB tokens into the accounts of large Shiba Inu holders, it is worth noting that the token&#8217;s price has experienced a continuous downtrend in the past week. This raises questions about the impact of these whale movements on the overall market dynamics and investor sentiment toward Shiba Inu. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Remains In Red Despite Whales SHIB Buying Spree Over the past 7 days, Shiba Inu has continued to move downwards, particularly in the meme coin market. The token has plummeted nearly 6% in the past week, down from a high of $0.00000911 seen last Wednesday to $0.00000871 at the time of writing. The supposed Dogecoin Killer has also recorded a huge loss in its market capitalization in the past month. SHIB&#8217;s market cap has plunged 23% over this period, from a cap-high of above $6 billion to $5.1 billion. It is worth noting this plummet in the asset&#8217;s market cap can be attributed to the hype in the frog-themed meme coin PEPE, which took the spotlight away from several meme coins, including SHIB. Featured image from Shutterstock, Chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the world of cryptocurrencies, strange and unexpected events are not uncommon. The latest puzzling development revolves around Shiba Inu (SHIB), as trillions of these tokens have mysteriously found their way into large holders&#8217; accounts, often called whales. </p>
<p>The influx of SHIB tokens into these wallets has caught the attention of crypto enthusiasts and analysts, sparking curiosity and speculation about the motives behind these substantial transfers. Interestingly, regardless of this activity, SHIB has only continued to move in a downward trend. </p>
<h2>Large Shiba Inu Holders Record Large Inflows</h2>
<p>According to <a href="https://app.intotheblock.com/coin/SHIB/deep-dive?group=ownership&amp;chart=all" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a> provided by the crypto intelligence portal IntoTheBlock, the past day has witnessed an unprecedented surge in the number of SHIB tokens flowing into the addresses of large Shiba Inu holders.</p>

<p>The total inflow recorded amounts to a staggering 20.1 trillion SHIB tokens. To put this into perspective, this activity level has not been observed since March 23 and January of this year, suggesting that something significant may be unfolding within the Shiba Inu ecosystem.</p>
<p>Interestingly, previous instances of such massive inflows were accompanied by similarly large outflows. The recent surge is no exception, as more than 20.16 trillion <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-faces-tough-resistance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">SHIB tokens</a> were observed to flow out of these large wallets within the same 24-hour period. </p>
<p>Though the exact reason behind these anomalous activities remains unclear, it is suggested that it could result from redistribution between exchange wallets.</p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Meanwhile, renowned crypto tracking platform Whale Alert has also <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1658531184635256832?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reported</a> consecutive transactions involving five trillion SHIB tokens each, totaling $43.6 million. </p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">While the scale of these transfers might suggest internal transactions within a major crypto exchange, it is important to note that similar large SHIB transactions among Binance&#8217;s crypto wallets have been <a href="https://etherscan.io/tx/0x0238025a48930779b5037ceecc7a5d6e7075bc29115d765054a6e2219d53f54b" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">confirmed</a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">SHIB Remains In Red</h2>
<p>Despite the intriguing influx of SHIB tokens into the accounts of large Shiba Inu holders, it is worth noting that the token&#8217;s price has experienced a<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-remains-in-red-despite-whales-shib-buying-spree/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> continuous downtrend</a> in the past week. This raises questions about the impact of these whale movements on the overall market dynamics and investor sentiment toward Shiba Inu.</p>

<p>Over the past 7 days, Shiba Inu has continued to move downwards, particularly in the meme coin market. The token has plummeted nearly 6% in the past week, down from a high of $0.00000911 seen last Wednesday to $0.00000871 at the time of writing.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/mV3Nb4Cb/" alt="Shiba Inu (SHIB)&#039;s price chart on TradingView" width="2768" height="1556"/>
<p>The supposed Dogecoin Killer has also recorded a huge loss in its market capitalization in the past month. SHIB&#8217;s market cap has plunged 23% over this period, from a cap-high of above $6 billion to $5.1 billion.</p>
<p>It is worth noting this plummet in the asset&#8217;s market cap can be attributed to the hype in the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/discovering-the-next-pepe-and-shib-whales-to-keep-track-of/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">frog-themed meme coin PEPE</a>, which took the spotlight away from several meme coins, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-shib-is-successful-memecoin-than-pepe-and-doge/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">including SHIB</a>.</p>
<p>Featured image from Shutterstock, Chart from TradingView.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SHIB-Shibarium.jpg" width="350" height="250" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Bitcoin Headed For Another Crash? Here&#8217;s What The Data Says</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/is-bitcoin-headed-for-another-crash-heres-what-the-data-says/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533638</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC), the leading cryptocurrency by market capitalization, has been trading in a sideways trend since its drop from the $28,000 level. As of the time of writing, BTC is currently valued at $26,800, having experienced significant declines across all time frames. The question on everyone&#8217;s mind now is whether this downturn will continue or if Bitcoin is headed for another crash.  Related Reading: Crypto Assets Flow From Ethereum To BSC, Are Users Escaping High Gas Fees? Can Bitcoin Holders Expect Another 40% Drop In The Coming Weeks Cryptocurrency enthusiasts and traders closely monitor Bitcoin&#8217;s performance after its recent price drop. According to Miles Deutscher, an experienced cryptocurrency analyst, Bitcoin typically experiences a temporary rally after a decline, followed by a new low 5-8 weeks later. Deutscher&#8217;s analysis shows that in 2020, Bitcoin&#8217;s price dropped by 56% within 59 days after rallying initially. Similarly, in 2021, Bitcoin&#8217;s price dropped by 24% within 47 days, and in 2022, Bitcoin&#8217;s price dropped by 42% within 40 days. With this said, with BTC trading at $26,800, if it experiences a 20% drop, its price will likely fall to $21,440, while a 30% drop would bring it down to $18,760. A 40% drop would result in a price of $16,080, potentially taking Bitcoin back to the lowest point of the 2022 bear market. 2023 Is Set To Be The Best Year For BTC Yet? On the other hand, according to cryptocurrency analyst Adrian Zdunczyk, historical data suggests that pre-election years are the best-performing years on record for Bitcoin, with a 98.8% chance of a bull run in 2023. Even though the worst six months of the year usually begin with May, Zdunczyk believes a bullish trend will likely emerge in the coming months. Looking at the weekly chart, Zdunczyk notes that Bitcoin is currently experiencing a complete throwback to the 200-week trend, completing the mean reversion. While a strong correlation (0.42) exists between Bitcoin and the S&#38;P 500, the critical support near $25,000 has been defended. However, if this support level breaks, traders could see prices fall into the lower $20,000 area. Furthermore, Zdunczyk believes more downside is possible if Bitcoin stays below $30,000. However, after a successful retest of the 200-day baseline, the support level has been confirmed by multiple techniques. Meanwhile, there has been a deterioration in the 50-day average volatility, and the long-term trend has been temporarily exhausted. Related Reading: US Prosecutes Russian Hacker For Orchestrating $200 Million Crypto-Ransomware Attacks Zdunczyk&#8217;s analysis suggests a clear head and shoulders pattern has been completed, with a technical breakout target of $22,000. However, if the pattern fails to break, it could trigger a cascade rally beyond $35,000.  As seen in the chart above, the local resistance is currently at $28,000, backed by the BirbicatorPRO (BPRO) analysis. The bears maintain control until there is a powerful close above this level. Bitcoin bulls must wait for a decisive breakout above $30,000 to ensure a more reliable upward trend. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC), the leading cryptocurrency by market capitalization, has been trading in a sideways trend since its drop from the $28,000 level. As of the time of writing, BTC is currently valued at $26,800, having experienced significant declines across all time frames. The question on everyone&#8217;s mind now is whether this downturn will continue or if Bitcoin is headed for another crash. </p>

<h2><b>Can Bitcoin Holders Expect Another 40% Drop In The Coming Weeks</b></h2>
<p>Cryptocurrency enthusiasts and traders closely monitor Bitcoin&#8217;s performance after its recent price drop. <a href="https://twitter.com/milesdeutscher/status/1658826681883164672?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to Miles Deutscher, an experienced cryptocurrency analyst, Bitcoin typically experiences a temporary rally after a decline, followed by a new low 5-8 weeks later.</p>
<p>Deutscher&#8217;s analysis shows that in 2020, Bitcoin&#8217;s price dropped by 56% within 59 days after rallying initially. Similarly, in 2021, Bitcoin&#8217;s price dropped by 24% within 47 days, and in 2022, Bitcoin&#8217;s price dropped by 42% within 40 days.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-533641" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwVWEkEWwAAdnQQ-860x574.jpg" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="574" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwVWEkEWwAAdnQQ-860x574.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwVWEkEWwAAdnQQ-460x307.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwVWEkEWwAAdnQQ-768x512.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwVWEkEWwAAdnQQ-1536x1025.jpg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwVWEkEWwAAdnQQ-750x500.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwVWEkEWwAAdnQQ-1140x760.jpg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwVWEkEWwAAdnQQ.jpg 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>With this said, with BTC trading at $26,800, if it experiences a 20% drop, its price will likely fall to $21,440, while a 30% drop would bring it down to $18,760. A 40% drop would result in a price of $16,080, potentially taking Bitcoin back to the lowest point of the 2022 bear market.</p>
<b>2023 Is Set To Be The Best Year For BTC Yet?</b>
<p>On the other hand, <a href="https://twitter.com/crypto_birb/status/1658233673349562369?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">according </a>to cryptocurrency analyst Adrian Zdunczyk, historical data suggests that pre-election years are the best-performing years on record for Bitcoin, with a 98.8% chance of a bull run in 2023. Even though the worst six months of the year usually begin with May, Zdunczyk believes a bullish trend will likely emerge in the coming months.</p>
<p>Looking at the weekly chart, Zdunczyk notes that Bitcoin is currently experiencing a complete throwback to the 200-week trend, completing the mean reversion. While a strong correlation (0.42) exists between Bitcoin and the S&amp;P 500, the critical support near $25,000 has been defended. However, if this support level breaks, traders could see prices fall into the lower $20,000 area.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Zdunczyk believes more downside is possible if Bitcoin stays below $30,000. However, after a successful retest of the 200-day baseline, the support level has been confirmed by multiple techniques. Meanwhile, there has been a deterioration in the 50-day average volatility, and the long-term trend has been temporarily exhausted.</p>

<p>Zdunczyk&#8217;s analysis suggests a clear head and shoulders pattern has been completed, with a technical breakout target of $22,000. However, if the pattern fails to break, it could trigger a cascade rally beyond $35,000. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-533640" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwNE8cnXsAYDOwr-860x541.jpg" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="541" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwNE8cnXsAYDOwr-860x541.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwNE8cnXsAYDOwr-460x289.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwNE8cnXsAYDOwr-768x483.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwNE8cnXsAYDOwr-1536x966.jpg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwNE8cnXsAYDOwr-2048x1288.jpg 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwNE8cnXsAYDOwr-750x472.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FwNE8cnXsAYDOwr-1140x717.jpg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>As seen in the chart above, the local resistance is currently at $28,000, backed by the BirbicatorPRO (BPRO) analysis. The bears maintain control until there is a powerful close above this level. Bitcoin bulls must wait for a decisive breakout above $30,000 to ensure a more reliable upward trend.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/olfLVCEL/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1813" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1305769484-1-1-460x272.jpg" width="460" height="272" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SUSHI Down 45%: What&#8217;s Driving the Decline?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/defi/sushi-down-45-whats-driving-the-decline/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 23:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto winter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sushi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SushiSwap]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533626</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The price of SUSHI, the native token of SushiSwap, a decentralized exchange, is down 45% from February 2023, when prices peaked at $1.63, the highest level in six months. SushiSwap Token Redesign This contraction is despite the successful implementation of a proposal to redesign SUSHI’s tokenomics, making SUSHI, a governance token, more deflationary. The proposal was first made in December 2022 by Chief Chef Jeremy Grey and was voted on and agreed on by the community early this year. Related Reading: SushiSwap To Redirect 100% Trading Fees To Treasury The proposal passed with a majority vote and will seek to reduce the SUSHI supply over the years. At the same time, it will increase the rewards for liquidity providers while encouraging users to stake SUSHI for longer. Grey argued that this implementation would promote decentralization while making the protocol have “more equitable governance with sustainable economics.” Eventually, by redesigning SUSHI’s tokenomics, the goal will be to keep annual inflation between 1% to 3%. The latest data from MoneyPrinter shows that SUSHI’s annual inflation stands at 1.23%, aligning with SushiSwap’s tokenomics redesign. If anything, this inflation rate is lower than Bitcoin, which has an annual issuance rate of 1.82%. SUSHI’s inflation is also lower than Cardano, which has an annual emission of 1.79%. While analysts expect low inflation to support prices in the long haul, the performance of SUSHI in the first half of 2023 has been dismal. SUSHI is down 45% from 2023 highs and 99% from 2021 peaks when the token changed hands at around $22. Blame The Winter, Hack, And Regulators While the markets have recovered, some, including SUSHI, could still be reeling from the effects of the crypto winter. Last year, Bitcoin, the largest coin by market cap, crashed by over 70% after peaking at over $69,000 in November 2021. The collapse of BTC dragged the altcoin market with it, forcing the more volatile assets even lower, adversely affecting SUSHI. Related Reading: SushiSwap Burns $5 Million Per Year, But Will It Rebrand In 2023? As an illustration, SUSHI is trending at 2022 lows at around $0.89, retesting a critical multi-month support level. Prices are also capped as investor confidence took a hit following SushiSwap’s RouterProcessor2 contract exploit in early April 2023. Hackers ended up with $3.3 million. Although the flaw has since been patched, the reputational damage associated with the vulnerability dents investor confidence. It remains to be seen how SushiSwap will navigate potential new regulations, particularly those from the United States. Some policymakers have taken a negative stance towards cryptocurrency, causing users in the country to hesitate to engage with DeFi protocols due to potential legal consequences. Feature Image From Canva, Chart From TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price of SUSHI, the native token of SushiSwap, a decentralized exchange, is down 45% from February 2023, when prices peaked at $1.63, the highest level in six months.</p>
<h2>SushiSwap Token Redesign</h2>
<p>This contraction is despite the successful implementation of a proposal to redesign SUSHI’s tokenomics, making SUSHI, a governance token, more deflationary.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://forum.sushi.com/t/sushi-tokenomics-redesign/11621" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">proposal</a> was first made in December 2022 by Chief Chef Jeremy Grey and was voted on and agreed on by the community early this year.</p>

<p>The proposal passed with a majority vote and will seek to reduce the SUSHI supply over the years. At the same time, it will increase the rewards for liquidity providers while encouraging users to stake SUSHI for longer.</p>
<p>Grey argued that this implementation would promote decentralization while making the protocol have “more equitable governance with sustainable economics.” Eventually, by redesigning SUSHI’s tokenomics, the goal will be to keep annual inflation between 1% to 3%.</p>
<p>The latest data from MoneyPrinter <a href="https://moneyprinter.info/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shows</a> that SUSHI’s annual inflation stands at 1.23%, aligning with SushiSwap’s tokenomics redesign. If anything, this inflation rate is lower than Bitcoin, which has an annual issuance rate of 1.82%. SUSHI’s inflation is also lower than Cardano, which has an annual emission of 1.79%.</p>
<p>While analysts expect low inflation to support prices in the long haul, the performance of SUSHI in the first half of 2023 has been dismal. SUSHI is down 45% from 2023 highs and 99% from 2021 peaks when the token changed hands at around $22.</p>
<h2>Blame The Winter, Hack, And Regulators</h2>
<p>While the markets have recovered, some, including SUSHI, could still be reeling from the effects of the crypto winter.</p>
<p>Last year, Bitcoin, the largest coin by market cap, crashed by over 70% after peaking at over $69,000 in November 2021. The collapse of BTC dragged the altcoin market with it, forcing the more volatile assets even lower, adversely affecting SUSHI.</p>

<p>As an illustration, SUSHI is trending at 2022 lows at around $0.89, retesting a critical multi-month support level.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/DtED8OH2/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/DtED8OH2/" alt="SushiSwap Price On May 17| Source: SUSHIUSDT On Binance, TradingView" width="1225" height="595"/></a>
<p>Prices are also capped as investor confidence took a hit following SushiSwap’s RouterProcessor2 contract exploit in early April 2023. Hackers ended up with $3.3 million. Although the flaw has since been patched, the reputational damage associated with the vulnerability dents investor confidence.</p>
<p>It remains to be seen how SushiSwap will navigate potential new regulations, particularly those from the United States. Some policymakers have taken a negative stance towards cryptocurrency, causing users in the country to hesitate to engage with DeFi protocols due to potential legal consequences.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/SushiSwap-SUSHI-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>French Regulator Extends Open Arms to Fleeing U.S. Crypto Firms</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/french-regulator-extends-open-arms-to-fleeing-u-s-crypto-firms/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 23:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[regulator]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533621</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[France is demonstrating its dedication to becoming a top choice for cryptocurrency companies seeking clear regulations by offering a welcoming environment for those fleeing uncertainty in the United States. Earlier today, a report from CoinDesk stated that the French regulator, particularly the Autorité des Marchés Financiers (AMF), disclosed its open arms and invitation toward crypto companies looking to flee from their US branch and relocate to other regions with clear regulations on the sector. Opening The Doors For Crypto Firms As the European Union (EU) takes significant steps towards implementing the Markets in Crypto Assets (MiCA) rules, France has positioned itself as a potential hub for crypto. The country currently has 74 registered crypto companies, which is expected to rise to around 100 as more firms anticipate the implementation of the EU&#8217;s comprehensive regulatory framework. Related Reading: Coinbase Turns To Europe For Growth Amid Clampdown By US Regulators According to several analysts, this framework is designed to provide a robust and standardized set of rules for crypto assets, ensuring greater investor protection and market integrity.  France&#8217;s notable advantage is its defined crypto service asset provider regime, PSAN, introduced in 2019. The PSAN legislation provides clear guidelines and regulations for crypto businesses, fostering an environment of transparency and stability. Benoît de Juvigny, Secretary General of the Autorité des marchés financiers (AMF), emphasized France&#8217;s welcoming approach by stating: If American players want to benefit, in the very short term, from the French regime, and from the start of 2025 from European arrangements, clearly they are welcome. The Secretary General of the IMF also highlighted the positive relationships and ongoing discussions with U.S. counterparts, demonstrating France&#8217;s commitment to international cooperation in the crypto industry. Firms Fleeing The US Over the past months, many crypto firms have been considering or actively pursuing relocation from the United States. Regulatory concerns and an uncertain environment have prompted these companies to explore alternative jurisdictions that offer more favorable conditions for their operations. Crypto companies, such as Coinbase and Kraken, have expressed unease about the regulatory landscape in the United States. Various countries and regions have emerged as attractive destinations for crypto firms seeking more favorable regulatory environments. Such destinations are France, United Arab Emirates (UAE), Switzerland, and Singapore. France has actively embraced digital assets and implemented a regulatory framework offering legal certainty. The country&#8217;s commitment to providing clear guidelines, such as the crypto service asset provider regime (PSAN), has caught the attention of crypto firms looking for stability and regulatory clarity. Related Reading: BNB Remains Under Pressure As Regulators Crack Down On Binance Asides from France, crypto companies such as Coinbase have also been eyeing the UAE. In a Dubai Fintech Summit on May 8, Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong noted: [The UAE is] exciting for us as a potential hub to build as well, an international hub for Coinbase that could serve not only in the Middle East but parts of Africa or other countries in Asia. I think the U.S. right now is a little bit behind in terms of regulatory clarity and some of the rhetoric from the top. The fact that crypto companies are moving out of the United States highlights the negative impact of regulatory ambiguity on the country&#8217;s position in the worldwide cryptocurrency market. While some firms may choose to maintain a presence in the United States, the departure of key players raises questions about the country&#8217;s competitiveness and ability to attract and retain crypto talent. Regardless, the crypto market has maintained composure despite the regulatory scrutiny on the industry. Over the past 24 hours, the global crypto market has seen a 0.4% loss, with a value sitting firmly above $1 trillion. Chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>France is demonstrating its dedication to becoming a top choice for cryptocurrency companies seeking clear regulations by offering a welcoming environment for those fleeing uncertainty in the United States.</p>
<p>Earlier today, a report from <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/05/17/fleeing-us-crypto-firms-welcome-french-regulator-says/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinDesk</a> stated that the French regulator, particularly the Autorité des Marchés Financiers (AMF), disclosed its open arms and invitation toward crypto companies looking to flee from their US branch and relocate to other regions with clear regulations on the sector.</p>
<h2>Opening The Doors For Crypto Firms</h2>
<p>As the European Union (EU) takes significant steps towards implementing the Markets in Crypto Assets (MiCA) rules, France has positioned itself as a potential hub for crypto. The country currently has 74 registered crypto companies, which is expected to rise to around 100 as more firms anticipate the implementation of the EU&#8217;s comprehensive regulatory framework.</p>

<p>According to several analysts, this framework is designed to provide a robust and standardized set of rules for crypto assets, ensuring greater investor protection and market integrity. </p>
<p>France&#8217;s notable advantage is its defined crypto service asset provider regime, PSAN, introduced in 2019. The PSAN legislation provides clear guidelines and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/binance-coin/bnb-remains-under-pressure-as-regulators-crack-down-on-binance/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">regulations for crypto businesses</a>, fostering an environment of transparency and stability.</p>
<p>Benoît de Juvigny, Secretary General of the Autorité des marchés financiers (AMF), emphasized France&#8217;s welcoming approach by stating:</p>
<blockquote><p>If American players want to benefit, in the very short term, from the French regime, and from the start of 2025 from European arrangements, clearly they are welcome.</p></blockquote>
<p>The  Secretary General of the IMF also highlighted the positive relationships and ongoing discussions with U.S. counterparts, demonstrating France&#8217;s commitment to international cooperation in the crypto industry.</p>
<h2>Firms Fleeing The US</h2>
<p>Over the past months, many crypto firms have been considering or actively pursuing relocation from the United States. <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/new-york-attorney-general-proposes-new-crypto-regulatory-act/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Regulatory concerns</a> and an uncertain environment have prompted these companies to explore alternative jurisdictions that offer more favorable conditions for their operations. </p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Crypto companies, such as Coinbase and Kraken, have <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/coinbase-turns-to-europe-for-growth/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">expressed unease about the regulatory landscape in the United States.</a> Various countries and regions have emerged as attractive destinations for crypto firms seeking more favorable regulatory environments. </p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">Such destinations are France, United Arab Emirates (UAE), Switzerland, and Singapore. France has actively embraced digital assets and implemented a regulatory framework offering legal certainty. </p>
<p class="selectable-text copyable-text iq0m558w" dir="ltr">The country&#8217;s commitment to providing clear guidelines, such as the crypto service asset provider regime (PSAN), has caught the attention of crypto firms looking for stability and regulatory clarity.</p>

<p dir="ltr">Asides from France, crypto companies such as Coinbase have also been eyeing the UAE. In a Dubai Fintech Summit on May 8, Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/the-uae-recognising-the-transformative-potential-of-the-cryptoeconomy" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">noted:</a></p>
<blockquote>
<p dir="ltr">[The UAE is] exciting for us as a potential hub to build as well, an international hub for Coinbase that could serve not only in the Middle East but parts of Africa or other countries in Asia. I think the U.S. right now is a little bit behind in terms of regulatory clarity and some of the rhetoric from the top.</p>
</blockquote>
<p dir="ltr">The fact that crypto companies are moving out of the United States highlights the negative impact of regulatory ambiguity on the country&#8217;s position in the worldwide cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While some firms may choose to maintain a presence in the United States, the departure of key players raises questions about the country&#8217;s competitiveness and ability to attract and retain crypto talent.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/VzHB6XCm/" alt="The total crypt market cap price chart on TradingView" width="2768" height="1556"/>
<p dir="ltr">Regardless, the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/crypto-assets-flow-from-ethereum-to-bsc-are-users-escaping-high-gas-fees/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">crypto market</a> has maintained composure despite the regulatory scrutiny on the industry. Over the past 24 hours, the global crypto market has seen a 0.4% loss, with a value sitting firmly above $1 trillion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chart from Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/France-Regulator-Welcomes-Crypto-Firms-Fleeing-U.S-460x306.jpeg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tether Bets On Bitcoin: Allocates Up To 15% Of Profits For BTC Purchases</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/tether-bets-on-bitcoin-allocates-up-to-15-of-profits-for-btc-purchases/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 22:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tether]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533616</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tether, the company managing the reserves of the world’s largest stablecoin USDT, has announced a new investment strategy aimed at strengthening its reserves portfolio. Tether will now allocate up to 15% of its net realized operating profits toward purchasing Bitcoin (BTC) regularly. This move is expected to diversify Tether’s reserves, which currently hold approximately $1.5 billion in BTC. Tether’s Q1 2023 Assurance Report highlights the company’s commitment to maintaining a strong shareholder capital cushion while increasing its Bitcoin holdings. The report also notes that Tether takes possession of the private keys associated with all of its Bitcoin holdings, reflecting the company’s philosophy of “not your keys, not your Bitcoin.” Tether To Boost Bitcoin Reserves According to the announcement, under this new approach, Tether will disregard unrealized capital gains generated by price increases and will focus solely on the tangible gains from its operations. The company will consider the difference between the purchase price and net proceeds from the sale or the reimbursed amount in case of a maturing investment.  Related Reading: Cosmos (ATOM) Price Trends Upwards: A Potential Breakout Or Impending Correction? Paolo Ardoino, CTO of Tether, said Bitcoin has continually proven its resilience and has emerged as a long-term store of value with substantial growth potential. Bitcoin&#8217;s limited supply, decentralized nature, and widespread adoption have positioned it as a favored choice among institutional and retail investors alike. What&#8217;s more, Tether&#8217;s investment in Bitcoin is not only aimed at enhancing the performance of its portfolio but also at aligning itself with a transformative technology that has the potential to reshape the way we conduct business and live our lives. Furthermore, Tether believes that Bitcoin has demonstrated its investment potential with a track record of impressive returns over the past decade. Bitcoin&#8217;s performance, combined with increasing recognition and adoption by major financial institutions, has cemented its position as a key component in diversified investment portfolios, which reflects the company&#8217;s confidence in the cryptocurrency&#8217;s long-term potential. Moreover, Tether&#8217;s decision to allocate a portion of its net realized operating profits toward Bitcoin highlights the company&#8217;s confidence in the cryptocurrency market and its belief in supporting the broader ecosystem. The move is part of Tether&#8217;s strategy to diversify its reserves portfolio and maintain stability in the ever-evolving digital asset landscape. Related Reading: Polkadot Latest Update Fuels Anticipation Of Higher Price For DOT In addition to investing in Bitcoin, Tether is focusing on building communication, energy, and Bitcoin mining infrastructure. These investments are aimed at enhancing the company&#8217;s operations and supporting the broader digital asset ecosystem. Overall, Tether’s new investment strategy demonstrates the company&#8217;s commitment to transparency, stability, and prudent decision-making. By focusing on realized profits and increasing its exposure to Bitcoin, Tether aims to strengthen its position as a leading player in the stablecoin market while maintaining a strong and diversified reserves portfolio. As of this writing, the largest cryptocurrency by market cap is currently trading at $26,800, down by 0.8% in the last 24 hours.  Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tether, the company managing the reserves of the world’s largest stablecoin USDT, has <a href="https://tether.to/en/tether-to-further-strengthen-reserves-through-purchase-of-bitcoin-with-realized-net-operating-profits/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced </a>a new investment strategy aimed at strengthening its reserves portfolio. Tether will now allocate up to 15% of its net realized operating profits toward purchasing Bitcoin (BTC) regularly. This move is expected to diversify Tether’s reserves, which currently hold approximately $1.5 billion in BTC.</p>
<p>Tether’s Q1 2023 <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/tether-smashes-records-1-48-billion-profit-in-q1-surplus-over-reserves-hits-all-time-high/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Assurance Report</a> highlights the company’s commitment to maintaining a strong shareholder capital cushion while increasing its Bitcoin holdings. The report also notes that Tether takes possession of the private keys associated with all of its Bitcoin holdings, reflecting the company’s philosophy of “not your keys, not your Bitcoin.”</p>
<h2><b>Tether To Boost Bitcoin Reserves</b></h2>
<p>According to the announcement, under this new approach, Tether will disregard unrealized capital gains generated by price increases and will focus solely on the tangible gains from its operations. The company will consider the difference between the purchase price and net proceeds from the sale or the reimbursed amount in case of a maturing investment. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/cosmos-atom/cosmos-atom-price-trends-upwards-a-potential-breakout-or-impending-correction/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Cosmos (ATOM) Price Trends Upwards: A Potential Breakout Or Impending Correction?</a></p>
<p>Paolo Ardoino, CTO of Tether, said Bitcoin has continually proven its resilience and has emerged as a long-term store of value with substantial growth potential. Bitcoin&#8217;s limited supply, decentralized nature, and widespread adoption have positioned it as a favored choice among institutional and retail investors alike. </p>
<p>What&#8217;s more, Tether&#8217;s investment in Bitcoin is not only aimed at enhancing the performance of its portfolio but also at aligning itself with a transformative technology that has the potential to reshape the way we conduct business and live our lives.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Tether believes that Bitcoin has demonstrated its investment potential with a track record of impressive returns over the past decade. </p>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s performance, combined with increasing recognition and adoption by major financial institutions, has cemented its position as a key component in diversified investment portfolios, which reflects the company&#8217;s confidence in the cryptocurrency&#8217;s long-term potential.</p>
<p>Moreover, Tether&#8217;s decision to allocate a portion of its net realized operating profits toward Bitcoin highlights the company&#8217;s confidence in the cryptocurrency market and its belief in supporting the broader ecosystem. The move is part of Tether&#8217;s strategy to diversify its reserves portfolio and maintain stability in the ever-evolving digital asset landscape.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/polkadot-latest-update-fuels-anticipation-of-higher-price-for-dot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Polkadot Latest Update Fuels Anticipation Of Higher Price For DOT</a></p>
<p>In addition to investing in Bitcoin, Tether is focusing on building communication, energy, and Bitcoin mining infrastructure. These investments are aimed at enhancing the company&#8217;s operations and supporting the broader digital asset ecosystem.</p>
<p>Overall, Tether’s new investment strategy demonstrates the company&#8217;s commitment to transparency, stability, and prudent decision-making. By focusing on realized profits and increasing its exposure to Bitcoin, Tether aims to strengthen its position as a leading player in the stablecoin market while maintaining a strong and diversified reserves portfolio.</p>
<p>As of this writing, the largest cryptocurrency by market cap is currently trading at $26,800, down by 0.8% in the last 24 hours. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/xN7Rm96G/" alt="Tether" width="1813" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1314042576-460x288.jpg" width="460" height="288" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Acquires Crypto Custody Firm Metaco In $250 Million Deal</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ripple/ripple-acquires-crypto-custody-firm-metaco-in-250-million-deal/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 21:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto custody]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Metaco]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=533561</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[US-based cryptocurrency company Ripple has recently announced its acquisition of Metaco. Metaco is a Swiss-based crypto custody firm and the deal, valued at $250 million, marks Ripple&#8217;s foray into the acquisition space. Metaco specializes in developing cutting-edge technology that enables financial institutions to securely store and effectively manage digital assets. Some of its notable clients comprise Citi, BNP Paribas, and the digital asset arm of Societe Generale. Related Reading: Polkadot Latest Update Fuels Anticipation Of Higher Price For DOT After the acquisition, Ripple will become the exclusive shareholder of Metaco. It will, however, allow the company to retain its independent brand identity and continue its operations uninterrupted. Nevertheless, this acquisition holds significant importance for Ripple. Its own cryptocurrency, XRP, currently ranks as the sixth largest in the world based on market capitalization. Ripple expressed that this acquisition will serve as a catalyst for expanding its institutional offering. Additionally, this will also strengthen its position in the cryptocurrency market. By integrating Metaco&#8217;s expertise and technology, Ripple aims to enhance its capabilities in providing secure storage and management solutions for digital assets. Investor Caution Has Been Growing Regarding Crypto Asset Storage Following a decline in cryptocurrency prices in 2022 along with notable collapses of major crypto firms like the U.S. exchange FTX, investor enthusiasm for crypto assets has waned. A critical factor contributing to this shift in sentiment is the growing alertness among investors regarding the storage of crypto assets. Several crypto platforms had frozen their withdrawals resulting in significant losses for investors. This has prompted them to choose and prioritize secure storage solutions to store their digital assets. Anticipating a surge in demand from institutional investors, Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse expressed his expectation for an upswing in the need for crypto custody services. He also stated: By focusing on the infrastructure &#8230; you&#8217;re not really subject to the same gyrations of the crypto winters. If ultimately you&#8217;re solving a clear problem at scale for these customers, there&#8217;s going to be demand there. Amidst the intensifying enforcement actions by US regulators against crypto firms, CEO Brad Garlinghouse highlighted the added appeal of Metaco, being based in Switzerland and having a workforce comprised of non-US employees. Garlinghouse emphasized that the regulatory landscape in markets outside the United States offers greater and better clarity. This enables companies to make sound and informed investments. Related Reading: Decentraland (MANA) Leads Crypto Market Gains, Here’s Why He noted that these transparent and well-defined rules in other jurisdictions have been responsible for creating an environment conducive to business growth and innovation. Following its recent private financing round, Ripple was valued at $15 billion even though the company had encountered a significant level of regulatory ambiguity. The uncertainty escalated when the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filed a lawsuit against the company and two of its executives, alleging the sale of unregistered securities. This legal action has further added to the regulatory challenges faced by the crypto giant. Featured Image From, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>US-based cryptocurrency company Ripple has recently <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/17/ripple-buhttps://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/?exchange=CRYPTOys-swiss-startup-metaco-as-sec-lawsuit-conclusion-looms.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced</a> its acquisition of Metaco. Metaco is a Swiss-based crypto custody firm and the deal, valued at $250 million, marks Ripple&#8217;s foray into the acquisition space.</p>
<p>Metaco specializes in developing cutting-edge technology that enables financial institutions to securely store and effectively manage digital assets. Some of its notable clients comprise Citi, BNP Paribas, and the digital asset arm of Societe Generale.</p>

<p>After the acquisition, Ripple will become the exclusive shareholder of Metaco. It will, however, allow the company to retain its independent brand identity and continue its operations uninterrupted.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, this acquisition holds significant importance for Ripple. Its own cryptocurrency, XRP, currently ranks as the sixth largest in the world based on market capitalization.</p>
<p>Ripple expressed that this acquisition will serve as a catalyst for expanding its institutional offering. Additionally, this will also strengthen its position in the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p>By integrating Metaco&#8217;s expertise and technology, Ripple aims to enhance its capabilities in providing secure storage and management solutions for digital assets.</p>
<h2>Investor Caution Has Been Growing Regarding Crypto Asset Storage</h2>
<p>Following a decline in cryptocurrency prices in 2022 along with notable collapses of major crypto firms like the U.S. exchange FTX, investor enthusiasm for crypto assets has waned.</p>
<p>A critical factor contributing to this shift in sentiment is the growing alertness among investors regarding the storage of crypto assets. Several crypto platforms had frozen their withdrawals resulting in significant losses for investors. This has prompted them to choose and prioritize secure storage solutions to store their digital assets.</p>
<p>Anticipating a surge in demand from institutional investors, Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse expressed his expectation for an upswing in the need for crypto custody services.</p>
<p>He also stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>By focusing on the infrastructure &#8230; you&#8217;re not really subject to the same gyrations of the crypto winters. If ultimately you&#8217;re solving a clear problem at scale for these customers, there&#8217;s going to be demand there.</p></blockquote>
<p>Amidst the intensifying enforcement actions by US regulators against crypto firms, CEO Brad Garlinghouse highlighted the added appeal of Metaco, being based in Switzerland and having a workforce comprised of non-US employees.</p>
<p>Garlinghouse emphasized that the regulatory landscape in markets outside the United States offers greater and better clarity. This enables companies to make sound and informed investments.</p>

<p>He noted that these transparent and well-defined rules in other jurisdictions have been responsible for creating an environment conducive to business growth and innovation.</p>
<p>Following its recent private financing round, Ripple was valued at $15 billion even though the company had encountered a significant level of regulatory ambiguity.</p>
<p>The uncertainty escalated when the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filed a lawsuit against the company and two of its executives, alleging the sale of unregistered securities. This legal action has further added to the regulatory challenges faced by the crypto giant.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-533608 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-17_20-07-18.png" alt="Crypto" width="1816" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-17_20-07-18.png 1816w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-17_20-07-18-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-17_20-07-18-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-17_20-07-18-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-17_20-07-18-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-17_20-07-18-750x343.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD_2023-05-17_20-07-18-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/istockphoto-1365598845-612x612-1-460x304.jpg" width="460" height="304" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
