<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 04:40:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Key Trend is Forming and Swift Recovery Could Occur</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-key-trend-1250/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 04:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513491</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum is attempting an upside break above the $1,230 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH could start a strong increase if it settles above the $1,230 and $1,250 resistance levels. Ethereum tested the $1,180 level and climbed higher sharply. The price is now trading above $1,200 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There was a break above a key contracting triangle with resistance near $1,215 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could gain bullish momentum if there is a clear move above $1,230 and $1,250. Ethereum Price Eyes Fresh Rally Ethereum price started a downside correction from the $1,230 resistance zone. ETH spiked below the $1,200 support zone and the 100 hourly simple moving average. However, the bulls were active above the $1,160 support zone. A low was formed near $1,180 and the price climbed higher sharply, similar to bitcoin. There was a strong move above the $1,200 level. Besides, there was a break above a key contracting triangle with resistance near $1,215 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. Ether price is now trading above $1,200 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. It is now trading just below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent wave from the $1,180 swing low to $1,237 high. An immediate resistance is near the $1,230 level. The next major resistance is near the $1,250 level. A clear upside break above the $1,250 resistance could start a strong upward move. In the stated case, the price may perhaps rise towards the $1,300 resistance. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com The next major resistance could be $1,350. If the bulls clear the $1,350 resistance, the price might rise towards $1,400. Any more gains might send the price towards the $1,500 resistance zone. Fresh Drop in ETH? If ethereum fails to climb above the $1,250 resistance, it could start another drop. An initial support on the downside is near the $1,210 level and the 100 hourly simple moving average. The next major support is near the $1,200 level. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent wave from the $1,180 swing low to $1,237 high. A downside break below $1,200 might spark a move towards the $1,150 support. Any more losses could lead the price towards the $1,100 zone. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now losing momentum in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,200 Major Resistance Level – $1,230]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum is attempting an upside break above the $1,230 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH could start a strong increase if it settles above the $1,230 and $1,250 resistance levels.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum tested the $1,180 level and climbed higher sharply.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $1,200 and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</li>
<li>There was a break above a key contracting triangle with resistance near $1,215 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could gain bullish momentum if there is a clear move above $1,230 and $1,250.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Eyes Fresh Rally</h2>
<p>Ethereum price started a downside correction from the $1,230 resistance zone. ETH spiked below the $1,200 support zone and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</p>
<p>However, the bulls were active above the $1,160 support zone. A low was formed near $1,180 and the price climbed higher sharply, similar to <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-shows-life-17k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bitcoin</a>. There was a strong move above the $1,200 level. Besides, there was a break above a key contracting triangle with resistance near $1,215 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD.</p>
<p>Ether price is now trading above $1,200 and the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-consolidates-1250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">100 hourly simple moving average</a>. It is now trading just below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent wave from the $1,180 swing low to $1,237 high.</p>
<p>An immediate resistance is near the $1,230 level. The next major resistance is near the $1,250 level. A clear upside break above the $1,250 resistance could start a strong upward move. In the stated case, the price may perhaps rise towards the $1,300 resistance.</p>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-17.png"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-513492" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-17.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-17.png 1834w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-17-460x212.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-17-860x396.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-17-768x354.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-17-1536x708.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-17-750x346.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-17-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The next major resistance could be $1,350. If the bulls clear the $1,350 resistance, the price might rise towards $1,400. Any more gains might send the price towards the $1,500 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Fresh Drop in ETH?</h2>
<p>If ethereum fails to climb above the $1,250 resistance, it could start another drop. An initial support on the downside is near the $1,210 level and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $1,200 level. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent wave from the $1,180 swing low to $1,237 high. A downside break below $1,200 might spark a move towards the $1,150 support. Any more losses could lead the price towards the $1,100 zone.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is now losing momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,200</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,230</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Depositphotos_103793088_s-2019-460x251.jpg" width="460" height="251" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Shows Signs of Life and Could Soon Clear This Hurdle</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-shows-life-17k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 02:45:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513487</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is attempting an upside break above $16,800. BTC could start a decent increase if it clears the $16,800 and $17,000 resistance levels. Bitcoin is still facing a strong resistance near $17,000 and $17,200. The price is trading above $16,700 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $16,800 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could attempt a fresh increase if there is a clear move above the $17,000 resistance zone. Bitcoin Price Eyes Recovery Bitcoin price remained stable above the $16,500 zone. BTC attempted an upside break above the $17,000 resistance, but it faced sellers. A high was formed near $17,067 and the price started a downside correction. There was a move below the $16,800 level and the 100 hourly simple moving average. The price declined below the 50% Fib retracement level of the up move from the $16,260 swing low to $17,067 high. Bitcoin price tested the $16,550 level, where it found support. It remained stable above the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the up move from the $16,260 swing low to $17,067 high. The price recovered losses and climbed above $16,700. It is now trading above $16,700 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $16,800 zone. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $16,800 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The first major resistance is near the $17,000 zone. A clear move above the $17,000 resistance might encourage the bulls to pump the price above the $17,200 resistance. If they succeed, the price could even surpass the $17,500 level. The next major resistance is near $18,000, above which the price climb towards the $18,500 resistance zone. Fresh Drop in BTC? If bitcoin fails to clear the $17,000 resistance, there could be a fresh drop. An immediate support on the downside is near the $16,750 level and the 100 hourly SMA The next major support is near the $16,550 level. A downside break below the $16,550 support might call for a move towards the $16,350 level. Any more losses might send the price towards $16,000. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $16,700, followed by $16,550. Major Resistance Levels – $16,800, $17,000 and $17,500.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is attempting an upside break above $16,800. BTC could start a decent increase if it clears the $16,800 and $17,000 resistance levels.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is still facing a strong resistance near $17,000 and $17,200.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $16,700 and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $16,800 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could attempt a fresh increase if there is a clear move above the $17,000 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Eyes Recovery</h2>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-recovery-fade-17-2k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin price remained stable above the $16,500 zone</a>. BTC attempted an upside break above the $17,000 resistance, but it faced sellers.</p>
<p>A high was formed near $17,067 and the price started a downside correction. There was a move below the $16,800 level and the 100 hourly simple moving average. The price declined below the 50% Fib retracement level of the up move from the $16,260 swing low to $17,067 high.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price tested the $16,550 level, where it found support. It remained stable above the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the up move from the $16,260 swing low to $17,067 high.</p>
<p>The price recovered losses and climbed above $16,700. It is now trading above $16,700 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $16,800 zone. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $16,800 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-21.png"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-513488" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-21.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-21.png 1834w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-21-460x212.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-21-860x396.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-21-768x354.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-21-1536x708.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-21-750x346.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-21-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $17,000 zone. A clear move above the $17,000 resistance might encourage the bulls to pump the price above the $17,200 resistance. If they succeed, the price could even surpass the $17,500 level. The next major resistance is near $18,000, above which the price climb towards the $18,500 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Fresh Drop in BTC?</h2>
<p>If bitcoin fails to clear the $17,000 resistance, there could be a <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-signals-rejection-17k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">fresh drop</a>. An immediate support on the downside is near the $16,750 level and the 100 hourly SMA</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $16,550 level. A downside break below the $16,550 support might call for a move towards the $16,350 level. Any more losses might send the price towards $16,000.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $16,700, followed by $16,550.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $16,800, $17,000 and $17,500.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/Depositphotos_179514440_s-2019-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Classic Hashrate Dumps Almost 50% In 3 Months, What About ETC?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/etc/ethereum-classic-hashrate-dumps-almost-50/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 23:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETC hashrate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[etc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hashrate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ravencoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513410</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum Classic saw its hashrate balloon when Ethereum finally moved to a proof of stake mechanism. The miners who were being kicked out of the network and could no longer use their machines had switched to others such as Ethereum Classic and Ravencoin to put their very specific machines to use. At the time, ETC’s hashrate had grown more than 200%, but now the network is seeing its hashrate fall once more. Ethereum Classic Hashrate Down By Almost 50% On Sep. 16, the mining hashrate of the Ethereum Classic network reached a new all-time high of 199.4 terahashes per second (TH/s) after climbing steadily for more than a week. With this growth had come more usage on the network, triggering staggering growth in its price. Related Reading: Bitcoin Retail Investors Now Hold 17% Of Total BTC Supply, But Is It Good News? However, as the Ethereum network has settled into its proof of stake (POS) consensus mechanism, the Ethereum Classic hashrate is correcting downwards. Hashrate is now down almost 50% in the last 3 months to be sitting at 109.3 TH/s on Dec. 22. ETC hashrate down almost 50% in 3 months &#124; Source: Coinwarz The decline can also be attributed to the bear market and the muted interest from investors. Since bitcoin’s price touched below $20,000, all of the cryptocurrencies in the space have seen a similar decline. Ravencoin, another proof of work network that got massive attention following Ethereum’s move to proof of stake, has also seen its hashrate plummet in the last 3 months. Ravencoin’s hashrate now sits at 9.49 TH/s compared to its Sep. 22, 2022 peak of 17.59 TH/s. Meanwhile, other leading proof of work networks including Litecoin and Dogecoin has seen an increase in mining hashrate, whereas bitcoin remains mostly around 250 exahashes per second (EH/s). What About ETC Price? ETC, the native cryptocurrency of the Ethereum Classic network, was basically on a rollercoaster in the three months since Ethereum moved to proof of stake. At first, as the network began to get more attention, ETC’s price had risen drastically. It eventually peaked above $42 before starting another downtrend. Related Reading: https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/microstrategy-bought-bitcoin/ At current prices, the digital asset has lost over 68% of its value from September 2022 and is still very bearish. A lot of attention had also moved on to Dogecoin, a proof-of-work cryptocurrency that saw a surge in price following Elon Musk’s takeover of Twitter. ETC price down 68% in 3 months &#124; Source: ETCUSD on TradingView.com Obviously, this increase in the price of DOGE had incentivized miners to move over to Dogecoin, eventually taking share from Ethereum Classic. As interest fell, so did the mining hashrate and price naturally followed the same trend. ETC now sits below its 100-day moving average, which means that investors are expecting lower prices to come. It is trading at $16.41 at the time of this writing, down 11% in the last 7 days. Featured image from Crypto News Flash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Ethereum Classic saw its hashrate balloon when Ethereum finally moved to a proof of stake mechanism. The miners who were being kicked out of the network and could no longer use their machines had switched to others such as Ethereum Classic and Ravencoin to put their very specific machines to use. At the time, ETC’s hashrate had grown more than 200%, but now the network is seeing its hashrate fall once more.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Ethereum Classic Hashrate Down By Almost 50%</h2>
<p class="p2">On Sep. 16, the mining hashrate of the Ethereum Classic network reached a new all-time high of 199.4 terahashes per second (TH/s) after climbing steadily for more than a week. With this growth had come more usage on the network, triggering staggering growth in its price.</p>

<p class="p2">However, as the Ethereum network has settled into its proof of stake (POS) consensus mechanism, the Ethereum Classic hashrate is correcting downwards. <a href="https://www.coinwarz.com/mining/ethereum-classic/hashrate-chart" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Hashrate is now down almost 50% in the last 3 months</a> to be sitting at 109.3 TH/s on Dec. 22.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-513412 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-22-at-11.43.23-460x208.png" alt="Ethereum Classic hashrate" width="460" height="208" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-22-at-11.43.23-460x208.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-22-at-11.43.23-860x389.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-22-at-11.43.23-768x347.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-22-at-11.43.23-1536x695.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-22-at-11.43.23-2048x926.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-22-at-11.43.23-750x339.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-22-at-11.43.23-1140x516.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p class="p2">The decline can also be attributed to the bear market and the muted interest from investors. Since bitcoin’s price touched below $20,000, all of the cryptocurrencies in the space have seen a similar decline. Ravencoin, another proof of work network that got massive attention following Ethereum’s move to proof of stake, has also seen its hashrate plummet in the last 3 months.</p>
<p class="p2">Ravencoin’s hashrate now sits at 9.49 TH/s compared to its Sep. 22, 2022 peak of 17.59 TH/s. Meanwhile, other leading proof of work networks including Litecoin and Dogecoin has seen an increase in mining hashrate, whereas bitcoin remains mostly around 250 exahashes per second (EH/s).</p>
<h2 class="p2">What About ETC Price?</h2>
<p class="p2">ETC, the native cryptocurrency of the Ethereum Classic network, was basically on a rollercoaster in the three months since Ethereum moved to proof of stake. At first, as the network began to get more attention, ETC’s price had risen drastically. It eventually peaked above $42 before starting another downtrend.</p>

<p class="p2">At current prices, the digital asset has lost over 68% of its value from September 2022 and is still very bearish. A lot of attention had also moved on to Dogecoin, a proof-of-work cryptocurrency that saw a surge in price following Elon Musk’s takeover of Twitter.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/aprkK5EA/" alt="Ethereum Classic (ETC) price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1760" /></p>

<p class="p2">Obviously, this increase in the price of DOGE had incentivized miners to move over to Dogecoin, eventually taking share from Ethereum Classic. As interest fell, so did the mining hashrate and price naturally followed the same trend.</p>
<p class="p2">ETC now sits below its 100-day moving average, which means that investors are expecting lower prices to come. It is trading at $16.41 at the time of this writing, down 11% in the last 7 days.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-Classic-hashrate-460x276.jpeg" width="460" height="276" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Volatility Will Spike By End 2022, Which Way Will It Push BTC?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-volatility-spike-2022-which-way/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 19:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513388</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin is stuck at its current levels, but the market might begin moving again before 2023 makes its entry. The key factors shaping global markets are changing, and cryptocurrencies are bound to follow the general trend into the new year.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Correction Soon? MVRV Triple Ribbon Approaches Bearish Cross As of this writing, Bitcoin trades at $16,800 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. On higher timeframes, the cryptocurrency records a 6% loss. Other assets in the crypto top 10 by market capitalization are moving in tandem with BTC and record losses in this period.  Bitcoin Investors Should Brace For Incoming Volatility Bitcoin and the crypto market are poised for volatile days during the holiday season. From now until the end of the year, markets will see less trading volume, making assets susceptible to sudden price movements.  According to a report from crypto exchange Bitfinex, the number of active Bitcoin addresses is declining. This number has been trending to the downside across 2022.  The chart below shows that the number of daily active addresses averaged 921,445 during this period, representing a decline of 1.1 million compared to 2021. This reduction in activity will contribute to the spike in volatility.  The last week of the year has seen a steeper decline in activity, and trading volume, since 2013. In addition, the downside action  Data since 2013 suggests that there is always a decline of 3-4 percent in the number of daily active addresses in the last week of the year compared to the previous month. Aside from the decline in trading volumes, the fall in DAA could also correspond to reduced mining operations as miners&#8217; activity corresponds to BTC&#8217;s most significant on-chain movements. Finding Direction For The BTC Price According to the report, one metric is vital to forecast BTC&#8217;s direction amid higher volatility. This metric is the Monthly Realised Volatility, which measures what has happened in the market over the past 30 days.  This metric is at its lowest &#8220;since Q3 of 2022, just before the last bull run.&#8221; As seen in the chart below, each time Monthly Realised Volatility reached similar levels, the Bitcoin price trends to the upside over the coming months.  Related Reading: Tron Shows Bullish Energy And Attracts Investors To Buy TRX The current trend in the market is to the downside, but many experts have begun shifting their predictions. As NewsBTC reported yesterday, a different report claims the long-term bullish case for Bitcoin strengthened: (…) the value proposition for bitcoin has only strengthened this year as sovereign currencies around the world have shown signs of stress and central banks continue to grapple with policy credibility.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Bitcoin is stuck at its current levels, but the market might begin moving again before 2023 makes its entry. The key factors shaping global markets are changing, and cryptocurrencies are bound to follow the general trend into the new year. </strong></p>

<p>As of this writing, Bitcoin trades at $16,800 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. On higher timeframes, the cryptocurrency records a 6% loss. Other assets in the crypto top 10 by market capitalization are moving in tandem with BTC and record losses in this period. </p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-513432 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-10-860x376.png" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT" width="860" height="376" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-10-860x376.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-10-460x201.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-10-768x336.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-10-1536x672.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-10-750x328.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-10-1140x499.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-10.png 1813w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<h2>Bitcoin Investors Should Brace For Incoming Volatility</h2>
<p>Bitcoin and the crypto market are poised for volatile days during the holiday season. From now until the end of the year, markets will see less trading volume, making assets susceptible to sudden price movements. </p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://blog.bitfinex.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitfinex-Alpha-35.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a> from crypto exchange Bitfinex, the number of active Bitcoin addresses is declining. This number has been trending to the downside across 2022. </p>
<p>The chart below shows that the number of daily active addresses averaged 921,445 during this period, representing a decline of 1.1 million compared to 2021. This reduction in activity will contribute to the spike in volatility. </p>
<p>The last week of the year has seen a steeper decline in activity, and trading volume, since 2013. In addition, the downside action </p>
<blockquote><p>Data since 2013 suggests that there is always a decline of 3-4 percent in the number of daily active addresses in the last week of the year compared to the previous month. Aside from the decline in trading volumes, the fall in DAA could also correspond to reduced mining operations as miners&#8217; activity corresponds to BTC&#8217;s most significant on-chain movements.</p></blockquote>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-513431 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-Glassnode.jpg" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT Chart 2 Glassnode" width="860" height="479" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-Glassnode.jpg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-Glassnode-460x256.jpg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-Glassnode-768x428.jpg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-Glassnode-750x418.jpg 750w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
Finding Direction For The BTC Price
<p>According to the report, one metric is vital to forecast BTC&#8217;s direction amid higher volatility. This metric is the Monthly Realised Volatility, which measures what has happened in the market over the past 30 days. </p>
<p>This metric is at its lowest &#8220;since Q3 of 2022, just before the last bull run.&#8221; As seen in the chart below, each time Monthly Realised Volatility reached similar levels, the Bitcoin price trends to the upside over the coming months. </p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-513430 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-BW-860x550.jpg" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT Chart 3 BW" width="860" height="550" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-BW-860x550.jpg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-BW-460x294.jpg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-BW-768x491.jpg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-BW-750x480.jpg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-3-BW.jpg 982w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />

<p>The current trend in the market is to the downside, but many experts have begun shifting their predictions. As NewsBTC <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-holders-loss-number-positive-btc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> yesterday, a different report claims the long-term bullish case for Bitcoin strengthened:</p>
<blockquote><p>(…) the value proposition for bitcoin has only strengthened this year as sovereign currencies around the world have shown signs of stress and central banks continue to grapple with policy credibility.</p></blockquote>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/iStock-1403389740-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bottom Signal: This Bitcoin Ratio Declines To Four-Year Low</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-ratio-declined-lowest-bottom-near/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 19:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bottom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin long-term holders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin short-term holders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin SOPR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin SOPR Ratio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513380</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows a Bitcoin ratio has hit the lowest value since February 2019, something that may suggest the bottom could be near for the current cycle. Bitcoin SOPR Ratio Hits Lows Not Seen Since 4 Years Ago As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, the SOPR Ratio has a value of just 0.53 right now. The &#8220;Spent Output Profit Ratio&#8221; (SOPR) is an indicator that tells us whether Bitcoin investors as a whole are selling at a profit or at a loss currently. There are two main investor groups in the BTC market, the &#8220;short-term holders&#8221; (STHs) and the &#8220;long-term holders&#8221; (LTHs). STHs include all holders that have been holding onto their coins for less than 155 days, while LTHs are investors who have been keeping their coins dormant for longer than this threshold amount. Now, there is a metric called the &#8220;SOPR Ratio&#8221; that measures the ratio between the SOPR values for the LTHs and the STHs. When this indicator has a value greater than 1, it means the LTHs are realizing more profits than the STHs right now. On the other hand, values below 1 suggest STHs have been raking in a higher amount of profits. Related Reading: Altcoin Indexes Take Beating As Investors Flip Alts For Bitcoin Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin SOPR Ratio over the course of the entire history of the cryptocurrency: The value of the metric seems to have declined recently &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As the above graph highlights, the Bitcoin SOPR Ratio has historically gone below a value of 1 during bear markets. The reason behind this is that the holders who bought during the preceding bull run slowly mature into LTHs as a bear takes hold, while the STH cohort starts being made up of investors who bought at the lower, bear-market prices. Related Reading: XRP Accumulation: Key Sharks And Whales Group Hits All-Time High Holdings During bears, both holder groups generally realize losses as a whole, but since STHs acquire their coins at relatively lower prices, their losses are lesser. The reverse happens in bull runs, as the LTHs who bought at the cycle lows amass large profits, and thus the SOPR Ratio attains values higher than 1. Recently, the indicator has dropped to a value of 0.53, which suggests large-scale capitulation from the LTHs. The current value is the lowest since February 2019, around when the lows of the previous cycle were observed. This could hint that the bottom for the current bear market may also be near, if not already in. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin&#8217;s price floats around $16,800, down 4% in the last week. Looks like BTC has shown boring price action in the last few days &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Jievani Weerasinghe on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows a Bitcoin ratio has hit the lowest value since February 2019, something that may suggest the bottom could be near for the current cycle.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin SOPR Ratio Hits Lows Not Seen Since 4 Years Ago</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/quicktake/63a2fbf76cac345516c0812e-SOPR-Ratio-reaches-lowest-value-in-3-years" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">post</a>, the SOPR Ratio has a value of just 0.53 right now. The &#8220;<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-capitulation-asopr-plunges-dec-2018-lows/">Spent Output Profit Ratio</a>&#8221; (SOPR) is an indicator that tells us whether Bitcoin investors as a whole are selling at a profit or at a loss currently.</p>
<p>There are two main investor groups in the BTC market, the &#8220;<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-declines-short-term-holders-take-profits/">short-term holders</a>&#8221; (STHs) and the &#8220;<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin-holders-losing-faith-in-btc/">long-term holders</a>&#8221; (LTHs). STHs include all holders that have been holding onto their coins for less than 155 days, while LTHs are investors who have been keeping their coins dormant for longer than this threshold amount.</p>
<p>Now, there is a metric called the &#8220;SOPR Ratio&#8221; that measures the ratio between the SOPR values for the LTHs and the STHs. When this indicator has a value greater than 1, it means the LTHs are realizing more profits than the STHs right now. On the other hand, values below 1 suggest STHs have been raking in a higher amount of profits.</p>

<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin SOPR Ratio over the course of the entire history of the cryptocurrency:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/3285/quicktake/nUs830_88a5d4f503b26504ed25f8cf38a0b97ddfd234c4f024896a96a3fa363de0660b.png" alt="Bitcoin SOPR Ratio" width="1280" height="368" /></p>

<p>As the above graph highlights, the Bitcoin SOPR Ratio has historically gone below a value of 1 during bear markets. The reason behind this is that the holders who bought during the preceding bull run slowly mature into LTHs as a bear takes hold, while the STH cohort starts being made up of investors who bought at the lower, bear-market prices.</p>

<p>During bears, both holder groups generally realize losses as a whole, but since STHs acquire their coins at relatively lower prices, their losses are lesser. The reverse happens in bull runs, as the LTHs who bought at the cycle lows amass large profits, and thus the SOPR Ratio attains values higher than 1.</p>
<p>Recently, the indicator has dropped to a value of 0.53, which suggests large-scale capitulation from the LTHs. The current value is the lowest since February 2019, around when the lows of the previous cycle were observed. This could hint that the bottom for the current bear market may also be near, if not already in.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin&#8217;s price floats around $16,800, down 4% in the last week.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-513403 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-28-460x258.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="460" height="258" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-28-460x258.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-28-860x483.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-28-768x431.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-28-750x421.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-28.png 972w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/jievani-weerasinghe-NHRM1u4GD_A-unsplash-460x282.jpg" width="460" height="282" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Santa Claus Rally: How Often Does The Christmas Miracle Occur In Crypto?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-santa-claus-rally-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony Spilotro]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 18:59:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513414</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[With Christmas almost here, hopes for a Santa Claus rally in Bitcoin and the rest of crypto are fading fast. But what exactly is the phenomenon, and how often has the Christmas miracle occurred in the past? What&#8217;s A Santa Claus Rally? The Most-Wished For Gift By Bitcoin Bulls A Santa Claus rally is defined as a &#8220;calendar effect&#8221; that occurs right around the holidays. According to Investopedia, there&#8217;s some slight disagreement over the exact timing of a Santa Claus rally. One camp claims its the lead up to Christmas where stock holders get an early present, while the other side states its the post-Christmas week leading into January 2nd. The idea behind the rally is the same: investors are suddenly euphoric due to the joyfulness of the holiday season, are considering year-end tax-related repositioning, and often have fresh Christmas bonuses to spend. The low-volume and liquidity holiday market conditions allow prices to move more swiftly, like Dasher, Dancer, Prancer, and Vixen through the snowy night sky. Related Reading: No Santa For Cryptos This Year: Large Cap Coins Touch December Lows Investopedia further concludes that there isn&#8217;t much validity to the idea behind the Santa Claus rally when analyzing S&#38;P 500 returns during this period. But what about Bitcoin and crypto, where retail investors dominate the market and trade 24/7 – even on Christmas Day? The complete history of holiday seasons in crypto &#124; BTCUSD on TradingView.com The Scrooge Effect: Bears Say Bah Humbug To Possible Crypto Rally The above chart depicts the crypto version of the Santa Claus rally, taking into consideration both the weeks before and after the annual holiday. At only a mere few cents, a breakout Christmas rally sustained until Bitcoin reached $40 for the first time. In 2011, December price action was more red than green. The next Santa Claus rally kept delivering gifts for crypto holders for nearly an entire year, until December 2013 struck and one of the worst downtrends on record followed all the way through until December 2014. Bitcoin reached its final bear market bottom back then only days away from Christmas. The following two Christmases in 2015 and 2016 were merry and bright for Bitcoin bulls. But December 2017 euphoria around Christmas-time turned out to be the top, resulting in yet another bear market. Related Reading: Bitcoin Bear Market Monthly Momentum Reaches Worst On Record In 2018, we&#8217;ve marked December in blue as the most neutral of all holiday price action. Although Bitcoin had fallen prior, it had already bottomed, and in the months following began a new bull run. It&#8217;s tough to call this price action bullish or bearish. Much like the bull market in 2015 and 2016 saw back to back green seasons, so did crypto investors in December 2019 and December 2020. In fact, December 2020 gave BTC a new all-time high – the first since December 2017. More all-time highs were made in 2021, but by December, it was back to a brutal downtrend for crypto. Here we are one year later, and the chart above does give us some clues about what might happen next. During the two largest bear markets, Bitcoin suffered from Scrooge-like behavior in the crypto industry two Decembers in a row. While we dubbed the second December in the second bear market neutral, it also wasn&#8217;t bullish by any stretch. Considering this pattern, this December has a cyclical rhythm that could suggest yet another lump of coal for investors this year. However, when looking at the data alone, there&#8217;s roughly a 50/50 chance that this holiday season is something to celebrate across crypto. Follow @TonySpilotroBTC on Twitter or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for exclusive daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With Christmas almost here, hopes for a Santa Claus rally in <a href="https://newsbtc.com/crypto/no-santa-for-crypto-this-year-large-cap-coins/">Bitcoin</a> and the rest of crypto are fading fast. But what exactly is the phenomenon, and how often has the Christmas miracle occurred in the past?</p>
<h2>What&#8217;s A Santa Claus Rally? The Most-Wished For Gift By Bitcoin Bulls</h2>
<p>A Santa Claus rally is defined as a &#8220;calendar effect&#8221; that occurs right around the holidays. According to <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/terms/s/santaclauseffect.asp" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Investopedia</a>, there&#8217;s some slight disagreement over the exact timing of a Santa Claus rally. One camp claims its the lead up to Christmas where stock holders get an early present, while the other side states its the post-Christmas week leading into January 2nd.</p>
<p>The idea behind the rally is the same: investors are suddenly euphoric due to the joyfulness of the holiday season, are considering year-end tax-related repositioning, and often have fresh Christmas bonuses to spend. The low-volume and liquidity holiday market conditions allow prices to move more swiftly, like Dasher, Dancer, Prancer, and Vixen through the snowy night sky.</p>

<p>Investopedia further concludes that there isn&#8217;t much validity to the idea behind the Santa Claus rally when analyzing S&amp;P 500 returns during this period. But what about Bitcoin and crypto, where retail investors dominate the market and trade 24/7 – even on Christmas Day?</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-large wp-image-513419 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-22_10-10-55-860x506.png" alt="BTCUSD_2022-12-22_10-10-55" width="860" height="506" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-22_10-10-55-860x506.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-22_10-10-55-460x271.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-22_10-10-55-768x452.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-22_10-10-55-1536x903.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-22_10-10-55-2048x1204.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-22_10-10-55-750x441.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-22_10-10-55-1140x670.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>

<h2>The Scrooge Effect: Bears Say Bah Humbug To Possible Crypto Rally</h2>
<p>The above chart depicts the crypto version of the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/crypto/no-santa-for-crypto-this-year-large-cap-coins/">Santa Claus rally</a>, taking into consideration both the weeks before and after the annual holiday.</p>
<p>At only a mere few cents, a breakout Christmas rally sustained until Bitcoin reached $40 for the first time. In 2011, December price action was more red than green.</p>
<p>The next Santa Claus rally kept delivering gifts for crypto holders for nearly an entire year, until December 2013 struck and one of the worst downtrends on record followed all the way through until December 2014. Bitcoin reached its final bear market bottom back then only days away from Christmas.</p>
<p>The following two Christmases in 2015 and 2016 were merry and bright for Bitcoin bulls. But December 2017 euphoria around Christmas-time turned out to be the top, resulting in yet another bear market.</p>

<p>In 2018, we&#8217;ve marked December in blue as the most neutral of all holiday price action. Although Bitcoin had fallen prior, it had already bottomed, and in the months following began a new bull run. It&#8217;s tough to call this price action bullish or bearish.</p>
<p>Much like the bull market in 2015 and 2016 saw back to back green seasons, so did crypto investors in December 2019 and December 2020. In fact, December 2020 gave BTC a new all-time high – the first since December 2017. More all-time highs were made in 2021, but by December, it was back to a brutal downtrend for crypto.</p>
<p>Here we are one year later, and the chart above does give us some clues about what might happen next. During the two largest bear markets, Bitcoin suffered from Scrooge-like behavior in the crypto industry two Decembers in a row. While we dubbed the second December in the second bear market neutral, it also wasn&#8217;t bullish by any stretch.</p>
<p>Considering this pattern, this December has a cyclical rhythm that could suggest yet another lump of coal for investors this year. However, when looking at the data alone, there&#8217;s roughly a 50/50 chance that this holiday season is something to celebrate across crypto.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/iStock-1358722232-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Exchange Inflows, Outflows At A Stalemate As Bitcoin Refuses To Budge</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-refuses-to-budge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 17:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513411</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin is still struggling below $17,000 and centralized exchange inflows and inflows seem to be mirroring the trend of the digital asset. Over the last 24 hours, the net flows from exchanges have been seeing a near balance between inflows and outflows. Balancing Each Other Out The exchange net flows reported by Glassnode show barely any difference between the amounts flowing into and out of exchanges. For bitcoin, it recorded $538.6 million worth of BTC flowing into exchanges and $557.4 million flowing out for the same time period. This brought net flows to a measly negative $18.8 million in the 24-hour period. Related Reading: https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/microstrategy-bought-bitcoin/ Ethereum was not much different in this regard with $247.8 million in inflows and $245 million in outflows. For the second-largest cryptocurrency by market cap, net flows were at a positive $2.8 million, showing even less disparity compared to bitcoin. The USDT stablecoin issued by Tether was still very muted in this regard. The $563.6 million in outflows compared to $572.8 million in inflows brought its net flows to a positive $9.2 million. More disparity compared to ethereum but is just as muted. 📊 Daily On-Chain Exchange Flow#Bitcoin $BTC➡️ $538.6M in⬅️ $557.4M out📉 Net flow: -$18.8M#Ethereum $ETH➡️ $247.8M in⬅️ $245.0M out📈 Net flow: +$2.8M#Tether (ERC20) $USDT➡️ $572.8M in⬅️ $563.6M out📈 Net flow: +$9.2Mhttps://t.co/dk2HbGwhVw &#8212; glassnode alerts (@glassnodealerts) December 22, 2022 What This Means For Bitcoin With the FUD around the Binance crypto exchange losing steam already, there is not much to trigger either large inflows or outflows at a time. This is why these top assets are seeing almost identical net flows. The market is still reeling from the contagion of the FTX collapse and traders and investors alike are refusing to take any big bets. Related Reading: Bitcoin Retail Investors Now Hold 17% Of Total BTC Supply, But Is It Good News? The impact of this has been that the price of bitcoin has not seen any meaningful movement. While it continues to maintain its critical support level above $16,500, there has been not much momentum to help it retest the $17,000 resistance level. BTC falls below $16,700 &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com Investor sentiment is also holding steady around 28 on the Fear &#38; Greed Index, putting investors out of the misery that is extreme fear but also leaving just enough caution in the market to prevent any panic buying or selling. If momentum fails to pick up, decreased trading volume around the holidays for the next two weeks could push bitcoin below the $16,000 level. If this happens, then the digital asset could end up closing the month of December in the red. BTC is changing hands at $16,690 at the time of this writing. It is down 4.94% in the last 7 days and 0.23% in the last 24 hours. Featured image from Vauld, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Bitcoin is still struggling below $17,000 and centralized exchange inflows and inflows seem to be mirroring the trend of the digital asset. Over the last 24 hours, the net flows from exchanges have been seeing a near balance between inflows and outflows.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Balancing Each Other Out</h2>
<p class="p2">The exchange net flows reported by Glassnode show barely any difference between the amounts flowing into and out of exchanges. For bitcoin, it recorded $538.6 million worth of BTC flowing into exchanges and $557.4 million flowing out for the same time period. This brought net flows to a measly negative $18.8 million in the 24-hour period.</p>

<p class="p2">Ethereum was not much different in this regard with $247.8 million in inflows and $245 million in outflows. For the second-largest cryptocurrency by market cap, net flows were at a positive $2.8 million, showing even less disparity compared to bitcoin.</p>
<p class="p2">The USDT stablecoin issued by Tether was still very muted in this regard. The $563.6 million in outflows compared to $572.8 million in inflows brought its net flows to a positive $9.2 million. More disparity compared to ethereum but is just as muted.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4ca.png" alt="📊" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Daily On-Chain Exchange Flow<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#Bitcoin</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$BTC</a><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/27a1.png" alt="➡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />  $538.6M in<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b05.png" alt="⬅" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />  $557.4M out<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4c9.png" alt="📉" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Net flow: -$18.8M<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Ethereum?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#Ethereum</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$ETH</a><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/27a1.png" alt="➡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />  $247.8M in<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b05.png" alt="⬅" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />  $245.0M out<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4c8.png" alt="📈" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Net flow: +$2.8M<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Tether?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#Tether</a> (ERC20) <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24USDT&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$USDT</a><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/27a1.png" alt="➡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />  $572.8M in<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b05.png" alt="⬅" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />  $563.6M out<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4c8.png" alt="📈" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Net flow: +$9.2M<a href="https://t.co/dk2HbGwhVw" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">https://t.co/dk2HbGwhVw</a></p>
<p>&mdash; glassnode alerts (@glassnodealerts) <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnodealerts/status/1605790234205208576?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">December 22, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<h2 class="p2">What This Means For Bitcoin</h2>
<p class="p2">With the FUD around the Binance crypto exchange losing steam already, there is not much to trigger either large inflows or outflows at a time. This is why these top assets are seeing almost identical net flows. The market is still reeling from the contagion of the FTX collapse and traders and investors alike are refusing to take any big bets.</p>

<p class="p2">The impact of this has been that the price of bitcoin has not seen any meaningful movement. While it continues to maintain its critical support level above $16,500, there has been not much momentum to help it retest the $17,000 resistance level.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/GiIjCuGd/" alt="Bitcoin price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1760" /></p>

<p class="p2">Investor sentiment is also holding steady around 28 on the Fear &amp; Greed Index, putting investors out of the misery that is extreme fear but also leaving just enough caution in the market to prevent any panic buying or selling.</p>
<p class="p2">If momentum fails to pick up, decreased trading volume around the holidays for the next two weeks could push bitcoin below the $16,000 level. If this happens, then the digital asset could end up closing the month of December in the red.</p>
<p class="p2">BTC is changing hands at $16,690 at the time of this writing. It is down 4.94% in the last 7 days and 0.23% in the last 24 hours.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-20-460x318.png" width="460" height="318" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Terra Luna Classic Up 6% On Rumor That Coinbase Is Buying LUNC</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/terra-luna/terra-luna-up-rumor-coinbase-buys-lunc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 15:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Terra (LUNA)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513378</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The collapse of Terra Luna and algorithmic stablecoin TerraUSD in May was one of the biggest setbacks for the broader crypto market this year. The previously thriving Terra ecosystem was completely wiped out in a matter of days, except for the Terra Luna token, which was resurrected as Terra Luna Classic (LUNC) by the community. Despite losing more than 99% of its value, the cryptocurrency still has one of the most active crypto communities on social media. And from it springs a rumor today that has pumped the price of LUNC by 6%. The rumor says that the second largest exchange in the world by trading volume, Coinbase, might buy the LUNC token in large quantities. Will Coinbase Buy Terra Luna Classic? Within the LUNC community, the news that Coinbase has authorized the purchase of $245 million in LUNC is currently spreading like wildfire. The speculation also indicates that the American exchange will make the news public on January 3, 2023, and provide information about additional LUNC burns. 🚨BREAKING NEWS🚨 Coinbase has just authorized the purchase of 245 million dollars in $LUNC. Internal source says that on the 3rd to announce publicly listing more off-chain burns. &#8212; WSB Trader Rocko 🚀🚀🚀 (@traderrocko) December 22, 2022 However, it is important to note that Coinbase has not yet issued an official statement on the matter. The various tweets also do not indicate a source, but merely make the claim based on a supposed source. Who this source of information is, whether it is someone internal, does not seem clear at the moment. Related Reading: Crypto Exchange Binance Dispels FUD Of A ‘Financial Black Box’ However, if the rumor turns out to be true, it could trigger the often-seen &#8220;Coinbase effect,&#8221; which causes altcoins to rise sharply before a listing on Coinbase. Remarkably, the rumor of a listing of LUNC is not new either. Just two months ago, the Luna Classic community started a petition to list LUNC on Coinbase, as NewsBTC reported. The Terra community wants to follow in the footsteps of the Shiba Inu community, which managed to get the meme coin listed. The Coinbase effect provided SHIB with a short-lived 20% pump. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Recovery Could Soon Fade If BTC Fails To Surpass $17.2K LUNC Price Rises By 6% At press time, the LUNC price stood at $0.00013625, registering a 6% price increase in the last 24 hours. Along with the surge in price, the trading volume of LUNC has also grown noticeably. Within the last 24 hours, it amounted to $90 million, which is 56% higher than the previous day. However, a look at the 4-hour chart reveals that LUNC remains in a deep bearish trading range. The short-lived rally ended just before the crucial resistance at $0.00014138. To set a bullish trend, LUNC needs to cross the trading range of $0.00013787 to $0.00015379. If the rally is short-lived, the support zone at $0.00012612 could be an important mark. Otherwise, the all-time low of LUNC at $0.00012136 would probably be on the table. Featured image from Depositphotos, Chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The collapse of Terra Luna and algorithmic stablecoin TerraUSD in May was one of the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/company/what-happens-if-crypto-exchange-binance-bust-like-ftx-and-terra/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">biggest setbacks</a> for the broader crypto market this year. The previously thriving Terra ecosystem was completely wiped out in a matter of days, except for the Terra Luna token, which was resurrected as Terra Luna Classic (LUNC) by the community.</p>
<p>Despite losing more than 99% of its value, the cryptocurrency still has one of the most active crypto communities on social media. And from it springs a <a href="https://twitter.com/OlusileCrypto/status/1605792324511940608" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">rumor</a> today that has pumped the price of LUNC by 6%. The rumor says that the second largest exchange in the world by trading volume, Coinbase, might buy the LUNC token in large quantities.</p>
<h2>Will Coinbase Buy Terra Luna Classic?</h2>
<p>Within the LUNC community, the news that Coinbase has authorized the purchase of $245 million in LUNC is currently spreading like wildfire. The speculation also indicates that the American exchange will make the news public on January 3, 2023, and provide information about additional LUNC burns.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />BREAKING NEWS<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>Coinbase has just authorized the purchase of 245 million dollars in <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24LUNC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$LUNC</a>. Internal source says that on the 3rd to announce publicly listing more off-chain burns.</p>
<p>&mdash; WSB Trader Rocko <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@traderrocko) <a href="https://twitter.com/traderrocko/status/1605877574248308737?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">December 22, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>However, it is important to note that Coinbase has not yet issued an official statement on the matter. The various tweets also do not indicate a source, but merely make the claim based on a supposed source. Who this source of information is, whether it is someone internal, does not seem clear at the moment.</p>

<p>However, if the rumor turns out to be true, it could trigger the often-seen &#8220;Coinbase effect,&#8221; which causes altcoins to rise sharply before a listing on Coinbase. Remarkably, the rumor of a listing of LUNC is not new either.</p>
<p>Just two months ago, the Luna Classic community started a petition to list LUNC on Coinbase, as NewsBTC <a href="https://newsbtc.com/terra-luna/lunc-community-clamors-for-coinbase-listing-can-it-reach-1/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a>. The Terra community wants to follow in the footsteps of the Shiba Inu community, which managed to get the meme coin listed. The Coinbase effect provided SHIB with a short-lived 20% pump.</p>

<h2>LUNC Price Rises By 6%</h2>
<p>At press time, the LUNC price stood at $0.00013625, registering a 6% price increase in the last 24 hours. Along with the surge in price, the trading volume of LUNC has also grown noticeably. Within the last 24 hours, it amounted to $90 million, which is 56% higher than the previous day.</p>
<p>However, a look at the 4-hour chart reveals that LUNC remains in a deep bearish trading range. The short-lived rally ended just before the crucial resistance at $0.00014138. To set a bullish trend, LUNC needs to cross the trading range of $0.00013787 to $0.00015379.</p>
<p>If the rally is short-lived, the support zone at $0.00012612 could be an important mark. Otherwise, the all-time low of LUNC at $0.00012136 would probably be on the table.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-513389 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSDT_2022-12-22_13-58-45.png" alt="Terra Luna Classic LUNC USDT 2022-12-22" width="3618" height="1611" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSDT_2022-12-22_13-58-45.png 3618w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSDT_2022-12-22_13-58-45-460x205.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSDT_2022-12-22_13-58-45-860x383.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSDT_2022-12-22_13-58-45-768x342.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSDT_2022-12-22_13-58-45-1536x684.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSDT_2022-12-22_13-58-45-2048x912.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSDT_2022-12-22_13-58-45-750x334.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LUNCUSDT_2022-12-22_13-58-45-1140x508.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3618px) 100vw, 3618px" />
<p>Featured image from Depositphotos, Chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/Depositphotos_350919960_s-2019-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Correction Soon? MVRV Triple Ribbon Approaches Bearish Cross</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-correction-mvrv-bearish-cross/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 14:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin bearish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bearish Crossover]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin correction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin MVRV Ratio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin MVRV Ratio Triple Ribbon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513364</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Bitcoin MVRV Ratio Triple Ribbon is approaching a bearish cross, a sign that a correction could be coming soon for the crypto&#8217;s price. Bitcoin MVRV Ratio Triple Ribbon Is Close To Bearish Crossover As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, the MVRV ratio warns that a new round of decline may be coming for BTC. The &#8220;MVRV ratio&#8221; is an indicator that measures the ratio between the market cap of Bitcoin and its realized cap. The realized cap is a capitalization model for BTC that calculates a sort of &#8220;real value&#8221; for the asset by assuming that the true worth of each coin in circulation is the price at which the particular coin was last moved. Related Reading: XRP Accumulation: Key Sharks And Whales Group Hits All-Time High Holdings By comparing this realized cap with the market cap, the indicator tells us whether the coin&#8217;s actual price is fair or not right now. Here is a chart that shows the trend in three moving averages (10-day, 15-day, and 20-day) of this metric over the last few months: The three MAs seem to have been closing in on each other in recent days &#124; Source: CryptoQuant These three MAs of the Bitcoin MVRV Ratio together form the &#8220;Triple Ribbon&#8221; indicator, and crossovers between these ribbons have historically had implications for the price of the asset. As you can see in the above graph, whenever the 10-day MA has passed below both the 15-day and the 20-day versions, while at the same time the 20-day has gone above both the others (thus keeping the 15-day&#8217;s position unchanged in the middle), a bearish crossover has formed for BTC. There have been two instances of such a cross during the last few months; the first one occurred back in August when Bitcoin was at the height of its first relief rally of this bear market, while the other one formed in November right as the FTX crash came around. In both of these occurrences, BTC&#8217;s price took a deep plunge following the cross formation. Related Reading: Altcoin Indexes Take Beating As Investors Flip Alts For Bitcoin From the chart, it&#8217;s apparent that the MVRV Ratio Triple Ribbon has once again been approaching this same kind of bearish crossover recently. If these MAs continue in this trajectory and the cross does end up happening, then it might mean the crypto will see another sharp drop soon. BTC Price Looks like the value of the asset has continued to move sideways in the last few days &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView At the time of writing, Bitcoin&#8217;s price floats around $16,800, down 5% in the last week. Featured image from Mark Basarab on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows the Bitcoin MVRV Ratio Triple Ribbon is approaching a bearish cross, a sign that a correction could be coming soon for the crypto&#8217;s price.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin MVRV Ratio Triple Ribbon Is Close To Bearish Crossover</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/quicktake/63a353fa70bbe0191de9beb6-A-warning-signal-about-the-likely-next-decline-in-Bitcoin" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">post</a>, the MVRV ratio warns that a new round of decline may be coming for BTC. The &#8220;<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-mvrv-ratio-below-average-holder-slips-loss/">MVRV ratio</a>&#8221; is an indicator that measures the ratio between the market cap of Bitcoin and its realized cap. The realized cap is a capitalization model for BTC that calculates a sort of &#8220;real value&#8221; for the asset by assuming that the true worth of each coin in circulation is the price at which the particular coin was last moved.</p>

<p>By comparing this realized cap with the market cap, the indicator tells us whether the coin&#8217;s actual price is fair or not right now. Here is a chart that shows the trend in three moving averages (10-day, 15-day, and 20-day) of this metric over the last few months:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/35304/quicktake/DWeItfH_f3cd5cfb3346d4dcede90180a5ee7573fb41e577fac55bcfc26e8f41983ecca0.png" alt="Bitcoin MVRV Ratio Tripple Ribbon" width="1034" height="448" /></p>

<p>These three MAs of the Bitcoin MVRV Ratio together form the &#8220;<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bracebitcoin-mvrv-triple-ribbon-forms-bearish-cross/">Triple Ribbon</a>&#8221; indicator, and crossovers between these ribbons have historically had implications for the price of the asset. As you can see in the above graph, whenever the 10-day MA has passed below both the 15-day and the 20-day versions, while at the same time the 20-day has gone above both the others (thus keeping the 15-day&#8217;s position unchanged in the middle), a bearish crossover has formed for BTC.</p>
<p>There have been two instances of such a cross during the last few months; the first one occurred back in August when Bitcoin was at the height of its first relief rally of this bear market, while the other one formed in November right as the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/ftx-crash-triggers-major-selloff-in-solana-price-how-deep-will-sol-dive/">FTX crash</a> came around. In both of these occurrences, BTC&#8217;s price took a deep plunge following the cross formation.</p>

<p>From the chart, it&#8217;s apparent that the MVRV Ratio Triple Ribbon has once again been approaching this same kind of bearish crossover recently. If these MAs continue in this trajectory and the cross does end up happening, then it might mean the crypto will see another sharp drop soon.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-513367 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-27-460x257.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="460" height="257" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-27-460x257.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-27-860x481.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-27-768x430.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-27-750x420.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/chart-27.png 974w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin&#8217;s price floats around $16,800, down 5% in the last week.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/mark-basarab-y421kXlUOQk-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tron Shows Bullish Energy And Attracts Investors To Buy TRX</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/tron-shows-bullish-energy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 13:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Justin Sun]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tron price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRX Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513390</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TRON has been on an uptrend and looking bullish for the past 12 hours. The technical indicators all imply an increased demand on the asset and a steady streak.  Here&#8217;s a quick glance of how the crypto has been performing of late: TRX price up by 0.20% as of this writing Technical indicators show increased TRX demand TRON second in line in terms of TVL Tron Price Retraces By Half According to CoinMarketCap, TRX price has spiked by 0.20% or is trading at .05529 as of this writing. TRON has tested the key support level of $0.54 several times this month. TRX price has also retraced by 50% or currently at the $0.0578 level as the coin retreated from 0.066 to $0.047. Related Reading: VeChain Jumps By 4% As VET Investors Look To Profit Before Christmas Source: TradingView The Visible Range Volume Profile looked promising too as it showcased the point of control which is at the $0.055 level and with the value area high seen at $0.059. On November 26, TRON retested the key support level of $0.0527. The bullish breaker can be spotted right below this level extending from $0.0527 to $0.0516. Evidently, the price has tried to retest the bullish breaker several times, seeing a visible reaction on every retest performed. TRON has recently disclosed they are second in line in terms of Total Value Locked (TVL), trailing behind Ethereum. It also demonstrated an impressive burn rate which only supports the premise of TRON’s accelerating growth. TRX total market cap at $5 billion on the daily chart &#124; Chart: TradingView.com The frequent retests done on the bullish breakers as well as the higher lows has triggered the formation of a right-angled pattern which could be signaling a breakout northwards on price. On the other hand, Bitcoin is trying to barrel past the mounting pressure experienced at the $17k-$17.4k, which hints that a pullback could give the bulls an opening to go and buy TRX. Related Reading: Why Bitcoin Long-Term Holders Seem To Be Losing Interest In BTC Source: TradingView Tron OBV On The Rise TRX is now being supported, but is failing to make any notable chart moves. Instead, price action is continuing to move sideways within the pennant that formed. Meanwhile, a further rejection would send the TRX price action back down, where it would then attempt to test the support provided by the the ascending trendline. Source: TradingView Should that level be breached, bearish follow-through trading towards $0.051 can be anticipated. Since November, it has been observed that TRON&#8217;s on-balance volume has been rapidly increasing, which demonstrates an exceptionally high level of buying pressure. In this case, although the formation of the right-angled pattern hints at an upward breakout, there seems to be another scenario as shown in the flat open interest chart. This suggests that TRX price may have already peaked which means a lack of further momentum could signify a weakening in the trend.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TRON has been on an uptrend and looking bullish for the past 12 hours. The technical indicators all imply an increased demand on the asset and a steady streak. </p>
<p>Here&#8217;s a quick glance of how the crypto has been performing of late:</p>
<ul>
<li>TRX price up by 0.20% as of this writing</li>
<li>Technical indicators show increased TRX demand</li>
<li>TRON second in line in terms of TVL</li>
</ul>
<h2><b>Tron Price Retraces By Half</b></h2>
<p>According to<a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/tron/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> CoinMarketCap</a>, TRX price has spiked by 0.20% or is trading at .05529 as of this writing.</p>
<p>TRON has tested the key support level of $0.54 several times this month. TRX price has also retraced by 50% or currently at the $0.0578 level as the coin retreated from 0.066 to $0.047.</p>

<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-513391 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/a-11.png" alt="" width="622" height="347" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/a-11.png 622w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/a-11-460x257.png 460w" sizes="(max-width: 622px) 100vw, 622px" /></p>

<p>The Visible Range Volume Profile looked promising too as it showcased the point of control which is at the $0.055 level and with the value area high seen at $0.059.</p>
<p>On November 26, <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/tron-in-a-healthy-uptrend-despite-fear-in-the-market-should-traders-look-to-buy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">TRON</a> retested the key support level of $0.0527. The bullish breaker can be spotted right below this level extending from $0.0527 to $0.0516. </p>
<p>Evidently, the price has tried to retest the bullish breaker several times, seeing a visible reaction on every retest performed.</p>
<p>TRON has recently disclosed they are second in line in terms of Total Value Locked (TVL), trailing behind Ethereum. It also demonstrated an impressive burn rate which only supports the premise of TRON’s accelerating growth.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/iE3rknUc/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>

<p>The frequent retests done on the bullish breakers as well as the higher lows has triggered the formation of a right-angled pattern which could be signaling a breakout northwards on price.</p>
<p>On the other hand,<a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> Bitcoin</a> is trying to barrel past the mounting pressure experienced at the $17k-$17.4k, which hints that a pullback could give the bulls an opening to go and buy TRX.</p>

<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-513396 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/b-1.png" alt="" width="591" height="322" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/b-1.png 591w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/b-1-460x251.png 460w" sizes="(max-width: 591px) 100vw, 591px" /></p>

<h2><b>Tron OBV On The Rise</b></h2>
<p>TRX is now being supported, but is failing to make any notable chart moves. Instead, price action is continuing to move sideways within the pennant that formed.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, a further rejection would send the TRX price action back down, where it would then attempt to test the support provided by the the ascending trendline.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-513397 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/c-1-460x232.png" alt="" width="460" height="232" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/c-1-460x232.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/c-1.png 694w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p>Should that level be breached, bearish follow-through trading towards $0.051 can be anticipated.</p>
<p>Since November, it has been observed that TRON&#8217;s on-balance volume has been rapidly increasing, which demonstrates an exceptionally high level of buying pressure.</p>
<p>In this case, although the formation of the right-angled pattern hints at an upward breakout, there seems to be another scenario as shown in the flat open interest chart.</p>
<p>This suggests that TRX price may have already peaked which means a lack of further momentum could signify a weakening in the trend.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Tron-1-460x306.png" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
