<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 04:13:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Monero (XMR) Higher 13 Days In A Row: What’s Next?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/monero/monero-xmr-higher-13-days-in-a-row-whats-next/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[dbthequant]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 04:21:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Monero]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[monero]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monero (XMR) Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monero (XMR) Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XMR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XMRUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xmrusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539833</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[An altcoin with a long and storied history, Monero is currently running to the upside in a way it never has before. After closing higher for twelve consecutive days &#8211; a new record for the privacy-focused altcoin &#8211; Monero looks poised to once again make history with a thirteenth straight higher close. What&#8217;s happened after other Monero winning streaks in the past? Let’s take a closer look at the price history to find out. Monero Win Streak Making History Monero&#8217;s current winning streak of twelve consecutively higher closes breaks the previous record set in 2021 of ten straight higher closes. While the price advance is clearly impressive, its unprecedented nature means we&#8217;ll have to look at earlier and shorter win streaks to get an understanding of what might be ahead for Monero in the future. In other words, we&#8217;ll use the prior shorter historical win streaks to generate enough occurrences to make a more statistically meaningful conclusion. Monero 2023 Winning Streak &#124; XMRUSD on TradingView.com &#160; Monero 2021 Winning Streak &#124; XMRUSD on TradingView.com Related Reading: After Raising $3M, HedgeUp (HDUP) Receives Influx of Shiba Inu (SHIB) and Monero (XMR) Investors Because the number of occurrences varies based on holding time, we’ll start by listing the number of times that six straight higher closes has happened next to our several hypothetical hold times of 7 days through 365 days. Holding time is defined as the amount of time one held the asset before exiting. For example, if one hypothetically purchased Monero following the trigger event (i.e., 6 straight higher closes) and sold it 30 days later, this would be a holding time of 30 days. Monero Occurrences of Six Consecutive Higher Closes by Holding Time (May 2014 &#8211; Present) 12 occurrences using a 7-day hold time 12 occurrences using a 15-day hold time 12 occurrences using a 30-day hold time 11 occurrences using a 60-day hold time 11 occurrences using a 90-day hold time 7 occurrences using a 180-day hold time 5 occurrences using a 356-day hold time While the number of occurrences remains limited even with the shorter win streak, past Monero winning streaks of six consecutively higher closes provides enough data to examine so let&#8217;s dive into the analysis. Past Monero Win Streaks Suggest More Strength Ahead The hypothetical average trade results for Monero (XMR) show a consistent positive edge across all holding times from 7 days through one year. Please note that even though the average historical trade results are positive for each hold time we examine, losses have also occurred for each hold time. Monero Hold Time Results for Six Straight Higher Closes &#124; SOURCE: Tableau Going out to a roughly three-month hold time, the past win streaks have delivered far greater gains on average, with an average trade of +65.1% with a 90-day hold, +121.7% with a 180-day hold, to an impressive +373.8% with a 365-day hold. Related Reading: Solana (SOL), Monero (XMR), and DigiToads (TOADS) Form an Unbeatable Trio for Crypto Investors While we&#8217;ve certainly never seen a streak of consecutively higher closes to match the current twelve and nearly thirteen, Monero&#8217;s long price history suggests that more strength could be ahead, especially going out to three months and beyond. DB the Quant is the author of the REKTelligence Report newsletter on Substack. Follow @REKTelligence on Twitter for evidence-based crypto market research and analysis. Important Note: This content is strictly educational in nature and should not be considered investment advice. Featured images created with Tableau. Charts from TradingView.com.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An altcoin with a long and storied history, Monero is currently running to the upside in a way it never has before. After closing higher for twelve consecutive days &#8211; a new record for the privacy-focused altcoin &#8211; Monero looks poised to once again make history with a thirteenth straight higher close. What&#8217;s happened after other Monero winning streaks in the past? Let’s take a closer look at the price history to find out.</p>
<h2>Monero Win Streak Making History</h2>
<p>Monero&#8217;s current winning streak of twelve consecutively higher closes breaks the previous record set in 2021 of ten straight higher closes. While the price advance is clearly impressive, its unprecedented nature means we&#8217;ll have to look at earlier and shorter win streaks to get an understanding of what might be ahead for Monero in the future. In other words, we&#8217;ll use the prior shorter historical win streaks to generate enough occurrences to make a more statistically meaningful conclusion.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-540009 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XMR_2023-Streak10-460x233.png" alt="" width="460" height="233" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XMR_2023-Streak10-460x233.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XMR_2023-Streak10-860x436.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XMR_2023-Streak10-768x389.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XMR_2023-Streak10-1536x779.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XMR_2023-Streak10-750x380.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XMR_2023-Streak10-1140x578.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XMR_2023-Streak10.png 1566w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>
<p style="text-align: center">Monero 2023 Winning Streak | XMRUSD on TradingView.com</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-540010 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XMR_2021-Streak10-460x233.png" alt="" width="460" height="233" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XMR_2021-Streak10-460x233.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XMR_2021-Streak10-860x436.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XMR_2021-Streak10-768x389.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XMR_2021-Streak10-1536x779.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XMR_2021-Streak10-750x380.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XMR_2021-Streak10-1140x578.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XMR_2021-Streak10.png 1566w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>









Because the number of occurrences varies based on holding time, we’ll start by listing the number of times that six straight higher closes has happened next to our several hypothetical hold times of 7 days through 365 days. Holding time is defined as the amount of time one held the asset before exiting. For example, if one hypothetically purchased Monero following the trigger event (i.e., 6 straight higher closes) and sold it 30 days later, this would be a holding time of 30 days.

<p><strong>Monero Occurrences of Six Consecutive Higher Closes by Holding Time (May 2014 &#8211; Present)</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>12 occurrences using a 7-day hold time</li>
<li>12 occurrences using a 15-day hold time</li>
<li>12 occurrences using a 30-day hold time</li>
<li>11 occurrences using a 60-day hold time</li>
<li>11 occurrences using a 90-day hold time</li>
<li>7 occurrences using a 180-day hold time</li>
<li>5 occurrences using a 356-day hold time</li>
</ul>
<p>While the number of occurrences remains limited even with the shorter win streak, past Monero winning streaks of six consecutively higher closes provides enough data to examine so let&#8217;s dive into the analysis.</p>
<h2>Past Monero Win Streaks Suggest More Strength Ahead</h2>
<p>The hypothetical average trade results for Monero (XMR) show a consistent positive edge across all holding times from 7 days through one year. Please note that even though the average historical trade results are positive for each hold time we examine, losses have also occurred for each hold time.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-540019 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XMR-HOLD-TIMES-6d-streaks-460x286.png" alt="" width="460" height="286" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XMR-HOLD-TIMES-6d-streaks-460x286.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XMR-HOLD-TIMES-6d-streaks-860x534.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XMR-HOLD-TIMES-6d-streaks-768x477.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XMR-HOLD-TIMES-6d-streaks-750x466.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XMR-HOLD-TIMES-6d-streaks.png 976w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>



<p>Going out to a roughly three-month hold time, the past win streaks have delivered far greater gains on average, with an average trade of +65.1% with a 90-day hold, +121.7% with a 180-day hold, to an impressive +373.8% with a 365-day hold.</p>



<p>While we&#8217;ve certainly never seen a streak of consecutively higher closes to match the current twelve and nearly thirteen, Monero&#8217;s long price history suggests that more strength could be ahead, especially going out to three months and beyond.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/3B158745-F82A-41DC-AF98-743554CFBF8A-460x307.jpeg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>LINK Price Prediction: Chainlink Could Lift-off Toward $8</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/link/link-price-prediction-chainlink-to-8-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 04:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LINK]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chainlink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Link]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LINKUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[linkusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540049</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Chainlink’s LINK price is showing positive signs above $6.00. The price could rise further if it clears the $6.30 and $6.50 resistance levels. Chainlink token price is showing positive signs and rising from $5.00 against the US dollar. The price is trading above the $6.00 level and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $5.10 on the 4-hour chart of the LINK/USD pair (data source from Kraken). The price could extend its recovery and rally toward the $8.0 resistance zone. Chainlink (LINK) Eyes More Gains After a major decline, LINK price found support near the $5.0 zone against the US Dollar. A low was formed near $5.004 and the price started a fresh increase, similar to Bitcoin and Ethereum. There was a clear move above the $5.10 and $5.50 resistance levels. Besides, there was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $5.10 on the 4-hours chart of the LINK/USD pair. The upward move gained pace above the $5.80 resistance. LINK even jumped above $6.0 before the bears appeared. A high is formed near $6.37 and the price is now consolidating gains. Chainlink price is now trading above the $6.00 level and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). It is also showing positive signs above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $5.00 swing low to the $6.37 high. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $6.35 zone. Source: LINKUSD on TradingView.com The first major resistance is near the $6.50 zone. A clear break above $6.50 may possibly start a fresh increase toward the $7.20 and $7.25 levels. The next major resistance is near the $7.80 level, above which the price could revisit $8.0. Dips Supported? If chainlink’s price fails to climb above the $6.50 resistance level, there could be a downside correction. Initial support on the downside is near the $6.05 level. The next major support is near the $5.70 level, below which the price might test the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $5.00 swing low to the $6.37 high at $5.50. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $5.00 level in the near term. Technical Indicators 4 hours MACD – The MACD for LINK/USD is losing momentum in the bullish zone. 4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LINK/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $6.05 and $5.70. Major Resistance Levels – $6.35 and $6.50.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Chainlink’s LINK price is showing positive signs above $6.00. The price could rise further if it clears the $6.30 and $6.50 resistance levels.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Chainlink token price is showing positive signs and rising from $5.00 against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is trading above the $6.00 level and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $5.10 on the 4-hour chart of the LINK/USD pair (data source from Kraken).</li>
<li>The price could extend its recovery and rally toward the $8.0 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Chainlink (LINK) Eyes More Gains</h2>
<p>After a major decline, LINK price found support near the $5.0 zone against the US Dollar. A low was formed near $5.004 and the price started a fresh increase, similar to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-consolidates-below-31k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a> and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-correction-1790/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum</a>.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above the $5.10 and $5.50 resistance levels. Besides, there was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $5.10 on the 4-hours chart of the LINK/USD pair. The upward move gained pace above the $5.80 resistance.</p>
<p>LINK even jumped above $6.0 before the bears appeared. A high is formed near $6.37 and the price is now consolidating gains. Chainlink price is now trading above the $6.00 level and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>It is also showing positive signs above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $5.00 swing low to the $6.37 high. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $6.35 zone.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-540050" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Chainlink-LINK.png" alt="LINK Price Prediction" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Chainlink-LINK.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Chainlink-LINK-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Chainlink-LINK-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Chainlink-LINK-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Chainlink-LINK-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Chainlink-LINK-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Chainlink-LINK-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LINKUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">LINKUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $6.50 zone. A clear break above $6.50 may possibly start a fresh increase toward the $7.20 and $7.25 levels. The next major resistance is near the $7.80 level, above which the price could revisit $8.0.</p>
<h2>Dips Supported?</h2>
<p>If chainlink’s price fails to climb above the $6.50 resistance level, there could be a downside correction. Initial support on the downside is near the $6.05 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $5.70 level, below which the price might test the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $5.00 swing low to the $6.37 high at $5.50. Any more losses could lead the price toward the $5.00 level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>4 hours MACD – The MACD for LINK/USD is losing momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4 hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for LINK/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $6.05 and $5.70.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $6.35 and $6.50.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/shutterstock_1312720985-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Indicators Signal Extended Correction To $1,790</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-correction-1790/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 03:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540046</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum price is slowly moving lower from the $1,920 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH could extend its decline toward the $1,790 support. Ethereum is still struggling to surpass the $1,920 resistance. The price is trading below $1,900 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $1,885 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could decline further toward the $1,790 support in the coming sessions. Ethereum Price Stuck In A Range Ethereum’s price attempted another upside break above the key $1,920 resistance zone. ETH failed to gain bullish momentum for a close above the $1,920 level, similar to Bitcoin. A high is formed near $1,912 and the price is now moving lower. There was a break below the $1,900 level. The price declined below the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $1,838 low to the $1,912 high. Besides, there was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $1,885 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. Ether is now trading below $1,900 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. It is now testing the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $1,838 low to the $1,912 high. If Ethereum stays above $1,850, it could attempt another increase. Immediate resistance is near the $1,880 level or the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. The next major resistance is near the $1,900 level. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com The main barrier is still near the $1,920 and $1,930 levels. A close above the $1,930 zone could start a steady increase and send the price further higher. The next resistance sits near $2,000, above which the price could rise toward the $2,050 level. Any more gains could send Ether toward the $2,120 resistance. More Losses in ETH? If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,900 resistance, it could continue to move down. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,850 level. The next major support is near the $1,840 level. If there is a move below $1,840, the price could accelerate lower toward $1,790. Any more losses may perhaps send the price toward the $1,750 support. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is gaining momentum in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is now below the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,840 Major Resistance Level – $1,900]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum price is slowly moving lower from the $1,920 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH could extend its decline toward the $1,790 support.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum is still struggling to surpass the $1,920 resistance.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $1,900 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</li>
<li>There was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $1,885 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could decline further toward the $1,790 support in the coming sessions.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Stuck In A Range</h2>
<p>Ethereum’s price attempted another upside break above the key $1,920 resistance zone. ETH failed to gain bullish momentum for a close above the $1,920 level, similar to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-consolidates-below-31k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p>A high is formed near $1,912 and the price is now moving lower. There was a break below the $1,900 level. The price declined below the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $1,838 low to the $1,912 high. Besides, there was a break below a key bullish trend line with support near $1,885 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD.</p>
<p>Ether is now trading below $1,900 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-lacks-momentum-above-1900/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100-hourly Simple Moving Average</a>. It is now testing the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $1,838 low to the $1,912 high.</p>
<p>If Ethereum stays above $1,850, it could attempt another increase. Immediate resistance is near the $1,880 level or the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. The next major resistance is near the $1,900 level.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-540047" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-18.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-18.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-18-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-18-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-18-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-18-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-18-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-18-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The main barrier is still near the $1,920 and $1,930 levels. A close above the $1,930 zone could start a steady increase and send the price further higher. The next resistance sits near $2,000, above which the price could rise toward the $2,050 level. Any more gains could send Ether toward the $2,120 resistance.</p>
<h2>More Losses in ETH?</h2>
<p>If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,900 resistance, it could continue to move down. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,850 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $1,840 level. If there is a move below $1,840, the price could accelerate lower toward $1,790. Any more losses may perhaps send the price toward the $1,750 support.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is gaining momentum in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,840</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,900</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/shutterstock_1100038610-460x272.jpg" width="460" height="272" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Struggles As Bears Attempt To Drive It Below $30,000</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-price-struggles-as-bears-attempt-to-drive-it-below-30000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 03:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540020</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) failed to break through the $31,500 resistance level and has since retreated to a range between $30,300 and $30,800 in the past few days. The cryptocurrency has also been unable to reclaim the $31,000 territory, leading some to believe that Bitcoin bears may still have the upper hand. Despite recent signs of strength, Bitcoin&#8217;s inability to overcome key resistance levels has left many investors wary. The digital currency&#8217;s failure to break out of its current range suggests that it may be vulnerable to further losses in the short term. Liquidity Grab Sends Bitcoin Tumbling Bitcoin has been on a remarkable run since June 15th, gaining 25% in nine days. However, according to crypto analyst Justin Bennet, recent price action suggests a pullback may be in order. BTC longs have piled into the rally, but as Bennet notes, Bitcoin doesn&#8217;t usually offer free rides for those late to the party. A pullback from current levels just above $30,000 would make sense, and the price action on the 8-hour time frame looks very similar to the April swing high. Related Reading: BLUR Up By 11% Following This Announcement Bitcoin closed above $30,400 on the 8-hour trend line in April, only to close below it within the next few candles. While BTC has held up better this time, the 4-hour time frame has already broken below $30,400. The next few 8-hour candles will confirm whether this breakdown is sustained. If so, Bennet believes a pullback into the $28,000 area to flush out late BTC longs seems likely. How the Bitcoin price action develops at $27,000-$28,000 if and when tested will determine where BTC trends in July. On the other hand, a sustained break above $31,000 would suggest that bulls remain in control and expose $32,500. Nevertheless, despite the uncertain market conditions, the current uptrend in Bitcoin is far from over as long as bulls do not lose the $30,000 line.  Historical data suggests that if Bitcoin can consolidate and maintain this key level of support, there are many chances for it to continue to breach higher levels and mark new yearly highs. Conversely, the $29,500 support level will be the next floor to watch if Bitcoin succumbs to bearish pressure. A downside movement could continue if BTC drops below this level, potentially leading to a further decline toward the $27,300 line.  Related Reading: Ripple Thrives Despite Legal Battle – What’s The Market Reaction Of XRP? Despite the potential downside risks, the Bitcoin market continues to receive positive news with the applications of Fidelity and Blackrock&#8217;s Spot Exchange-Traded Funds (ETF). The approval of these ETF applications could further boost the current price action and potentially lead to new yearly highs. Bitcoin is currently trading at $30,600, representing a modest increase of 1.4% over the past 24 hours. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC) failed to break through the $31,500 resistance level and has since retreated to a range between $30,300 and $30,800 in the past few days. The cryptocurrency has also been unable to reclaim the $31,000 territory, leading some to believe that Bitcoin bears may still have the upper hand.</p>
<p>Despite recent signs of strength, Bitcoin&#8217;s inability to overcome key resistance levels has left many investors wary. The digital currency&#8217;s failure to break out of its current range suggests that it may be vulnerable to further losses in the short term.</p>
<h2>Liquidity Grab Sends Bitcoin Tumbling</h2>
<p>Bitcoin has been on a remarkable run since June 15th, gaining 25% in nine days. However, <a href="https://dailypriceaction.com/crypto/bitcoin-pull-back-this-week/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">according </a>to crypto analyst Justin Bennet, recent price action suggests a pullback may be in order.</p>
<p>BTC longs have piled into the rally, but as Bennet notes, Bitcoin doesn&#8217;t usually offer free rides for those late to the party. A pullback from current levels just above $30,000 would make sense, and the price action on the 8-hour time frame looks very similar to the April swing high.</p>

<p>Bitcoin closed above $30,400 on the 8-hour trend line in April, only to close below it within the next few candles. While BTC has held up better this time, the 4-hour time frame has already broken below $30,400. The next few 8-hour candles will confirm whether this breakdown is sustained.</p>
<p>If so, Bennet believes a pullback into the $28,000 area to flush out late BTC longs seems likely. How the Bitcoin price action develops at $27,000-$28,000 if and when tested will determine where BTC trends in July.</p>
<p>On the other hand, a sustained break above $31,000 would suggest that bulls remain in control and expose $32,500.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, despite the uncertain market conditions, the current uptrend in Bitcoin is far from over as long as bulls do not lose the $30,000 line. </p>
<p>Historical data suggests that if Bitcoin can consolidate and maintain this key level of support, there are many chances for it to continue to breach higher levels and mark new yearly highs.</p>
<p>Conversely, the $29,500 support level will be the next floor to watch if Bitcoin succumbs to bearish pressure. A downside movement could continue if BTC drops below this level, potentially leading to a further decline toward the $27,300 line. </p>

<p>Despite the potential downside risks, the Bitcoin market continues to receive positive news with the applications of Fidelity and Blackrock&#8217;s Spot Exchange-Traded Funds (ETF). The approval of these ETF applications could further boost the current price action and potentially lead to new yearly highs.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/0pl2p1LP/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>Bitcoin is currently trading at $30,600, representing a modest increase of 1.4% over the past 24 hours.</p>





<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com</p>





]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/thomas-bonometti-5PdgQPopE3Q-unsplash-307x460.jpg" width="307" height="460" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Consolidates Below $31K As The Bulls Take Back Seat</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-consolidates-below-31k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 02:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540043</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is still struggling to clear the $31,000 resistance. BTC is trading in a range and might revisit the $30,000 support zone. Bitcoin is consolidating above the $30,000 support zone. The price is trading just below $30,500 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $30,300 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could correct lower toward the $30,000 support or even $29,550. Bitcoin Price Faces Resistance Bitcoin price remained supported near the $30,000 zone. BTC traded as low as $29,914 and recently started a fresh increase. There was a move above the $30,200 and $30,250 levels. The price cleared the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $31,436 swing high to the $29,914 low. Besides, there was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $30,300 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. However, the bears seem to be active near the $31,000 resistance zone. Bitcoin struggled to clear the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $31,436 swing high to the $29,914 low. The price is now trading just below $30,500 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. Immediate resistance is near the $30,680 level. The first major resistance is near the $30,950 level, above which the price might revisit the $31,400 resistance zone. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The next major resistance is near the $32,000 level. An upside break above the $32,000 resistance might send BTC toward $32,500. Any more gains could open the doors for a move toward the $33,200 resistance zone. More Losses in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $30,950 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $30,250 level or the broken trend line zone. The next major support is near the $30,000 level, below which there could be a drop toward the $29,550 support. Any more losses might send the price toward the $28,750 support region in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is below the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $30,000, followed by $29,550. Major Resistance Levels – $30,680, $30,950, and $31,400.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is still struggling to clear the $31,000 resistance. BTC is trading in a range and might revisit the $30,000 support zone.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is consolidating above the $30,000 support zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading just below $30,500 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $30,300 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could correct lower toward the $30,000 support or even $29,550.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Faces Resistance</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-aims-higher-30500/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">remained supported near the $30,000 zone</a>. BTC traded as low as $29,914 and recently started a fresh increase. There was a move above the $30,200 and $30,250 levels.</p>
<p>The price cleared the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $31,436 swing high to the $29,914 low. Besides, there was a break above a major bearish trend line with resistance near $30,300 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>However, the bears seem to be active near the $31,000 resistance zone. Bitcoin struggled to clear the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $31,436 swing high to the $29,914 low.</p>
<p>The price is now trading just below $30,500 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-correction-29200/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>. Immediate resistance is near the $30,680 level. The first major resistance is near the $30,950 level, above which the price might revisit the $31,400 resistance zone.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-540044" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-19.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-19.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-19-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-19-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-19-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-19-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-19-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-19-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $32,000 level. An upside break above the $32,000 resistance might send BTC toward $32,500. Any more gains could open the doors for a move toward the $33,200 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>More Losses in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $30,950 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $30,250 level or the broken trend line zone.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $30,000 level, below which there could be a drop toward the $29,550 support. Any more losses might send the price toward the $28,750 support region in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $30,000, followed by $29,550.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $30,680, $30,950, and $31,400.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/shutterstock_1439986673-460x325.jpg" width="460" height="325" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Global Interest In Bitcoin Is Fast-Falling, What’s Happening?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/global-interest-in-bitcoin-is-fast-falling-whats-happening/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 01:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin bulls]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin prices]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google trends]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540012</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[According to Google Trends data, interest in Bitcoin is heading to historic lows as of June 27. In a screenshot shared by a Twitter user, organic searches related to “Bitcoin” have dropped in the last six months.  Google Trends is a free tool that tracks how people search for specific terms or phrases on Google, the world’s largest search engine. Interest in a particular topic or asset can be ascertained in real time depending on the number of search terms. Currently, few users are searching for the term “Bitcoin.” Interest In Bitcoin Fast Falling Notably, BTC and crypto prices have steadily recovered after bears wiped gains last year. As an illustration, BTC is up roughly 87% when writing and trending at around 2023 highs. On the other hand, organic searches related to the world’s most valuable cryptocurrency are at multi-year lows, sharply falling in the first half of 2023. Related Reading: PEPE Coin Shines Among Top Gainers, Tallies 78% In Last Week Data from Google Trends show that interest in searches around Bitcoin is below 2018 levels and could drop lower, considering how fast the reading has been free-falling in the first half of the year. This “disinterest” in Bitcoin seemed to have been spilled over from the second half of 2022.  In the first half of last year, searches temporarily expanded before dropping. Even so, at that time, Bitcoin search readings, according to Google Trends, were lower than that registered in 2021 when it was at record highs. Based on this development, there appears to be a direct correlation between sentiment and prices, as deduced from Google Trends data on Bitcoin. BTC prices peaked at over $69,000 in November 2021 after steadily rising from late 2019. Notably, prices more than doubled as they rallied below $10,000, breaking December 2017 highs of around $20,000 and soaring to new all-time highs of about $70,000 registered in Q4 2021. When prices roared, searches related to Bitcoin, Google Trends data shows, also rose. The inverse was observed in the past 19 months when prices contracted from all-time highs, dropping by over 70% to as lows as sub-$16,000 in November 2022.  What Could Be The Cause? From the current BTC price action, there is a divergence between Google Trends data on Bitcoin and prices. While prices are rising, shaking off bears of Q4 2022 and the first half of Q1 2023, interest in Bitcoin is shrinking.  This observation can be pinned on several factors, including increasing regulatory scrutiny of Bitcoin and cryptocurrencies in the United States and worldwide. Related Reading: BTC Continues Uptrend As Fidelity Plans To Submit Bitcoin Spot ETF Filing Although the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has clarified that Bitcoin is a commodity, the regulator’s action against popular exchanges, including Coinbase and Binance, might have impacted sentiment, puncturing user interest. Feature Image From Canva, Chart From TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to Google Trends data, interest in Bitcoin is heading to historic lows as of June 27. In a screenshot <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/decodejar/status/1673446498913353729" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shared</a> by a Twitter user, organic searches related to “Bitcoin” have dropped in the last six months. </p>
<p>Google Trends is a free tool that tracks how people search for specific terms or phrases on Google, the world’s largest search engine. Interest in a particular topic or asset can be ascertained in real time depending on the number of search terms. Currently, few users are searching for the term “Bitcoin.”</p>
<h2>Interest In Bitcoin Fast Falling</h2>
<p>Notably, BTC and crypto prices have steadily recovered after bears wiped gains last year. As an illustration, BTC is up roughly 87% when writing and trending at around 2023 highs. On the other hand, organic searches related to the world’s most valuable cryptocurrency are at multi-year lows, sharply falling in the first half of 2023.</p>

<p>Data from Google Trends show that interest in searches around Bitcoin is below 2018 levels and could drop lower, considering how fast the reading has been free-falling in the first half of the year. This “disinterest” in Bitcoin seemed to have been spilled over from the second half of 2022. </p>
<p>In the first half of last year, searches temporarily expanded before dropping. Even so, at that time, Bitcoin search readings, according to Google Trends, were lower than that registered in 2021 when it was at record highs.</p>
<p>Based on this development, there appears to be a direct correlation between sentiment and prices, as deduced from Google Trends data on Bitcoin. BTC prices peaked at over $69,000 in November 2021 after steadily rising from late 2019. </p>
<p>Notably, prices more than doubled as they rallied below $10,000, breaking December 2017 highs of around $20,000 and soaring to new all-time highs of about $70,000 registered in Q4 2021. When prices roared, searches related to Bitcoin, Google Trends data shows, also rose. The inverse was observed in the past 19 months when prices contracted from all-time highs, dropping by over 70% to as lows as sub-$16,000 in November 2022. </p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/OVLziKgd/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/OVLziKgd/" alt="Bitcoin price on June 27| Source: BTCUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>
<h2>What Could Be The Cause?</h2>
<p>From the current BTC price action, there is a divergence between Google Trends data on Bitcoin and prices. While prices are rising, shaking off bears of Q4 2022 and the first half of Q1 2023, interest in Bitcoin is shrinking. </p>
<p>This observation can be pinned on several factors, including increasing regulatory scrutiny of Bitcoin and cryptocurrencies in the United States and worldwide. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/btc-uptrend-fidelity-to-submit-bitcoin-spot-etf-filing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">BTC Continues Uptrend As Fidelity Plans To Submit Bitcoin Spot ETF Filing</a></p>
<p>Although the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has clarified that Bitcoin is a commodity, the regulator’s action against popular exchanges, including Coinbase and Binance, might have impacted sentiment, puncturing user interest.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-Google-Trends-Data-Falling-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nigeria Leads The Pack: ConsenSys Study Shows Crypto Recognition At 92% Globally</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/nigeria-leads-the-pack-consensys-study-shows-crypto-recognition-at-92-globally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto survey]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nigeria]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540000</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There is no disputing that cryptocurrencies are now widely accepted. Cryptocurrencies are now firmly part of the global conversation; whether it be investors trading crypto, businesses accepting it as a mode of payment, or just reports about the latest surge or crash in the crypto market. And now, according to a new ConsenSys survey, an impressive 92% of people around the world are aware of cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin. Developing Regions Show Strong Crypto Recognition According to a recent poll conducted by the private blockchain software company ConsenSys and YouGov, 92% of people worldwide are aware of cryptocurrencies. Over 15,158 people in 15 nations, with an average age of 18, were surveyed for the report. However, while awareness of crypto is high, understanding is low. A total of 92% of respondents to the survey had heard of crypto, but only 8% could confidently say they were familiar with the general concept of Web3. Related Reading: BLUR Up By 11% Following This Announcement Interestingly, developing regions of the world actually show some of the strongest recognition and interest in cryptocurrencies. Nigeria, South Africa, and Brazil lead in the pack in crypto awareness, with 99% of Nigerian respondents demonstrating awareness of crypto and over 70% accurately guessing the definition of a blockchain. While developed nations debate regulating crypto, developing regions seem more open to innovation. Cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum have helped to address the inherent risks of unstable currencies leading to high inflation rates and the lack of financial infrastructure for money movement that many people face in developing nations. This stands in stark contrast to the larger level of mistrust toward cryptocurrency displayed by European nations and Asian nations like Japan and South Korea. In Japan and Indonesia, only 1 in 3 respondents claim to understand what cryptocurrency is. Total market cap recovers as Bitcoin rebounds &#124; Source: Crypto Total Market Cap on TradingView.com Only 8% Of Respondents Very Familiar With The Concept Of Web3 In a country like Argentina, whose currency has been through a significant devaluation and instability in recent years, 56% of respondents indicated a higher likelihood of owning cryptocurrency as a store of value.  While crypto and blockchain have gained mainstream awareness, most people still have a lot to learn about web3, the decentralized internet of the future. 36% and 34% of respondents were familiar with the Metaverse and NFTs, but only 24% are aware of Web3, with only 8% saying they are “very familiar” with the concept. Related Reading: PEPE Coin Shines Among Top Gainers, Tallies 78% In Last Week As web3 projects emerge and gain traction, crypto literacy rates should rise. ConsenSys predicts broader understanding will come through a more practical understanding and utilization of web3 technologies. Featured image from Freebitcoin, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There is no disputing that cryptocurrencies are now widely accepted. Cryptocurrencies are now firmly part of the global conversation; whether it be investors trading crypto, businesses accepting it as a mode of payment, or just reports about the latest surge or crash in the crypto market. And now, according to a new ConsenSys survey, an impressive 92% of people around the world are aware of cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin.</p>
<h2>Developing Regions Show Strong Crypto Recognition</h2>
<p>According to a recent <a href="https://consensys.io/insight-report/web3-and-crypto-global-survey-2023" rel="nofollow">poll</a> conducted by the private blockchain software company ConsenSys and YouGov, 92% of people worldwide are aware of cryptocurrencies. Over 15,158 people in 15 nations, with an average age of 18, were surveyed for the report.</p>
<p>However, while awareness of crypto is high, understanding is low. A total of 92% of respondents to the survey had heard of crypto, but only 8% could confidently say they were familiar with the general concept of Web3.</p>

<p>Interestingly, developing regions of the world actually show some of the strongest recognition and interest in cryptocurrencies. Nigeria, South Africa, and Brazil lead in the pack in crypto awareness, with 99% of Nigerian respondents demonstrating awareness of crypto and over 70% accurately guessing the definition of a blockchain.</p>
<p>While developed nations debate regulating crypto, developing regions seem more open to innovation. Cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum have helped to address the inherent risks of unstable currencies leading to high inflation rates and the lack of financial infrastructure for money movement that many people face in developing nations.</p>
<p>This stands in stark contrast to the larger level of mistrust toward cryptocurrency displayed by European nations and Asian nations like Japan and South Korea. In Japan and Indonesia, only 1 in 3 respondents claim to understand what cryptocurrency is.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/RYqNZ2pM/" alt="Total crypto market cap chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1724"/></p>

<h2>Only 8% Of Respondents Very Familiar With The Concept Of Web3</h2>
<p>In a country like Argentina, whose currency has been through a significant devaluation and instability in recent years, 56% of respondents indicated a higher likelihood of owning cryptocurrency as a store of value. </p>
<p>While crypto and blockchain have gained mainstream awareness, most people still have a lot to learn about web3, the decentralized internet of the future. 36% and 34% of respondents were familiar with the Metaverse and NFTs, but only 24% are aware of Web3, with only 8% saying they are “very familiar” with the concept.</p>

<p>As web3 projects emerge and gain traction, crypto literacy rates should rise. ConsenSys predicts broader understanding will come through a more practical understanding and utilization of web3 technologies.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Crypto-Nigeria-460x258.png" width="460" height="258" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Starts To Bite Back Says Reptilian Technical Signal</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-starts-to-bite-back-says-reptilian-technical-signal/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony "The Bull"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:19:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540033</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A reptilian technical signal is back in Bitcoin, and it has started to feast upon a new uptrend, according to how the tool works. Take a closer look below at the one-week BTCUSD Williams Alligator, and learn more about what it says about the king of the cryptocurrency market. Bye Crypto Bear Market. See You Later, Says Alligator Bitcoin price is back above $30,000 and the recent push higher has possibly changed the trend. That is according to the one-week Williams Alligator, which has started “eating with its mouth open.” Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Breaks Above $30,000: Is The Bull Run Back On? The Williams Alligator consists of three smoothed moving averages, set at 5, 8, and 13-periods. These averages represent what creator Bill Williams has labeled the Lips, Teeth, and Jaw of the gator, respectively. When the three moving averages are moving upward, and the Lips are above the Teeth and Jaw, it suggests that an asset is trending. As such, the chart below suggests that Bitcoin is once again trending up. The Alligator is hungry for BTC &#124; BTCUSD/NDX on TradingView.com Bitcoin Could Be Trending For A While Crocodile As the image depicts, after Bitcoin begins trending according to the technical tool and timeframe, it continues until a climax. At that point the Alligator is sated and begins “sleeping”. Given the recent macro environment, regulatory pressure, and more, investors might still be sleeping on the crypto market. But if you read the Williams Alligator correctly, it suggests that the gator has awakened, and an uptrend is here. Related Reading: Momentum: Why The Bitcoin Train Is Ready To Leave The Station Upon examining the last three major uptrends, the current most closely resembles the 2020 rally. In 2019 the Aligator ate for 50 days before a peak. In 2021, it lasted 75 days. But the big one in 2020 lasted a full 350 days before a reversal. Thus far, the Alligator started eating 125 days ago, surpassing 2019 and 2021 combined. Yet it’s not even halfway done with its meal if the rally is as strong as 2020. How long will the Williams Alligator stay hungry for BTC? The 1W Williams Alligator 🐊 is hungry for more expensive #Bitcoin It has started eating with an open mouth, thus following the trend It is done dining when the 5, 8, and 13 (Fib numbers) period smoothed MAs cross and turn down Eat, or be eaten pic.twitter.com/V12PykySYr — Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221; (@tonythebullBTC) June 27, 2023 Tony is the author of the CoinChartist (VIP) newsletter. Follow @TonyTheBullBTC &#38; @coinchartist_io on Twitter. Or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A reptilian technical signal is back in Bitcoin, and it has started to feast upon a new uptrend, according to how the tool works.</p>
<p>Take a closer look below at the one-week BTCUSD Williams Alligator, and learn more about what it says about the king of the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<h2>Bye Crypto Bear Market. See You Later, Says Alligator</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price is back above $30,000 and the recent push higher has possibly changed the trend. That is according to the one-week Williams Alligator, which has started “eating with its mouth open.”</p>

<p>The Williams Alligator consists of three smoothed moving averages, set at 5, 8, and 13-periods. These averages represent what creator Bill Williams has labeled the Lips, Teeth, and Jaw of the gator, respectively.</p>
<p>When the three moving averages are moving upward, and the Lips are above the Teeth and Jaw, it suggests that an asset is trending. As such, the chart below suggests that Bitcoin is once again trending up.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-large wp-image-540035" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/F3B1C939-D756-43A7-86FD-E38704E7901C-860x535.png" alt="Bitcoin alligator " width="860" height="535" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/F3B1C939-D756-43A7-86FD-E38704E7901C-860x535.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/F3B1C939-D756-43A7-86FD-E38704E7901C-460x286.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/F3B1C939-D756-43A7-86FD-E38704E7901C-768x478.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/F3B1C939-D756-43A7-86FD-E38704E7901C-1536x955.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/F3B1C939-D756-43A7-86FD-E38704E7901C-2048x1274.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/F3B1C939-D756-43A7-86FD-E38704E7901C-750x466.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/F3B1C939-D756-43A7-86FD-E38704E7901C-1140x709.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<h2>Bitcoin Could Be Trending For A While Crocodile</h2>
<p>As the image depicts, after Bitcoin begins trending according to the technical tool and timeframe, it continues until a climax. At that point the Alligator is sated and begins “sleeping”.</p>
<p>Given the recent macro environment, regulatory pressure, and more, investors might still be sleeping on the crypto market. But if you read the Williams Alligator correctly, it suggests that the gator has awakened, and an uptrend is here.</p>

<p>Upon examining the last three major uptrends, the current most closely resembles the 2020 rally. In 2019 the Aligator ate for 50 days before a peak. In 2021, it lasted 75 days. But the big one in 2020 lasted a full 350 days before a reversal.</p>
<p>Thus far, the Alligator started eating 125 days ago, surpassing 2019 and 2021 combined. Yet it’s not even halfway done with its meal if the rally is as strong as 2020. How long will the Williams Alligator stay hungry for BTC?</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">The 1W Williams Alligator <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f40a.png" alt="🐊" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> is hungry for more expensive <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Bitcoin</a></p>
<p>It has started eating with an open mouth, thus following the trend</p>
<p>It is done dining when the 5, 8, and 13 (Fib numbers) period smoothed MAs cross and turn down</p>
<p>Eat, or be eaten <a href="https://t.co/V12PykySYr" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/V12PykySYr</a></p>
<p>— Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221; (@tonythebullBTC) <a href="https://twitter.com/tonythebullBTC/status/1673825267985309699?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/8BBD89E6-49BC-4B7B-83D4-CEF71B2D71F7-460x307.jpeg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nevada FID Files Petition To Take Control Of Troubled Prime Trust</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/nevada-fid-files-petition-to-take-control-of-troubled-prime-trust/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 23:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AUDIO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AUDIOUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prime Trust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=540001</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Nevada Department of Business and Industry&#8217;s Financial Institutions Division (FID) has taken action against Prime Trust, LLC. This US-based financial institution specializes in custody and settlement services for digital assets.  The FID has alleged that Prime Trust has violated Nevada regulations and has a shortfall in customer funds, which has deteriorated to a critically deficient level. As a result, the FID has filed a petition to place Prime Trust into receivership. This means that a court-appointed receiver will take control of the company&#8217;s assets and operations to protect the interests of creditors and other stakeholders. Prime Trust Accused Of Using Customer Assets To Buy Back Crypto The allegations against Prime Trust are significant, with the FID claiming that the firm lost access to legacy wallets in 2021 and used customer assets to buy back crypto.  Prime Trust reportedly owes its customers $85,670,000 in fiat currency but only has $2,904,000, while it owes $69,509,000 in digital currency but only has $68,648,000. The receivership of Prime Trust could potentially have significant implications for the firm&#8217;s customers. If the court grants the petition filed by the Nevada FID, a receiver will be appointed to take control of the firm&#8217;s assets and operations. Related Reading: PEPE Coin Shines Among Top Gainers, Tallies 78% In Last Week During the receivership, the receiver will manage and administer Prime Trust&#8217;s assets and liabilities. This could include selling off assets to pay off creditors, negotiating with customers to resolve outstanding issues, and taking other actions to wind down the firm&#8217;s operations. For customers of Prime Trust, the receivership could lead to delays and disruptions in accessing their accounts and assets held by the firm. The receiver may need to freeze or restrict customer accounts while they assess the firm&#8217;s financial position and develop a plan for winding down its operations. Customers who have assets held by Prime Trust may also face the risk of loss if the firm&#8217;s assets are insufficient to cover its liabilities. While the receiver will work to maximize the recovery of funds for creditors, the outcome of the receivership is uncertain, and customers may not receive the full value of their assets. The petition to place Prime Trust into receivership will be subject to a hearing, where the court will determine whether the firm should be placed into receivership and whether a receiver should be appointed.  The Majority Of Prime Trust&#8217;s Digital Currency Holdings Tied To AUDIO The news of Prime Trust&#8217;s receivership filing has sent shockwaves through the digital asset community, particularly for investors in AUDIO. According to Connor, Director at Coinbase, 88% of the digital currency held by Prime Trust is AUDIO, the native token of the Audius music streaming platform. This news could trouble AUDIO investors, as the receivership process could result in significant losses for those holding the token.  While the receiver will work to maximize the recovery of funds for creditors and stakeholders, the outcome is uncertain, and investors may not receive the full value of their AUDIO holdings. Related Reading: BLUR Up By 11% Following This Announcement The situation is especially concerning, given the recent volatility in the digital asset markets. AUDIO has experienced significant price swings over the past months, and investors may be hesitant to hold a token that is so heavily concentrated in the hands of a single custodian. At the time of writing, the value of AUDIO stands at $0.1853. This represents a 1.7% decrease in value over the last 24 hours. The token&#8217;s price has remained relatively stable following the news of Prime Trust&#8217;s receivership filing. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Nevada Department of Business and Industry&#8217;s Financial Institutions Division (FID) has taken <a href="https://fid.nv.gov/uploadedFiles/fidnvgov/content/Opinion/Prime%20Trust%20-%20C%20and%20D%206.21.23.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">action against</a> Prime Trust, LLC. This US-based financial institution specializes in custody and settlement services for digital assets. </p>
<p>The FID has alleged that Prime Trust has violated Nevada regulations and has a shortfall in customer funds, which has deteriorated to a critically deficient level.</p>
<p>As a result, the FID has filed a petition to place Prime Trust into receivership. This means that a court-appointed receiver will take control of the company&#8217;s assets and operations to protect the interests of creditors and other stakeholders.</p>
<h2>Prime Trust Accused Of Using Customer Assets To Buy Back Crypto</h2>
<p>The allegations against Prime Trust are significant, with the FID claiming that the firm lost access to legacy wallets in 2021 and used customer assets to buy back crypto. </p>
<p>Prime Trust <a href="https://twitter.com/tier10k/status/1673744184572887049?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reportedly </a>owes its customers $85,670,000 in fiat currency but only has $2,904,000, while it owes $69,509,000 in digital currency but only has $68,648,000.</p>
<p>The receivership of Prime Trust could potentially have significant implications for the firm&#8217;s customers. If the court grants the petition filed by the Nevada FID, a receiver will be appointed to take control of the firm&#8217;s assets and operations.</p>

<p>During the receivership, the receiver will manage and administer Prime Trust&#8217;s assets and liabilities. This could include selling off assets to pay off creditors, negotiating with customers to resolve outstanding issues, and taking other actions to wind down the firm&#8217;s operations.</p>
<p>For customers of Prime Trust, the receivership could lead to delays and disruptions in accessing their accounts and assets held by the firm. The receiver may need to freeze or restrict customer accounts while they assess the firm&#8217;s financial position and develop a plan for winding down its operations.</p>
<p>Customers who have assets held by Prime Trust may also face the risk of loss if the firm&#8217;s assets are insufficient to cover its liabilities. While the receiver will work to maximize the recovery of funds for creditors, the outcome of the receivership is uncertain, and customers may not receive the full value of their assets.</p>
<p>The petition to place Prime Trust into receivership will be subject to a hearing, where the court will determine whether the firm should be placed into receivership and whether a receiver should be appointed. </p>
The Majority Of Prime Trust&#8217;s Digital Currency Holdings Tied To AUDIO
<p>The news of Prime Trust&#8217;s receivership filing has sent shockwaves through the digital asset community, particularly for investors in AUDIO. <a href="https://twitter.com/jconorgrogan/status/1673745065057959960?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to Connor, Director at Coinbase, 88% of the digital currency held by Prime Trust is AUDIO, the native token of the Audius music streaming platform.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-540002" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_3-860x493.jpg" alt="Prime Trust" width="860" height="493" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_3-860x493.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_3-460x264.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_3-768x440.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_3-750x430.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot_3.jpg 944w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>This news could trouble AUDIO investors, as the receivership process could result in significant losses for those holding the token. </p>
<p>While the receiver will work to maximize the recovery of funds for creditors and stakeholders, the outcome is uncertain, and investors may not receive the full value of their AUDIO holdings.</p>

<p>The situation is especially concerning, given the recent volatility in the digital asset markets. AUDIO has experienced significant price swings over the past months, and investors may be hesitant to hold a token that is so heavily concentrated in the hands of a single custodian.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/KNHLHI0L/" alt="Prime Trust " width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>At the time of writing, the value of AUDIO stands at $0.1853. This represents a 1.7% decrease in value over the last 24 hours. The token&#8217;s price has remained relatively stable following the news of Prime Trust&#8217;s receivership filing.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cristina-gottardi-maaWpQVgi00-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Is Outperforming Previous Bear Cycle, Reveals ITC Crypto CEO</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/ada/cardano-ada-is-outperforming-previous-bear-cycle-reveals-itc-crypto-ceo/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bear]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=539964</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the continually evolving world of cryptocurrencies, market resilience often proves a key determiner of long-term value and growth. Benjamin Cowen, CEO and founder of ITC Crypto, recently underscored this premise and spotlighted Cardano (ADA) for its performance amid the prevailing crypto bear market. Related Reading: Cardano Poised For Consolidation In This Price Zone Prior To Attempting Reversal In a series of Twitter posts, Cowen shared insights comparing ADA&#8217;s current performance with its past trajectory, with implications for ADA&#8217;s investors and potential adopters. A Historical Perspective: ADA&#8217;s Bear Market Performance Cowen&#8217;s analysis brought to the fore an observation. According to Cowen, Cardano&#8217;s resilience in the current bear market outpaces its performance during the 2018-2020 bearish phase. He used a snapshot of ADA&#8217;s Return on Investment (ROI) to illustrate this, wherein two distinct trends emerged. Comparing #ADA bear markets Blue Line (Jan 2018 &#8211; Mar 2020) Orange Line ( Sep 2021-Present) So far, we are seeing diminishing losses as a function of time. The orange line will reach the length of the blue line on Nov. 13th, 2023. pic.twitter.com/XXKKSjiEmF — Benjamin Cowen (@intocryptoverse) June 26, 2023 The graphic showcased a blue line depicting the bear market spanning January 2018 to March 2020, while the orange line represented the ongoing bear market that commenced in September 2021. Notably, the orange line displayed a trend of diminishing losses over time. Navigating The Bear Market: Cardano&#8217;s Improved Resilience Cowen&#8217;s observations suggest a slower rate of decline for ADA price in this bear market compared to its previous cycle. Projections place at the end of the current cycle around November 13, 2023, when the orange line is anticipated to reach the same length as the blue line. These insights could signal a less severe impact on ADA&#8217;s price amid the existing bear market compared to the previous cycle. Although ADA has experienced a decrease in price over the last 24 hours, the broader analysis paints a picture of enhanced market resilience. Although the asset declined in the past day, it is worth noting that ADA has been bullish over the past week, up by nearly 10%. The asset currently trades at $0.28 with a trading volume above $185 million and a market cap of $9.8 billion. Over the past 7 days, more than $500 million has been added to ADA&#8217;s market cap following the asset market capitalization surge from $9.1 billion seen last Tuesday. ADA has also recorded a surge in its trading volume, indicating rising trading activity. Related Reading: Cardano (ADA) Soars 10% In The Last Week, More Rallies Ahead? Cardano&#8217;s ability to navigate bear markets with diminishing losses is a testament to its resilience and inherent value proposition. While the immediate trend reflects a downturn, the longer-term performance of ADA signals a pattern of robustness.  Featured image from Shutterstock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the continually evolving world of cryptocurrencies, market resilience often proves a key determiner of long-term value and growth. Benjamin Cowen, CEO and founder of ITC Crypto, recently underscored this premise and spotlighted Cardano (ADA) for its performance amid the prevailing crypto bear market.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-poised-for-consolidation-in-this-price-zone-prior-to-attempting-reversal/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Cardano Poised For Consolidation In This Price Zone Prior To Attempting Reversal</a></p>
<p>In a series of Twitter posts, Cowen <a href="https://twitter.com/intocryptoverse/status/1673368433491058689?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shared</a> insights comparing ADA&#8217;s current performance with its past trajectory, with implications for ADA&#8217;s investors and potential adopters.</p>
<h2>A Historical Perspective: ADA&#8217;s Bear Market Performance</h2>
<p>Cowen&#8217;s analysis brought to the fore an observation. According to Cowen, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-poised-for-consolidation-in-this-price-zone-prior-to-attempting-reversal/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Cardano&#8217;s resilience</a> in the current bear market outpaces its performance during the 2018-2020 bearish phase. He used a snapshot of ADA&#8217;s Return on Investment (ROI) to illustrate this, wherein two distinct trends emerged.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Comparing <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ADA?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#ADA</a> bear markets</p>
<p>Blue Line (Jan 2018 &#8211; Mar 2020)
Orange Line ( Sep 2021-Present)</p>
<p>So far, we are seeing diminishing losses as a function of time.</p>
<p>The orange line will reach the length of the blue line on Nov. 13th, 2023. <a href="https://t.co/XXKKSjiEmF" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/XXKKSjiEmF</a></p>
<p>— Benjamin Cowen (@intocryptoverse) <a href="https://twitter.com/intocryptoverse/status/1673368433491058689?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">June 26, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>The graphic showcased a blue line depicting the bear market spanning January 2018 to March 2020, while the orange line represented the ongoing bear market that commenced in September 2021. Notably, the orange line displayed a trend of diminishing losses over time.</p>
<h2>Navigating The Bear Market: Cardano&#8217;s Improved Resilience</h2>
<p>Cowen&#8217;s observations suggest a slower rate of decline for <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/ada/ada-price-cardano-liftoff-0-35/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">ADA price</a> in this bear market compared to its previous cycle. Projections place at the end of the current cycle around November 13, 2023, when the orange line is anticipated to reach the same length as the blue line.</p>
<p>These insights could signal a less severe impact on ADA&#8217;s price amid the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-price-surges-amidst-a-thriving-bull-run-how-long-will-this-last/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">existing bear market</a> compared to the previous cycle. Although ADA has experienced a decrease in price over the last 24 hours, the broader analysis paints a picture of enhanced market resilience.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/rwazab9k/" alt="Cardano (ADA)&#039;s price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<p>Although the asset declined in the past day, it is worth noting that ADA has <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-ada-soars-10-in-the-last-week-more-rallies-ahead/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">been bullish</a> over the past week, up by nearly 10%. The asset currently trades at $0.28 with a trading volume above $185 million and a market cap of $9.8 billion.</p>
<p>Over the past 7 days, more than $500 million has been added to ADA&#8217;s market cap following the asset market capitalization surge from $9.1 billion seen last Tuesday. ADA has also recorded a surge in its trading volume, indicating rising trading activity.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-ada-soars-10-in-the-last-week-more-rallies-ahead/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Cardano (ADA) Soars 10% In The Last Week, More Rallies Ahead?</a></p>
<p>Cardano&#8217;s ability to navigate bear markets with diminishing losses is a testament to its resilience and inherent value proposition. While the immediate trend reflects a downturn, the longer-term performance of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano-ada-price-sheds-19/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">ADA signals</a> a pattern of robustness. </p>
<p>Featured image from Shutterstock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Cardano-ADA-Poised-For-Bullish-Breakout-460x329.jpeg" width="460" height="329" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
