<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 06:05:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Traders’ Interest In XRP Remains Solid Despite Price Retreat, Data Shows</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/interest-in-xrp-remains-solid/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 06:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC VS Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544943</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The enduring allure of XRP, despite market volatility, may be evidence of its continued relevance, as it has continued to attract the interest of traders and investors equally. Even as the dust settles after Ripple&#8217;s recent victory jubilation, the cryptocurrency market remains keen on XRP. Kaiko, a provider of market data on digital assets, reports that the open interest ratio on XRP futures trades on prominent exchanges remains quite impressive. Recently, the crypto market has experienced a pervasive price reversal. Despite the pullbacks, traders&#8217; interest in the Ripple cryptocurrency remained remarkably high, according to Kaiko. At the time of writing, XRP was in the red in all timeframes, trading at $$0.712, down a measly 0.02% in the last 24 hours, and a considerable 8.4% in the last seven days, data from crypto market tracker Coingecko shows. Given these numbers, XRP is still able to shine in another key department. XRP in crimson in all timeframes during the weekend. Source: Coingecko XRP Community Remains Upbeat About The Crypto Kaiko shows that across numerous markets, XRP&#8217;s volume-to-open interest ratio is consistently higher than the median value. This reliability suggests that the XRP coin is actively traded in a healthy market. This percentage is significantly greater than the market average, indicating strong liquidity and sustained interest from traders and investors. On prominent exchanges, the volume-to-open-interest ratio is also used to measure trading activity. When the interest metric is high, it indicates that more purchasers and sellers are willing to trade the token, which indicates speculative interest. A favorable volume-to-open interest ratio could be a signal for market participants to trade in such a token. Related Reading: Dogecoin Ascendance: How It Captured PEPE Investors’ Attention Ripple&#8217;s popularity on social media, as assessed by Santiment, has increased dramatically over the previous two months, reflecting the excitement surrounding the cryptocurrency. Its social dominance increased dramatically in late May and early June, peaking at over 4%. Source: Santiment Ripple had just roughly 2% of the social market share at the time this story was published. Despite the fact that this number may appear tiny, it demonstrates that the cryptocurrency has a significant presence and impact in the crypto community as a whole. Despite the fact that Ripple appears to be a minor topic of discussion, it has managed to stand out as a formidable contender, attracting the attention of enthusiasts and experts alike and causing them to discuss it. XRP market cap currently at $37 billion. Chart: TradingView.com In the ever-evolving world of cryptocurrencies, where numerous digital assets vie for attention and recognition, Ripple carved out a useful niche for itself, influencing discussions about blockchain technology and financial innovation. Strong Social Footprint Even though Ripple must contend with other well-known cryptocurrencies, the fact that it has maintained a strong social presence indicates that it has a large number of supporters and investors. Related Reading: Is Arbitrum Promise Fading? Downtime, Metrics Decline Raise ARB Price Alarms Meanwhile, the loss of nearly 10% of XRP&#8217;s value over the past week appeared insignificant to some speculators. Based on figures from Santiment, the funding rate for cryptocurrencies was 0.1%. A positive reading of the funding rate indicated favorable sentiment on average. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from Times Tabloid]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The enduring allure of XRP, despite market volatility, may be evidence of its continued relevance, as it has continued to attract the interest of traders and investors equally.</p>
<p>Even as the dust settles after Ripple&#8217;s recent victory jubilation, the cryptocurrency market remains keen on XRP. Kaiko, a provider of market data on digital assets, reports that the open interest ratio on XRP futures trades on prominent exchanges remains quite impressive.</p>
<p>Recently, the crypto market has experienced a pervasive price reversal. Despite the pullbacks, traders&#8217; interest in the Ripple cryptocurrency remained remarkably high, according to Kaiko.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, XRP was in the red in all timeframes, <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">trading at $$0.712</a>, down a measly 0.02% in the last 24 hours, and a considerable 8.4% in the last seven days, data from crypto market tracker Coingecko shows. Given these numbers, XRP is still able to shine in another key department.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-544946" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-3.png" alt="" width="989" height="65" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-3.png 989w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-3-460x30.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-3-860x57.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-3-768x50.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-3-750x49.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 989px) 100vw, 989px"/></p>

<h2><strong>XRP Community Remains Upbeat About The Crypto</strong></h2>
<p>Kaiko shows that across numerous markets, XRP&#8217;s <a href="https://twitter.com/KaikoData/status/1684529048754573313/photo/1" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">volume-to-open interest ratio</a> is consistently higher than the median value. This reliability suggests that the XRP coin is actively traded in a healthy market. This percentage is significantly greater than the market average, indicating strong liquidity and sustained interest from traders and investors.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-544948 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-178-860x449.png" alt="" width="860" height="449" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-178-860x449.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-178-460x240.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-178-768x401.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-178-1536x802.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-178-750x392.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-178-1140x596.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-178.png 1587w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>On prominent exchanges, the volume-to-open-interest ratio is also used to measure trading activity. When the interest metric is high, it indicates that more purchasers and sellers are willing to trade the token, which indicates speculative interest. A favorable volume-to-open interest ratio could be a signal for market participants to trade in such a token.</p>

<p>Ripple&#8217;s <a href="https://statics.ambcrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-XRP-10.38.38-26-Jul-2023.png" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">popularity on social media,</a> as assessed by Santiment, has increased dramatically over the previous two months, reflecting the excitement surrounding the cryptocurrency. Its social dominance increased dramatically in late May and early June, peaking at over 4%.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-544950 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-179-860x294.png" alt="" width="860" height="294" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-179-860x294.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-179-460x157.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-179-768x262.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-179-1536x525.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-179-750x256.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-179-1140x390.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-179.png 1542w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>Ripple had just roughly 2% of the social market share at the time this story was published. Despite the fact that this number may appear tiny, it demonstrates that the cryptocurrency has a significant presence and impact in the crypto community as a whole.</p>
<p>Despite the fact that Ripple appears to be a minor topic of discussion, it has managed to stand out as a formidable contender, attracting the attention of enthusiasts and experts alike and causing them to discuss it.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/QPFRGlWM/" width="2475" height="1187"/></p>

<p>In the ever-evolving world of cryptocurrencies, where numerous digital assets vie for attention and recognition, Ripple carved out a useful niche for itself, influencing discussions about blockchain technology and financial innovation.</p>
<h2><strong>Strong Social Footprint</strong></h2>
<p>Even though Ripple must contend with other well-known cryptocurrencies, the fact that it has maintained a strong social presence indicates that it has a large number of supporters and investors.</p>

<p>Meanwhile, the loss of nearly 10% of XRP&#8217;s value over the past week appeared insignificant to some speculators. Based on figures from Santiment, the funding rate for cryptocurrencies was 0.1%. A positive reading of the funding rate indicated favorable sentiment on average.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Times Tabloid</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-182-460x303.png" width="460" height="303" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Casper (CSPR) Spikes 15% Following Key Partnership &#8211; What&#8217;s Next?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/casper-cspr-spikes-15-following-key-partnership-whats-next/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olowoporoku Adeniyi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 03:26:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Casper]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Casper Network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CSPR Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544936</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Casper (CSPR) has been making significant strides in the cryptocurrency market, attracting attention with its aim to accelerate enterprise and developer adoption of blockchain technology. As a live proof-of-stake blockchain built off the Casper CBC specification, Casper offers unique features and growth potential, drawing interest from investors and enthusiasts alike. In the past week, there has been a significant upturn in its on-chain volume. Casper has experienced a substantial price surge in the past 24 hours, with its value increasing by 4.62%. This surge has created excitement among investors, especially as the cryptocurrency has displayed steady growth over the past 7 days, gaining an impressive 14.58%. The positive price movement has generated enthusiasm and optimism among Casper investors, who are pleased with their returns during this period. As of the latest data, Casper (CSPR) is ranked 84th among all cryptocurrencies, with a current price of $0.04035. The circulating supply of Casper stands at 11,202,499,993, contributing to a total market capitalization of $456,309,769. The cryptocurrency&#8217;s recent performance has been particularly noteworthy, showcasing impressive short- and long-term growth. Collaboration With INX Boosts Market Sentiment A contributing factor to Casper&#8217;s recent growth can be attributed to its strategic partnership with INX, a United States-regulated broker-dealer. Casper&#8217;s equity was tokenized and listed through this collaboration, enhancing investor confidence and further supporting the cryptocurrency&#8217;s upward trajectory. This strategic move has enabled Casper to tap into new markets and expand its reach to a broader audience. Related Reading: Cardano (ADA) Price Remains Muted Despite Significant Milestones, Why? Casper&#8217;s price surge aligns with the optimistic market sentiment toward cryptocurrencies. The growing interest from institutional investors and the increasing mainstream adoption of digital assets has instilled confidence in crypto. Additionally, influential figures within the blockchain industry have shared positive views on cryptocurrencies, including Casper, contributing to the overall positive outlook. Casper (CSPR) Price Analysis Casper has experienced a consistent upward trend in July after it bottomed at $0.0365. Since then, its price has increased by 30% and has hit heights of $0.0405. This positive trend is likely to continue in the coming weeks with more developments expected to be deployed on Casper. From a technical analysis standpoint, Casper exhibits promising signals. The daily chart reveals the formation of a bullish falling wedge pattern, indicating a potential trend reversal. CSPR has also surpassed the 25-day exponential moving average and is currently testing the 50-day MA. If the bullish trend continues the next resistance point is $0.40 while a bearish downturn will see the support at $0.0397. Related Reading: Why Worldcoin (WLD) And PEPE Dominate The Crypto Market Trends This Week As Casper continues to gain visibility and traction in the market, its future growth potential remains promising. The cryptocurrency&#8217;s underlying technology, including its proof-of-stake consensus mechanism, offers scalability, security, and energy efficiency. These features position Casper as an attractive enterprise adoption and long-term development candidate.  (This site’s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Casper (CSPR) has been making significant strides in the cryptocurrency market, attracting attention with its aim to accelerate enterprise and developer adoption of blockchain technology. As a live <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/terms/p/proof-stake-pos.asp" rel="nofollow">proof-of-stake</a> blockchain built off the Casper CBC specification, Casper offers unique features and growth potential, drawing interest from investors and enthusiasts alike. </p>
<p>In the past week, there has been a significant upturn in its on-chain volume. Casper has experienced a substantial price surge in the past 24 hours, with its value increasing by 4.62%. This surge has created excitement among investors, especially as the cryptocurrency has displayed steady growth over the past 7 days, gaining an impressive 14.58%. The positive price movement has generated enthusiasm and optimism among Casper investors, who are pleased with their returns during this period.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-544937 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CSPRUSDT_2023-07-29_02-30-27-860x406.png" alt="Casper (CSPR) price has spiked in the past few days: Source @Tradingview" width="860" height="406" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CSPRUSDT_2023-07-29_02-30-27-860x406.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CSPRUSDT_2023-07-29_02-30-27-460x217.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CSPRUSDT_2023-07-29_02-30-27-768x363.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CSPRUSDT_2023-07-29_02-30-27-1536x726.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CSPRUSDT_2023-07-29_02-30-27-750x354.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CSPRUSDT_2023-07-29_02-30-27-1140x539.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CSPRUSDT_2023-07-29_02-30-27.png 1835w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<p>As of the latest data, Casper (CSPR) is ranked 84th among all cryptocurrencies, with a current price of $0.04035. The circulating supply of Casper stands at 11,202,499,993, contributing to a total market capitalization of $456,309,769. The cryptocurrency&#8217;s recent performance has been particularly noteworthy, showcasing impressive short- and long-term growth.</p>
<h2><strong>Collaboration With INX Boosts Market Sentiment</strong></h2>
<p>A contributing factor to Casper&#8217;s recent growth can be attributed to its strategic partnership with <a href="https://www.inx.co/" rel="nofollow">INX</a>, a United States-regulated broker-dealer. Casper&#8217;s equity was tokenized and listed through this collaboration, enhancing investor confidence and further supporting the cryptocurrency&#8217;s upward trajectory. This strategic move has enabled Casper to tap into new markets and expand its reach to a broader audience.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading</strong>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-ada-price-remains-muted-despite-significant-milestones-why/?swcfpc=1">Cardano (ADA) Price Remains Muted Despite Significant Milestones, Why?</a></p>
<p>Casper&#8217;s price surge aligns with the optimistic market sentiment toward cryptocurrencies. The growing interest from institutional investors and the increasing mainstream adoption of digital assets has instilled confidence in crypto. Additionally, influential figures within the blockchain industry have shared positive views on cryptocurrencies, including Casper, contributing to the overall positive outlook.</p>
<h2><strong>Casper (CSPR) Price Analysis</strong> </h2>
<p>Casper has experienced a consistent upward trend in July after it bottomed at $0.0365. Since then, its price has increased by 30% and has hit heights of $0.0405. This positive trend is likely to continue in the coming weeks with more developments expected to be deployed on Casper.</p>
<p>From a technical analysis standpoint, Casper exhibits promising signals. The daily chart reveals the formation of a bullish falling wedge pattern, indicating a potential trend reversal.
CSPR has also surpassed the 25-day exponential moving average and is currently testing the 50-day MA. If the bullish trend continues the next resistance point is $0.40 while a bearish downturn will see the support at $0.0397.</p>
<p><b>Related Reading</b>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/why-worldcoin-wld-and-pepe-dominate-the-crypto-market-trends-this-week/?swcfpc=1">Why Worldcoin (WLD) And PEPE Dominate The Crypto Market Trends This Week</a></p>
<p>As Casper continues to gain visibility and traction in the market, its future growth potential remains promising. The cryptocurrency&#8217;s underlying technology, including its proof-of-stake consensus mechanism, offers scalability, security, and energy efficiency. These features position Casper as an attractive enterprise adoption and long-term development candidate. </p>
<p><i>(This site’s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</i></p>
<p><i>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView</i></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-1370952479-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cup And Handle Pattern Emerges In XRP Chart: What Does It Mean?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/cup-and-handle-pattern-emerges-in-xrp-chart-what-does-it-mean/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 00:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544927</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Despite a favorable ruling as a non-security token, XRP had experienced a correction for over a week and a half, losing bullish momentum after reaching a yearly high of $0.94. It is trading above the $0.70 mark, with the $0.66 level acting as a support. Related Reading: Stanford MBA Explains Why Next Bitcoin Cycle Could Be “Bigger” Over the past 24 hours, XRP has exhibited sideways trading yet shows potential signs of price appreciation. The technical analysis indicates a leaning toward bullish sentiment, with positive buying strength, demand, and accumulation. Even though the emergence of a pattern suggesting further bullishness is possible, it remains critical for XRP to maintain support at $0.66 and $0.56 levels. Additionally, breaking through critical resistance levels is essential for the bulls to retain market control. Encouragingly, the altcoin&#8217;s market capitalization has increased, signaling a positive development for the altcoin. XRP Price Analysis: One-Day Chart When writing, the altcoin XRP was trading at $0.71. The XRP price chart shows the formation of a bullish reversal pattern known as a cup and handle. Despite this positive pattern, the coin&#8217;s true bullish potential will be determined by its ability to surpass two significant resistance levels at $0.76 and $0.84, respectively. It&#8217;s worth noting that after reaching a yearly high of $0.94, XRP encountered resistance at $0.84 twice. On the downside, if there is a decline from the current price level, XRP may find support at $0.66 and then at $0.56. Technical Analysis In recent trading sessions, the buying strength of the altcoin has shown consistency. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) has held steady around the 60-mark over the past few weeks, indicating buyers have maintained control of the price action. This positive signal suggests that the coin will attract more buyers if the price remains above the $0.66 level. Moreover, the price of XRP has remained above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, indicating buoyant demand and confirming that buyers are actively driving the price momentum in the market. With the surge in purchasing power, the altcoin exhibits a decline in sell signals. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) reflects changes in price momentum. Related Reading: Here’s How Crypto Offers A Lifeline For This Bahamian Payment Company Red signal bars appear below the half-line, indicating decreased sell signals. Meanwhile, the Bollinger Bands suggest a likelihood of price volatility and fluctuations in the upcoming trading sessions. The considerable widening of the bands indicates the potential for significant price fluctuation shortly. Featured image from UnSplash, charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite a favorable ruling as a non-security token, XRP had experienced a correction for over a week and a half, losing bullish momentum after reaching a yearly high of $0.94. It is trading above the $0.70 mark, with the $0.66 level acting as a support.</p>

<p>Over the past 24 hours, XRP has exhibited sideways trading yet shows potential signs of price appreciation. The technical analysis indicates a leaning toward bullish sentiment, with positive buying strength, demand, and accumulation.</p>
<p>Even though the emergence of a pattern suggesting further bullishness is possible, it remains critical for XRP to maintain support at $0.66 and $0.56 levels.</p>
<p>Additionally, breaking through critical resistance levels is essential for the bulls to retain market control. Encouragingly, the altcoin&#8217;s market capitalization has increased, signaling a positive development for the altcoin.</p>
<h2>XRP Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-544929 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-10-17.png" alt="XRP" width="1817" height="735" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-10-17.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-10-17-460x186.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-10-17-860x348.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-10-17-768x311.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-10-17-1536x621.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-10-17-750x303.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-10-17-1140x461.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>When writing, the altcoin XRP was trading at $0.71. The XRP price chart shows the formation of a bullish reversal pattern known as a cup and handle.</p>
<p>Despite this positive pattern, the coin&#8217;s true bullish potential will be determined by its ability to surpass two significant resistance levels at $0.76 and $0.84, respectively.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s worth noting that after reaching a yearly high of $0.94, XRP encountered resistance at $0.84 twice. On the downside, if there is a decline from the current price level, XRP may find support at $0.66 and then at $0.56.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-544930 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-24.png" alt="XRP" width="1817" height="735" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-24.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-24-460x186.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-24-860x348.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-24-768x311.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-24-1536x621.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-24-750x303.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-24-1140x461.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>In recent trading sessions, the buying strength of the altcoin has shown consistency. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) has held steady around the 60-mark over the past few weeks, indicating buyers have maintained control of the price action.</p>
<p>This positive signal suggests that the coin will attract more buyers if the price remains above the $0.66 level. Moreover, the price of XRP has remained above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, indicating buoyant demand and confirming that buyers are actively driving the price momentum in the market.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-544931 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-48.png" alt="XRP" width="1817" height="735" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-48.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-48-460x186.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-48-860x348.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-48-768x311.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-48-1536x621.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-48-750x303.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT_2023-07-29_00-20-48-1140x461.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>With the surge in purchasing power, the altcoin exhibits a decline in sell signals. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) reflects changes in price momentum.</p>

<p>Red signal bars appear below the half-line, indicating decreased sell signals. Meanwhile, the Bollinger Bands suggest a likelihood of price volatility and fluctuations in the upcoming trading sessions. The considerable widening of the bands indicates the potential for significant price fluctuation shortly.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/fabio-spano-2lHhfn7KXTw-unsplash-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Price Remains Muted Despite Significant Milestones, Why?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-ada-price-remains-muted-despite-significant-milestones-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 23:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[adausd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano network]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544897</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) has been at the forefront of network development over the last few months. This continued commitment to further development on the blockchain has led to the network hitting multiple new milestones. However, the price of ADA has remained stagnant, so what’s going on? Latest Achievements For Cardano The year 2023 has been a good year for the Cardano network so far as it has celebrated multiple achievements during this time. The first of these is the fact that the Cardano network has recorded one of the longest uptimes of any blockchain in the space. Related Reading: Dogecoin Falls While Others Rally, Is It Decoupling From The Market? Cardano has recorded a continuous uptime record of 2,131 days as of July 28, which means that the network has not had an outage in almost six years. This achievement points to the sound technology behind the blockchain, in comparison to competitors such as Solana which has been characterized by multiple outages since its launch. Cardano has a current UPTIME of 2129 days exactly. That&#8217;s 5.83 YEARS with NO downtime. Built to last, an uptime the largest service providers in the world cannot &#38; will never come close to challenging. Research Wins. We are Cardano. Choose Cardano. 🙌👏@IOHK_Charles @Cardano… — Dave 🧑‍🚀💽 🐋 (@beaumont_dvd) July 26, 2023 Another achievement for the network has the consistent development taking place. Cardano has consistently ranked among the top 3 ecosystems when it comes to development and this time around has been no different. ADA price trending at $0.31 &#124; Source: ADAUSD on TradingView.com According to data from the on-chain tracker Santiment, the network is number 3 on the list of assets with the most developments over the last 30 days. This puts it behind only Polkadot (DOT) and Kusama Network (KSM), both of which emerged 1st and 2nd, respectively. This placement also puts Cardano ahead of its largest competitor Ethereum in terms of development. 🧑‍💻 Top 10 #crypto assets by development activity: notable #github commits, past 30 days: T1 @Polkadot $DOT T1 @kusamanetwork $KSM 3 @Cardano $ADA 4 @dfinity $ICP 5 @hedera $HBAR 6 @vegaprotocol $VEGA 7 @ethstatus $SNT 8 @cosmos $ATOM 9 @Ethereum $ETH 10 @decentraland $MANA pic.twitter.com/SnWDQf5a3y — Santiment (@santimentfeed) July 27, 2023 But Why Is ADA Not Reflecting The Achievements? Usually, when a network such as Cardano is recording such achievements as it has, it is reflected in the price of its native in the form of a rally. However, there has been no such performance from ADA. Rather, the altcoin has been shedding its gains since June. The problem may not be from ADA and might stem from the fact that the crypto market just reverted into another bear market trend. As a result, the broader market has been following the movement of Bitcoin, which on its own has reversed toward the low $29,000s. Related Reading: Bitcoin Pre-Halving Patterns Suggest Bull Market Is Not Starting In 2023 Given Cardano’s developments, if the market were to resume its rally, then ADA may emerge as one of the top performers. This would stem from the positive sentiment surrounding the token due to its significant achievements. Meanwhile, ADA is still performing well on a broader scale. At its current price, the digital asset’s price is up over 40% from its June lows, and ADA holding a good chunk of these gains shows that demand is rising to meet supply, thereby steadying the price. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Cardano (ADA) has been at the forefront of network development over the last few months. This continued commitment to further development on the blockchain has led to the network hitting multiple new milestones. However, the price of ADA has remained stagnant, so what’s going on?</p>
<h2 class="p2">Latest Achievements For Cardano</h2>
<p class="p2">The year 2023 has been a good year for the Cardano network so far as it has celebrated multiple achievements during this time. The first of these is the fact that the Cardano network has recorded one of the longest uptimes of any blockchain in the space.</p>

<p class="p2">Cardano has recorded a continuous uptime record of 2,131 days as of July 28, which means that the network has not had an outage in almost six years. This achievement points to the sound technology behind the blockchain, in comparison to competitors such as Solana which has been characterized by multiple outages since its launch.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Cardano has a current UPTIME of 2129 days exactly.
That&#8217;s 5.83 YEARS with NO downtime.</p>
<p>Built to last, an uptime the largest service providers in the world cannot &amp; will never come close to challenging.</p>
<p>Research Wins. We are Cardano. Choose Cardano. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f64c.png" alt="🙌" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f44f.png" alt="👏" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><a href="https://twitter.com/IOHK_Charles?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@IOHK_Charles</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/Cardano?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@Cardano</a>…</p>
<p>— Dave <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f9d1-200d-1f680.png" alt="🧑‍🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4bd.png" alt="💽" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f40b.png" alt="🐋" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@beaumont_dvd) <a href="https://twitter.com/beaumont_dvd/status/1684210481039302656?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 26, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p class="p2">Another achievement for the network has the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano-development-activity-dropping-what-does-it-mean-for-ada-price/?swcfpc=1">consistent development taking place</a>. Cardano has consistently ranked among the top 3 ecosystems when it comes to development and this time around has been no different.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/e4I8nrST/" alt="Cardano (ADA) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>

<p class="p2">According to data from the on-chain tracker Santiment, the network is number 3 on the list of assets with the most developments over the last 30 days. This puts it behind only Polkadot (DOT) and Kusama Network (KSM), both of which emerged 1st and 2nd, respectively. This placement also puts Cardano ahead of its largest competitor Ethereum in terms of development.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f9d1-200d-1f4bb.png" alt="🧑‍💻" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Top 10 <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/crypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#crypto</a> assets by development activity: notable <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/github?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#github</a> commits, past 30 days:</p>
<p>T1 <a href="https://twitter.com/Polkadot?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@Polkadot</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24DOT&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$DOT</a>
T1 <a href="https://twitter.com/kusamanetwork?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@kusamanetwork</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24KSM&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$KSM</a>
3 <a href="https://twitter.com/Cardano?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@Cardano</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ADA&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$ADA</a>
4 <a href="https://twitter.com/dfinity?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@dfinity</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ICP&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$ICP</a>
5 <a href="https://twitter.com/hedera?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@hedera</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24HBAR&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$HBAR</a>
6 <a href="https://twitter.com/vegaprotocol?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@vegaprotocol</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24VEGA&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$VEGA</a>
7 <a href="https://twitter.com/ethstatus?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@ethstatus</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24SNT&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$SNT</a>
8 <a href="https://twitter.com/cosmos?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@cosmos</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ATOM&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$ATOM</a>
9 <a href="https://twitter.com/ethereum?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@Ethereum</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$ETH</a>
10 <a href="https://twitter.com/decentraland?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@decentraland</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24MANA&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$MANA</a> <a href="https://t.co/SnWDQf5a3y" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/SnWDQf5a3y</a></p>
<p>— Santiment (@santimentfeed) <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1684430107925176322?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<h2 class="p2">But Why Is ADA Not Reflecting The Achievements?</h2>
<p class="p2">Usually, when a network such as Cardano is recording such achievements as it has, it is reflected in the price of its native in the form of a rally. However, there has been no such performance from ADA. Rather, the altcoin has been shedding its gains since June.</p>
<p class="p2">The <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-ada-price-action-potential-trend-reversal/?swcfpc=1">problem may not be from ADA</a> and might stem from the fact that the crypto market just reverted into another bear market trend. As a result, the broader market has been following the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-rally-may-not-resume-until-this-happens/?swcfpc=1">movement of Bitcoin</a>, which on its own has reversed toward the low $29,000s.</p>

<p class="p2">Given Cardano’s developments, if the market were to resume its rally, then ADA may emerge as one of the top performers. This would stem from the positive sentiment surrounding the token due to its significant achievements.</p>
<p class="p2">Meanwhile, ADA is still performing well on a broader scale. At its current price, the digital asset’s price is up over 40% from its June lows, and ADA holding a good chunk of these gains shows that demand is rising to meet supply, thereby steadying the price.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1336958377-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Worldcoin (WLD) And PEPE Dominate The Crypto Market Trends This Week</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/why-worldcoin-wld-and-pepe-dominate-the-crypto-market-trends-this-week/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 22:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPEUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WLD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WLDUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WorldCoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544894</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Worldcoin and its native token WLD have been taking the attention of crypto investors, according to recent data from Coingecko. The project recently announced its worldwide launch inviting users to “visit the orb” and receive rewards by onboarding the platform. Related Reading: Bitcoin Rally May Not Resume Until This Happens WLD has doubled its value from its launch on July 24th, when the cryptocurrency was trading at around $1. The token rose to $2.19 the following week and has been moving sideways since amid a surge in controversy from different angles. Worldcoin (WLD) Leads Crypto Tendencies In addition to WLD, Coingecko shows that Bitcoin (BTC), Unibot (UNIBOT), Chainlink (LINK), HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu, and Pepe Coin (PEPE) have been trending along with other tokens. Bitcoin remains the leader on this chart despite the crash in the BTC.D chart. This metric gauges the percentage of the crypto total market cap comprised solely of Bitcoin’s market capitalization. Often, when the chart trends to the upside, altcoins, such as Worldcoin (WLD) and PEPE, experience a drop in their prices and vice versa. In that sense, WLD’s launch came at a favorable time for small tokens. The project has promised a reward for every user willing to scan their eyeballs with one of the devices scattered around different countries. Thus, sparking controversy about their practices from the crypto community and regulators, some of which are already looking into the project’s legitimacy. Via his Twitter (X) account, Adam Cochran wondered if the hype around WLD is organic or fabricated by a marketing strategy. Cochran wrote: So either Worldcoin, or some group of Orb operators are legit paying plants to stand in line at orbs both for videos and to create demand for the orbs. Got pinged by an old marketing firm friend who does field event marketing, who was asking if Worldcoin is legit. PEPE Leads Trends In The United States While WLD took over the global attention in the nascent sector, PEPE Coin is still the king of the top trending tokens in 2023. Research conducted by Marketplace Fairness indicates that the token has been trending across 23 of the 50 states in the U.S., including Florida, California, and Texas. Related Reading: UK Regulator To Enquire About Worldcoin, As WLD Declines By 17% One Day Post-Launch The cryptocurrency was launched a few months ago but has already garnered more interest than Cardano (ADA), XRP, Litecoin (LTC), Dogecoin, etc. Most of these tokens only trended in 2 of the 50 states in the U.S. in 2023.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Worldcoin and its native token WLD have been taking the attention of crypto investors, according to recent data from Coingecko. The project recently announced its worldwide launch inviting users to “visit the orb” and receive rewards by onboarding the platform. </strong></p>

<p>WLD has doubled its value from its launch on July 24th, when the cryptocurrency was trading at around $1. The token rose to $2.19 the following week and has been moving sideways since amid a surge in controversy from different angles.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-544905 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Worldcoin-WLD-WLDUSDT-860x410.png" alt="Worldcoin WLD WLDUSDT" width="860" height="410" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Worldcoin-WLD-WLDUSDT-860x410.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Worldcoin-WLD-WLDUSDT-460x219.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Worldcoin-WLD-WLDUSDT-768x366.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Worldcoin-WLD-WLDUSDT-1536x732.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Worldcoin-WLD-WLDUSDT-750x358.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Worldcoin-WLD-WLDUSDT-1140x543.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Worldcoin-WLD-WLDUSDT.png 1758w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
<h2>Worldcoin (WLD) Leads Crypto Tendencies</h2>
<p>In addition to WLD, Coingecko <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/watchlists" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shows</a> that Bitcoin (BTC), Unibot (UNIBOT), Chainlink (LINK), HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu, and Pepe Coin (PEPE) have been trending along with other tokens. Bitcoin remains the leader on this chart despite the crash in the BTC.D chart.</p>
<p>This metric gauges the percentage of the crypto total market cap comprised solely of Bitcoin’s market capitalization. Often, when the chart trends to the upside, altcoins, such as Worldcoin (WLD) and PEPE, experience a drop in their prices and vice versa.</p>
<p>In that sense, WLD’s launch came at a favorable time for small tokens. The project has promised a reward for every user willing to scan their eyeballs with one of the devices scattered around different countries.</p>
<p>Thus, sparking controversy about their practices from the crypto community and regulators, some of which are already looking into the project’s legitimacy.</p>
<p>Via his Twitter (X) account, Adam Cochran wondered if the hype around WLD is organic or fabricated by a marketing strategy. Cochran <a href="https://twitter.com/adamscochran/status/1684702689752383488" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">wrote</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>So either Worldcoin, or some group of Orb operators are legit paying plants to stand in line at orbs both for videos and to create demand for the orbs. Got pinged by an old marketing firm friend who does field event marketing, who was asking if Worldcoin is legit.</p></blockquote>
<strong>PEPE Leads Trends In The United States</strong>
<p>While WLD took over the global attention in the nascent sector, PEPE Coin is still the king of the top trending tokens in 2023. Research conducted by Marketplace Fairness <a href="https://www.marketplacefairness.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">indicates</a> that the token has been trending across 23 of the 50 states in the U.S., including Florida, California, and Texas.</p>

<p>The cryptocurrency was launched a few months ago but has already garnered more interest than Cardano (ADA), XRP, Litecoin (LTC), Dogecoin, etc. Most of these tokens only trended in 2 of the 50 states in the U.S. in 2023.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Worldcoin-PEPE-WLDUSDT-PEPEUSDT-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Ledger&#8217;s L2 Smart Contract Development Reaches Key Stage</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-ledgers-l2-smart-contract-development-reaches-key-stage/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 20:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Ledger]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544918</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Evernode, the XRP Ledger (XRPL) Layer 2 platform, has shared a series of updates on its journey toward launch, offering insights into its progress and the challenges it has faced. XRP Ledger Layer 2 Platform Audit Scheduled For Mid-August Evernode is a Layer 2 platform that seeks to bring smart contracts to the XRP Ledger ecosystem via Hooks. The platform is being developed by a team of experienced developers working to enhance the XRP Ledger network with advanced functionalities. Related Reading: Data Shows: Bitcoin Traders Going Long, Blast Above $30,000 Looming? In the first update, Evernode announced that the audit of their three hooks is tentatively scheduled to begin in mid-August. However, the team is still waiting for paperwork and funding from Ripple to confirm the audit, just like other XRPL Grants Grantees. In the second update, the Evernode team shared that the Nomad contract proved more challenging than expected. The contract did not persist on the betanet, which helped the development team identify bugs and areas for improvement. The team has been working hard to resolve these issues and remains optimistic that they will overcome the obstacles soon. Ultimately, Evernode appreciated the approximately 104 betahosts who have provided invaluable feedback in testing and improving the platform in a near-live environment. These updates highlight the complexity of developing a Layer 2 platform for XRP Ledger and the importance of thorough testing and auditing. It also emphasizes the dedication and hard work of the Evernode team throughout the development process. However, upon successful launch, Evernode&#8217;s platform will enable developers to build and deploy smart contracts on the XRP Ledger network, opening up new use cases and applications for the ecosystem. This will enable XRP Ledger to compete with other smart contract platforms such as Ethereum, which has gained significant traction in decentralized finance (DeFi). Moreover, Evernode&#8217;s platform will help drive the adoption of XRP Ledger by attracting more developers to the ecosystem. As the number of developers grows, the network&#8217;s capabilities will expand, leading to more use cases and applications, ultimately driving adoption and value. The development of Evernode&#8217;s Layer 2 platform for XRP Ledger is a significant milestone for the XRP Ledger community. It showcases the continued innovation and development within the ecosystem, which are critical for its growth and success. Related Reading: Bitcoin Rally May Not Resume Until This Happens Overall, Evernode&#8217;s updates on the progress toward launching a Layer 2 platform for XRP Ledger demonstrate the importance of rigorous testing and auditing in developing complex systems.  The successful launch of the platform will open up new opportunities for developers, potentially driving adoption and growth in the XRP Ledger ecosystem.  At the time of writing, XRP has encountered a sideways price movement since Monday. As the fourth largest cryptocurrency in the market regarding trading volume and market capitalization, it is currently trading at $0.7119, representing a decrease of 1.6% over the last 24 hours. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Evernode, the XRP Ledger (XRPL) Layer 2 platform, has shared a <a href="https://twitter.com/EvernodeXRPL/status/1684748272966180864?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">series of updates</a> on its journey toward launch, offering insights into its progress and the challenges it has faced.</p>
<h2>XRP Ledger Layer 2 Platform Audit Scheduled For Mid-August</h2>
<p>Evernode is a Layer 2 platform that seeks to bring smart contracts to the XRP Ledger ecosystem via Hooks. The platform is being developed by a team of experienced developers working to enhance the XRP Ledger network with advanced functionalities.</p>

<p>In the first update, Evernode announced that the audit of their three hooks is tentatively scheduled to begin in mid-August. However, the team is still waiting for paperwork and funding from Ripple to confirm the audit, just like other XRPL Grants Grantees.</p>
<p>In the second update, the Evernode team shared that the Nomad contract proved more challenging than expected. The contract did not persist on the betanet, which helped the development team identify bugs and areas for improvement. The team has been working hard to resolve these issues and remains optimistic that they will overcome the obstacles soon.</p>
<p>Ultimately, Evernode appreciated the approximately 104 betahosts who have provided invaluable feedback in testing and improving the platform in a near-live environment.</p>
<p>These updates highlight the complexity of developing a Layer 2 platform for XRP Ledger and the importance of thorough testing and auditing. It also emphasizes the dedication and hard work of the Evernode team throughout the development process.</p>
<p>However, upon successful launch, Evernode&#8217;s platform will enable developers to build and deploy smart contracts on the XRP Ledger network, opening up new use cases and applications for the ecosystem. This will enable XRP Ledger to compete with other smart contract platforms such as Ethereum, which has gained significant traction in decentralized finance (DeFi).</p>
<p>Moreover, Evernode&#8217;s platform will help drive the adoption of XRP Ledger by attracting more developers to the ecosystem. As the number of developers grows, the network&#8217;s capabilities will expand, leading to more use cases and applications, ultimately driving adoption and value.</p>
<p>The development of Evernode&#8217;s Layer 2 platform for XRP Ledger is a significant milestone for the XRP Ledger community. It showcases the continued innovation and development within the ecosystem, which are critical for its growth and success.</p>

<p>Overall, Evernode&#8217;s updates on the progress toward launching a Layer 2 platform for XRP Ledger demonstrate the importance of rigorous testing and auditing in developing complex systems. </p>
<p>The successful launch of the platform will open up new opportunities for developers, potentially driving adoption and growth in the XRP Ledger ecosystem. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/z5rXEvPR/" alt="XRP" width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>At the time of writing, XRP has encountered a sideways price movement since Monday. As the fourth largest cryptocurrency in the market regarding trading volume and market capitalization, it is currently trading at $0.7119, representing a decrease of 1.6% over the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1365598845-2-460x304.jpg" width="460" height="304" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stanford MBA Explains Why Next Bitcoin Cycle Could Be &#8220;Bigger&#8221;</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/stanford-mba-explains-why-next-bitcoin-cycle-could-be-bigger/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 19:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bull Rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cycle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stanford]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stanford MBA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544886</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A Stanford MBA has explained why the current Bitcoin cycle was different from the others, and why the next one could end up being bigger. This Bitcoin Cycle Faced Obstacles That May Not Be There Next Time A &#8220;cycle&#8221; for Bitcoin refers to the period between two consecutive halvings. The halvings, events where the rewards miners receive for solving blocks on the network are permanently slashed in half, are chosen as the start and end points for the cycles due to the immense significance they hold for the cryptocurrency. The rewards miners earn are essentially the only way new supply can be introduced into circulation, so since halvings cut these in half, the production rate of the asset itself gets tightened. Because of basic supply-demand dynamics, Bitcoin&#8217;s post-halving scarcity increases the asset&#8217;s valuation. It&#8217;s not a coincidence that the bull markets have always followed these special events. The halvings occur roughly every four years, with the next one being scheduled for next year. As BTC transitions towards a new cycle, Jesse Myers, a Stanford MBA, has released a new post that looks back at this cycle so far and compares it with the previous cycles. At first sight, one difference becomes immediately clear: the structure of the top during this past bull market wasn&#8217;t anything like what the previous cycles displayed. How the previous halving cycles looked like at the current stage &#124; Source: Once-In-A-Species &#8220;Instead of a parabolic advance culminating in a blow-off top, we got a bi-modal rounded top spread out over six months,&#8221; notes Myers. So, why did the BTC price behave differently during this bull market? Well, there are mainly four factors at play here. The first and undoubtedly the biggest one would be COVID-19 and the US government&#8217;s response to it. The onset of the virus and the black swan crash that came with it just preceded the cycle, meaning that the cycle kicked off in anomalous conditions. During the cycle itself, the Fed was giving out stimulus checks as a way to mitigate the economic impacts of COVID. &#8220;That Quantitative Easing (QE) undoubtedly helped fuel the 2021 Bitcoin bull market,&#8221; explains the Stanford MBA. The problem came, however, when the Fed changed its policy and switched to Quantitative Tightening (QT). Interestingly, this switch appears to be what marked the Bitcoin top in November 2021. In the middle of all this, another factor was also at play: the May 2021 China ban on Bitcoin mining. Back then, China was the biggest hub of cryptocurrency mining, so the ban naturally delivered a significant shock to the sector. The resulting selling pressure crashed the market, leading to the bull rally prematurely halting. It wasn&#8217;t until three months later that bullish winds once again returned for the asset. While these factors have been quite influential for BTC, it&#8217;s apparent that they are unlikely to repeat, meaning they shouldn&#8217;t have any presence in the next cycle. On the contrary, the other two factors that made this cycle different are likely to appear in the next cycle as well. This previous bull market was the first one where investors widely used leveraged futures trading. Probably, leverage would again come into play in the next bull market. Related Reading: PEPE Whales Load Up Their Bags As Memecoin Jumps 13% Lastly, there is the fact that platforms like FTX issue a lot of &#8220;paper Bitcoin.&#8221; Supply equivalent to 25% of the mined BTC that year was owned by FTX&#8217;s customers, but this BTC didn&#8217;t exist; it was only there on &#8220;paper.&#8221; The analyst believes that such fudging will likely be present during the upcoming cycle. While there had been some developments in this cycle that ultimately shortened the bull market, some changes can be favorable for the next cycle. The Bitcoin supply is quickly moving off exchanges, and the HODLers getting hold of the majority of the supply has often been making the news recently. Still, there is another super exciting factor. Accumulation from the small investors &#124; Source: Once-In-A-Species According to this chart from Glassnode, the relatively small entities on the network (holding less than 100 BTC) have been accumulating 275% of all Bitcoin being mined. The fact that this rate is more than 100% suggests that the smaller investors are taking coins off the likes of whales. &#8220;This has never happened before. We have reached some kind of inflection point,&#8221; says Mjers. Soon the halving will occur, and this supply shock brewing in the market will only get tighter. Perhaps the smaller investors are looking to get in before this happens. Related Reading: Bitcoin Rally May Not Resume Until This Happens Mjers mentions, however, that these individuals aren&#8217;t the only ones catching on; asset managers like Blackrock are also coming around and pushing to get themselves into the industry. As mentioned before, the QT policy proved disastrous for BTC in this cycle, but a shift back towards QE may be imminent, which would naturally boost the market instead. The analyst thinks this event might coincide with the upcoming halving of the cryptocurrency. Now, based on all these factors, these are probabilities that Mjers has assigned to the different price range predictions for the next cycle: The likeliness of each price range &#124; Source: Once-In-A-Species The Stanford MBA believes that a growth of more than 8x, a multiplier higher than what the current cycle saw, is the second most probable scenario, given all the potentially positive developments. A cycle outperforming the previous has never happened in the cryptocurrency&#8217;s history, so if this scenario happens, it would be a first. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,300, down 2% in the last week. BTC continues to move sideways &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from iStock.com, charts from TradingView.com, Glassnode.com, onceinaspecies.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Stanford MBA has explained why the current Bitcoin cycle was different from the others, and why the next one could end up being bigger.</p>
<h2>This Bitcoin Cycle Faced Obstacles That May Not Be There Next Time</h2>
<p>A &#8220;cycle&#8221; for Bitcoin refers to the period between two consecutive halvings. The <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-bull-market-not-starting-in-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">halvings</a>, events where the rewards miners receive for solving blocks on the network are permanently slashed in half, are chosen as the start and end points for the cycles due to the immense significance they hold for the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>The rewards miners earn are essentially the only way new supply can be introduced into circulation, so since halvings cut these in half, the production rate of the asset itself gets tightened.</p>
<p>Because of basic supply-demand dynamics, Bitcoin&#8217;s post-halving scarcity increases the asset&#8217;s valuation. It&#8217;s not a coincidence that the bull markets have always followed these special events.</p>
<p>The halvings occur roughly every four years, with the next one being scheduled for next year. As BTC transitions towards a new cycle, Jesse Myers, a Stanford MBA, has released a new<a href="https://www.onceinaspecies.com/p/next-cycle-could-be-bigger" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> post</a> that looks back at this cycle so far and compares it with the previous cycles.</p>
<p>At first sight, one difference becomes immediately clear: the structure of the top during this past bull market wasn&#8217;t anything like what the previous cycles displayed.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/w_1456,c_limit,f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2F75422a64-3d49-457c-9838-cd50cfb46c20_1900x1025.png" alt="Bitcoin Halving Cycles" width="1456" height="785"/></p>

<p>&#8220;Instead of a parabolic advance culminating in a blow-off top, we got a bi-modal rounded top spread out over six months,&#8221; notes Myers. So, why did the BTC price behave differently during this bull market?</p>
<p>Well, there are mainly four factors at play here. The first and undoubtedly the biggest one would be COVID-19 and the US government&#8217;s response to it. The onset of the virus and the black swan crash that came with it just preceded the cycle, meaning that the cycle kicked off in anomalous conditions.</p>
<p>During the cycle itself, the Fed was giving out stimulus checks as a way to mitigate the economic impacts of COVID. &#8220;That Quantitative Easing (QE) undoubtedly helped fuel the 2021 Bitcoin bull market,&#8221; explains the Stanford MBA.</p>
<p>The problem came, however, when the Fed changed its policy and switched to Quantitative Tightening (QT). Interestingly, this switch appears to be what marked the Bitcoin top in November 2021.</p>
<p>In the middle of all this, another factor was also at play: the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-mining-more-damaging-to-the-environment-after-china-ban-study-says/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">May 2021 China ban</a> on Bitcoin mining. Back then, China was the biggest hub of cryptocurrency mining, so the ban naturally delivered a significant shock to the sector.</p>
<p>The resulting selling pressure crashed the market, leading to the bull rally prematurely halting. It wasn&#8217;t until three months later that bullish winds once again returned for the asset.</p>
<p>While these factors have been quite influential for BTC, it&#8217;s apparent that they are unlikely to repeat, meaning they shouldn&#8217;t have any presence in the next cycle.</p>
<p>On the contrary, the other two factors that made this cycle different are likely to appear in the next cycle as well. This previous bull market was the first one where investors widely used leveraged futures trading. Probably, leverage would again come into play in the next bull market.</p>

<p>Lastly, there is the fact that platforms like FTX issue a lot of &#8220;paper Bitcoin.&#8221; Supply equivalent to 25% of the mined BTC that year was owned by FTX&#8217;s customers, but this BTC didn&#8217;t exist; it was only there on &#8220;paper.&#8221; The analyst believes that such fudging will likely be present during the upcoming cycle.</p>
<p>While there had been some developments in this cycle that ultimately shortened the bull market, some changes can be favorable for the next cycle.</p>
<p>The Bitcoin supply is quickly <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-exchange-supply-only-slips-further-despite-price-decline/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">moving off exchanges</a>, and the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-plunge-to-29200-sends-5-9-supply-into-loss/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">HODLers getting hold of the majority of the supply</a> has often been making the news recently. Still, there is another super exciting factor.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/w_1456,c_limit,f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2F66e9f288-b78d-406b-879a-e716609e85af_1495x861.jpeg" alt="Bitcoin Shrimps And Fish" width="1456" height="839"/></p>

<p>According to this chart from Glassnode, the relatively small entities on the network (holding less than 100 BTC) have been accumulating 275% of all Bitcoin being mined.</p>
<p>The fact that this rate is more than 100% suggests that the smaller investors are taking coins off the likes of whales. &#8220;This has never happened before. We have reached some kind of inflection point,&#8221; says Mjers.</p>
<p>Soon the halving will occur, and this supply shock brewing in the market will only get tighter. Perhaps the smaller investors are looking to get in before this happens.</p>

<p>Mjers mentions, however, that these individuals aren&#8217;t the only ones catching on; asset managers like Blackrock are also coming around and pushing to get themselves into the industry.</p>
<p>As mentioned before, the QT policy proved disastrous for BTC in this cycle, but a shift back towards QE may be imminent, which would naturally boost the market instead. The analyst thinks this event might coincide with the upcoming halving of the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>Now, based on all these factors, these are probabilities that Mjers has assigned to the different price range predictions for the next cycle:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-544909 size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/table-4-460x220.png" alt="Bitcoin Predictions" width="460" height="220" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/table-4-460x220.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/table-4.png 699w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>

<p>The Stanford MBA believes that a growth of more than 8x, a multiplier higher than what the current cycle saw, is the second most probable scenario, given all the potentially positive developments.</p>
<p>A cycle outperforming the previous has never happened in the cryptocurrency&#8217;s history, so if this scenario happens, it would be a first.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,300, down 2% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Vm21XvEl/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1384277890-460x239.jpg" width="460" height="239" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Whales Make Alarming Deposits To Exchanges Amid Falling Prices</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-whales-deposits-to-exchanges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 18:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[whales]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544901</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It would appear that Bitcoin whales are shifting their BTC into exchanges at an alarming rate, which is a warning that they may be getting ready to liquidate their holdings. Recent on-chain data shows that Bitcoin whale exchange deposits reached $275 million in a single day as the cryptocurrency continues to struggle to cross over $30,000. Bitcoin Whales Moving Funds to Exchanges Tweets from the whale transaction tracker @whale_alert indicate that a total of 9,406 Bitcoins, with an approximate worth of $275 million, have been moved into exchanges through separate transactions.  Related Reading: Ripple Attorney Withdraws From SEC Lawsuit, Will It Affect XRP? The vast majority of these trades entered Binance twice, with the largest single deposit being the entry of 2,459 BTC with a total value of $72.6 million. Another significant transaction included the deposit of 1,499 BTC with a total value of $44.3 million into the Binance exchange.  The actions of these Bitcoin whales, or large holders, often significantly impact the overall market. There are a few possible for big money transfers, but when whales make large deposits to exchanges, it usually signals they are preparing to sell in large volumes, which can crash the market, at least temporarily. Many traders consider this a bearish signal and can spark worry that prices may soon drop. For smaller investors, this can mean opportunity or risk ahead. The price of Bitcoin crossed over $30,000 last month, showing promising signs of an upward trend for investors. However, the cryptocurrency has experienced a slight decline in the last seven days, dropping by around 1.57%. Further massive selloffs by whales can have a counter effect on this bullish sentiment. BTC price trending above $29,300 &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com BTC HODLer Net Position Change Reaches 1-Month Low In the same vein of waning bullish sentiment, the number of net Bitcoin position changes recently reached a 1-month low. The metric, which measures the position change of long-term investors on a monthly basis, shows whether investors are opening or closing positions in Bitcoin.  Related Reading: VC Firm Sequoia Capital Slashes Crypto Fund By 65% Amid Bear Market According to data from Glassnode alerts, this metric just reached a one-month low of 17,604.723. This shows that more holders have been closing out their BTC positions to withdraw their profits for the past few weeks than those opening new ones. 📉 #Bitcoin $BTC HODLer Net Position Change just reached a 1-month low of 17,604.723 Previous 1-month low of 22,095.894 was observed on 18 July 2023 View metric:https://t.co/CU3jPaaHXh pic.twitter.com/8k2EHP0nsi — glassnode alerts (@glassnodealerts) July 28, 2023 It is important to keep an eye on whale selloffs, but other factors, like the shift in the net position of HODLers, also help to reveal where the price of Bitcoin is headed in the short term. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It would appear that Bitcoin whales are shifting their BTC into exchanges at an alarming rate, which is a warning that they may be getting ready to liquidate their holdings. Recent on-chain data shows that Bitcoin whale exchange deposits reached $275 million in a single day as the cryptocurrency continues to struggle to cross over $30,000.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Whales Moving Funds to Exchanges</h2>
<p>Tweets from the whale transaction tracker @whale_alert indicate that a total of 9,406 Bitcoins, with an approximate worth of $275 million, have been moved into exchanges through separate transactions. </p>

<p>The vast majority of these trades entered Binance twice, with the largest single deposit being the entry of <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1684508594056622081?s=20" rel="nofollow">2,459 BTC with a total value of $72.6 million</a>. Another significant transaction included the <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1684502383827488768?s=20" rel="nofollow">deposit of 1,499 BTC with a total value of $44.3 million</a> into the Binance exchange. </p>
<p>The actions of these Bitcoin whales, or large holders, often significantly impact the overall market. There are a few possible for big money transfers, but when whales make large deposits to exchanges, it usually signals they are preparing to sell in large volumes, which can crash the market, at least temporarily. </p>
<p>Many traders consider this a bearish signal and can spark worry that prices may soon drop. For smaller investors, this can mean opportunity or risk ahead.</p>
<p>The price of Bitcoin crossed over $30,000 last month, showing promising signs of an upward trend for investors. However, the cryptocurrency has experienced a slight decline in the last seven days, dropping by around 1.57%. Further massive selloffs by whales can have a counter effect on this bullish sentiment.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/gzBQ4cMh/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>

<h2>BTC HODLer Net Position Change Reaches 1-Month Low</h2>
<p>In the same vein of waning bullish sentiment, the number of net Bitcoin position changes recently reached a 1-month low. The metric, which measures the position change of long-term investors on a monthly basis, shows whether investors are opening or closing positions in Bitcoin. </p>

<p>According to data from Glassnode alerts, this metric just reached a one-month low of 17,604.723. This shows that more holders have been closing out their BTC positions to withdraw their profits for the past few weeks than those opening new ones.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4c9.png" alt="📉" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Bitcoin</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$BTC</a> HODLer Net Position Change just reached a 1-month low of 17,604.723</p>
<p>Previous 1-month low of 22,095.894 was observed on 18 July 2023</p>
<p>View metric:<a href="https://t.co/CU3jPaaHXh" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/CU3jPaaHXh</a> <a href="https://t.co/8k2EHP0nsi" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/8k2EHP0nsi</a></p>
<p>— glassnode alerts (@glassnodealerts) <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnodealerts/status/1684824928476958722?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 28, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>It is important to keep an eye on whale selloffs, but other factors, like the shift in the net position of HODLers, also help to reveal where the price of Bitcoin is headed in the short term.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1338758941-1-460x315.jpg" width="460" height="315" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Data Shows: Bitcoin Traders Going Long, Blast Above $30,000 Looming?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/data-shows-bitcoin-traders-going-long-blast-above-30000-looming/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 17:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544864</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin continues to trade sideways during today’s trading session, holding the line draw for the past few weeks. Recent data shows that the cryptocurrency has been recording “crab-like” price action in the short term, but operators favor the long side of their trades. Related Reading: Why This Billionaire Continues To Advocate For Bitcoin Amid Surging US Debt? As of this writing, Bitcoin trades at $29,700 with a 0.7% loss in the last 24 hours and a 2% loss in the previous week. The cryptocurrency’s implied volatility has been trending to the downside while BTC’s price holds still at its current levels. Low Volatility Set The Stage For A Bitcoin Price Explosion? Data from a report posted by crypto analytics firm Block Scholes via Deribit indicates that Bitcoin and Ethereum traders have been seeking long exposure to these cryptocurrencies. As mentioned above, this behavior coincides with a decline in delivered volatility. As a result, the BTC and ETH perpetual swap markets are experiencing a shift in funding rates. This measure determines the percentage paid by long to short positions at a given time. The chart below shows that funding rates have been trending to the upside since last September 2022. At that time, the price of Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies hit a multi-year low. Now, the BTC price experienced a 100% recovery from those levels leading to a change in the derivatives sector. The chart shows that funding rates across the BTC, ETH, and USDC trading pairs have been positive for the past three months. This data shows that traders are going long and willing to pay short positions for their exposure. A positive funding rate is often linked to the sentiment among operators and could hint at an upcoming bullish run when found on platforms like Deribit, where “smart money” trades. Why Are BTC Traders Going Long? Conversely, Block Scholes wonders: why are traders going long when implied volatility fell to new all-time lows? What’s driving operators for long exposure while the price trades sideways so much that they are willing to pay a premium? The report stated: We find it somewhat odd that traders are willing to pay such a consistently high rate for long exposure despite such low expectations of volatility. Related Reading: Bitcoin Set To Accelerate As A Store Of Value In Wake Of Bank Collapses, Cathie Wood The above is unclear; it could be traders hedging their positions on the options market could be traders getting ready for an upcoming move as the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) deliberates on the potential approval of a spot Bitcoin Exchange Traded Fund (ETF).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Bitcoin continues to trade sideways during today’s trading session, holding the line draw for the past few weeks. Recent data shows that the cryptocurrency has been recording “crab-like” price action in the short term, but operators favor the long side of their trades. </strong></p>

<p>As of this writing, Bitcoin trades at $29,700 with a 0.7% loss in the last 24 hours and a 2% loss in the previous week. The cryptocurrency’s implied volatility has been trending to the downside while BTC’s price holds still at its current levels.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-544881" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-460x219.png" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT" width="460" height="219" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-460x219.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-860x410.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-768x366.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1536x732.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-750x358.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1140x543.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT.png 1758w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/>
<h2>Low Volatility Set The Stage For A Bitcoin Price Explosion?</h2>
<p>Data from a report <a href="https://insights.deribit.com/industry/weekly-commentary-whered-all-the-vol-go/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">posted</a> by crypto analytics firm Block Scholes via Deribit indicates that Bitcoin and Ethereum traders have been seeking long exposure to these cryptocurrencies. As mentioned above, this behavior coincides with a decline in delivered volatility.</p>
<p>As a result, the BTC and ETH perpetual swap markets are experiencing a shift in funding rates. This measure determines the percentage paid by long to short positions at a given time.</p>
<p>The chart below shows that funding rates have been trending to the upside since last September 2022. At that time, the price of Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies hit a multi-year low.</p>
<p>Now, the BTC price experienced a 100% recovery from those levels leading to a change in the derivatives sector. The chart shows that funding rates across the BTC, ETH, and USDC trading pairs have been positive for the past three months.</p>
<p>This data shows that traders are going long and willing to pay short positions for their exposure. A positive funding rate is often linked to the sentiment among operators and could hint at an upcoming bullish run when found on platforms like Deribit, where “smart money” trades.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-544877 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-860x386.jpg" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT Chart 2" width="860" height="386" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-860x386.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-460x207.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-768x345.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-1536x690.jpg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-750x337.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-1140x512.jpg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2.jpg 1601w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
Why Are BTC Traders Going Long?
<p>Conversely, Block Scholes wonders: why are traders going long when implied volatility fell to new all-time lows? What’s driving operators for long exposure while the price trades sideways so much that they are willing to pay a premium? The report stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>We find it somewhat odd that traders are willing to pay such a consistently high rate for long exposure despite such low expectations of volatility.</p></blockquote>

<p>The above is unclear; it could be traders hedging their positions on the options market could be traders getting ready for an upcoming move as the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) deliberates on the potential approval of a spot Bitcoin Exchange Traded Fund (ETF).</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1-460x365.jpg" width="460" height="365" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Attorney Withdraws From SEC Lawsuit, Will It Affect XRP?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/ripple-attorney-withdraws-from-sec-lawsuit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 16:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple attorney]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple lawsuit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple v SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544879</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A recent development in the ongoing showdown between the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has seen the withdrawal of another Ripple attorney from the lawsuit, recent court filings reveal. This comes after a motion was filed earlier in the month for Anna R. Gressel to withdraw as attorney of defendant Ripple Labs. This recent withdrawal has cast a shadow of uncertainty as holders of XRP ponder on the likely impact of this development. Ripple Remains Upbeat Despite Attorney’s Withdrawal According to details in the filing made at the District Court for the Southern District of New York on July 27, Ripple is asking for the leave of the court to withdraw Lisa R. Zornberg as an attorney to the defendants in the ongoing XRP vs. SEC lawsuit.  Related Reading: VC Firm Sequoia Capital Slashes Crypto Fund By 65% Amid Bear Market Ripple is appealing to the court to grant Lisa R. Zornberg of the popular Debevoise &#38; Plimpton LLP permission to withdraw as an attorney in the lawsuit. This is in light of the fact that Lisa R. Zornberg will no longer be working with the law firm from July 31.  The foremost federal prosecutor was appointed by New York City Mayor Eric Adams as City Hall&#8217;s Chief Counsel earlier this week. However, this move does not in any way affect Ripple’s relationship with Debevoise &#38; Plimpton LLP as other attorneys of the firm will continue representing Ripple Labs in the case.  Ripple has also reiterated that the withdrawal of Lisa R. Zornberg does not in any way affect its interests, including those of CEO Brad Garlinghouse and co-founder Chris Larsen. It’s also important to note that the court had previously approved withdrawal motions for three attorneys Kylie Chiseul Kim, Clayton J. Masterman, and Anna R. Gressel to exit the lawsuit.   Attorney Withdraws As Case Grinds to a Close The withdrawal of Lisa R. Zornbergs comes in the wake of Judge Analisa Torres&#8217; referral of the lawsuit to Magistrate Judge Sarah Netburn. Magistrate Judge Netburn instructed the SEC and Ripple to reach an agreement on three mutually suitable dates to hold a settlement conference on issues like institutional sales of XRP. Related Reading: Bitcoin Set To Accelerate As A Store Of Value In Wake Of Bank Collapses, Cathie Wood XRP’s price witnessed a surge in the wake of the summary judgment entered in favor of Ripple. The plans unveiled by Ripple have also helped in bolstering investor confidence as the demand for XRP among institutional investors continues to surge. XRP is currently trading at $0.071, down 0.5% in the last 24 hours according to data from CoinGecko. However, its current price puts it 33% higher than its July opening price of $0.47. XRP price is 33% higher compared to July lows &#124; Source: XRPUSD on Tradingview.com Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A recent development in the ongoing showdown between the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has seen the withdrawal of another Ripple attorney from the lawsuit, recent court <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.551082/gov.uscourts.nysd.551082.880.0.pdf" rel="nofollow">filings</a> reveal. This comes after a motion was <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.551082/gov.uscourts.nysd.551082.873.0.pdf" rel="nofollow">filed</a> earlier in the month for Anna R. Gressel to withdraw as attorney of defendant Ripple Labs.</p>
<p>This recent withdrawal has cast a shadow of uncertainty as holders of XRP ponder on the likely impact of this development.</p>
<h2>Ripple Remains Upbeat Despite Attorney’s Withdrawal</h2>
<p>According to details in the <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.551082/gov.uscourts.nysd.551082.880.0.pdf" rel="nofollow">filing</a> made at the District Court for the Southern District of New York on July 27, Ripple is asking for the leave of the court to withdraw Lisa R. Zornberg as an attorney to the defendants in the ongoing XRP vs. SEC lawsuit. </p>

<p>Ripple is appealing to the court to grant Lisa R. Zornberg of the popular Debevoise &amp; Plimpton LLP permission to withdraw as an attorney in the lawsuit. This is in light of the fact that Lisa R. Zornberg will no longer be working with the law firm from July 31. </p>
<p>The foremost federal prosecutor was appointed by New York City Mayor Eric Adams as City Hall&#8217;s Chief Counsel earlier this week. However, this move does not in any way affect Ripple’s relationship with Debevoise &amp; Plimpton LLP as other attorneys of the firm will continue representing Ripple Labs in the case. </p>
<p>Ripple has also reiterated that the withdrawal of Lisa R. Zornberg does not in any way affect its interests, including those of CEO Brad Garlinghouse and co-founder Chris Larsen.</p>
<p>It’s also important to note that the court had previously approved <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/press-releases/why-did-ripple-attorney-exit-sec-lawsuit-defense-team-sleeping-whales-awaken-they-are-buying-this-altcoin/">withdrawal motions</a> for three attorneys Kylie Chiseul Kim, Clayton J. Masterman, and Anna R. Gressel to exit the lawsuit.  </p>
<h2>Attorney Withdraws As Case Grinds to a Close</h2>
<p>The withdrawal of Lisa R. Zornbergs comes in the wake of Judge Analisa Torres&#8217; referral of the lawsuit to Magistrate Judge Sarah Netburn. Magistrate Judge Netburn instructed the SEC and Ripple to reach an agreement on three mutually suitable dates to hold a <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-vs-sec-judge-orders-settlement-conference/" rel="nofollow">settlement conference</a> on issues like institutional sales of XRP.</p>

<p>XRP’s price witnessed a surge in the wake of the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-judge-deems-xrp-sale-non-investment-contract/" rel="nofollow">summary judgment</a> entered in favor of Ripple. The plans unveiled by Ripple have also helped in bolstering investor confidence as the demand for XRP among institutional investors continues to surge.</p>
<p>XRP is currently trading at $0.071, down 0.5% in the last 24 hours according to data from <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/xrp" rel="nofollow">CoinGecko</a>. However, its current price puts it 33% higher than its July opening price of $0.47.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/GtqNBi1w/" alt="Ripple (XRP) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1135927483-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
