<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 03:59:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Is Showing Early Signs of Fresh Increase, But This Resistance Is Key</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-increase-above-1920/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 03:59:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543285</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum price is finding bids above the $1,875 support zone against the US Dollar. ETH could gain bullish momentum above the $1,940 resistance. Ethereum is holding the key support near $1,875. The price is trading below $1,920 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $1,900 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could gain pace if it clears the $1,920 and $1,940 resistance levels. Ethereum Price Could Start Fresh Increase Ethereum’s price declined again below the $1,900 support. However, ETH bulls were active near the $1,875 level. It seems like a double bottom pattern is forming near the $1,875 level. A low is formed near $1,875 and the price is now attempting a fresh increase. It broke the $1,900 resistance level. There was also a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $1,900 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. The pair cleared the 50% Fib retracement level recent drop from the $1,944 swing high to the $1,874 low. Ether is now trading below $1,920 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $1,920 level. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level recent drop from the $1,944 swing high to the $1,874 low. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com The first major resistance is near the $1,940 zone, above which the price could rise toward the $1,985 resistance zone. The next major resistance is near the $2,000 level. Any more gains could send Ether toward the $2,050 resistance or even $2,080. Fresh Decline in ETH? If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,920 resistance, it could start a fresh decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,900 level. The first major support is near the $1,875 level, below which the price could extend its decline. The next major support is near the $1,825 support level. Any more losses could open the doors for a move toward the $1,780 support level in the near term. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is gaining momentum in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,875 Major Resistance Level – $1,920]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum price is finding bids above the $1,875 support zone against the US Dollar. ETH could gain bullish momentum above the $1,940 resistance.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum is holding the key support near $1,875.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $1,920 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</li>
<li>There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $1,900 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could gain pace if it clears the $1,920 and $1,940 resistance levels.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Could Start Fresh Increase</h2>
<p>Ethereum’s price declined again below the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-downsides-1900/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$1,900 support</a>. However, ETH bulls were active near the $1,875 level. It seems like a double bottom pattern is forming near the $1,875 level.</p>
<p>A low is formed near $1,875 and the price is now attempting a fresh increase. It broke the $1,900 resistance level. There was also a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $1,900 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. The pair cleared the 50% Fib retracement level recent drop from the $1,944 swing high to the $1,874 low.</p>
<p>Ether is now trading below $1,920 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-move-1900/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100-hourly Simple Moving Average</a>. On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $1,920 level. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level recent drop from the $1,944 swing high to the $1,874 low.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-543286" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-12.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-12.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-12-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-12-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-12-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-12-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-12-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-12-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $1,940 zone, above which the price could rise toward the $1,985 resistance zone. The next major resistance is near the $2,000 level. Any more gains could send Ether toward the $2,050 resistance or even $2,080.</p>
<h2>Fresh Decline in ETH?</h2>
<p>If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,920 resistance, it could start a fresh decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,900 level.</p>
<p>The first major support is near the $1,875 level, below which the price could extend its decline. The next major support is near the $1,825 support level. Any more losses could open the doors for a move toward the $1,780 support level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,875</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,920</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/iStock-1329407939-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Bulls Keeps Pushing, Why Fresh Increase To $31K Seems Likely</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-bulls-pushing-31k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 03:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543278</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is attempting a fresh increase from $29,500. BTC could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $30,200 resistance zone in the near term. Bitcoin is slowly moving higher from the $29,500 level. The price is trading below $30,200 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,100 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could start a decent increase if there is a close above the $30,200 resistance. Bitcoin Price Aims Higher Bitcoin price followed a bearish path below the $30,200 pivot level. BTC even broke the $29,850 level and tested the $29,500 level. A low is formed near $29,500 and the price is now attempting a fresh increase. The price climbed above the $29,850 and $30,000 resistance levels. There was a move above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $30,448 swing high to the $29,500 low. The price is now consolidating near $30,000. Bitcoin price is still trading below $30,200 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. Immediate resistance is near the $30,080 level. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,100 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. The trend line is near the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $30,448 swing high to the $29,500 low. The first major resistance is near $30,200. A close above the $30,200 level might start a fresh increase. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The next major resistance is near the $30,500 level. Any more gains could open the doors for a move toward the $31,000 resistance zone. More Losses in BTC? If Bitcoin fails to clear the $30,200 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $29,650 level. The next major support is near the $29,500 level, below which the price could gain bearish momentum. In the stated case, the price could drop toward the $29,200 support zone. Any more losses might send the price toward the $28,750 level in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $29,650, followed by $29,200. Major Resistance Levels – $30,100, $30,200, and $30,500.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is attempting a fresh increase from $29,500. BTC could gain bullish momentum if it clears the $30,200 resistance zone in the near term.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is slowly moving higher from the $29,500 level.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $30,200 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,100 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start a decent increase if there is a close above the $30,200 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Aims Higher</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price followed a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-30500-fresh-rally/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">bearish path below the $30,200 pivot level</a>. BTC even broke the $29,850 level and tested the $29,500 level. A low is formed near $29,500 and the price is now attempting a fresh increase.</p>
<p>The price climbed above the $29,850 and $30,000 resistance levels. There was a move above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $30,448 swing high to the $29,500 low. The price is now consolidating near $30,000.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is still trading below $30,200 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-aims-31k/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>. Immediate resistance is near the $30,080 level. There is also a major bearish trend line forming with resistance near $30,100 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>The trend line is near the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $30,448 swing high to the $29,500 low. The first major resistance is near $30,200. A close above the $30,200 level might start a fresh increase.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-543279" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-12.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-12.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-12-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-12-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-12-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-12-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-12-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-12-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The next major resistance is near the $30,500 level. Any more gains could open the doors for a move toward the $31,000 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>More Losses in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin fails to clear the $30,200 resistance, it could continue to move down. Immediate support on the downside is near the $29,650 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $29,500 level, below which the price could gain bearish momentum. In the stated case, the price could drop toward the $29,200 support zone. Any more losses might send the price toward the $28,750 level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $29,650, followed by $29,200.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $30,100, $30,200, and $30,500.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/Depositphotos_78872860_s-2019-1-460x293.jpg" width="460" height="293" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Avalanche (AVAX) Q2 Success: Network Activity Surges, Revenue Jumps 170%</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/avalanche/avalanche-avax-q2-success-network-activity-surges-revenue-jumps-170/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 02:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Avalanche]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche Ecosystem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAXUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543272</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Avalanche, the smart contract platform for decentralized applications, witnessed remarkable growth in  Q2 2023, driven by increased activity on the C-Chain- one of the three chains that make up the Avalanche network- and the launch of new subnets.  According to a recent report by Messari, the network&#8217;s daily average active addresses and transactions on the C-Chain was increased by 132.1% and 162.2%, respectively, primarily due to a rise in stablecoin liquidity and activity from LayerZero.  Avalanche’s Unprecedented Growth Per the report, despite the challenging regulatory climate, Avalanche&#8217;s financial performance improved in Q2, with revenue in AVAX increasing by 173.1% Quarter-Over Quarter (QoQ) (up 150.3% in USD terms).  The increased revenue was partly due to higher transaction fees but primarily due to the activity stemming from LayerZero.  The difference between the change in revenue versus market cap suggests that the overall fundamental network utility was more significant than market behavior in Q2. Avalanche concluded the quarter as the 18th largest crypto asset by market capitalization, reaching $4.5 billion. Related Reading: Thodex CEO Sentenced To Prison For Tax Evasion Furthermore, the platform has been launching new subnets like Evergreen Subnets and Spruce, which have ushered in partners like T. Rowe Price, WisdomTree, Wellington Management, and Cumberland.  Alibaba Cloud also launched Cloudverse, a launchpad for businesses to deploy metaverses on Avalanche, and SK, one of South Korea&#8217;s largest conglomerates, launched its dedicated Avalanche Subnet, UPTN. In Q4 2022, LayerZero, an Omnichain interoperability protocol enabling cross-chain applications, launched support for BTC.b, a token representing Bitcoin on Avalanche.  Compared to other natively bridged Bitcoin assets, BTC.b allows users to freely transfer native Bitcoin without relying on custodians. BTC.b adoption on Avalanche quickly grew after LayerZero&#8217;s support in Q4 2022. Avalanche NFT Secondary Sales And Unique Buyers Decrease According to Messari, the Avalanche NFT sector experienced a decline in Q2 of 2023, with secondary sales volume and the number of unique NFT buyers decreasing by 38.3% and 49.8%, respectively.  However, despite the decline, Avalanche&#8217;s developer ecosystem expanded the NFT sector through new initiatives and partnerships. One such initiative was the Avaissance program, launched in Q1 to accelerate artists&#8217; careers and catalyze the Avalanche NFT ecosystem. The program comprised an Artist-in-Residence program and the Mona Lisa Initiative for digital art curation.  During Q2, 70 artists were selected to participate in the 6-month Artist-in-Residence program, and the Mona Lisa Initiative announced the initial group of participating DAOs. Superchief Gallery NFT, Zeroone, and Peek NFT, three new marketplaces also announced partnerships with Avalanche and Ava Labs to launch unique NFT marketplaces.  In the gaming sector, DeFi Kingdoms continued to dominate, generating the lion&#8217;s share of transaction activity on the Avalanche network. However, several developments are underway to usher in more gaming activity from other applications.  Related Reading: XRP Overtakes Bitcoin In Highest Weekly Trading Volume Following Legal Triumph Avalanche introduced Avalanche Arcad3, a program to accelerate gaming development with partners like GREE, Loco, and TSM, and Merit Circle&#8217;s launch of Beam, a subnet catering to gamers and game developers. Gunzilla Games, Battle for Giostone (BFG), Draft Labs, Defimons, and NEOBRED announced their Avalanche launches during Q2. Overall, Q2 was a positive quarter for Avalanche, and the platform&#8217;s plans for 2023 remain robust as it seeks to remain competitive throughout the rest of the year. Despite the challenges posed by the SEC, Avalanche&#8217;s renewed network activity and expansion plans suggest that the platform is well-equipped to navigate the evolving landscape of the blockchain industry. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Avalanche, the smart contract platform for decentralized applications, witnessed remarkable growth in  Q2 2023, driven by increased activity on the C-Chain- one of the three chains that make up the Avalanche network- and the launch of new subnets. </p>
<p>According to a recent <a href="https://messari.io/report/state-of-avalanche-q2-2023?referrer=all-research?utm_medium=organic_social" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report </a>by Messari, the network&#8217;s daily average active addresses and transactions on the C-Chain was increased by 132.1% and 162.2%, respectively, primarily due to a rise in stablecoin liquidity and activity from LayerZero. </p>
<h2>Avalanche’s Unprecedented Growth</h2>
<p>Per the report, despite the challenging regulatory climate, Avalanche&#8217;s financial performance improved in Q2, with revenue in AVAX increasing by 173.1% Quarter-Over Quarter (QoQ) (up 150.3% in USD terms). </p>
<p>The increased revenue was partly due to higher transaction fees but primarily due to the activity stemming from LayerZero. </p>
<p>The difference between the change in revenue versus market cap suggests that the overall fundamental network utility was more significant than market behavior in Q2. Avalanche concluded the quarter as the 18th largest crypto asset by market capitalization, reaching $4.5 billion.</p>

<p>Furthermore, the platform has been launching new subnets like Evergreen Subnets and Spruce, which have ushered in partners like T. Rowe Price, WisdomTree, Wellington Management, and Cumberland. </p>
<p>Alibaba Cloud also launched Cloudverse, a launchpad for businesses to deploy metaverses on Avalanche, and SK, one of South Korea&#8217;s largest conglomerates, launched its dedicated Avalanche Subnet, UPTN.</p>
<p>In Q4 2022, LayerZero, an Omnichain interoperability protocol enabling cross-chain applications, launched support for BTC.b, a token representing Bitcoin on Avalanche. </p>
<p>Compared to other natively bridged Bitcoin assets, BTC.b allows users to freely transfer native Bitcoin without relying on custodians. BTC.b adoption on Avalanche quickly grew after LayerZero&#8217;s support in Q4 2022.</p>
Avalanche NFT Secondary Sales And Unique Buyers Decrease
<p>According to Messari, the Avalanche NFT sector experienced a decline in Q2 of 2023, with secondary sales volume and the number of unique NFT buyers decreasing by 38.3% and 49.8%, respectively. </p>
<p>However, despite the decline, Avalanche&#8217;s developer ecosystem expanded the NFT sector through new initiatives and partnerships.</p>
<p>One such initiative was the Avaissance program, launched in Q1 to accelerate artists&#8217; careers and catalyze the Avalanche NFT ecosystem. The program comprised an Artist-in-Residence program and the Mona Lisa Initiative for digital art curation. </p>
<p>During Q2, 70 artists were selected to participate in the 6-month Artist-in-Residence program, and the Mona Lisa Initiative announced the initial group of participating DAOs.</p>
<p>Superchief Gallery NFT, Zeroone, and Peek NFT, three new marketplaces also announced partnerships with Avalanche and Ava Labs to launch unique NFT marketplaces. </p>
<p>In the gaming sector, DeFi Kingdoms continued to dominate, generating the lion&#8217;s share of transaction activity on the Avalanche network. However, several developments are underway to usher in more gaming activity from other applications. </p>

<p>Avalanche introduced Avalanche Arcad3, a program to accelerate gaming development with partners like GREE, Loco, and TSM, and Merit Circle&#8217;s launch of Beam, a subnet catering to gamers and game developers. Gunzilla Games, Battle for Giostone (BFG), Draft Labs, Defimons, and NEOBRED announced their Avalanche launches during Q2.</p>
<p>Overall, Q2 was a positive quarter for Avalanche, and the platform&#8217;s plans for 2023 remain robust as it seeks to remain competitive throughout the rest of the year. </p>
<p>Despite the challenges posed by the SEC, Avalanche&#8217;s renewed network activity and expansion plans suggest that the platform is well-equipped to navigate the evolving landscape of the blockchain industry.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/2VLTPl8k/" alt="Avalanche" width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/zac-durant-_6HzPU9Hyfg-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin&#8217;s Worst Performance Period Ever: Is the Bottom In Sight?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoins-worst-performance-period-ever-is-the-bottom-in-sight/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 01:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin bears]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hash rate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543252</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The ongoing bear market in Bitcoin is the longest in the network&#8217;s history, Glassnode data shows. According to trackers, the winter started on November 10, 2021, after prices peaked at over $69,000. As of July 18, 2023, BTC is trading at around the $30,000 level, down by almost 55% from its all-time high. However, despite the crash and bears persistence, recent developments suggest that the bottom might be in. Bitcoin Bear Run Over? Trackers reveal that this is the second largest phase when the coin&#8217;s prices have remained under water for this extended period. Between 2015 and 2016, which was still the formative stages of the coin when its liquidity was building up, the coin remained depressed for 386 days. BTC investors were also under pressure between 2018 and 2019 when prices drastically fell from 2017 peaks, crashing to as low as $4,000 at the depth of the crypto winter of 2018. The extended bear run from 2021 has been influenced by several fundamental factors, including the U.S. Federal Reserve&#8217;s intervention which saw the central bank take measures to tame inflation by raising interest rates in eight consecutive sessions. There have been fear factors relating to the collapse of major crypto firms, including 3AC, FTX, Voyager, and the spectacular depegging and crash of UST and LUNA. Following the collapse of FTX in November, Bitcoin prices fell to all low as $15,800 before expanding, roughly doubling in the first half of 2023. Hash Rate And BlackRock ETF Application Despite relatively low Bitcoin prices and the continuation of the bear run, the network&#8217;s hash rate is trending at a near-all-time high. As of July 18, Bitcoin&#8217;s hash rate stood at over 385 EH/s, retracing from all-time highs of 465 EH/s recorded in late June 2021.  Related Reading: Litecoin Whales Deposit Big To Exchanges, Bearish Sign? Historically, prices and hash rate are directly correlated but falling coin prices didn&#8217;t dissuade miners from buying new gear and plugging into the network, fortifying it against attacks.  The hash rate measures processing power channeled to a proof-of-work network like Bitcoin. The higher it is, the more secure the blockchain is against potential attackers. Reports on July 16 indicated that the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) had accepted BlackRock&#8217;s application for a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF). This is a significant milestone for the Bitcoin-related proposal and may strengthen prices if the regulator eventually approves the derivative, allowing institutions to have exposure. Presently, Bitcoin is teetering close to $30,000 and looks weak. Bulls have been unable to close above $32,000 despite BlackRock&#8217;s reapplication of the spot Bitcoin ETF. Related Reading: ARK Invest CEO Says Firm Is Still Bullish On Coinbase Despite Selling COIN Stocks BlackRock is the world&#8217;s largest asset manager, with over $9.4 trillion in assets. The firm filed for its first spot Bitcoin ETF in June, only for changes to the made and the application to be updated before being resubmitted. It remains to be seen if the approval of an ETF marks the bottom for Bitcoin and the nascent asset class. Feature image from Canva, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The ongoing bear market in Bitcoin is the longest in the network&#8217;s history, Glassnode data <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/_AustinHerbert/status/1680562747103141888" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shows</a>. </p>
<p>According to trackers, the winter started on November 10, 2021, after prices peaked at over $69,000. As of July 18, 2023, BTC is trading at around the $30,000 level, down by almost 55% from its all-time high. </p>
<p>However, despite the crash and bears persistence, recent developments suggest that the bottom might be in.
</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Bear Run Over?</h2>
<p>Trackers reveal that this is the second largest phase when the coin&#8217;s prices have remained under water for this extended period. Between 2015 and 2016, which was still the formative stages of the coin when its liquidity was building up, the coin remained depressed for 386 days. </p>
<p>BTC investors were also under pressure between 2018 and 2019 when prices drastically fell from 2017 peaks, crashing to as low as $4,000 at the depth of the crypto winter of 2018.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/60mbFqSU/" rel="nofollow"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/60mbFqSU/" alt="Bitcoin price on July 18| Source: BTCUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1226" height="595"/></a>
<p>The extended bear run from 2021 has been influenced by several fundamental factors, including the U.S. Federal Reserve&#8217;s intervention which saw the central bank take measures to tame inflation by raising interest rates in eight consecutive sessions. </p>
<p>There have been fear factors relating to the collapse of major crypto firms, including 3AC, FTX, Voyager, and the spectacular depegging and crash of UST and LUNA. Following the collapse of FTX in November, Bitcoin prices fell to all low as $15,800 before expanding, roughly doubling in the first half of 2023.</p>
<h2>Hash Rate And BlackRock ETF Application</h2>
<p>Despite relatively low Bitcoin prices and the continuation of the bear run, the network&#8217;s hash rate is trending at a near-all-time high. As of July 18, Bitcoin&#8217;s hash rate <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://bitinfocharts.com/comparison/bitcoin-hashrate.html#3y" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">stood</a> at over 385 EH/s, retracing from all-time highs of 465 EH/s recorded in late June 2021. </p>

<p>Historically, prices and hash rate are directly correlated but falling coin prices didn&#8217;t dissuade miners from buying new gear and plugging into the network, fortifying it against attacks. </p>
<p>The hash rate measures processing power channeled to a proof-of-work network like Bitcoin. The higher it is, the more secure the blockchain is against potential attackers.</p>
<p>Reports on July 16 <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.sec.gov/rules/sro/nasdaq.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">indicated</a> that the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) had accepted BlackRock&#8217;s application for a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF). This is a significant milestone for the Bitcoin-related proposal and may strengthen prices if the regulator eventually approves the derivative, allowing institutions to have exposure. </p>
<p>Presently, Bitcoin is teetering close to $30,000 and looks weak. Bulls have been unable to close above $32,000 despite BlackRock&#8217;s reapplication of the spot Bitcoin ETF.
</p>

<p>BlackRock is the world&#8217;s largest asset manager, with over $9.4 trillion in assets. The firm filed for its first spot Bitcoin ETF in June, only for changes to the made and the application to be updated before being resubmitted.</p>
<p>It remains to be seen if the approval of an ETF marks the bottom for Bitcoin and the nascent asset class.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-ETF-SEC-Hash-Rate-BlackRock-460x260.jpg" width="460" height="260" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chainlink Price Pattern Formation: What It Means For Its Price Action</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/chainlink/chainlink-recent-pattern-formation-what-it-means-for-its-price-movement/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Chainlink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chainlink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Link]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LINKUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[linkusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543251</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In recent trading sessions, Chainlink (LINK) has exhibited a bullish trend. It experienced a significant rebound from its $5 support level and has since continued on an upward trajectory. Related Reading: Litecoin Whales Deposit Big To Exchanges, Bearish Sign? Over the past week, LINK has surged more than 12%, although its daily chart indicates a slowdown in gains. The coin formed a bullish reversal pattern, driving a substantial price surge. The technical outlook for LINK reflects bullish strength, albeit with a slight decline in demand and accumulation on the chart. In recent trading sessions, LINK has formed a pattern that suggests a potential reversal in price direction. To prevent this reversal, it is crucial for LINK to maintain its upward movement and surpass immediate resistance levels. Additionally, a slight decline in market capitalization indicates a decrease in buying strength. Chainlink Price Analysis: One-Day Chart At the time of writing, Chainlink (LINK) was trading at $6.90. The coin has demonstrated significant bullish strength following its recent reversal from the $5 level, driven by the formation of an inverted head and shoulders pattern in the last week. However, despite the upward surge, LINK may encounter resistance around the $7.30 mark, which has historically acted as a strong ceiling for the coin. This resistance is further supported by the formation of a double-top pattern (marked in red), which is considered a bearish signal. As a result, there is a possibility that LINK may experience a decline towards the local support level of $6.60 and potentially even further to $5.80 before attempting a recovery once again. Technical Analysis During the formation of the double-top pattern, there was a notable decline in buying strength, suggesting an impending bearish price movement. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) indicated a bearish divergence, indicating a decrease in demand. Although the RSI remained above the half-line, readings indicated a fading buying strength. Despite this, LINK has managed to stay above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, indicating that buyers still have control over price momentum. However, if there is a drop from the current price level, it could lead to LINK falling below the 20-SMA (red), which could bring sellers back into the market. On the one-day chart, the altcoin has exhibited buy signals, although these signals have been experiencing a slight decline. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicator, which reflects price momentum and trend reversals, has formed declining green histograms, suggesting a potential decrease in buy signals. Related Reading: This Under-The-Radar Coin Just Beat The Top 100 Cryptocurrencies With 120% Explosion Additionally, the Bollinger Bands, which indicate volatility, are wide open, indicating the potential for significant price volatility in the upcoming trading sessions. Featured image from UnSplash, charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In recent trading sessions, Chainlink (LINK) has exhibited a bullish trend. It experienced a significant rebound from its $5 support level and has since continued on an upward trajectory.</p>

<p>Over the past week, LINK has surged more than 12%, although its daily chart indicates a slowdown in gains. The coin formed a bullish reversal pattern, driving a substantial price surge.</p>
<p>The technical outlook for LINK reflects bullish strength, albeit with a slight decline in demand and accumulation on the chart. In recent trading sessions, LINK has formed a pattern that suggests a potential reversal in price direction.</p>
<p>To prevent this reversal, it is crucial for LINK to maintain its upward movement and surpass immediate resistance levels. Additionally, a slight decline in market capitalization indicates a decrease in buying strength.</p>
<h2>Chainlink Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-543253 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSDT_2023-07-19_00-02-52.png" alt="Chainlink" width="1817" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSDT_2023-07-19_00-02-52.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSDT_2023-07-19_00-02-52-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSDT_2023-07-19_00-02-52-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSDT_2023-07-19_00-02-52-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSDT_2023-07-19_00-02-52-1536x702.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSDT_2023-07-19_00-02-52-750x343.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSDT_2023-07-19_00-02-52-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>At the time of writing, Chainlink (LINK) was trading at $6.90. The coin has demonstrated significant bullish strength following its recent reversal from the $5 level, driven by the formation of an inverted head and shoulders pattern in the last week.</p>
<p>However, despite the upward surge, LINK may encounter resistance around the $7.30 mark, which has historically acted as a strong ceiling for the coin.</p>
<p>This resistance is further supported by the formation of a double-top pattern (marked in red), which is considered a bearish signal.</p>
<p>As a result, there is a possibility that LINK may experience a decline towards the local support level of $6.60 and potentially even further to $5.80 before attempting a recovery once again.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-543257 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSDT_2023-07-19_00-03-31.png" alt="Chainlink" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSDT_2023-07-19_00-03-31.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSDT_2023-07-19_00-03-31-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSDT_2023-07-19_00-03-31-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSDT_2023-07-19_00-03-31-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSDT_2023-07-19_00-03-31-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSDT_2023-07-19_00-03-31-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSDT_2023-07-19_00-03-31-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>During the formation of the double-top pattern, there was a notable decline in buying strength, suggesting an impending bearish price movement. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) indicated a bearish divergence, indicating a decrease in demand.</p>
<p>Although the RSI remained above the half-line, readings indicated a fading buying strength. Despite this, LINK has managed to stay above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, indicating that buyers still have control over price momentum.</p>
<p>However, if there is a drop from the current price level, it could lead to LINK falling below the 20-SMA (red), which could bring sellers back into the market.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-543261 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSDT_2023-07-19_00-04-05.png" alt="Chainlink" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSDT_2023-07-19_00-04-05.png 1817w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSDT_2023-07-19_00-04-05-460x188.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSDT_2023-07-19_00-04-05-860x352.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSDT_2023-07-19_00-04-05-768x314.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSDT_2023-07-19_00-04-05-1536x628.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSDT_2023-07-19_00-04-05-750x307.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LINKUSDT_2023-07-19_00-04-05-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px"/>
<p>On the one-day chart, the altcoin has exhibited buy signals, although these signals have been experiencing a slight decline.</p>
<p>The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicator, which reflects price momentum and trend reversals, has formed declining green histograms, suggesting a potential decrease in buy signals.</p>

<p>Additionally, the Bollinger Bands, which indicate volatility, are wide open, indicating the potential for significant price volatility in the upcoming trading sessions.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/nick-fewings-_FP7nTmlyJM-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why This Upcoming Event Is Bearish For Axie Infinity (AXS)</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/axs/upcoming-event-is-bearish-for-axie-infinity/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 23:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AXS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Axie Infinity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AXS unlock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AXSUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AXUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Token unlcok]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543144</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Axie Infinity (AXS) continues to be one of the top performers in the market even though the bear market trend. However, an upcoming token unlock event could put an end to the alt coin’s bullish trend given the amount of tokens involved. $21.7 Million In AXS Set To Be Unlock The upcoming Axie Infinity (AXS) token unlock event is the most notable unlock happening this week. Out of the total $27.4 million in tokens set to be unlocked across the space today, AXS unlocks make up the vast majority. Related Reading: Bearish Signal: BNB Open Interest Skyrockets To New Highs According to the token tracking website Token Unlocks, a total of 3.43 million tokens are set to be unlocked in four days on July 22. Going by the current price of AXS tokens at the time of this writing, this translates to $21.55 million in tokens. $21.55 million in AXS tokens set to be unlocked &#124; Source: Token Unlocks This next unlock will see another 2.96% of the total 270 million supply being sent back into circulation. However, unlike its last token unlock held on April 23, the entirety of this token unlock is going toward staking rewards for users of the platform. Will This Affect The Axie Infinity Token Price? The Axie Infinity (AXS) token unlock will no doubt put bearish pressure on the price of the digital asset. This is because the unlock will increase the circulating supply amid declining demand in the market. As such, AXS&#8217;s price could see a decline from July 22. However, it is important to note that as these tokens are only going toward staking, they will likely not hit the market at the same time. Such staggered introduction into the market could mitigate selling pressure, giving the buyers time to garner enough demand to offset the new supply. AXS price at $6.24 &#124; Source: AXSUSD on TradingView.com This is possible though as long as the general crypto market does not succumb to the bear pressure current mounting. If Bitcoin is able to recover above $31,000 once more, then coins like AXS will benefit as market sentiment recovers. Related Reading: Crypto Liquidations Cross $300 Million Amid Massive Market Recovery For now, AXS is still holding steady compared to others in the space. The altcoin is currently changing hands at a price of $6.24, recording a 0.32% decline in the last 24 hours, but seeing 6.86% gains on the 7-day chart. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from Crypto Ticker, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Axie Infinity (AXS) continues to be one of the top performers in the market even though the bear market trend. However, an upcoming token unlock event could put an end to the alt coin’s bullish trend given the amount of tokens involved.</p>
<h2 class="p2">$21.7 Million In AXS Set To Be Unlock</h2>
<p class="p2">The upcoming Axie Infinity (AXS) token unlock event is the most notable unlock happening this week. Out of the total $27.4 million in tokens set to be unlocked across the space today, AXS unlocks make up the vast majority.</p>

<p class="p2">According to the token tracking website <a href="https://token.unlocks.app/axie-infinity" rel="nofollow">Token Unlocks</a>, a total of 3.43 million tokens are set to be unlocked in four days on July 22. Going by the current price of AXS tokens at the time of this writing, this translates to $21.55 million in tokens.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-543194 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-18-at-14.41.51-460x186.png" alt="Axie Infinity (AXS)" width="460" height="186" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-18-at-14.41.51-460x186.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-18-at-14.41.51-860x348.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-18-at-14.41.51-768x310.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-18-at-14.41.51-1536x621.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-18-at-14.41.51-750x303.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-18-at-14.41.51-1140x461.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-18-at-14.41.51.png 1984w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px"/></p>

<p class="p2">This next unlock will see another 2.96% of the total 270 million supply being sent back into circulation. However, unlike its last token unlock held on April 23, the entirety of this token unlock is going toward staking rewards for users of the platform.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Will This Affect The Axie Infinity Token Price?</h2>
<p class="p2">The Axie Infinity (AXS) token unlock will no doubt put bearish pressure on the price of the digital asset. This is because the unlock will increase the circulating supply amid declining demand in the market. As such, AXS&#8217;s price could see a decline from July 22.</p>
<p class="p2">However, it is important to note that as these tokens are only going toward staking, they will likely not hit the market at the same time. Such staggered introduction into the market could mitigate selling pressure, giving the buyers time to garner enough demand to offset the new supply.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/LzAGsIdH/" alt="Axie Infinity (AXS) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>

<p class="p2">This is possible though as long as the general crypto market does not succumb to the bear pressure current mounting. If Bitcoin is able to recover above $31,000 once more, then coins like AXS will benefit as market sentiment recovers.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/crypto-liquidations-cross-300-million/?swcfpc=1">Crypto Liquidations Cross $300 Million Amid Massive Market Recovery</a></p>
<p class="p2">For now, AXS is still holding steady compared to others in the space. The altcoin is currently changing hands at a price of $6.24, recording a 0.32% decline in the last 24 hours, but seeing 6.86% gains on the 7-day chart.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Axie-Infinity-AXS-460x348.jpeg" width="460" height="348" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Dives Deeper Into Metaverse With $54 Million Investment In Futureverse</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/ripple-dives-deeper-into-metaverse-with-54-million-investment-in-futureverse/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 21:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Metaverse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543258</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Futureverse, a metaverse infrastructure and content company, has received a $54 million investment round from Ripple and other investors to create an open, scalable, and interoperable infrastructure within the metaverse industry.  The company plans to roll up 11 metaverse infrastructure and content companies into a collaborative ecosystem, providing essential components for constructing any metaverse application. It also aims to become a leader in an entirely new frontier of Artificial Intelligence (AI) gaming. Ripple Invests Big In Futureverse&#8217;s Vision The firm&#8217;s comprehensive technology includes its Futureverse Platform featuring &#8220;Powered By Futureverse&#8221; tools and products, which it will develop further using the proceeds from the funding round.  Futureverse is using The Root Network, a blockchain, and suite of protocols with ready-made runtimes for building next-generation metaverse apps, games, and experiences. The Root Network is integrated with Ripple&#8217;s XRP Ledger (XRPL) and supports the use of XRP as a gas token, as well as the XLS-20 NFT standard. Futureverse has been making strides in the metaverse industry, with strategic partnerships with renowned organizations such as FIFA, Authentic Brands Group, Mastercard, Wimbledon, and more.  Related Reading: Litecoin Whales Deposit Big To Exchanges, Bearish Sign? The company is run by metaverse pioneer Aaron McDonald, tech and entertainment investor/operator Shara Senderoff, technology and information security expert Marco Brondani, and Futureverse business operator Dan Gillespie. Ripple&#8217;s investment in Futureverse is a significant step towards realizing the potential of the metaverse and creating a seamless, interconnected experience for users. Ripple&#8217;s president, Monica Long, stated that the company is thrilled to contribute to the foundational infrastructure layer and provide real utility to the end users of the open metaverse. The Futureverse founders believe that the metaverse is the next evolution of the internet, defined by immersive convergence and data, wherein users are empowered to own and control their identity, social graph, content, and value online.  With the new Ripple investment, they are confident that the Futureverse Platform will make the content layer interoperable, providing a seamless, interconnected experience for users. In conclusion, Futureverse&#8217;s series A funding round is a significant milestone for the company, with the investment from Ripple and other investors contributing to the company&#8217;s momentum.  Futureverse&#8217;s vision of creating an open, scalable, and interoperable infrastructure within the metaverse industry is becoming a reality, and the company&#8217;s comprehensive technology and strategic partnerships position it as a major player in the metaverse industry. Crypto Giant Adds XRP To Its Roster According to a recent announcement, XRP has been listed on the prestigious Liechtenstein-based LCX Exchange, as of July 18th. The exchange will support three trading pairs for the token, namely XRP/USDC, XRP/EUR, and XRP/LCX. Deposits have been available since the same date and trading will start in Post-Only Mode, with full Trading Mode activated when pairs reach minimum liquidity. LCX Exchange is one of the world&#8217;s most prestigious crypto exchanges, with a reputation for offering top-quality trading services and innovative technology. The exchange&#8217;s support for XRP is a testament to the token&#8217;s credibility and market appeal, as well as its potential to drive growth in the cryptocurrency industry. Related Reading: ARK Invest CEO Says Firm Is Still Bullish On Coinbase Despite Selling COIN Stocks According to the LCX Exchange, the addition of XRP to its platform will provide users with access to one of the most widely used cryptocurrencies in the world, with a market capitalization of over $60 billion. The exchange also noted that XRP&#8217;s low transaction fees, fast settlement times, and broad adoption make it an attractive option for traders and investors. As of the time of writing, XRP continues to maintain its position among the top four cryptocurrencies in the market in terms of market capitalization and trading volume. Over the past 24 hours, the token has experienced a significant surge, increasing by over 5% and trading at $0.7669. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Futureverse, a metaverse infrastructure and content company, has <a href="https://venturebeat.com/metaverse/futureverse-raises-54m-to-marry-ai-and-the-metaverse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">received </a>a $54 million investment round from Ripple and other investors to create an open, scalable, and interoperable infrastructure within the metaverse industry. </p>
<p>The company plans to roll up 11 metaverse infrastructure and content companies into a collaborative ecosystem, providing essential components for constructing any metaverse application. It also aims to become a leader in an entirely new frontier of Artificial Intelligence (AI) gaming.</p>
<h2>Ripple Invests Big In Futureverse&#8217;s Vision</h2>
<p>The firm&#8217;s comprehensive technology includes its Futureverse Platform featuring &#8220;Powered By Futureverse&#8221; tools and products, which it will develop further using the proceeds from the funding round. </p>
<p>Futureverse is using The Root Network, a blockchain, and suite of protocols with ready-made runtimes for building next-generation metaverse apps, games, and experiences. The Root Network is integrated with Ripple&#8217;s XRP Ledger (XRPL) and supports the use of XRP as a gas token, as well as the XLS-20 NFT standard.</p>
<p>Futureverse has been making strides in the metaverse industry, with strategic partnerships with renowned organizations such as FIFA, Authentic Brands Group, Mastercard, Wimbledon, and more. </p>

<p>The company is run by metaverse pioneer Aaron McDonald, tech and entertainment investor/operator Shara Senderoff, technology and information security expert Marco Brondani, and Futureverse business operator Dan Gillespie.</p>
<p>Ripple&#8217;s investment in Futureverse is a significant step towards realizing the potential of the metaverse and creating a seamless, interconnected experience for users. Ripple&#8217;s president, Monica Long, stated that the company is thrilled to contribute to the foundational infrastructure layer and provide real utility to the end users of the open metaverse.</p>
<p>The Futureverse founders believe that the metaverse is the next evolution of the internet, defined by immersive convergence and data, wherein users are empowered to own and control their identity, social graph, content, and value online. </p>
<p>With the new Ripple investment, they are confident that the Futureverse Platform will make the content layer interoperable, providing a seamless, interconnected experience for users.</p>
<p>In conclusion, Futureverse&#8217;s series A funding round is a significant milestone for the company, with the investment from Ripple and other investors contributing to the company&#8217;s momentum. </p>
<p>Futureverse&#8217;s vision of creating an open, scalable, and interoperable infrastructure within the metaverse industry is becoming a reality, and the company&#8217;s comprehensive technology and strategic partnerships position it as a major player in the metaverse industry.</p>
Crypto Giant Adds XRP To Its Roster
<p>According to a recent <a href="https://www.lcx.com/xrp-is-getting-listed-on-the-lcx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announcement</a>, XRP has been listed on the prestigious Liechtenstein-based LCX Exchange, as of July 18th.</p>
<p>The exchange will support three trading pairs for the token, namely XRP/USDC, XRP/EUR, and XRP/LCX. Deposits have been available since the same date and trading will start in Post-Only Mode, with full Trading Mode activated when pairs reach minimum liquidity.</p>
<p>LCX Exchange is one of the world&#8217;s most prestigious crypto exchanges, with a reputation for offering top-quality trading services and innovative technology. The exchange&#8217;s support for XRP is a testament to the token&#8217;s credibility and market appeal, as well as its potential to drive growth in the cryptocurrency industry.</p>

<p>According to the LCX Exchange, the addition of XRP to its platform will provide users with access to one of the most widely used cryptocurrencies in the world, with a market capitalization of over $60 billion. The exchange also noted that XRP&#8217;s low transaction fees, fast settlement times, and broad adoption make it an attractive option for traders and investors.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/chhNE5zq/" alt="Ripple" width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>As of the time of writing, XRP continues to maintain its position among the top four cryptocurrencies in the market in terms of market capitalization and trading volume. Over the past 24 hours, the token has experienced a significant surge, increasing by over 5% and trading at $0.7669.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-471085352-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thodex CEO Sentenced To Prison For Tax Evasion</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/thodex-ceo-sentenced-to-prison-for-tax-evasion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 20:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Farouk Fatih Özer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thodex]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543210</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Farouk Fatih Özer, the former CEO of the now-defunct crypto exchange Thodex, has been sentenced to seven months in jail. The executive was convicted for failing to submit the required documents to Turkey&#8217;s tax board. Related Reading: This Under-The-Radar Coin Just Beat The Top 100 Cryptocurrencies With 120% Explosion Thodex, which was once a prominent crypto exchange in Turkey, experienced an abrupt closure, leading its CEO, Farouk Fatih Özer, to flee to Albania. However, after an Interpol Red Notice was issued, Özer was deported back to Turkey to be held accountable for the approximately $2 billion worth of cryptocurrencies belonging to investors. Özer, along with 21 other defendants, is embroiled in a protracted court case facing charges of alleged fraud, money laundering, and operating a criminal network through Thodex. Throughout the trial, Özer vehemently denied any wrongdoing and asserted that he was not the official representative of Thodex at the time, which made him unable to produce the requested books. Former CEO Of Thodex Claims To Have Been &#8220;Framed&#8221; In addition to the aforementioned charges, Özer is also facing accusations of defrauding Thodex investors and is currently awaiting a hearing to address these claims. Despite the allegations, the entrepreneur maintains his innocence and asserts that the defendants have framed him. During Özer&#8217;s first court appearance in June, he denied all charges and claimed to have been framed. He stated, &#8220;I started my company and my company was hacked,&#8221; addressing the court. The legal proceedings against Özer commenced after his failure to adhere to a notification issued on October 30, 2021. The notification requested the submission of documents pertaining to his business. Despite the notification, Özer did not provide the best  requested documents within the designated legal timeframe. Özer&#8217;s claim that a trustee had been assigned to oversee the company in his absence, he was unable to produce the required documents to the Tax Inspection Board. As a result, he was convicted. Initially, the prosecutor in Özer&#8217;s case requested a five-year prison sentence on charges of &#8220;smuggling&#8221; under the Tax Procedure Law. However, the court initially sentenced the crypto entrepreneur to one year and six months of imprisonment. It was subsequently reduced to seven months and 15 days. The reduction in sentences can be attributed to various factors. These included Özer&#8217;s social relations, as well as his overall behaviour and conduct throughout the trial. Related Reading: Litecoin Whales Deposit Big To Exchanges, Bearish Sign? In April 2021, the defunct cryptocurrency exchange platform abruptly halted trading and withdrawal services. This left approximately 391,000 customers with losses amounting to around $2 billion. Following this incident, Turkish police authorities initiated a large-scale investigation into the platform. Featured image from Gearrice, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Farouk Fatih Özer, the former CEO of the now-defunct crypto exchange Thodex, has been <a href="https://www.hurriyetdailynews.com/crypto-boss-sentenced-for-failure-to-submit-documents-184790" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">sentenced</a> to seven months in jail. The executive was convicted for failing to submit the required documents to Turkey&#8217;s tax board.</p>

<p>Thodex, which was once a prominent crypto exchange in Turkey, experienced an abrupt closure, leading its CEO, Farouk Fatih Özer, to flee to Albania.</p>
<p>However, after an Interpol Red Notice was issued, Özer was deported back to Turkey to be held accountable for the approximately $2 billion worth of cryptocurrencies belonging to investors.</p>
<p>Özer, along with 21 other defendants, is embroiled in a protracted court case facing charges of alleged fraud, money laundering, and operating a criminal network through Thodex.</p>
<p>Throughout the trial, Özer vehemently denied any wrongdoing and asserted that he was not the official representative of Thodex at the time, which made him unable to produce the requested books.</p>
<h2>Former CEO Of Thodex Claims To Have Been &#8220;Framed&#8221;</h2>
<p>In addition to the aforementioned charges, Özer is also facing accusations of defrauding Thodex investors and is currently awaiting a hearing to address these claims. Despite the allegations, the entrepreneur maintains his innocence and asserts that the defendants have framed him.</p>
<p>During Özer&#8217;s <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-04-20/ceo-of-collapsed-crypto-exchange-arrested-in-turkey-on-return" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">first</a> court appearance in June, he denied all charges and claimed to have been framed. He stated, &#8220;I started my company and my company was hacked,&#8221; addressing the court.</p>
<p>The legal proceedings against Özer commenced after his failure to adhere to a notification issued on October 30, 2021. The notification requested the submission of documents pertaining to his business. Despite the notification, Özer did not provide the best  requested documents within the designated legal timeframe.</p>
<p>Özer&#8217;s claim that a trustee had been assigned to oversee the company in his absence, he was unable to produce the required documents to the Tax Inspection Board. As a result, he was convicted.</p>
<p>Initially, the prosecutor in Özer&#8217;s case requested a five-year prison sentence on charges of &#8220;smuggling&#8221; under the Tax Procedure Law.</p>
<p>However, the court initially sentenced the crypto entrepreneur to one year and six months of imprisonment. It was subsequently reduced to seven months and 15 days.</p>
<p>The reduction in sentences can be attributed to various factors. These included Özer&#8217;s social relations, as well as his overall behaviour and conduct throughout the trial.</p>

<p>In April 2021, the defunct cryptocurrency exchange platform abruptly halted trading and withdrawal services. This left approximately 391,000 customers with losses amounting to around $2 billion. Following this incident, Turkish police authorities initiated a large-scale investigation into the platform.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-543226 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-18_17-31-59.png" alt="Thodex" width="1818" height="830" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-18_17-31-59.png 1818w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-18_17-31-59-460x210.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-18_17-31-59-860x393.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-18_17-31-59-768x351.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-18_17-31-59-1536x701.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-18_17-31-59-750x342.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TOTAL_2023-07-18_17-31-59-1140x520.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1818px) 100vw, 1818px"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/yeni-proje-2023-07-16t173555-LD7P_cover-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>ARK Invest CEO Says Firm Is Still Bullish On Coinbase Despite Selling COIN Stocks</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/coinbase/ark-invest-ceo-still-bullish-on-coinbase/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 18:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ark invest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cathie Wood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543214</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cathie Wood, the CEO of ARK Investment Management, has reaffirmed her bullish stance on Coinbase, one of the leading cryptocurrency exchanges, despite ARK&#8217;s recent sale of COIN stocks. Wood&#8217;s optimism comes in the wake of Ripple&#8217;s partial victory over the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on July 13. This ruling, while not entirely in favor of Ripple, has been viewed as a positive development for the broader crypto industry, particularly for crypto exchanges. Moreover, Wood&#8217;s confidence aligns with other experts who believe that this ruling could have significant implications for Coinbase and its ongoing legal battles with regulatory authorities. Ripple Court Ruling: A Boost for Crypto Exchanges and Coinbase The recent court ruling in favor of Ripple against the SEC has sparked reactions within the crypto industry. Cathie Wood, along with several industry pundits, has lauded the ruling, recognizing its potential positive impact on Coinbase and other exchanges. Related Reading: 29% Of Bitcoin’s Circulating Supply Is Now Presumed Lost Forever The court found that XRP tokens sold to retail investors on crypto exchanges were not securities, setting a precedent that could favor Coinbase and Binance in their legal disputes with the SEC. Wood, in a video posted on Bloomberg&#8217;s Twitter handle, emphasized that despite receiving a Wells notice in March and facing a lawsuit from the SEC in June, Coinbase&#8217;s share price demonstrated resilience, suggesting the robustness of its stock value. The CEO’s bullish comments come after ARK Investment Management recently sold a significant number of Coinbase shares, with three of its ETFs cashing in on the exchange&#8217;s rally. Despite these sales, Wood&#8217;s bullish outlook on Coinbase remains unshaken.  COIN price sitting at $106.75 &#124; Source: Coinbase Global, Inc. on TradingView.com The cryptocurrency exchange&#8217;s share price, which started the year at $33.60, has surged over 184%, reaching $105.55 at the time of publication. However, while industry players increasingly express optimism toward Coinbase, analysts from Berenberg Capital Markets caution that various regulatory challenges for crypto exchanges are yet to be fully resolved. Regulatory Concerns Linger Despite Coinbase&#8217;s Resilience Despite Coinbase&#8217;s strong performance and Wood&#8217;s optimism, regulatory uncertainties persist within the crypto exchange sector. Berenberg Capital Markets analysts highlight unresolved aspects of crypto exchange regulation, including concerns about Coinbase Earn, a product that offers yield on crypto staking.  The comments made by Judge Analisa Torres raise questions about the potential classification of Coinbase Earn as a security, signaling the need for further clarity in this area.  Related Reading: USDC Market Cap Drops As Redemptions Climb To $1.4 Billion Nevertheless, Wood&#8217;s continued bullish stance on Coinbase following the Ripple court ruling reflects her confidence in the exchange&#8217;s ability to navigate regulatory challenges successfully.  It is also crucial to acknowledge that the evolving regulatory landscape and ongoing legal battles with the SEC require careful monitoring. Achieving clarity and resolution in crypto exchange regulation remains essential to ensure the long-term stability and growth of the industry. Featured image from Bankrate, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cathie Wood, the CEO of ARK Investment Management, has <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/videos/2023-07-17/cathie-wood-on-ark-fund-flows-coinbase-ai-investments-video" rel="nofollow">reaffirmed</a> her bullish stance on Coinbase, one of the leading cryptocurrency exchanges, despite ARK&#8217;s recent sale of COIN stocks. Wood&#8217;s optimism comes in the wake of Ripple&#8217;s partial victory over the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on July 13.</p>
<p>This ruling, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/ripple-victory-against-the-sec-may-be-short-lived/?swcfpc=1">while not entirely in favor of Ripple</a>, has been viewed as a positive development for the broader crypto industry, particularly for crypto exchanges. Moreover, Wood&#8217;s confidence aligns with other experts who believe that this ruling could have significant implications for Coinbase and its ongoing legal battles with regulatory authorities.</p>
<h2>Ripple Court Ruling: A Boost for Crypto Exchanges and Coinbase</h2>
<p>The recent court ruling in favor of Ripple against the SEC has sparked reactions within the crypto industry. Cathie Wood, along with several industry pundits, has lauded the ruling, recognizing its potential positive impact on Coinbase and other exchanges.</p>

<p>The court found that XRP tokens sold to retail investors on crypto exchanges were not securities, setting a precedent that could favor Coinbase and Binance in their legal disputes with the SEC. </p>
<p>Wood, in a video posted on Bloomberg&#8217;s Twitter handle, <a href="https://twitter.com/BloombergTV/status/1681046859563909122" rel="nofollow">emphasized</a> that despite receiving a Wells notice in March and facing a lawsuit from the SEC in June, Coinbase&#8217;s share price demonstrated resilience, suggesting the robustness of its stock value.</p>
<p>The CEO’s bullish comments come after ARK Investment Management recently sold a significant number of Coinbase shares, with three of its ETFs cashing in on the exchange&#8217;s rally. Despite these sales, Wood&#8217;s bullish outlook on Coinbase remains unshaken. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/uIVbaGxS/" alt="Coinbase (COIN) stock price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>

<p>The cryptocurrency exchange&#8217;s share price, which started the year at $33.60, has surged over 184%, reaching $105.55 at the time of publication. However, while industry players increasingly express optimism toward Coinbase, analysts from Berenberg Capital Markets caution that various regulatory challenges for crypto exchanges are yet to be fully resolved.</p>
<h2>Regulatory Concerns Linger Despite Coinbase&#8217;s Resilience</h2>
<p>Despite Coinbase&#8217;s strong performance and Wood&#8217;s optimism, regulatory uncertainties persist within the crypto exchange sector. Berenberg Capital Markets analysts highlight unresolved aspects of crypto exchange regulation, including concerns about <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/why-we-stand-by-staking" rel="nofollow">Coinbase Earn</a>, a product that offers yield on crypto staking. </p>
<p>The comments made by Judge Analisa Torres raise questions about the potential classification of Coinbase Earn as a security, signaling the need for further clarity in this area. </p>

<p>Nevertheless, Wood&#8217;s continued bullish stance on Coinbase following the Ripple court ruling reflects her confidence in the exchange&#8217;s ability to navigate regulatory challenges successfully. </p>
<p>It is also crucial to acknowledge that the evolving regulatory landscape and ongoing legal battles with the SEC require careful monitoring. Achieving clarity and resolution in crypto exchange regulation remains essential to ensure the long-term stability and growth of the industry.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Coinbase-460x259.jpeg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin Whales Deposit Big To Exchanges, Bearish Sign?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/litecoin-whales-deposit-big-to-exchanges-bearish-sign/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 16:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin bearish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin Exchange Inflow]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin Whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc/usd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=543091</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Data shows that Litecoin whales have deposited a large amount of the asset to exchanges during the past day, a sign that may be bearish for LTC. Litecoin Whales Have Made Significant Exchange Inflows In 24 Hours According to data from the cryptocurrency transaction tracker service Whale Alert, several large transfers have taken place on the LTC blockchain during the past day. In total, there have been four such transactions, with the largest of them involving the movement of 500,000 LTC (around $46 million at the time the transfer went through). While the other three interestingly all saw the same number of tokens moving on the network: 78,760 LTC (the USD price fluctuated between each of these transactions, but on average, the stacks were worth $7.2 million at the time of movement). As all these transactions are so large, it&#8217;s possible that whale entities were behind them. The whales are generally influential beings in the market, as they hold very large amounts in their wallets. Thus, their movements are usually something to look out for, as they may precede volatility in the price. Naturally, how the price may be influenced by these humongous investors&#8217; transfers depends on what exactly they wanted to achieve with said transactions. Here are some additional details regarding the largest of today&#8217;s transfers, which may help shed some light on the context surrounding it: Looks like this LTC transfer required a negligible fee to go through &#124; Source: Whale Alert As you can see above, the sending address in the case of this Litecoin transfer was an unknown wallet, meaning that it was unattached to any known centralized platform. Such addresses are usually investors&#8217; personal wallets. The receiving address, on the other hand, was connected to a centralized platform: the cryptocurrency exchange Binance. Transfers like this where coins move from self-custodial wallets to exchanges are called &#8220;exchange inflows.&#8221; Usually, one of the major reasons why holders may deposit their coins to exchanges is for selling-related purposes, so exchange inflows can have bearish effects on the price. Related Reading: Bitcoin Miners Selling Again, Will Price Crash Again? It&#8217;s possible that the whale here also made this deposit with a similar intention. Naturally, if it&#8217;s truly the case, the price could feel visible negative effects from it, considering the scale of the transaction. As for the other three transactions that were all of the exact same scale, two of these transfers were inflows similar to this one, while the remaining one was an outflow. Two of these transfers (both inflows) shared the same sending and receiving addresses, making it likely that the same whale might have been behind the deposits. The outflow&#8217;s receiving address doesn&#8217;t match any of the transactions from today, so it&#8217;s unknown if it&#8217;s related to them. However, it involves the exact same number of coins as the two inflows, so it raises suspicion that the same whale entity may have been behind it after all. Related Reading: Stablecoin Exchange Deposits Remain Low, What Does It Mean For Bitcoin? In any case, one reality continues to stand: there were total net inflows of $53.2 million in the last 24 hours, which can act as a source of significant selling pressure in the market for the cryptocurrency. LTC Price At the time of writing, Litecoin is trading around $91, down 6% in the last week. LTC has slipped down recently &#124; Source: LTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Data shows that Litecoin whales have deposited a large amount of the asset to exchanges during the past day, a sign that may be bearish for LTC.</p>
<h2>Litecoin Whales Have Made Significant Exchange Inflows In 24 Hours</h2>
<p>According to data from the cryptocurrency transaction tracker service <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Whale Alert</a>, several large transfers have taken place on the LTC blockchain during the past day.</p>
<p>In total, there have been four such transactions, with the largest of them involving the movement of 500,000 LTC (around $46 million at the time the transfer went through). While the other three interestingly all saw the same number of tokens moving on the network: 78,760 LTC (the USD price fluctuated between each of these transactions, but on average, the stacks were worth $7.2 million at the time of movement).</p>
<p>As all these transactions are so large, it&#8217;s possible that <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/pepe-sees-sharp-17-surge-but-whale-spoil-party/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">whale</a> entities were behind them. The whales are generally influential beings in the market, as they hold very large amounts in their wallets. Thus, their movements are usually something to look out for, as they may precede volatility in the price.</p>
<p>Naturally, how the price may be influenced by these humongous investors&#8217; transfers depends on what exactly they wanted to achieve with said transactions.</p>
<p>Here are some additional details regarding the largest of today&#8217;s transfers, which may help shed some light on the context surrounding it:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-543125 size-large aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/details-1-860x472.png" alt="Litecoin Whale" width="860" height="472" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/details-1-860x472.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/details-1-460x252.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/details-1-768x421.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/details-1-750x412.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/details-1-1140x626.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/details-1.png 1168w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/></p>

<p>As you can see above, the sending address in the case of this Litecoin transfer was an unknown wallet, meaning that it was unattached to any known centralized platform. Such addresses are usually investors&#8217; personal wallets.</p>
<p>The receiving address, on the other hand, was connected to a centralized platform: the cryptocurrency exchange Binance. Transfers like this where coins move from self-custodial wallets to exchanges are called &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-short-term-holders-exchange-inflows-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">exchange inflows</a>.&#8221;</p>
<p>Usually, one of the major reasons why holders may deposit their coins to exchanges is for selling-related purposes, so exchange inflows can have bearish effects on the price.</p>

<p>It&#8217;s possible that the whale here also made this deposit with a similar intention. Naturally, if it&#8217;s truly the case, the price could feel visible negative effects from it, considering the scale of the transaction.</p>
<p>As for the other three transactions that were all of the exact same scale, two of these transfers were inflows similar to this one, while the remaining one was an <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/binance/not-immune-to-fud-binance-sees-1-5-billion-in-outflows-in-24-hours/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">outflow</a>.</p>
<p>Two of these transfers (both inflows) shared the same sending and receiving addresses, making it likely that the same whale might have been behind the deposits.</p>
<p>The outflow&#8217;s receiving address doesn&#8217;t match any of the transactions from today, so it&#8217;s unknown if it&#8217;s related to them. However, it involves the exact same number of coins as the two inflows, so it raises suspicion that the same whale entity may have been behind it after all.</p>

<p>In any case, one reality continues to stand: there were total net inflows of $53.2 million in the last 24 hours, which can act as a source of significant selling pressure in the market for the cryptocurrency.</p>
<h2>LTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Litecoin is trading around $91, down 6% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Qu6tUykH/" alt="Litecoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/kanchanara-PxGgCR0IZ80-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
