<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 18:35:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Crypto Market Trade Volume Hits Lowest Point Since 2020 Amid Market Turbulence</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/crypto-trade-volume-hits-lowest-point-amid-turbulence/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 19:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[comp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kaiko]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[report]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trueusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541369</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In recent months, the crypto markets have witnessed significant turbulence leading to the lowest quarterly trade volume since 2020. Amid varying economic factors, a bearish perception of investors toward cryptocurrencies and the broader economic climate reflects a dynamic yet challenging landscape. Kaiko, a crypto market data provider, shed light on this development alongside various key industry trends. Despite the lowered trade volumes, the crypto industry concluded the quarter positively, demonstrating resilience. Challenges Faced By TrueUSD And Impact On Crypto Market Prime Trust, the crypto custodian of TrueUSD (TUSD), has encountered financial difficulties, placing the stablecoin under scrutiny. The custodian&#8217;s financial shortfall, amounting to approximately $82 million, led to significant challenges, with customers unable to execute withdrawals. Related Reading: Crypto Market Cap Poised For Breakout: Analyst Predict 23% Upside Potential The challenges also included considerable sales pressure on TrueUSD on decentralized exchanges after the disclosure that True USD&#8217;s present auditing firm is a restructured version of FTX&#8217;s auditor. However, despite the selling pressure on decentralized exchanges, the price of TUSD remained around $0.999. Kaiko revealed that the potential liquidation of Prime Trust&#8217;s holdings could significantly impact the token&#8217;s price due to the holdings&#8217; scale.  Mixed Performances And Emerging Trends In the realm of performance, the second quarter witnessed a drop in the open interest for altcoins. Layer 2 tokens, which had initially reported gains in the first quarter, experienced a reduction ranging from 20% to 40% during Q2, according to Kaiko. On the flip side, DeFi tokens wrapped up the quarter marking a decline of 8%, yet picked up steam in June, largely fueled by the rise of tokens like MakerDAO&#8217;s MKR and Compound&#8217;s COMP. COMP experienced a boost of over 50% as large-scale investors in Binance intensified their purchasing activities. Kaiko further revealed that the Korean won (KRW)-denominated trade volume surpassed USD in the quarter&#8217;s final week, primarily spurred by WAVES and Bitcoin Cash (BCH). The spike in volume was largely attributed to WAVES&#8217; price jump after securing support from DWF Labs, while Bitcoin Cash (BCH) saw a massive rise following its listing on EDX Markets. Related Reading: Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Up 55% Following BlackRock’s ETF Application, EDX Markets Launch Meanwhile, EUR-denominated volume on centralized exchanges recorded a two-year low since the crypto bull run in late 2020. This trend indicates a shift in European market sentiment, adding to the quarter&#8217;s varied developments. Regardless, the crypto market has shown recovery from its bloodbath last year. Over the last 7 months, the crypto market has grown compared to the bearish trend seen all through 2022. Both small caps and Larger crypto assets such as Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) have broken multiple resistance surpassing important levels. Bitcoin has recently traded above $31,000 before retracing below $30,427 at the time of writing. Ethereum, on the other hand, has also surged and trades above the $1,900 mark and now looking to break past the $2,000 region. Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In recent months, the crypto markets have witnessed significant turbulence leading to the lowest quarterly trade volume since 2020. Amid varying economic factors, a bearish perception of investors toward cryptocurrencies and the broader economic climate reflects a dynamic yet challenging landscape.</p>
<p>Kaiko, a crypto market data provider, <a href="https://research.kaiko.com/insights/lowest-quarterly-volume-since-2020" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shed light</a> on this development alongside various key industry trends. Despite the lowered trade volumes, the crypto industry concluded the quarter positively, demonstrating resilience.</p>
<h2>Challenges Faced By TrueUSD And Impact On Crypto Market</h2>
<p>Prime Trust, the crypto custodian of TrueUSD (TUSD), has encountered financial difficulties, placing the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/stablecoin-volumes-stagnant/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">stablecoin</a> under scrutiny. The custodian&#8217;s financial shortfall, amounting to approximately $82 million, led to significant challenges, with customers unable to execute withdrawals.</p>

<p>The challenges also included considerable sales pressure on TrueUSD on decentralized exchanges after the disclosure that True USD&#8217;s present auditing firm is a restructured version of FTX&#8217;s auditor. However, despite the selling pressure on decentralized exchanges, the price of TUSD remained around $0.999.</p>
<p>Kaiko revealed that the potential liquidation of Prime Trust&#8217;s holdings could significantly impact the token&#8217;s price due to the holdings&#8217; scale. </p>
<h2>Mixed Performances And Emerging Trends</h2>
<p>In the realm of performance, the second quarter witnessed a drop in the open interest for altcoins. Layer 2 tokens, which had initially reported gains in the first quarter, experienced a reduction ranging from 20% to 40% during Q2, according to Kaiko.</p>
<p>On the flip side, DeFi tokens wrapped up the quarter marking a decline of 8%, yet picked up steam in June, largely fueled by the rise of tokens like MakerDAO&#8217;s MKR and Compound&#8217;s COMP. <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/compound-comp-surges-nearly-10-in-the-past-day/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">COMP experienced a boost</a> of over 50% as <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/whale-trades-link-and-bnb-for-pepe-and-eth/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">large-scale investors</a> in Binance intensified their purchasing activities.</p>
<p>Kaiko further revealed that the Korean won (KRW)-denominated trade volume surpassed USD in the quarter&#8217;s final week, primarily spurred by WAVES and Bitcoin Cash (BCH). The spike in volume was largely attributed to WAVES&#8217; price jump after securing support from DWF Labs, while <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin-cash/bitcoin-cash-bch-up-55-following-blackrocks-etf-application-edx-markets-launch/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin Cash (BCH) saw a massive rise following its listing on EDX Markets</a>.</p>

<p>Meanwhile, EUR-denominated volume on centralized exchanges recorded a two-year low since the crypto bull run in late 2020. This trend indicates a shift in European market sentiment, adding to the quarter&#8217;s varied developments.</p>
<p>Regardless, the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/crypto-market-cap-poised-for-breakout-analyst-predict-23-upside-potential/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">crypto market</a> has shown recovery from its bloodbath last year. Over the last 7 months, the crypto market has grown compared to the bearish trend seen all through 2022.</p>
<p>Both small caps and Larger crypto assets such as Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) have <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-could-soar-in-next-bull-cycle-predicts-crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">broken multiple resistance</a> surpassing important levels. Bitcoin has recently traded above $31,000 before retracing below $30,427 at the time of writing.</p>
<img decoding="async" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/0jvXJmne/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC)’s price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1556" loading="lazy"/>
<p>Ethereum, on the other hand, has also surged and trades above the $1,900 mark and now looking to break past the $2,000 region.</p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Bitcoin-shorts-460x306.jpeg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Valkyrie Follows In BlackRock’s Footsteps, Refiles For Spot Bitcoin ETF</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/valkyrie-follows-in-blackrocks-footsteps-refiles-for-spot-bitcoin-etf/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 18:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin spot ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[valkyrie]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541375</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The dream of a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) in the US is still yet to become a reality as various investment firms continue to seek approval from the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) despite multiple rejections. In a recent turn of events, Valkyrie, an alternative asset management company specializing in the emerging cryptocurrency sector, refiled its application for a Spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund. Valkyrie Takes Another Swing At Bitcoin ETF Approval In a new 19b-4 form submitted by the Tennessee-based firm, the latest Bitcoin ETF filing includes some key differences that may improve its chances of approval by the SEC. Related Reading: Solana (SOL) Notches 16% Gains On Weekly Chart, Will It Cross $20? For starters, Valkyrie mentions it is now bringing on Coinbase as a partner for market surveillance in support of the fund. The company also mentions that Coinbase had &#8220;executed a term sheet with Nasdaq&#8221; to &#8220;enter into a surveillance-sharing agreement.” Given that Coinbase is the largest cryptocurrency exchange based in the United States, Valkyrie&#8217;s partnership with Coinbase is most likely going to increase the likelihood that the application will be approved. Valkyrie is, however, not new to the BTC business, as the company is majorly focused on bridging the gap between traditional finance and the rapidly evolving digital asset industry. In 2022, the company received approval from the SEC for its Bitcoin Futures Fund.  In 2021, Valkyrie filed for a Spot Bitcoin ETF, but it was outrightly rejected by the SEC for the reason of being too risky for investors for various reasons such as market manipulation. The former application proposed that the fund be listed on NYSE Arca, but now it’s moving to Nasdaq with the ticker symbol $BRRR. BTC price recovers above $30,500 &#124; Source: BTCUSD on Tradingview.com How A Spot BTC ETF Could Impact Crypto Markets Other major players in the investment world have recently filed for their own Spot Bitcoin ETFs with the SEC. Investment companies like BlackRock and Fidelity have refiled their spot Bitcoin application in the past month. This news drove the price of Bitcoin high in late June, crossing over $30,000. Although these applications were previously said by the SEC to be &#8216;inadequate&#8217;, they have now been modified and refiled. Related Reading: Dogecoin Up 5%, But Social Media Talk Remains Low: Santiment With major investment companies entering the fray and refiling their applications, the SEC will likely face mounting pressure to approve a Spot Bitcoin ETF finally. As investors’ demand for digital assets grows, a spot ETF could provide a regulated way to gain exposure to BTC and lead to even more mainstream adoption of cryptocurrencies, especially for institutional investors. If any of these filings are approved, it would be the first Bitcoin spot ETF to win approval in the US and the fund(s) will be able to offer unlimited Bitcoin ETF shares to investors. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The dream of a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) in the US is still yet to become a reality as various investment firms continue to seek approval from the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) despite multiple rejections. In a recent turn of events, Valkyrie, an alternative asset management company specializing in the emerging cryptocurrency sector, <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/valkyrie-is-latest-etf-issuer-to-refile-bitcoin-fund-application-with-sec-1.1941797" rel="nofollow">refiled</a> its application for a Spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund.</p>
<h2>Valkyrie Takes Another Swing At Bitcoin ETF Approval</h2>
<p>In a new 19b-4 form submitted by the Tennessee-based firm, the latest Bitcoin ETF filing includes some key differences that may improve its chances of approval by the SEC.</p>

<p>For starters, Valkyrie mentions it is now bringing on Coinbase as a partner for market surveillance in support of the fund. The company also mentions that Coinbase had &#8220;executed a term sheet with Nasdaq&#8221; to &#8220;enter into a surveillance-sharing agreement.” </p>
<p>Given that Coinbase is the largest cryptocurrency exchange based in the United States, Valkyrie&#8217;s partnership with Coinbase is most likely going to increase the likelihood that the application will be approved.</p>
<p>Valkyrie is, however, not new to the BTC business, as the company is majorly focused on bridging the gap between traditional finance and the rapidly evolving digital asset industry. In 2022, the company received approval from the SEC for its Bitcoin Futures Fund. </p>
<p>In 2021, Valkyrie filed for a Spot Bitcoin ETF, but it was outrightly rejected by the SEC for the reason of being too risky for investors for various reasons such as market manipulation. The former application proposed that the fund be listed on NYSE Arca, but now it’s moving to Nasdaq with the ticker symbol $BRRR.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/iz1YkI1E/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1724"/></p>

<h2>How A Spot BTC ETF Could Impact Crypto Markets</h2>
<p>Other major players in the investment world have recently filed for their own Spot Bitcoin ETFs with the SEC. Investment companies like BlackRock and Fidelity have refiled their spot Bitcoin application in the past month. This news drove the price of Bitcoin high in late June, crossing over $30,000. Although these applications were previously said by the SEC to be &#8216;inadequate&#8217;, they have now been modified and refiled.</p>

<p>With major investment companies entering the fray and refiling their applications, the SEC will likely face mounting pressure to approve a Spot Bitcoin ETF finally. As investors’ demand for digital assets grows, a spot ETF could provide a regulated way to gain exposure to BTC and lead to even more mainstream adoption of cryptocurrencies, especially for institutional investors.</p>
<p>If any of these filings are approved, it would be the first Bitcoin spot ETF to win approval in the US and the fund(s) will be able to offer unlimited Bitcoin ETF shares to investors.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1316231784-460x339.jpg" width="460" height="339" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Up 5%, But Social Media Talk Remains Low: Santiment</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/dogecoin-2/dogecoin-up-5-but-social-media-talk-remains-low-santiment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 17:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin Social Dominance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541292</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dogecoin is up 5% during the past week, but data from Santiment reveals that social media talk around the asset still continues to be low. Interest In Dogecoin Remains Low Despite Surge In Price According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, there haven&#8217;t been many discussions around DOGE on social media recently. The relevant indicator here is &#8220;social dominance,&#8221; which tells us about the percentage of the total discussions happening on social media platforms related to the top 100 assets (by market cap) that involve the topic of Dogecoin. When the value of this metric is high, it means that the DOGE-related talks currently make up a significant part of the discussions involving the wider cryptocurrency market. Such a trend is usually a sign that the interest in the asset is high among the general investor. On the other hand, low values imply that social media users aren&#8217;t talking that much about the meme coin. Naturally, this kind of trend suggests that there is no excitement around the coin in the market at the moment. Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in Dogecoin&#8217;s social dominance over the last few months: Looks like the value of the metric has been relatively low in recent days &#124; Source: Santiment on Twitter As displayed in the above graph, the Dogecoin social dominance has been quite low during the past month. Currently, the indicator&#8217;s value is around 1.4%, which means that DOGE-related discussions make up for just 1.4% of all talks related to the top 100 assets. Related Reading: 75% Of Bitcoin Supply Now In Profit, Will A Drop Happen Here? These recent low values of the metric are particularly notable as the meme coin has observed an increase of about 5% during the last week or so. It would appear that despite this rise, interest in the cryptocurrency hasn&#8217;t particularly shifted one way or the other. In the chart, Santiment has also attached the data for another indicator: the &#8220;Binance funding rate.&#8221; This metric keeps track of the periodic fee that Dogecoin futures traders are exchanging with each other on the Binance platform. From the graph, it&#8217;s visible that this indicator became quite negative a while back, implying that a large number of short contracts piled up. Before long, however, the metric turned back positive as the price observed its latest rally. This timing would suggest that a &#8220;short squeeze&#8221; might have helped with the recent price growth. A short squeeze is an event where a mass liquidation of short contracts takes place at once and ends up providing fuel for an upward price move. Even though this was the largest short squeeze of 2023, it would appear that social media users have remained uninterested in the asset. This may not be all bad for Dogecoin, though, as excessive social media hype usually ends up in a top formation for the meme coin. Related Reading: XRP, Cardano Among Altcoins To Keep An Eye On: Santiment Nonetheless, the indicator still staying as low as it has can be concerning, as a lack of any attention also means that the rally may run out of fuel before too long. DOGE Price At the time of writing, Dogecoin is trading around $0.066, up 5% in the last week. DOGE has seen some rise recently &#124; Source: DOGEUSD on TradingView Featured image from iStock.com, charts from TradingView.com, Santiment.net]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dogecoin is up 5% during the past week, but data from Santiment reveals that social media talk around the asset still continues to be low.</p>
<h2>Interest In Dogecoin Remains Low Despite Surge In Price</h2>
<p>According to data from the on-chain analytics firm <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1676290377832333313" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Santiment</a>, there haven&#8217;t been many discussions around DOGE on social media recently. The relevant indicator here is &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/internet-computer-icp-social-dominance-hits-top-in/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">social dominance</a>,&#8221; which tells us about the percentage of the total discussions happening on social media platforms related to the top 100 assets (by market cap) that involve the topic of Dogecoin.</p>
<p>When the value of this metric is high, it means that the DOGE-related talks currently make up a significant part of the discussions involving the wider cryptocurrency market. Such a trend is usually a sign that the interest in the asset is high among the general investor.</p>
<p>On the other hand, low values imply that social media users aren&#8217;t talking that much about the meme coin. Naturally, this kind of trend suggests that there is no excitement around the coin in the market at the moment.</p>
<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in Dogecoin&#8217;s social dominance over the last few months:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/F0Ngl-YaEAAUwFz?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Dogecoin Social Dominance" width="2856" height="1821"/></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the Dogecoin social dominance has been quite low during the past month. Currently, the indicator&#8217;s value is around 1.4%, which means that DOGE-related discussions make up for just 1.4% of all talks related to the top 100 assets.</p>

<p>These recent low values of the metric are particularly notable as the meme coin has observed an increase of about 5% during the last week or so. It would appear that despite this rise, interest in the cryptocurrency hasn&#8217;t particularly shifted one way or the other.</p>
<p>In the chart, Santiment has also attached the data for another indicator: the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-funding-rates-bitmex-deep-red-why-bullish/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Binance funding rate</a>.&#8221; This metric keeps track of the periodic fee that Dogecoin futures traders are exchanging with each other on the Binance platform.</p>
<p>From the graph, it&#8217;s visible that this indicator became quite negative a while back, implying that a large number of short contracts piled up. Before long, however, the metric turned back positive as the price observed its latest rally.</p>
<p>This timing would suggest that a &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/curve-crv-observes-7-bounce-as-short-squeeze-occurs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">short squeeze</a>&#8221; might have helped with the recent price growth. A short squeeze is an event where a mass liquidation of short contracts takes place at once and ends up providing fuel for an upward price move.</p>
<p>Even though this was the largest short squeeze of 2023, it would appear that social media users have remained uninterested in the asset. This may not be all bad for Dogecoin, though, as excessive social media hype usually ends up in a top formation for the meme coin.</p>

<p>Nonetheless, the indicator still staying as low as it has can be concerning, as a lack of any attention also means that the rally may run out of fuel before too long.</p>
<h2>DOGE Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Dogecoin is trading around $0.066, up 5% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/jVZJFvKL/" alt="Dogecoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="881"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1351825546-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana (SOL) Notches 16% Gains On Weekly Chart, Will It Cross $20?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/solana/solana-sol-notches-16-gains-on-weekly-chart-will-it-cross-20/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kent Glory]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 16:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana ( SOL)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana Bearish Signal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541330</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) has recorded progressive gains in the past week, with its 7-day high at 15.95%. It is currently trading at $18.73 today with slight gains on its price. Although SOL is still 92.61% below its all-time high value of $260, its recent gains in the past week have pushed its price closer to the $20 price level.  SOL Price Outlook This Week Suggests A Bearish Trend SOL is in a sideways trend this week, following positive price action in the last two weeks. It has formed a small red candle on the weekly chart implying that the bears are active this week. Also, SOL is still trading in the lower region of the Donchian Channel (DC), expressing a bearish sentiment. Related Reading: Bitcoin Humpback Wallets Reach ATH, Is BlackRock Behind The Surge? Its Relative Strength Index (RSI) is at 45.60 in the neutral zone between the oversold region of 30 and the overbought region of 70. The RSI indicator reflects the sideways trend this week. SOL&#8217;s Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) is slightly above its signal line and shows convergence which is a bearish signal.  Although the MACD displays a negative value, the Histogram bars are green, signaling a bullish recovery ahead. So if the bulls prevail, SOL will likely move to an uptrend in the coming weeks.  SOL’s Key Support And Resistance Levels SOL is trading at $18.73 after it found critical support at the $15.43 price level weeks ago. This puts the altcoin close to the $19.48 resistance level. A break above the $19.48 resistance level will help to boost its price to reclaim the $20 psychological resistance level. If this happens, SOL will likely rally to the $21.81 resistance level after breaking above $20. However, a price decline below $18 in the short term remains possible due to its bearish outlook on the weekly chart.  Factors Influencing Solana’s Price There are several factors right now that could influence the SOL&#8217;s price. These factors include macroeconomic factors such as inflation and crypto regulation in several areas. Also, utility and adoption are vital factors alongside recent trends and developments in the ecosystem.  Another trend in SOL&#8217;s ecosystem likely influencing its price action this week is its decentralized exchange (DEX) volume. According to a report from the on-chain analytic platform DefiLlama, Solana&#8217;s weekly DEX volume increased to see it rank fifth on the list at press time.  Related Reading: Lido (LDO) Sustains Weekly Run With 16% Gain – What Fuels It? SOL’s DEX volume surged by 84%, and its 24-hour volume rose above $38 million. This increase will likely help to boost its price action in the coming week. However, despite an increase in its total DEX volume, its Total Value Locked (TVL) is stagnant. DefiLlama shows that SOL&#8217;s TVL has been stagnant since its decline in November 2022 following the collapse of FTX. The TVL is currently sitting at $273.26 million, with no notable increase in value despite slight gains in SOL&#8217;s price on the daily chart. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Solana (SOL) has recorded progressive gains in the past week, with its 7-day high at 15.95%. It is currently trading at $18.73 today with slight gains on its price. Although SOL is still 92.61% below its all-time high value of $260, its recent gains in the past week have pushed its price closer to the $20 price level. </p>
<h2>SOL Price Outlook This Week Suggests A Bearish Trend</h2>
<p>SOL is in a sideways trend this week, following positive price action in the last two weeks. It has formed a small red candle on the weekly chart implying that the bears are active this week. Also, SOL is still trading in the lower region of the Donchian Channel (DC), expressing a bearish sentiment.</p>

<p>Its Relative Strength Index (RSI) is at 45.60 in the neutral zone between the oversold region of 30 and the overbought region of 70. The RSI indicator reflects the sideways trend this week.</p>
<p>SOL&#8217;s Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) is slightly above its signal line and shows convergence which is a bearish signal.  Although the MACD displays a negative value, the Histogram bars are green, signaling a bullish recovery ahead. So if the bulls prevail, SOL will likely move to an uptrend in the coming weeks. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ATlGsywK/" alt="SOLUSD price chart" width="980" height="538"/>
<h2>SOL’s Key Support And Resistance Levels</h2>
<p>SOL is trading at $18.73 after it found critical support at the $15.43 price level weeks ago. This puts the altcoin close to the $19.48 resistance level.</p>
<p>A break above the $19.48 resistance level will help to boost its price to reclaim the $20 psychological resistance level. If this happens, SOL will likely rally to the $21.81 resistance level after breaking above $20. However, a price decline below $18 in the short term remains possible due to its bearish outlook on the weekly chart. </p>
Factors Influencing Solana’s Price
<p>There are several factors right now that could influence the SOL&#8217;s price. These factors include macroeconomic factors such as inflation and crypto regulation in several areas. Also, utility and adoption are vital factors alongside recent trends and developments in the ecosystem. </p>
<p>Another trend in SOL&#8217;s ecosystem likely influencing its price action this week is its decentralized exchange (DEX) volume. According to a <a href="https://defillama.com/dexs/chains/solana" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a> from the on-chain analytic platform DefiLlama, Solana&#8217;s weekly DEX volume increased to see it rank fifth on the list at press time. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/lido-ldo-sustains-weekly-run-with-16-gain-what-fuels-it/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Lido (LDO) Sustains Weekly Run With 16% Gain – What Fuels It?</a></p>
<p>SOL’s DEX volume surged by 84%, and its 24-hour volume rose above $38 million. This increase will likely help to boost its price action in the coming week.</p>
<p>However, despite an increase in its total DEX volume, its Total Value Locked (TVL) is stagnant. DefiLlama shows that SOL&#8217;s TVL has been stagnant since its decline in November 2022 following the collapse of FTX.</p>
<p>The TVL is currently sitting at $273.26 million, with no notable increase in value despite slight gains in SOL&#8217;s price on the daily chart.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Solana-460x305.jpg" width="460" height="305" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Analyst Says XRP Will Reach $100, Here’s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/analyst-says-xrp-will-reach-100-heres-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 15:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP burn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541348</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[XRP, one of the prominent cryptocurrencies in the market, has witnessed a remarkable surge in its daily burn rate, sparking speculation about its potential to go on a bull rally. Crypto analyst and influencer 24HRSCRYPTO is one of those who have put forward an extremely optimistic outlook for the XRP cryptocurrency. The analyst says that the altcoin, which is currently trading below $1, will reach as high as $100, and has provided reasons. XRP&#8217;s Daily Burn Rate Surges, Fueling Speculation of $100 Token Value 24HRSCRYPTO unveiled an astonishing increase in XRP&#8217;s burn rate through a series of tweets that captivated the attention of the XRP community. Related Reading: Bitcoin Humpback Wallets Reach ATH, Is BlackRock Behind The Surge? The surge in XRP&#8217;s daily burn rate has been a topic of great interest within the crypto community. Just a month ago, the total supply of XRP stood at 99,988,863,851. However, it has now dropped to 99,988,616,835, indicating a reduction of 247,016 XRP.  🚨 THIS IS HUGE! MASSIVE SPIKE IN DAILY BURN RATE 🚨 30 days ago, #XRP&#8216;s total supply was 99,988,863,851 👉🏻today the total supply is 99,988,616,835 (247,016 XRP burned and gone forever in 30days) about 8,233 a day &#8211; which goes perfectly with the below 24HR burn rate. That number… https://t.co/OipXjajMnx — 𝟸𝟺𝙷𝚁𝚂𝙲𝚁𝚈𝙿𝚃𝙾 (@24hrscrypto1) July 4, 2023 With the total supply of XRP decreasing by 247,016 over the course of just 30 days, equivalent to an average of approximately 8,233 XRP burned per day, the stage is set for a potential upward trend that could lead to a significant appreciation in XRP&#8217;s value. In comparison to the figures observed in previous months, the recent 247,016 burned XRP represents a significant increase. This development has prompted crypto enthusiasts to question the potential for further growth and whether it could drive XRP&#8217;s value to unprecedented heights. The increased burn rate and the subsequent reduction in XRP&#8217;s supply have sparked a wave of excitement among investors. It suggests the possibility of a bullish trend, with the burn rate potentially rising even further as trillions of dollars flow into the crypto market. XRP price trending above $0.47 &#124; Source: XRPUSD on TradingView.com Senior Ripple Engineer Shares Insight A deeper dive into the factors driving the heightened burn rate reveals valuable insights as a Software engineer at Ripple, Neil Hartner, shed light on the situation, attributing the surge to the deletion of XRPL accounts as a deleted account equals two XRP burned. Hartner specifically highlighted Poloniex, a leading crypto exchange, which recently deleted a staggering 85,566 outdated XRPL accounts. This action alone contributed to the burning of 171,132 XRP. As the burn rate accelerates and the supply of XRP dwindles, the prospect of XRP reaching $100 per token gains traction.  While some skeptics may question the validity of such a bold claim, the consistent upward trend in the burn rate provides a compelling argument if it continues at such a scale.  Related Reading: Zilliqa (ZIL) Notches 10% In Anticipation Of Network Upgrade The continuous rise in the burn rate and the deletion of XRPL accounts by prominent exchanges reflect the evolving landscape of the crypto market. Investors and enthusiasts are closely monitoring these trends, eagerly anticipating the future value of XRP and the potential rewards it may bring. Amidst these developments, XRP&#8217;s current trading price stands at $0.4883, with a market valuation exceeding $25.5 billion.  Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>XRP, one of the prominent cryptocurrencies in the market, has witnessed a remarkable surge in its daily burn rate, sparking speculation about its potential to go on a bull rally.</p>
<p>Crypto analyst and influencer 24HRSCRYPTO is one of those who have put forward an extremely optimistic outlook for the XRP cryptocurrency. The analyst says that the altcoin, which is currently trading below $1, will reach as high as $100, and has provided reasons.</p>
<h2>XRP&#8217;s Daily Burn Rate Surges, Fueling Speculation of $100 Token Value</h2>
<p>24HRSCRYPTO unveiled an astonishing increase in XRP&#8217;s burn rate through a series of <a href="https://twitter.com/24hrscrypto1/status/1676363256057974784" rel="nofollow">tweets</a> that captivated the attention of the XRP community.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-humpback-wallets-ath-blackrock-behind-surge/?swcfpc=1">Bitcoin Humpback Wallets Reach ATH, Is BlackRock Behind The Surge?</a></p>
<p>The surge in XRP&#8217;s daily burn rate has been a topic of great interest within the crypto community. Just a month ago, the total supply of XRP stood at 99,988,863,851. However, it has now dropped to 99,988,616,835, indicating a reduction of 247,016 XRP. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> THIS IS HUGE! MASSIVE SPIKE IN DAILY BURN RATE <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 30 days ago, <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/XRP?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#XRP</a>&#8216;s total supply was 99,988,863,851 <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f449-1f3fb.png" alt="👉🏻" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />today the total supply is 99,988,616,835 (247,016 XRP burned and gone forever in 30days) about 8,233 a day &#8211; which goes perfectly with the below 24HR burn rate. That number… <a href="https://t.co/OipXjajMnx" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/OipXjajMnx</a></p>
<p>— 𝟸𝟺𝙷𝚁𝚂𝙲𝚁𝚈𝙿𝚃𝙾 (@24hrscrypto1) <a href="https://twitter.com/24hrscrypto1/status/1676363256057974784?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 4, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>With the total supply of XRP decreasing by 247,016 over the course of just 30 days, equivalent to an average of approximately 8,233 XRP burned per day, the stage is set for a potential upward trend that could lead to a significant appreciation in XRP&#8217;s value.</p>
<p>In comparison to the figures observed in previous months, the recent 247,016 burned XRP represents a significant increase. This development has prompted crypto enthusiasts to question the potential for further growth and whether it could drive XRP&#8217;s value to unprecedented heights.</p>
<p>The increased burn rate and the subsequent reduction in XRP&#8217;s supply have sparked a wave of excitement among investors. It suggests the possibility of a bullish trend, with the burn rate potentially rising even further as trillions of dollars flow into the crypto market.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/AWiDw3O6/" alt="XRP price chart from TradingView.com" width="2884" height="1724"/></p>

<h2>Senior Ripple Engineer Shares Insight</h2>
<p>A deeper dive into the factors driving the heightened burn rate reveals valuable insights as a Software engineer at Ripple, Neil Hartner, shed light on the situation, attributing the surge to the deletion of XRPL accounts as a deleted account equals two XRP burned.</p>
<p>Hartner specifically highlighted Poloniex, a leading crypto exchange, which recently deleted a staggering 85,566 outdated XRPL accounts. This action alone contributed to the burning of 171,132 XRP.</p>
<p>As the burn rate accelerates and the supply of XRP dwindles, the prospect of XRP reaching $100 per token gains traction. </p>
<p>While some skeptics may question the validity of such a bold claim, the consistent upward trend in the burn rate provides a compelling argument if it continues at such a scale. </p>

<p>The continuous rise in the burn rate and the deletion of XRPL accounts by prominent exchanges reflect the evolving landscape of the crypto market. Investors and enthusiasts are closely monitoring these trends, eagerly anticipating the future value of XRP and the potential rewards it may bring.</p>
<p>Amidst these developments, XRP&#8217;s current trading price stands at $0.4883, with a market valuation exceeding $25.5 billion. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1436037805-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>AAVE Records 26% Weekly Gain, Looks To Break Key Resistance</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/aave/aave-records-26-weekly-gain-looks-to-break-key-resistance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Aave]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[aave]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AAVE Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AAVEUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541326</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[AAVE, one of the most prominent DeFi tokens, has made a bright start to July. The coin is experiencing a price rally, jumping by more than 26% in the past week. Overall, the AAVE market seems to be enjoying much attention as shown by recent high whale activity.  AAVE Aims For $90 Again &#8211; Price Action  AAVE has been on a positive run in the past few weeks. Since reaching a yearly low of $50 in mid-June, the token has been on a bullish course, which has seen its value rise by over 53%. Related Reading: Lido (LDO) Sustains Weekly Run With 16% Gain – What Fuels It? It is worth noting that the price of AAVE declined for a few days after touching the $75 mark on June 26. This fall caused the token to shed most of its price gain at the time. However, the DeFi token appears to have fully recovered from this loss, with its yearly high of $91.73 now in sight.  According to historical price data, there seems to be resistance at the $80 price zone. So the AAVE token would need to overcome this barrier in order to make its way to $90 again. If the coin fails to break this threshold, it could experience a slight retracement to find support at the $70 price level. CoinGecko data shows that AAVE currently trades at $75.81, losing more than 2% of its value in the past 24 hours. This signals a waning buying pressure, which could hamper the token’s chance of breaking the $80 resistance zone. AAVEUSD trading at $74.25 &#124; Source: AAVEUSD chart from TradingView Aave Freezes TUSD Reserve on V2 Ethereum Pool On July 3, 2023, the Aave community executed a proposal to freeze the TrueUSD (TUSD) reserve on the Aave V2 Ethereum pool. This comes in response to the recent controversy surrounding the stablecoin. This proposal will prevent users from depositing or borrowing TUSD on the Aave V2 Ethereum pool. “This AIP (Aave Improvement Proposal) is designed to take a conservative approach to the TUSD situation,” the proposal read. Related Reading: Aptos (APT) Gains By 10% Ahead Of July Token Release TUSD jitters started after its technology partner Prime Trust was rumored to have gone bankrupt. These issues were compounded when the embattled Fintech company shut off withdrawals and deposits due to pressure from Nevada state regulators. Although TrueUSD has halted the minting of its stablecoin via Prime Trust, there is still some uncertainty surrounding the use of its assets. And losing its dollar peg in the month of June didn&#8217;t help its case. This AIP to freeze TUSD reserves received overwhelming support, as nearly 84% of voters approved it. However, it is worth noting that users will still be able to repay and withdraw their TUSD from the stablecoin pool. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>AAVE, one of the most prominent DeFi tokens, has made a bright start to July. The coin is experiencing a price rally, jumping by more than 26% in the past week. Overall, the AAVE market seems to be enjoying much attention as shown by <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1676497038501101568?s=46&amp;t=24gHStMTZFDI48EGLNmngQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">recent high whale activity</a>. </p>
<h2>AAVE Aims For $90 Again &#8211; Price Action </h2>
<p>AAVE has been on a positive run in the past few weeks. Since reaching a yearly low of $50 in mid-June, the token has been on a bullish course, which has seen its value rise by over 53%.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/lido-ldo-sustains-weekly-run-with-16-gain-what-fuels-it/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Lido (LDO) Sustains Weekly Run With 16% Gain – What Fuels It?</a></p>
<p>It is worth noting that the price of AAVE declined for a few days after touching the $75 mark on June 26. This fall caused the token to shed most of its price gain at the time. However, the DeFi token appears to have fully recovered from this loss, with its yearly high of $91.73 now in sight. </p>
<p>According to historical price data, there seems to be resistance at the $80 price zone. So the AAVE token would need to overcome this barrier in order to make its way to $90 again. If the coin fails to break this threshold, it could experience a slight retracement to find support at the $70 price level.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/aave" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko data</a> shows that AAVE currently trades at $75.81, losing more than 2% of its value in the past 24 hours. This signals a waning buying pressure, which could hamper the token’s chance of breaking the $80 resistance zone.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/7X4ZIprv/" alt="AAVE" width="997" height="586"/></p>

<h2>Aave Freezes TUSD Reserve on V2 Ethereum Pool</h2>
<p>On July 3, 2023, the Aave community executed a proposal to freeze the TrueUSD (TUSD) reserve on the Aave V2 Ethereum pool. This comes in response to the recent controversy surrounding the stablecoin.</p>
<p>This <a href="https://app.aave.com/governance/proposal/?proposalId=253" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">proposal</a> will prevent users from depositing or borrowing TUSD on the Aave V2 Ethereum pool. “This AIP (Aave Improvement Proposal) is designed to take a conservative approach to the TUSD situation,” the proposal read.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/aptos-apt/aptos-apt-gains-by-10-ahead-of-july-token-release/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Aptos (APT) Gains By 10% Ahead Of July Token Release</a></p>
<p>TUSD jitters started after its technology partner Prime Trust was rumored to have gone bankrupt. These issues were compounded when the embattled Fintech company <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/nevada-regulators-order-prime-trust-to-shut-down/amp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shut off withdrawals and deposits</a> due to pressure from Nevada state regulators.</p>
<p>Although TrueUSD has halted the minting of its stablecoin via Prime Trust, there is still some <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/tusd-depegs-doubts-backing-crypto-drama/amp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">uncertainty</a> surrounding the use of its assets. And losing its dollar peg in the month of June didn&#8217;t help its case.</p>
<p>This AIP to freeze TUSD reserves received overwhelming support, as nearly 84% of voters approved it. However, it is worth noting that users will still be able to repay and withdraw their TUSD from the stablecoin pool.</p>



]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/mike-hindle-xl_MQrtiuvg-unsplash-1-1536x1024-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zilliqa (ZIL) Notches 10% In Anticipation Of Network Upgrade</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/zilliqa-zil-notches-10-in-anticipation-of-network-upgrade/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 13:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Network Upgrade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ZIL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zilliqa]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541311</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The ZIL token has seen a jump in its price over the last day in anticipation of the latest Zilliqa network upgrade. According to data by CoinMarketCap, ZIL has now gained 10.13% in the last 24 hours, emerging as the top gainer of the day.  Zilliqa Network Upgrade Now Underway According to a tweet by Zilliqa&#8217;s official Twitter handle, its mainnet network upgrade v9.2 has commenced today, July 5, as scheduled.  This network upgrade is expected to introduce vital improvements to the Zilliqa network, most notably increased interoperability between the Scilla &#8211; the platform&#8217;s customized smart contract language &#8211; and the Ethereum Virtual Machine.  Related Reading: Stablecoins Volume Down Despite Crypto Market Recovery, Ratings Agency Finds Furthermore, the upgrade will look to augment Zilliqa&#8217;s security and functionality by extending support for third-party EVM contracts and implementing full backward compatibility with all existing Scilla (v0.13.3) contracts.  That said, as the Zilliqa network upgrade got closer, its native token, ZIL, has experienced significant buying pressure in the last few days.  Most notably, in the early hours of today, ZIL gained by 11% moving from $0.0222 to hit a price of $0.0247 for the first time since the first week of June. Following that price gain, the ZIL token witnessed a slight price loss finding support at the $0.0237 price level and has since remained in that price zone. At the time of writing, Zilliqa (ZIL) is exchanging hands at $0.238, with a 0.10% decrease in the last hour. However, the token’s daily trading volume is up by 189.83% and is valued at $83 million. With a total market cap value of $377 million, Zilliqa is ranked as the 93rd biggest cryptocurrency. Zilliqa’s Price Analysis  Looking at ZIL’s hourly chart, the Relative Strength Index shows the token is descending from the overbought zone indicating the bullish run may be over.  Furthermore, Ziliqa’s Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) is just about crossing the signal line, meaning a potential incoming bearish run is on the horizon. According to chart data, ZIL appears to have encountered a resistance zone at the $0.0250 price mark. If the bulls are able to increase the buying pressure and push ZIL past this barrier, the token is expected to resume its upward price trajectory.  Related Reading: What’s Next For Bitcoin Price? Bulls Aren’t Running Out Of Steam Yet However, a significant level of selling pressure in the market could drive the token’s price as low as $0.0225, which represents its next support level. If this support level falls to hold, ZIL is likely to fall to the price level of $0.02.  Launched in 2019, Zilliqa is a public, permissionless blockchain, equipped with a sharded architecture designed to address the scalability and throughput issues common with most blockchains. ZIL Trading At $0.0228 On The Hourly Chart &#124; Source: ZILUSD Chart On Tradingview.com Featured Image from Binance Academy, Chart from Tradingview.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The ZIL token has seen a jump in its price over the last day in anticipation of the latest Zilliqa network upgrade. According to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/zilliqa/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data by CoinMarketCap</a>, ZIL has now gained 10.13% in the last 24 hours, emerging as the top gainer of the day. </p>
<h2>Zilliqa Network Upgrade Now Underway</h2>
<p>According to a <a href="https://twitter.com/zilliqa/status/1676504385277554689?s=46&amp;t=JAUmthpFclo8jS4VJkm3DQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">tweet</a> by Zilliqa&#8217;s official Twitter handle, its mainnet network upgrade v9.2 has commenced today, July 5, as scheduled.  This<a href="https://blog.zilliqa.com/upcoming-upgrade-of-zilliqa-mainnet-to-v9-2/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> network upgrade</a> is expected to introduce vital improvements to the Zilliqa network, most notably increased interoperability between the Scilla &#8211; the platform&#8217;s customized smart contract language &#8211; and the Ethereum Virtual Machine. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/stablecoin-volumes-stagnant/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Stablecoins Volume Down Despite Crypto Market Recovery, Ratings Agency Finds</a></p>
<p>Furthermore, the upgrade will look to augment Zilliqa&#8217;s security and functionality by extending support for third-party EVM contracts and implementing full backward compatibility with all existing Scilla (v0.13.3) contracts. </p>
<p>That said, as the Zilliqa network upgrade got closer, its native token, ZIL, has experienced significant buying pressure in the last few days. </p>
<p>Most notably, in the early hours of today, ZIL gained by 11% moving from $0.0222 to hit a price of $0.0247 for the first time since the first week of June. Following that price gain, the ZIL token witnessed a slight price loss finding support at the $0.0237 price level and has since remained in that price zone.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, Zilliqa (ZIL) is exchanging hands at $0.238, with a 0.10% decrease in the last hour. However, the token’s daily trading volume is up by 189.83% and is valued at $83 million. With a total market cap value of $377 million, Zilliqa is ranked as the 93rd biggest cryptocurrency.</p>
<h2>Zilliqa’s Price Analysis </h2>
<p>Looking at ZIL’s hourly chart, the Relative Strength Index shows the token is descending from the overbought zone indicating the bullish run may be over. </p>
<p>Furthermore, Ziliqa’s Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) is just about crossing the signal line, meaning a potential incoming bearish run is on the horizon.</p>
<p>According to chart data, ZIL appears to have encountered a resistance zone at the $0.0250 price mark. If the bulls are able to increase the buying pressure and push ZIL past this barrier, the token is expected to resume its upward price trajectory. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-price-bulls-arent-running-out-of-steam/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">What’s Next For Bitcoin Price? Bulls Aren’t Running Out Of Steam Yet</a></p>
<p>However, a significant level of selling pressure in the market could drive the token’s price as low as $0.0225, which represents its next support level. If this support level falls to hold, ZIL is likely to fall to the price level of $0.02. </p>
<p>Launched in 2019, Zilliqa is a public, permissionless blockchain, equipped with a sharded architecture designed to address the scalability and throughput issues common with most blockchains.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/X8uWXTuS/" alt="ZILIQA" width="1479" height="913"/></p>

<p>Featured Image from Binance Academy, Chart from Tradingview.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/97a368a13844484eacf6c991e8db35ff-460x259.png" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mercuryo&#8217;s Big Time Summit in Cyprus: Revolutionizing the FinTech Industry</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/mercuryos-big-time-summit-in-cyprus-revolutionizing-the-fintech-industry/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[NewsBTC]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 12:46:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541338</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The global payments infrastructure platform Mercuryo has announced the launch of Big Time Summit – a FinTech event to be held for the first time in Limassol, Cyprus, on July 7, 2023.  The event will be held with the support of Invest Cyprus, Mercuryo&#8217;s trusted partner. Their team is ready to support businesses during the location selection process and expanding operations in Cyprus.  Offering unparalleled value to professionals in the field, the conference will gather over 400 FinTech thought leaders, and industry innovators from around the globe. In order to put the Big Time Summit together, Mercuryo has partnered with a number of major industry representatives, including names like Binance, Coinbase, TrustWallet, MetaMask, 1inch, and Consensys.  Mercuryo has also struck an exclusive partnership with the international PR firm Drofa Comms for the purposes of providing media support and coverage of the event in global media. Throughout the course of the Summit, a lineup of 20+ keynote speakers will hold panels, roundtables and workshops on the topics relevant to the FinTech sector, discussing what trends and drivers this industry is seeing today. The event will also include plenty of opportunities for networking and an evening party where attendees will be able to engage in conversations of their preference.  The topics to be covered as part of the conference include leveraging blockchain technology in businesses, the latest trends in digital payments, current regulation landscape, and valuable learnings taken from a tumultuous period in the CEX and DEX markets.  Events like Big Time Summit represent a crucial element in the development of the global FinTech stage because they allow numerous participants of this market to interact with peers and industry leaders and exchange experiences. They get to share opinions and insights about the ongoing market agenda, as well as emerging trends and technologies.  “Attending such events is how industry members get to stay up-to-date on all the recent developments, broaden their knowledge base, and contribute to shaping the future of finance worldwide. At Mercuryo, we recognize this and it is our intention to hold more such events in the upcoming years,” – states Petr Kozyakov, CEO of Mercuryo. About Mercuryo Mercuryo is a global payments infrastructure platform, providing businesses from both the fiat and crypto worlds with a wide range of financial services accessible through API integration. Since its inception in 2018, Mercuryo has secured over 200 partners, working with leading industry players to accelerate growth and boost enterprise revenues worldwide. &#160;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="font-weight: 400">The global payments infrastructure platform <a href="https://mercuryo.io/" rel="nofollow">Mercuryo</a> has announced the launch of <a href="https://www.bigtimesummit.com/" rel="nofollow">Big Time Summit</a> – a FinTech event to be held for the first time in Limassol, Cyprus, on July 7, 2023. </p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">The event will be held with the support of <a href="https://www.investcyprus.org.cy/" rel="nofollow">Invest Cyprus</a>, Mercuryo&#8217;s trusted partner. Their team is ready to support businesses during the location selection process and expanding operations in Cyprus. </p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Offering unparalleled value to professionals in the field, the conference will gather over 400 FinTech thought leaders, and industry innovators from around the globe. In order to put the Big Time Summit together, Mercuryo has partnered with a number of major industry representatives, including names like Binance, Coinbase, TrustWallet, MetaMask, 1inch, and Consensys. </p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Mercuryo has also struck an exclusive partnership with the international PR firm <a href="https://drofa-ra.com/" rel="nofollow">Drofa Comms</a> for the purposes of providing media support and coverage of the event in global media.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Throughout the course of the Summit, a lineup of 20+ keynote speakers will hold panels, roundtables and workshops on the topics relevant to the FinTech sector, discussing what trends and drivers this industry is seeing today. The event will also include plenty of opportunities for networking and an evening party where attendees will be able to engage in conversations of their preference. </p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">The topics to be covered as part of the conference include leveraging blockchain technology in businesses, the latest trends in digital payments, current regulation landscape, and valuable learnings taken from a tumultuous period in the CEX and DEX markets. </p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Events like Big Time Summit represent a crucial element in the development of the global FinTech stage because they allow numerous participants of this market to interact with peers and industry leaders and exchange experiences. They get to share opinions and insights about the ongoing market agenda, as well as emerging trends and technologies. </p>
<p style="font-weight: 400"><i>“Attending such events is how industry members get to stay up-to-date on all the recent developments, broaden their knowledge base, and contribute to shaping the future of finance worldwide. At Mercuryo, we recognize this and it is our intention to hold more such events in the upcoming years,”</i> – states Petr Kozyakov, CEO of Mercuryo.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400"><b>About Mercuryo</b></p>
<p style="font-weight: 400"><a href="https://mercuryo.io/" rel="nofollow">Mercuryo</a> is a global payments infrastructure platform, providing businesses from both the fiat and crypto worlds with a wide range of financial services accessible through API integration. Since its inception in 2018, Mercuryo has secured over 200 partners, working with leading industry players to accelerate growth and boost enterprise revenues worldwide.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-05-at-8.45.44-AM-460x257.png" width="460" height="257" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Humpback Wallets Reach ATH, Is BlackRock Behind The Surge?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-humpback-wallets-ath-blackrock-behind-surge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 12:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[glassnode]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humpback]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shrimps]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[whales]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541290</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A recent development has caught the attention of on-chain analysts and Bitcoin enthusiasts alike. On-chain expert Axel Adler Jr, citing data from CryptoQuant, has revealed that wallets belonging to the &#8216;Humpback&#8217; cohort, have reached a new all-time high (ATH). This surge has raised speculation about the involvement of institutional giants such as BlackRock or Fidelity. Remarkably, not only humpback but also shrimps are currently displaying a historical high conviction. The Phenomenon Of Bitcoin Humpback Wallets The term &#8216;Humpback&#8217; refers to a specific cohort of wallets within the cryptocurrency ecosystem that hold an impressive amount of Bitcoin, surpassing the 5,000 BTC mark. The recent surge in these wallets reaching an ATH indicates a significant level of accumulation and activity within the crypto market. Related Reading: What’s Next For Bitcoin Price? Bulls Aren’t Running Out Of Steam Yet According to Axel Adler Jr, &#8220;The number of wallets in the &#8216;Humpback&#8217; cohort with a balance of over 5,000 BTC has shown a new ATH. Is this BlackRock, Fidelity, or other giants?&#8221; The mystery surrounding the identity of these major players has piqued curiosity and speculation about their motivations and impact on the market. From the on-chain data alone, it is not possible to determine which entity commenced the accumulation of BTC. However, the temporal connection with the ETF applications is striking. Regardless of the actual entity, a whale accumulation can be interpreted as a positive sign for the price. In this vein, expert Will Clemente recently stated: Even if Blackrock/Fidelity refile and the ETFs still get rejected by Gary, the cat is out of the bag &#8212; institutions want your Bitcoin and are looking to get a piece of this market. It is worth noting that Bitcoin&#8217;s whale &#38; shark addresses (different cohorts combined, wallets with 10 to 10,000 BTC) have continued to accumulate, with a big chunk of BTC buying coming in the last 2 weeks of June as news of ETF launches came out. On-chain-data provider Santiment tweeted on July 1 that the aforementioned cohorts have accumulated 154,500 BTC in the last week of June alone. &#8216;Shrimps&#8217; Show Crazy Conviction While the activity by Humpback wallets is astonishing another intriguing cohort known as the &#8216;Shrimps&#8217; has also come into focus. Lead analyst of Glassnode, Checkmate highlighted today the enthusiasm displayed by the Shrimp cohort in stacking sats (satoshi, the smallest unit of Bitcoin) at an astonishing rate. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Could See Fresh “Liftoff” if It’s Able to Hold One Key Level He states, &#8220;Bitcoin Shrimp (&#60; 1 $BTC) are stacking sats at a rate of 33.8k $BTC per month. Issuance is ~27.0k $BTC/month. For every 1 new coin, Shrimp are taking 1.25 off the market. Crazy conviction on display.&#8221; The Shrimp cohort, consisting of smaller Bitcoin holders, showcases an incredible conviction and sustained buying behavior despite market fluctuations. As Checkmate points out, &#8220;The last time the little guy stacked this hard was 2017 ATH, buying the top. Five years later, they are stacking harder, faster, and in a more sustained manner, despite all the bullshit. Bullish.&#8221; The simultaneous rise of both the Humpback and Shrimp cohorts signifies a captivating dichotomy within the ecosystem. On one hand, the Humpback wallets, with their massive holdings, hint at the potential involvement of institutional giants like BlackRock or Fidelity. Their accumulation of Bitcoin could serve as a catalyst for increased adoption and market confidence. On the other hand, the resilience and conviction displayed by the Shrimp cohort highlight the broader appeal and democratization of BTC. Despite previous market downturns, the Shrimp class remains undeterred, stacking sats at an unprecedented pace and demonstrating unwavering belief in the long-term potential of Bitcoin. At press time, the BTC price continued to hover below the $31,000 mark, trading at $30,728. Featured image from Thomas Kelley / Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A recent development has caught the attention of on-chain analysts and Bitcoin enthusiasts alike. On-chain expert Axel Adler Jr, citing data from CryptoQuant, has revealed that wallets belonging to the &#8216;Humpback&#8217; cohort, have reached a new all-time high (ATH).</p>
<p>This surge has raised speculation about the involvement of institutional giants such as BlackRock or Fidelity. Remarkably, not only humpback but also shrimps are currently displaying a historical high conviction.</p>
<h2>The Phenomenon Of Bitcoin Humpback Wallets</h2>
<p>The term &#8216;Humpback&#8217; refers to a specific cohort of wallets within the cryptocurrency ecosystem that hold an impressive amount of Bitcoin, surpassing the 5,000 BTC mark. The recent surge in these wallets reaching an ATH indicates a significant level of accumulation and activity within the crypto market.</p>

<p><a href="https://twitter.com/AxelAdlerJr/status/1676196588241182721" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According</a> to Axel Adler Jr, &#8220;The number of wallets in the &#8216;Humpback&#8217; cohort with a balance of over 5,000 BTC has shown a new ATH. Is this BlackRock, Fidelity, or other giants?&#8221; The mystery surrounding the identity of these major players has piqued curiosity and speculation about their motivations and impact on the market.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-541298 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-humpback-whales.jpg" alt="Bitcoin humpback whales" width="2048" height="1290" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-humpback-whales.jpg 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-humpback-whales-460x290.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-humpback-whales-860x542.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-humpback-whales-768x484.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-humpback-whales-1536x968.jpg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-humpback-whales-750x472.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-humpback-whales-1140x718.jpg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2048px) 100vw, 2048px"/>
<p>From the on-chain data alone, it is not possible to determine which entity commenced the accumulation of BTC. However, the temporal connection with the ETF applications is striking. Regardless of the actual entity, a whale accumulation can be interpreted as a positive sign for the price. In this vein, expert Will Clemente recently <a href="https://twitter.com/WClementeIII/status/1674787531324522502" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">stated</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>Even if Blackrock/Fidelity refile and the ETFs still get rejected by Gary, the cat is out of the bag &#8212; institutions want your Bitcoin and are looking to get a piece of this market.</strong></p></blockquote>
<p>It is worth noting that Bitcoin&#8217;s whale &amp; shark addresses (different cohorts combined, wallets with 10 to 10,000 BTC) have continued to accumulate, with a big chunk of BTC buying coming in the last 2 weeks of June as news of ETF launches came out. On-chain-data provider Santiment <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1674921536527171584" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">tweeted</a> on July 1 that the aforementioned cohorts have accumulated 154,500 BTC in the last week of June alone.</p>
<h2>&#8216;Shrimps&#8217; Show Crazy Conviction</h2>
<p>While the activity by Humpback wallets is astonishing another intriguing cohort known as the &#8216;Shrimps&#8217; has also come into focus. Lead analyst of Glassnode, Checkmate <a href="https://twitter.com/_Checkmatey_/status/1676503346688167936" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">highlighted</a> today the enthusiasm displayed by the Shrimp cohort in stacking sats (satoshi, the smallest unit of Bitcoin) at an astonishing rate.</p>

<p>He states, &#8220;Bitcoin Shrimp (&lt; 1 $BTC) are stacking sats at a rate of 33.8k $BTC per month. Issuance is ~27.0k $BTC/month. For every 1 new coin, Shrimp are taking 1.25 off the market. Crazy conviction on display.&#8221;</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-541299 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-shrimps.jpg" alt="Bitcoin shrimps" width="1495" height="861" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-shrimps.jpg 1495w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-shrimps-460x265.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-shrimps-860x495.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-shrimps-768x442.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-shrimps-750x432.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-shrimps-1140x657.jpg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1495px) 100vw, 1495px"/>
<p>The Shrimp cohort, consisting of smaller Bitcoin holders, showcases an incredible conviction and sustained buying behavior despite market fluctuations. As Checkmate points out, &#8220;The last time the little guy stacked this hard was 2017 ATH, buying the top. Five years later, they are stacking harder, faster, and in a more sustained manner, despite all the bullshit. Bullish.&#8221;</p>
<p>The simultaneous rise of both the Humpback and Shrimp cohorts signifies a captivating dichotomy within the ecosystem. On one hand, the Humpback wallets, with their massive holdings, hint at the potential involvement of institutional giants like BlackRock or Fidelity. Their accumulation of Bitcoin could serve as a catalyst for increased adoption and market confidence.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the resilience and conviction displayed by the Shrimp cohort highlight the broader appeal and democratization of BTC. Despite previous market downturns, the Shrimp class remains undeterred, stacking sats at an unprecedented pace and demonstrating unwavering belief in the long-term potential of Bitcoin.</p>
<p>At press time, the BTC price continued to hover below the $31,000 mark, trading at $30,728.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-541301 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-05_11-51-34.png" alt="BTC price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-05_11-51-34.png 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-05_11-51-34-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-05_11-51-34-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-05_11-51-34-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-05_11-51-34-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-05_11-51-34-2048x944.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-05_11-51-34-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-05_11-51-34-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3628px) 100vw, 3628px"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/thomas-kelley-t20pc32VbrU-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lido (LDO) Sustains Weekly Run With 16% Gain &#8211; What Fuels It?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/lido-ldo-sustains-weekly-run-with-16-gain-what-fuels-it/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 10:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LDO price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lido DAO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=541273</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Lido (LDO), a prominent player in the decentralized finance (DeFi) space, has emerged as a frontrunner in the rapidly expanding Liquidity Staking Derivatives (LSD) sector.  Amidst the turbulence caused by the highly controversial lawsuit filed by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in June, the decentralized finance (DeFi) sector has found itself in a state of uncertainty and caution. This legal battle has prompted many projects to reevaluate their strategies and has made investors more cautious in their approach. However, even in this challenging climate, the LSD space has managed to experience substantial growth and defy the odds. LSD Sector&#8217;s Dominance And Lido&#8217;s Remarkable Performance As per data from Messari, the LSD sector has demonstrated significant dominance in the cryptocurrency markets. One of the leading contributors to the sector&#8217;s expansion has been Lido, which has showcased impressive performance over recent months. SEC lawsuits against @BinanceUS and @Coinbase cause #DeFi TVL to plummet below $60B. But amidst the chaos, liquid staking protocols are thriving becoming DeFi&#8217;s dominating force by TVL. pic.twitter.com/RL9Qy8cwLE — Messari (@MessariCrypto) July 3, 2023 CoinGecko reports that currently, the price of Lido&#8217;s native token, LDO, stands at $2.16. While there has been a slight decline of 1.7% in the past 24 hours, the token has experienced a solid 15.7% increase in value during the last seven days. Source: Coingecko The surge in LDO&#8217;s price has also resulted in a noticeable increase in the MVRV ratio of the token. This signifies that a considerable number of addresses holding LDO have become profitable in the past few days, indicating a positive sentiment among investors and further fueling the success of Lido in the competitive DeFi landscape. Growth Amidst Concerns: Lido Declining APR Despite the notable growth and success witnessed by Lido, there has been a recent decline in the Annual Percentage Return (APR) offered by the platform. According to a recent LDO price report, his decline in APR over the past few days raises concerns about the attractiveness of using Lido for staking, potentially leading users to seek alternative options. Source: Dune Analytics The declining APR indicates that the rewards and returns generated from staking LDO tokens on the Lido platform have decreased. This development could discourage some users who prioritize maximizing their staking yields from continuing to use Lido. LDO market cap currently at $1.9 billion. Chart: TradingView.com As staking rewards play a crucial role in incentivizing users to participate in networks and secure their protocols, a sustained decline in APR might prompt individuals to explore alternative platforms that offer more competitive and potentially higher returns. Related Reading: Dwindling Optimism (OP) Value May Be A Result Of This Factor To maintain its position as a leading player in the LSD sector, Lido would need to address the declining APR and explore avenues to enhance the rewards offered to stakers, ensuring they remain competitive and appealing to their user base. Featured image from The Market Periodical]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lido (LDO), a prominent player in the decentralized finance (DeFi) space, has emerged as a frontrunner in the rapidly expanding Liquidity Staking Derivatives (LSD) sector. </p>
<p>Amidst the turbulence caused by the highly controversial lawsuit filed by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in June, the decentralized finance (DeFi) sector has found itself in a state of uncertainty and caution. </p>
<p>This legal battle has prompted many projects to reevaluate their strategies and has made investors more cautious in their approach. However, even in this challenging climate, the LSD space has managed to experience substantial growth and defy the odds.</p>
<h2><strong>LSD Sector&#8217;s Dominance And Lido&#8217;s Remarkable Performance</strong></h2>
<p>As per <a href="https://twitter.com/MessariCrypto/status/1676002897765736448" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from Messari</a>, the LSD sector has demonstrated significant dominance in the cryptocurrency markets. One of the leading contributors to the sector&#8217;s expansion has been Lido, which has showcased impressive performance over recent months.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">SEC lawsuits against <a href="https://twitter.com/BinanceUS?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@BinanceUS</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/coinbase?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@Coinbase</a> cause <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/DeFi?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#DeFi</a> TVL to plummet below $60B. But amidst the chaos, liquid staking protocols are thriving becoming DeFi&#8217;s dominating force by TVL. <a href="https://t.co/RL9Qy8cwLE" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/RL9Qy8cwLE</a></p>
<p>— Messari (@MessariCrypto) <a href="https://twitter.com/MessariCrypto/status/1676002897765736448?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 3, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/lido-dao" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a> reports that currently, the price of Lido&#8217;s native token, LDO, stands at $2.16. While there has been a slight decline of 1.7% in the past 24 hours, the token has experienced a solid 15.7% increase in value during the last seven days.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-541275" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-26.png" alt="" width="1134" height="63" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-26.png 1134w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-26-460x26.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-26-860x48.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-26-768x43.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-26-750x42.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1134px) 100vw, 1134px"/></p>

<p>The surge in LDO&#8217;s price has also resulted in a noticeable increase in the MVRV ratio of the token. This signifies that a considerable number of addresses holding LDO have become profitable in the past few days, indicating a positive sentiment among investors and further fueling the success of Lido in the competitive DeFi landscape.</p>
<h2><strong>Growth Amidst Concerns: Lido Declining APR</strong></h2>
<p>Despite the notable growth and success witnessed by Lido, there has been a recent decline in the Annual Percentage Return (APR) offered by the platform. According to a recent LDO price report, his decline in APR over the past few days raises concerns about the attractiveness of using Lido for staking, potentially leading users to seek alternative options.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-541278" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-27.png" alt="" width="718" height="286" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-27.png 718w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-27-460x183.png 460w" sizes="(max-width: 718px) 100vw, 718px"/></p>

<p>The declining APR indicates that the rewards and returns generated from staking LDO tokens on the Lido platform have decreased. This development could discourage some users who prioritize maximizing their staking yields from continuing to use Lido.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/nGcvl4vM/" width="2315" height="1109"/></p>

<p>As staking rewards play a crucial role in incentivizing users to participate in networks and secure their protocols, a sustained decline in APR might prompt individuals to explore alternative platforms that offer more competitive and potentially higher returns.</p>

<p>To maintain its position as a leading player in the LSD sector, Lido would need to address the declining APR and explore avenues to enhance the rewards offered to stakers, ensuring they remain competitive and appealing to their user base.</p>
<p><em>Featured image from The Market Periodical</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/a-28-460x230.png" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
