<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"

	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 16:31:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">221170450</site>	<item>
		<title>Crypto Funds Vs Bitcoin Holders: Who Was The Better Performer In H1 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/crypto-funds-vs-bitcoin-holders/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 23:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Holders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin performance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto funds]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto hedge funds]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545922</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A new report has shown investors who held Bitcoin actually outperformed most cryptocurrency funds in the first half of 2023. This is because, between January and June, Bitcoin gained over 80% in value.  Crypto funds, on the other hand, on the other hand, returned only about 15.2% profits on average. While still a positive return, it lagged far behind what regular Bitcoin investors made by just buying and sitting tight.  21e6 Capital’s Crypto Fund Performance in H1 2023 According to a recently released report from Switzerland-based investment adviser 21e6 Capital AG, Bitcoin traders outperformed most crypto funds by 68.8% in H1. Related Reading: Binance Celebrates Significant Milestone After Six Years In Operation This is not surprising, as BTC was one of the best-performing crypto assets in the first half of 2023, seeing massive gains from prospects of the SEC approving a Spot Bitcoin ETF. The price of Bitcoin started the year around $15,500 and climbed to over $31,400 in July. Crypto funds on average generated 15.2% return in the first half of 2023 lol pic.twitter.com/vb8pwYfiX9 — Alex Krüger (@krugermacro) August 5, 2023 Bitcoin outperforming crypto funds is relatively new, as crypto hedge funds are frequently able to outperform the BTC benchmark in the past significantly. But the crypto industry ended 2022 with more of a gloomy sentiment, as the market witnessed regulatory uncertainties and the collapse of FTX and Terra.  This seems to have caused crypto hedge funds to take a safer approach, leaving them with larger-than-normal cash positions. When crypto is hot, that cash doesn’t appreciate like BTC would unless the funds’ assets perform significantly better than Bitcoin. The report also noted that directional crypto funds generally outperformed non-directional crypto funds. Non-directional funds, like arbitrage, lending, and staking, do not depend on the market&#8217;s direction. BTC price holds at $29,000 &#124; Source: BTCUSD on Tradingview.com Outlook for Second Half of 2023: More Gains Ahead for Bitcoin? 21e6 Capital’s latest report shows the general sentiment of the crypto market. Crypto funds had a rough first half of 2023, with many closing down early this year. About 13% of crypto hedge funds shut this year, as a few of them have struggled to present a favorable value proposition to potential investors. Related Reading: Ethereum ETF Race Gets Hotter As SEC Receives 11 Filings In One Week The price of Bitcoin seems to be struggling to break over $30,000, but the outlook for Bitcoin in the second half of 2023 still looks positive. If approved, the price of Bitcoin is expected to spike further in the coming months as major investment companies start to offer Spot Bitcoin ETFs. This influx of capital could spark a fresh bull market for all cryptocurrencies, leading to further gains for BTC holders. This new volume could see the price of BTC rise above $30,000 once more. At the time of writing, BTC is trading at $29,043. Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new report has shown investors who held Bitcoin actually outperformed most cryptocurrency funds in the first half of 2023. This is because, between January and June, Bitcoin gained over 80% in value. </p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/dormant-bitcoin-supply-peaks-as-institutional-investors/">Crypto funds</a>, on the other hand, on the other hand, returned only about 15.2% profits on average. While still a positive return, it lagged far behind what regular Bitcoin investors made by just buying and sitting tight. </p>
<h2>21e6 Capital’s Crypto Fund Performance in H1 2023</h2>
<p>According to a recently released <a href="https://assets.21e6.io/blog/half-year-review-2023" rel="nofollow">report </a>from Switzerland-based investment adviser 21e6 Capital AG, Bitcoin traders outperformed most crypto funds by 68.8% in H1.</p>

<p>This is not surprising, as BTC was one of the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/institutional-investors-flock-to-bitcoin-paradigm-shift/">best-performing crypto assets</a> in the first half of 2023, seeing massive gains from prospects of the SEC approving a Spot Bitcoin ETF. The price of Bitcoin started the year around $15,500 and climbed to over $31,400 in July.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Crypto funds on average generated 15.2% return in the first half of 2023 lol <a href="https://t.co/vb8pwYfiX9" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/vb8pwYfiX9</a></p>
<p>— Alex Krüger (@krugermacro) <a href="https://twitter.com/krugermacro/status/1687642407578517504?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 5, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Bitcoin outperforming crypto funds is relatively new, as crypto hedge funds are frequently able to outperform the BTC benchmark in the past significantly. But the crypto industry ended 2022 with more of a gloomy sentiment, as the market witnessed regulatory uncertainties and the collapse of FTX and Terra. </p>
<p>This seems to have caused crypto hedge funds to take a safer approach, leaving them with larger-than-normal cash positions. When crypto is hot, that cash doesn’t appreciate like BTC would unless the funds’ assets perform significantly better than Bitcoin.</p>
<p>The report also noted that directional crypto funds generally outperformed non-directional crypto funds. Non-directional funds, like arbitrage, lending, and staking, do not depend on the market&#8217;s direction.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/yBnfNnPz/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2>Outlook for Second Half of 2023: More Gains Ahead for Bitcoin?</h2>
<p>21e6 Capital’s latest report shows the general sentiment of the crypto market. Crypto funds had a rough first half of 2023, with many closing down early this year. About 13% of crypto hedge funds shut this year, as a few of them have struggled to present a favorable value proposition to potential investors.</p>

<p>The price of Bitcoin seems to be struggling to break over $30,000, but the outlook for Bitcoin in the second half of 2023 still looks positive. If approved, the price of Bitcoin is expected to spike further in the coming months as <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/us-institutional-investors-flocking-back-to-bitcoin-bottom-in/">major investment companies start to offer Spot Bitcoin ETFs</a>. </p>
<p>This influx of capital could spark a fresh bull market for all cryptocurrencies, leading to further gains for BTC holders. This new volume could see the price of BTC rise above $30,000 once more.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, BTC is trading at $29,043.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1344135727.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545922</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Whales Trigger Price Decline With Large Selling</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-whales-trigger-price-decline/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 21:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545923</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Massive XRP whale wallets are at it again as recently, some of the largest holders of XRP have dumped over 100 million tokens, putting major selling pressure on the XRP price.  On-chain data shows that since July 19, the overall supply in addresses holding between 100,000-1,000,000 coins has decreased from 6.85 billion to 6.75 billion. Whales Taking Profit After Pump The actions of whales or large holders of cryptocurrencies seem to always tell the nature of general market sentiment. When whales sell off chunks of their holding, it often triggers a cascade of smaller holders selling in response, driving the price down.  Related Reading: These Are The Factors That Could Lead To Another Bitcoin Rally: ARK Invest While retail investors and smaller holders often get caught up in the excitement of price rises and buy-in at the top, whales are more likely to sell off after massive price jumps and buy back in after the pullback. Right now, XRP whales may be taking some profits after the recent pump in price following news of partial victory in the SEC case. The price of XRP rose over 70% in less than 24 hours to $0.85 on the back of the news but has since declined about 15% from the yearly high. Data shows that the price decline started two weeks ago, around the same time when XRP whales started selling off their holdings. Token price falls to $0.62 following whale dumps &#124; Source: XRPUSD on Tradingview.com What&#8217;s Next For XRP? The XRP ecosystem faced a similar selloff in June, as whales dumped around 120 million XRP after Ripple unlocked its escrow to add another 1 billion tokens into circulation. Sell-offs are likely to trigger more selloffs. So In the short term, we’re likely to see some price volatility and fluctuations as the market absorbs the impact of such a large amount of tokens entering circulation.  The price of XRP, on the other hand, is doing well compared to the overall market. It was reported earlier last month that whales have been amassing more than $500 million in XRP since February in anticipation of positive developments within the ecosystem.  Ripple, the company behind the altcoin, says it is now eyeing the tokenized assets market as it hopes to unlock trillions of dollars of value in the global financial system. Related Reading: Bank Of Canada Study Shows Crypto Ownership In The Country Fell In The Last 2 Years However, Ripple&#8217;s partial victory in court seems to be standing on one foot, as analysts expect an appeal from the SEC. If this happens, it could negatively impact the price of XRP, leading to a downtrend. In such a case, the altcoin&#8217;s gains from last month could quickly be wiped out. XRP is currently trading at $0.6253 and has risen by 31.52% in the last 30 days. Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Massive XRP whale wallets are at it again as recently, some of the largest holders of XRP have dumped over 100 million tokens, putting major selling pressure on the XRP price. </p>
<p>On-chain <a href="https://app.santiment.net/charts?settings=%7B%22slug%22%3A%22xrp%22%2C%22ticker%22%3A%22XRP%22%2C%22from%22%3A%222023-02-05T22%3A59%3A59.723Z%22%2C%22to%22%3A%222023-08-05T22%3A59%3A59.723Z%22%7D&amp;widgets=%5B%7B%22widget%22%3A%22ChartWidget%22%2C%22wm%22%3A%5B%22price_usd%22%5D%2C%22whm%22%3A%5B%5D%2C%22wax%22%3A%5B0%5D%2C%22wpax%22%3A%5B%5D%2C%22wc%22%3A%5B%22%2326C953%22%5D%7D%5D" rel="nofollow">data </a>shows that since July 19, the overall supply in addresses holding between 100,000-1,000,000 coins has decreased from 6.85 billion to 6.75 billion.</p>
<h2>Whales Taking Profit After Pump</h2>
<p>The actions of whales or large holders of cryptocurrencies seem to always tell the nature of general market sentiment. When whales sell off chunks of their holding, it often triggers a cascade of smaller holders selling in response, driving the price down. </p>

<p>While retail investors and smaller holders often get caught up in the excitement of price rises and buy-in at the top, whales are more likely to sell off after massive price jumps and buy back in after the pullback.</p>
<p>Right now, XRP whales may be taking some profits after the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/all/xrp-performance-woes-how-might-its-price-respond-to-current-market-realities/">recent pump in price</a> following news of partial victory in the SEC case. The price of XRP rose over 70% in less than 24 hours to $0.85 on the back of the news but has since declined about 15% from the yearly high. <a href="https://clankapp.com/ripple/" rel="nofollow">Data </a>shows that the price decline started two weeks ago, around the same time when XRP whales started selling off their holdings.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/TYxkKFCR/" alt="Ripple (XRP) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2>What&#8217;s Next For XRP?</h2>
<p>The XRP ecosystem faced a similar selloff in June, as whales dumped around 120 million XRP after Ripple unlocked its escrow to add another 1 billion tokens into circulation. Sell-offs are likely to trigger more selloffs. So In the short term, we’re likely to see some price volatility and fluctuations as the market absorbs the impact of such a large amount of tokens entering circulation. </p>
<p>The price of XRP, on the other hand, is doing well compared to the overall market. It was reported earlier last <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1677725914333863937?s=20" rel="nofollow">month </a>that whales have been amassing more than $500 million in XRP since February in anticipation of positive developments within the ecosystem. </p>
<p>Ripple, the company behind the altcoin, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ripple/ripple-eyes-tokenized-assets-sector/">says </a>it is now eyeing the tokenized assets market as it hopes to unlock trillions of dollars of value in the global financial system.</p>

<p>However, Ripple&#8217;s partial victory in court seems to be standing on one foot, as analysts expect an appeal from the SEC. If this happens, it could negatively impact the price of XRP, leading to a downtrend. In such a case, the altcoin&#8217;s gains from last month could quickly be wiped out.</p>
<p>XRP is currently trading at $0.6253 and has risen by 31.52% in the last 30 days.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1415215518.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545923</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Analyst Points To Bitcoin Price History Repeating Itself &#8211; Are The Signs Bullish?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/crypto-analyst-points-to-bitcoin-price-history-repeating-itself-are-the-signs-bullish/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 19:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin spot ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bullish price cycle]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545889</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The general crypto market has recorded a slight decline in the last week, with the market leader Bitcoin losing 0.78% of its value over the last seven days.   This price loss amplifies BTC’s negative monthly performance, pushing its total loss in the last 30 days to around 5.38%, according to data from CoinMarketCap. At the time of writing, the premier cryptocurrency is trading at around $29,022, with its daily trading volume valued at $10.746 billion, having gone down 12.54%.  However, amidst Bitcoin&#8217;s current downtrend, it appears the token&#8217;s larger performance could be indicating a bullish market in the coming months. Related Reading: These Are The Factors That Could Lead To Another Bitcoin Rally: ARK Invest Bitcoin Could Be Repeating Historic Bullish Price Cycle &#8211; What Does This Mean?  On Aug. 4, crypto analyst Ali Martinez on social media platform X posted that Bitcoin is likely repeating a popular bullish cycle of its price history.   According to Ali, the token current’s price trajectory since attaining its all-time high in November 2021 is identical to its price movement between 2013 and 2017 based on data from Glassnode.   Bitcoin price performance since cycle ATH &#124; Source: Glassnode If this analysis proves correct, with Bitcoin mirroring its 2013-2017 price cycle, it means Bitcoin is expected to show little price movement in August 2023 and September 2023, perhaps recording some slight gains along the way.  However, Glassnode data shows BTC could experience a price upswing in October 2023, maintaining a bullish momentum all through this month. Thereafter, the token is expected to undergo a major re-correction finding support in the first week of November 2023.  Based on the reference price cycle, Bitcoin could then experience a significant price drop in the last month of 2023 but close the year in a strong consolidation zone. Source: Glassnode Beyond 2023, the BTC market could also be set for huge profits in 2024 and 2025 if Bitcoin is indeed repeating the 2013-2017 price cycle during which the market leader famously gained by over 1600%. However, all investors are reminded that predictions are not guaranteed and should not be considered as investment advice.  Rising Optimism In The BTC Market In other news, it appears there is a rising positive sentiment around Bitcoin, with a significant increase in its accumulation by key holders. According to a report by on-chain analytics firm Santiment, BTC whales and sharks are currently swapping their BUSD and DAI for more BTC.  Santiment noted the situation was quite the opposite back in July, with the BTC heavyweights shedding some of their holdings. However, the analytics firm reports that if the current trend is maintained, we could see BTC trade above $30,000 again.  Related Reading: Bitcoin NVT Shows Bearish Crossover, Price Drop Incoming? In the last few weeks, Bitcoin has remained among the headlines, with much discussion on the ongoing Bitcoin ETF race in the US.  On Aug. 2, Bloomberg ETF analysts James Seyffart and Eric Balchunas rated the approval chances of the first spot Bitcoin ETF at 65%. This is an impressive upgrade from 50% some weeks ago and 1% a couple months ago.  BTC trading at $28,979 on the weekly chart &#124; Source: BTCUSD chart on Tradingview.com Featured image from Forbes, chart from Tradingview.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The general crypto market has recorded a slight decline in the last week, with the market leader Bitcoin losing 0.78% of its value over the last seven days.  </p>
<p>This price loss amplifies BTC’s negative monthly performance, pushing its total loss in the last 30 days to around 5.38%, according to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from CoinMarketCap.</a></p>
<p>At the time of writing, the premier cryptocurrency is trading at around $29,022, with its daily trading volume valued at $10.746 billion, having gone down 12.54%. </p>
<p>However, amidst Bitcoin&#8217;s current downtrend, it appears the token&#8217;s larger performance could be indicating a bullish market in the coming months.</p>

<h2><strong>Bitcoin Could Be Repeating Historic Bullish Price Cycle &#8211; What Does This Mean? </strong></h2>
<p>On Aug. 4, crypto analyst Ali Martinez on social media platform X<a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1687577147181842433?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1687577147181842433%7Ctwgr%5E2e50902dd4b8ed06655da86ac6ae5a5f1f319105%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fcoinedition.com%2Fbtc-could-pump-towards-the-end-of-the-year-predicts-analyst%2F" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> posted</a> that Bitcoin is likely repeating a popular bullish cycle of its price history.  </p>
<p>According to Ali, the token current’s price trajectory since attaining its all-time high in November 2021 is identical to its price movement between 2013 and 2017 based on data from Glassnode.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"> <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-545894 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-28.png?w=860&#038;resize=558%2C341" alt="bitcoin" width="558" height="341" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-28.png?w=1443 1443w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-28.png?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-28.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-28.png?w=860&#038;resize=558%2C341 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-28.png?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-28.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 558px) 100vw, 558px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>If this analysis proves correct, with Bitcoin mirroring its 2013-2017 price cycle, it means Bitcoin is expected to show little price movement in August 2023 and September 2023, perhaps recording some slight gains along the way. </p>
<p>However, Glassnode data shows BTC could experience a price upswing in October 2023, maintaining a bullish momentum all through this month. Thereafter, the token is expected to undergo a major re-correction finding support in the first week of November 2023. </p>
<p>Based on the reference price cycle, Bitcoin could then experience a significant price drop in the last month of 2023 but close the year in a strong consolidation zone.
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-545895 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-27.png?w=860&#038;resize=578%2C356" alt="" width="578" height="356" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-27.png?w=1416 1416w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-27.png?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-27.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-27.png?w=860&#038;resize=578%2C356 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-27.png?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-27.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 578px) 100vw, 578px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>Beyond 2023, the BTC market could also be set for huge profits in 2024 and 2025 if Bitcoin is indeed repeating the 2013-2017 price cycle during which the market leader famously gained by over 1600%.</p>
<p style="text-align: left">However, all investors are reminded that predictions are not guaranteed and should not be considered as investment advice. </p>
<h2><strong>Rising Optimism In The BTC Market</strong></h2>
<p>In other news, it appears there is a rising positive sentiment around Bitcoin, with a significant increase in its accumulation by key holders. According to a<a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1687512461178736640" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> report</a> by on-chain analytics firm Santiment, BTC whales and sharks are currently swapping their BUSD and DAI for more BTC. </p>
<p>Santiment noted the situation was quite the opposite back in July, with the BTC heavyweights shedding some of their holdings. However, the analytics firm reports that if the current trend is maintained, we could see BTC trade above $30,000 again. </p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-nvt-shows-bearish-crossover-price-drop-incoming/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin NVT Shows Bearish Crossover, Price Drop Incoming?</a></p>
<p style="text-align: left">In the last few weeks, Bitcoin has remained among the headlines, with much discussion on the ongoing Bitcoin ETF race in the US.  On Aug. 2, Bloomberg ETF analysts James Seyffart and Eric Balchunas <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-nvt-shows-bearish-crossover-price-drop-incoming/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">rated</a> the approval chances of the first spot Bitcoin ETF at 65%. This is an impressive upgrade from 50% some weeks ago and 1% a couple months ago. </p>

<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/aXM67OF9/" alt="Bitcoin" width="1480" height="906"/>BTC trading at $28,979 on the weekly chart | Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/chart/xg17RJqK/?symbol=BITSTAMP%3ABTCUSD" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD chart on Tradingview.com</a>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/pexels-alesia-kozik-6765363-scaled-1.jpg?fit=460%2C259" width="460" height="259" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545889</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Optimism (OP) Tallies 13% In 7 Days Despite High Profile DeFi Hack</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/optimism-op-tallies-13-in-7-days-despite-high-profile-defi-hack/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Olowoporoku Adeniyi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 18:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[optimism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Optimism (OP)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OPtimism OP analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545877</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the midst of the ever-changing cryptocurrency landscape, Optimism (OP) has shown remarkable resilience, posting a notable price increase of 13.53% in the past seven days. Despite facing a slight decline of 1.80% in the last 24 hours and a further 1.35% shrinkage within the hour, Optimism remains on an upward trajectory. With the current price sitting at $1.68 per OP and still 48.38% below its all-time high of $3.26, traders and investors are eager to uncover the reasons behind its recent gains. This article explores the factors contributing to Optimism&#8217;s recent surge and analyzes its prospects. High Profile Hack Could Stall Optimism (OP) Bullish Trajectory  Optimism&#8217;s positive trajectory took an unexpected turn when Coinbase&#8217;s newly launched BASE network, built on the Optimism Stack, fell victim to a backdoor contract exploit. This unfortunate event resulted in the loss of 597 Ether, equivalent to approximately $1 million. The exploit involved infiltrating a backdoor contract on the BASE Chain, which enabled the continuous minting of tokens that were subsequently sold for profit. The exploiters managed to mint 40 different tokens, generating significant profit, which was then moved out of the perpetrators&#8217; address. Related Reading: Curve Finance Exploiter Returns 61,000 ETH After Protocol’s Stern Warning As BASE anchors the OP Stack, there are concerns that the recent exploit could have repercussions on all associated protocols, including the Optimism network. Furthermore, the hype surrounding BASE had attracted several new addresses to the Optimism network, potentially dampening investor sentiment and a subsequent impact on OP&#8217;s price. The number of active addresses on the Optimism network increased following BASE&#8217;s launch in late February. However, the recent hack may stall this growth, as investors might exercise caution in the wake of the exploit. Will The Bulls Sustain The Impressive Rally? Despite the recent BASE exploit, Optimism (OP) has managed to maintain a sense of optimism in the market. The OP/USD daily chart displays promising signs of bullish momentum, with the bulls surpassing critical support levels. Short green candlesticks formed above the $1.631 support level indicate the market&#8217;s resilience and determination to keep the price afloat despite the challenges posed by the recent exploit. The technical indicators further reinforce the bullish outlook for Optimism. The Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) remains above the signal line, characterized by green histogram bars that signify the asset&#8217;s bullish momentum. Additionally, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) has entered the overbought region, reaching a value of 75. This suggests a considerable increase in buying pressure on OP as investors show confidence in the token&#8217;s potential for future growth. Related Reading: Coinbase Research Expert Decodes Latest Crypto And Finance Market Trends However, while the market sentiment remains positive, traders and investors should exercise caution. The recent BASE exploit has raised concerns about the potential impact on Optimism&#8217;s network and the broader sentiment surrounding the token.  The cryptocurrency market is known for its volatility, and external events can have significant implications for token prices. It is crucial for market participants to closely monitor developments related to the exploit and assess any potential consequences for Optimism&#8217;s price trajectory. Despite the positive indicators and bullish momentum, staying informed and vigilant in such a rapidly changing market is essential for making well-informed decisions. (This site’s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the midst of the ever-changing cryptocurrency landscape, Optimism (OP) has shown remarkable resilience, posting a notable price increase of 13.53% in the past seven days. Despite facing a slight decline of 1.80% in the last 24 hours and a further 1.35% shrinkage within the hour, Optimism remains on an upward trajectory. </p>
<p>With the current price sitting at $1.68 per OP and still 48.38% below its all-time high of $3.26, traders and investors are eager to uncover the reasons behind its recent gains. This article explores the factors contributing to Optimism&#8217;s recent surge and analyzes its prospects.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-545878" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/OPUSDT_2023-08-05_12-26-52.png?w=460&#038;resize=460%2C268" alt="optimism (OP) price has enjoyed a steady spike in the past week: Source @Tradingview" width="460" height="268" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/OPUSDT_2023-08-05_12-26-52.png?w=1534 1534w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/OPUSDT_2023-08-05_12-26-52.png?w=460&#038;resize=460%2C268 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/OPUSDT_2023-08-05_12-26-52.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/OPUSDT_2023-08-05_12-26-52.png?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/OPUSDT_2023-08-05_12-26-52.png?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/OPUSDT_2023-08-05_12-26-52.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<h2><strong>High Profile Hack Could Stall Optimism (OP) Bullish Trajectory </strong></h2>
<p>Optimism&#8217;s positive trajectory took an unexpected turn when Coinbase&#8217;s newly launched BASE network, built on the Optimism Stack, fell victim to a backdoor contract exploit. This unfortunate event resulted in the loss of 597 Ether, equivalent to approximately $1 million.</p>
<p>The exploit involved infiltrating a backdoor contract on the BASE Chain, which enabled the continuous minting of tokens that were subsequently sold for profit. The exploiters managed to mint 40 different tokens, generating significant profit, which was then moved out of the perpetrators&#8217; address.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading</strong>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/curve-finance-exploiter-returns-61000-eth-after-protocols-stern-warning/">Curve Finance Exploiter Returns 61,000 ETH After Protocol’s Stern Warning</a></p>
<p>As BASE anchors the OP Stack, there are concerns that the recent exploit could have repercussions on all associated protocols, including the Optimism network. Furthermore, the hype surrounding BASE had attracted several new addresses to the Optimism network, potentially dampening investor sentiment and a subsequent impact on OP&#8217;s price.</p>
<p>The number of active addresses on the Optimism network increased following BASE&#8217;s launch in late February. However, the recent hack may stall this growth, as investors might exercise caution in the wake of the exploit.</p>
<h2><strong>Will The Bulls Sustain The Impressive Rally?</strong></h2>
<p>Despite the recent BASE exploit, Optimism (OP) has managed to maintain a sense of optimism in the market. The OP/USD daily chart displays promising signs of bullish momentum, with the bulls surpassing critical support levels. Short green candlesticks formed above the $1.631 support level indicate the market&#8217;s resilience and determination to keep the price afloat despite the challenges posed by the recent exploit.</p>
<p>The technical indicators further reinforce the bullish outlook for Optimism. The Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) remains above the signal line, characterized by green histogram bars that signify the asset&#8217;s bullish momentum. Additionally, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) has entered the overbought region, reaching a value of 75. This suggests a considerable increase in buying pressure on OP as investors show confidence in the token&#8217;s potential for future growth.</p>
<p><strong>Related Reading</strong>: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/coinbase-research-expert-decodes-latest-crypto-and-finance-market-trends/">Coinbase Research Expert Decodes Latest Crypto And Finance Market Trends</a></p>
<p>However, while the market sentiment remains positive, traders and investors should exercise caution. The recent BASE exploit has raised concerns about the potential impact on Optimism&#8217;s network and the broader sentiment surrounding the token. </p>
<p>The cryptocurrency market is known for its volatility, and external events can have significant implications for token prices. It is crucial for market participants to closely monitor developments related to the exploit and assess any potential consequences for Optimism&#8217;s price trajectory. Despite the positive indicators and bullish momentum, staying informed and vigilant in such a rapidly changing market is essential for making well-informed decisions.</p>
<p><i>(This site’s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</i></p>
<p><i>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView</i></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/iStock-1291935777.jpg?fit=460%2C263" width="460" height="263" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545877</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tether May Now Be 11th Largest Bitcoin Holder, Analyst Says</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/stablecoin/tether-may-now-be-11th-largest-bitcoin-holder/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 17:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paolo Ardoino]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545861</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tether, the company behind the USDT stablecoin, may now be the 11th largest bitcoin holder in the world. This comes after the stablecoin issuer recently published its attestation report for Q2 2023. According to the report, Tether recorded an increase in excess reserves, which grew by $850 million. This brought the company’s total excess reserves to approximately $3.3 billion. These excess reserves are profits that the company does not distribute to shareholders as dividends. Instead, Tether keeps them to shore up its 100% reserves, which are used to back all USDT in circulation and keep the token stable. Related Reading: USDT Issuer Tether Reports A 30% Decline In Profit Tether Holds $1.6 Billion Worth Of BTC In Single Wallet? In the last quarter, Tether published that it held more than $1.5 billion worth of BTC (about 53,495 BTC) in its reserves. Based on the latest quarterly report, this figure has grown by more than $176 million, bringing the company’s Bitcoin holdings to roughly $1.676 billion (around 55,022 BTC). Tom Wan, a research analyst at 21.co, found in the last quarter that Tether may be holding all their Bitcoin in one wallet, making them the 12th largest BTC holder at the time. Fast forward to Q2 2023, it appears that the analyst has confirmed his initial speculations. In the first quarter, the BTC holdings of Tether’s “possible” wallet address matched the BTC amount published in the company’s attestation report. The BTC balance of this address has also increased in the second quarter, corresponding with the amount provided in Tether’s Q2 report. The analyst noted that only one Bitcoin address matches the figures of Tether’s BTC reserves. And this address, which may belong to the stablecoin issuer, is now the 11th largest Bitcoin holder in the world. While Wan sought Tether and the company’s CTO Paolo Ardoino to corroborate his findings, there has been no official confirmation from the stablecoin issuer. Tether’s BTC Holdings Consistent With Initial Plans This significant amount of BTC Tether holds in its reserves comes as no surprise, especially as the firm has always been clear about its Bitcoin investment intentions. In May, the stablecoin issuer announced plans to invest 15% of its future profit in Bitcoin. Tether’s CTO Paolo Ardoino, a vocal supporter of Bitcoin, stated that the cryptocurrency’s resilience is the reason for the company’s continuous investment in the asset.  Ardoino said:  The decision to invest in Bitcoin, the world’s first and largest cryptocurrency, is underpinned by its strength and potential as an investment asset. Bitcoin has continually proven its resilience and has emerged as a long-term store of value with substantial growth potential. Its limited supply, decentralized nature, and widespread adoption have positioned Bitcoin as a favored choice among institutional and retail investors alike. Related Reading: Tether (USDT) Market Cap Reaches New Peak, Edges Toward $84 Billion Mark However, there have been concerns about Tether and USDT’s exposure to risks due to increased investment in a highly volatile asset such as Bitcoin.  As of this writing, USDT is the largest stablecoin in the cryptocurrency market, with a market cap of roughly $83.81 billion. USDT market cap at $83.79 billion on the daily timeframe &#124; Source: USDT chart from TradingView Featured image from Wit Olszewski/Alamy, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tether, the company behind the USDT stablecoin, may now be the 11th largest bitcoin holder in the world. This comes after the stablecoin issuer recently published its attestation report for Q2 2023.</p>
<p>According to the report, Tether recorded an increase in excess reserves, which grew by $850 million. This brought the company’s total excess reserves to approximately $3.3 billion.</p>
<p>These excess reserves are profits that the company does not distribute to shareholders as dividends. Instead, Tether keeps them to shore up its 100% reserves, which are used to back all USDT in circulation and keep the token stable.</p>

<h2><strong>Tether Holds $1.6 Billion Worth Of BTC In Single Wallet?</strong></h2>
<p>In the last quarter, Tether published that it held more than $1.5 billion worth of BTC (about 53,495 BTC) in its reserves. Based on the latest quarterly report, this figure has grown by more than $176 million, bringing the company’s Bitcoin holdings to roughly $1.676 billion (around 55,022 BTC).</p>
<p>Tom Wan, a research analyst at 21.co, <a href="https://twitter.com/tomwanhh/status/1687304569750175744?s=46&amp;t=yUjNJ5Zx5TffuZOJeIegJQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">found</a> in the last quarter that Tether may be holding all their Bitcoin in one wallet, making them the 12th largest BTC holder at the time. Fast forward to Q2 2023, it appears that the analyst has confirmed his initial speculations.</p>
<p>In the first quarter, the BTC holdings of Tether’s “possible” wallet address matched the BTC amount published in the company’s attestation report. The BTC balance of this address has also increased in the second quarter, corresponding with the amount provided in Tether’s Q2 report.</p>
<p>The analyst noted that only one Bitcoin address matches the figures of Tether’s BTC reserves. And this address, which may belong to the stablecoin issuer, is now the 11th largest Bitcoin holder in the world.</p>
<p>While Wan sought Tether and the company’s CTO Paolo Ardoino to corroborate his findings, there has been no official confirmation from the stablecoin issuer.</p>
<h2><strong>Tether’s BTC Holdings Consistent With Initial Plans</strong></h2>
<p>This significant amount of BTC Tether holds in its reserves comes as no surprise, especially as the firm has always been clear about its Bitcoin investment intentions. In May, the stablecoin issuer <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/press-releases/tether-could-soon-become-one-of-the-largest-bitcoin-investors/?amp" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">announced</a> plans to invest 15% of its future profit in Bitcoin.</p>
<p>Tether’s CTO Paolo Ardoino, a vocal supporter of Bitcoin, stated that the cryptocurrency’s resilience is the reason for the company’s continuous investment in the asset. </p>
<p>Ardoino said: </p>
<blockquote><p>The decision to invest in Bitcoin, the world’s first and largest cryptocurrency, is underpinned by its strength and potential as an investment asset. Bitcoin has continually proven its resilience and has emerged as a long-term store of value with substantial growth potential. Its limited supply, decentralized nature, and widespread adoption have positioned Bitcoin as a favored choice among institutional and retail investors alike.</p></blockquote>

<p>However, there have been concerns about Tether and USDT’s exposure to risks due to increased investment in a highly volatile asset such as Bitcoin. </p>
<p>As of this writing, USDT is the largest stablecoin in the cryptocurrency market, with a <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/tether" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">market cap</a> of roughly $83.81 billion.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/FhgLJmQr/" alt="Tether" width="997" height="580"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/photo_2023-05-14_06-54-51.jpg?fit=460%2C259" width="460" height="259" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545861</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bone ShibaSwap Among Weekend 100 Biggest Hitters With 25% Rally</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/all/bone-shibaswap-rises-25/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 16:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BONE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ShibaSwap]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545901</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency market is currently growing in a variety of ways, but the Shiba Inu (SHIB) ecosystem&#8217;s tokens are currently noticeably on a positive run. Bone ShibaSwap (BONE), one of the leading tokens in the meme coin ecosystem, is on a clear uptrend, rising as much as 5.6% in the previous day to $1.74. The coin has increased by more than 25% over the last week as a result of the ecosystem&#8217;s overall buzz. The price of Bone Shibaswap has made a significant recovery in recent months. After soaring to a high of $1.7410, the highest point since March, it exceeded several of the initially pessimistic expectations. BONE price all in green in the weekend chart. TradingView.com BONE Showing Solid Performance While the price of Bitcoin and Ethereum has stabilized, the BONE cryptocurrency has increased by more than 130% since its June lows. The anticipation stems from the belief that the upcoming August mainnet release of Shibarium will mark the beginning of a transformative era. Ever since the launch timeline was disclosed earlier, members of the community have been attributing special significance to this event, particularly emphasizing the role of BONE. BONEUSD trading at $1.74 on the weekly chart: TradingView.com This enthusiasm is fueled by the potential impact of Shibarium&#8217;s launch on the overall landscape and the specific importance of BONE within this context. The idea of a crypto exchange is among the most crucial ones in the field of crypto. Because cryptocurrencies don&#8217;t have an inherent worth, having a market where they may be purchased, sold, or traded aids in determining their price. Related Reading: XRP Performance Woes: How Might Its Price Respond To Current Market Realities? To address possible problems with conventional, centralized exchanges (CEXes), decentralized exchanges, or DEXes, were developed. People can trade any cryptocurrency they want for any cryptocurrency they want at a price determined by the market, rather than being restricted to what a centralized authority says can and cannot be listed. Source: CoinMarketCap ShibaSwap is one of many decentralized exchanges available and is built on the Ethereum (ETH) network. The Bone ShibaSwap (BONE) crypto token serves as its backbone. It was established in 2021 by the team behind the Shiba Inu (SHIB) cryptocurrency. Shibarium Launch Boosts Token&#8217;s Price The impending arrival of Shibarium is the main reason why Bone Shibaswap is so high. To begin with, Shibarium is a forthcoming layer 2 network that aims to alter how Shiba Inu and ShibaSwap operate. Related Reading: All Hype? BALD Meme Coin’s Volume Shaved By 96% Meanwhile, in the last week, BONE outpaced the top performers in the market, including Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH). For the first time in nearly five months, the asset has broken above $1.6 thanks to the latest climb. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency market is currently growing in a variety of ways, but the Shiba Inu (SHIB) ecosystem&#8217;s tokens are currently noticeably on a positive run. Bone ShibaSwap (BONE), one of the leading tokens in the meme coin ecosystem, is on a clear uptrend, rising as much as 5.6% in the previous day to $1.74. The coin has increased by more than 25% over the last week as a result of the ecosystem&#8217;s overall buzz.</p>
<p>The price of <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" rel="nofollow">Bone Shibaswap</a> has made a significant recovery in recent months. After soaring to a high of $1.7410, the highest point since March, it exceeded several of the initially pessimistic expectations.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-545904" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BONE.png?resize=1024%2C51" alt="" width="1024" height="51" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BONE.png?resize=1024%2C51?w=1134 1134w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BONE.png?resize=1024%2C51?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BONE.png?resize=1024%2C51?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BONE.png?resize=1024%2C51?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BONE.png?resize=1024%2C51?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<h2><strong>BONE Showing Solid Performance</strong></h2>
<p>While the price of Bitcoin and Ethereum has stabilized, the BONE cryptocurrency has increased by more than 130% since its June lows.</p>
<p>The anticipation stems from the belief that the upcoming August mainnet release of Shibarium will mark the beginning of a transformative era.</p>
<p>Ever since the launch timeline was disclosed earlier, members of the community have been attributing special significance to this event, particularly emphasizing the role of BONE.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Ao2CqNJq/" width="2475" height="1179"/></p>

<p>This enthusiasm is fueled by the potential impact of Shibarium&#8217;s launch on the overall landscape and the specific importance of BONE within this context.</p>
<p>The idea of a crypto exchange is among the most crucial ones in the field of crypto. Because cryptocurrencies don&#8217;t have an inherent worth, having a market where they may be purchased, sold, or traded aids in determining their price.</p>

<p>To address possible problems with conventional, centralized exchanges (CEXes), decentralized exchanges, or DEXes, were developed. People can trade any cryptocurrency they want for any cryptocurrency they want at a price determined by the market, rather than being restricted to what a centralized authority says can and cannot be listed.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-545911" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-17.png?resize=1024%2C451" alt="" width="1024" height="451" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-17.png?resize=1024%2C451?w=1036 1036w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-17.png?resize=1024%2C451?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-17.png?resize=1024%2C451?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-17.png?resize=1024%2C451?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-17.png?resize=1024%2C451?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>ShibaSwap is one of many decentralized exchanges available and is built on the Ethereum (ETH) network. The Bone ShibaSwap (BONE) crypto token serves as its backbone. It was established in 2021 by the team behind the Shiba Inu (SHIB) cryptocurrency.</p>
<h2><strong>Shibarium Launch Boosts Token&#8217;s Price</strong></h2>
<p>The impending arrival of Shibarium is the main reason why Bone Shibaswap is so high. To begin with, Shibarium is a forthcoming layer 2 network that aims to alter how Shiba Inu and ShibaSwap operate.</p>

<p>Meanwhile, in the last week, BONE <a href="https://thecryptobasic.com/2023/08/03/shiba-inu-bone-now-biggest-gainer-among-top-100-up-24-amid-shibarium-hype/" rel="nofollow">outpaced</a> the top performers in the market, including Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH). For the first time in nearly five months, the asset has broken above $1.6 thanks to the latest climb.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from </em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545901</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum ETF Race Gets Hotter As SEC Receives 11 Filings In One Week</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-etf-race-gets-hotter/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 15:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum ETFs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545885</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has been flooded with many applications for Ethereum (ETH) Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs) in just one week. The applications currently stand at 12, with the latest addition coming from ProShares, a popular fund manager.  The platform filed four applications for Ether-based ETFs, including a dual Ether and Bitcoin futures strategy ETF, an Ether Strategy ETF, and a short Ether Strategy ETF.  Will The SEC Approve An Ethereum Futures ETF? The recent surge in applications started on the 28th of July this year after Volatility Shares filed its application. Ever since, other asset management companies, including ProShares, Roundhill Financial,  Bitwise, Van Eck, and Grayscale Investment, have filled submissions, with some bringing multiple applications.  Related Reading: These Are The Factors That Could Lead To Another Bitcoin Rally: ARK Invest The most recent application, filed on August 3 by ProShares, proposes an equal-weight Bitcoin and Ether ETF to measure the performance of holding long positions in the nearest maturing monthly Ether and Bitcoin contracts.  According to renowned Financial Expert at Bloomberg Intelligence, James Seyffart, ProShare filed four separate applications with the SEC. Bitwise also submitted three applications, while Grayscale Investments filed two applications.  However, despite the growing optimism, it remains to be seen if the Securities and Exchange Commission will approve these filings. The SEC has never approved an ETF that tracks Ether Futures contracts, unlike Bitcoin Futures ETFs that have been around since October 2021. Many market experts have argued that these applications are a mere gamble by these asset management companies, who do not want to miss out on being the first Ethereum ETF in the United States.  ETH price holds steady above $1,830 amid ETF race &#124; Source: ETHUSD on Tradingview.com The likelihood of receiving the SEC’s approval remains slim as the regulatory body has never approved an Ethereum futures ETF filing. Add to the mix the consistent refusal of SEC’s Chair, Gary Gensler, consistent refusal to answer if the agency considers ETH a security. This has further compounded regulatory uncertainty around the network. If none of the applications before the SEC get denied, the Ether ETFs will launch 75 days from their respective filing dates. Analysts expect the Volatility Shares ETF to lead the charge on 12th October.  Understanding The Difference Between Futures And Spot ETF Products The primary difference between futures and spot ETF products lies in the fact that while the former tracks the price of futures contracts, the latter requires the issuers to purchase the underlying assets. Spot ETFs are generally considered more valid since they require the fund manager to purchase and hold underlying assets.  Related Reading: Bank Of Canada Study Shows Crypto Ownership In The Country Fell In The Last 2 Years The current spike in Ether-based applications comes amidst a wave of filings from leading asset management companies, including BlackRock, the world’s largest asset manager, among others. These companies are looking to offer the first spot in Bitcoin ETF in the US.  Investors and members of the crypto community remain expectant of the outcome of the SEC’s consideration of the applications lying before it. Whatever decision the agency takes is likely to affect the attractiveness and accessibility of crypto investments, especially for larger institutional investors.  Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has been flooded with many applications for Ethereum (ETH) Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs) in just one week. The applications currently stand at 12, with the latest addition coming from <a href="https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1174610/000168386323005834/f26041d1.htm" rel="nofollow">ProShares</a>, a popular fund manager. </p>
<p>The platform filed four applications for Ether-based ETFs, including a dual Ether and Bitcoin futures strategy ETF, an Ether Strategy ETF, and a short Ether Strategy ETF. </p>
<h2>Will The SEC Approve An Ethereum Futures ETF?</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-etfs-heat-up/">recent surge in applications</a> started on the 28th of July this year after Volatility Shares filed its application. Ever since, other asset management companies, including ProShares, Roundhill Financial,  Bitwise, Van Eck, and Grayscale Investment, have filled submissions, with some bringing multiple applications. </p>

<p>The most recent application, filed on August 3 by ProShares, proposes an equal-weight Bitcoin and Ether ETF to measure the performance of holding long positions in the nearest maturing monthly Ether and Bitcoin contracts. </p>
<p>According to renowned Financial Expert at Bloomberg Intelligence, James Seyffart, ProShare <a href="https://twitter.com/JSeyff/status/1687307603922055168?s=20" rel="nofollow">filed</a> four separate applications with the SEC. Bitwise also submitted <a href="https://www.sec.gov/edgar/browse/?CIK=1928561" rel="nofollow">three</a> applications, while Grayscale Investments filed two applications. </p>
<p>However, despite the growing optimism, it remains to be seen if the Securities and Exchange Commission will approve these filings. The SEC has never approved an ETF that tracks Ether Futures contracts, unlike Bitcoin Futures ETFs that have been around since October 2021.</p>
<p>Many market experts have argued that these applications are a mere gamble by these asset management companies, who do not want to miss out on being the first Ethereum ETF in the United States. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/gdKZvaPp/" alt="Ethereum (ETH) price chart from Tradingview.com (ETFs)" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<p>The likelihood of receiving the SEC’s approval remains slim as the regulatory body has never approved an Ethereum futures ETF filing. Add to the mix the consistent refusal of SEC’s Chair, Gary Gensler, consistent refusal to answer if the agency considers ETH a security. This has further compounded regulatory uncertainty around the network.</p>
<p>If none of the applications before the SEC get denied, the Ether ETFs will launch 75 days from their respective filing dates. Analysts expect the Volatility Shares ETF to lead the charge on 12th October. </p>
<h2>Understanding The Difference Between Futures And Spot ETF Products</h2>
<p>The primary difference between futures and spot ETF products lies in the fact that while the former tracks the price of futures contracts, the latter requires the issuers to purchase the underlying assets. Spot ETFs are generally considered more valid since they require the fund manager to purchase and hold underlying assets. </p>

<p>The current spike in <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-etfs-heat-up/">Ether-based applications</a> comes amidst a wave of filings from leading asset management companies, including BlackRock, the world’s largest asset manager, among others. These companies are looking to offer the first spot in Bitcoin ETF in the US. </p>
<p>Investors and members of the crypto community remain expectant of the outcome of the SEC’s consideration of the applications lying before it. Whatever decision the agency takes is likely to affect the attractiveness and accessibility of crypto investments, especially for larger institutional investors. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1323353734.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545885</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Celebrates Significant Milestone After Six Years In Operation</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/binance/binance-celebrates-significant-milestone/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 12:54:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance users]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545886</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Binance, the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange by trading volume, has achieved another significant milestone. The firm, which recently turned six, keeps racking up several achievements despite the FUD that has surrounded it in recent times.  A Worthy Feat For Binance The world’s largest crypto exchange by daily trading volume has recently disclosed that its registered users now stand at a whopping 150 million. This was revealed in a tweet by its CEO, Changpeng “CZ” Zhao, on Thursday.  Related Reading: Bitstamp Makes Highly Anticipated XRP Announcement, But Does It Live Up To The Hype? In the tweet, CZ noted his company’s milestone amidst growing regulatory scrutiny of its operations the world over. However, despite navigating through different challenges, Binance has managed to captivate the interest of several millions of users around the globe. So this is a testament to the platform’s quality service delivery and amazing features.  Just over a year ago, in July 2022, the exchange’s user base stood at about 120 million. The astonishing growth of 30 million users within the span of just 12 months tells of Binance’s undeniable hold in the constantly evolving cryptocurrency ecosystem.  A cursory look at the platform&#8217;s traffic data for the last three months shows that the top five nations contributing to this spike are Vietnam, India, Russia, Turkey, and Argentina. The increased expansion across various diverse geographies demonstrates the heightened acceptance and penetration of digital currencies.  BNB price trends at $241 as users base reaches new high &#124; Source: BNBUSD on Tradingview.com Navigating Regulatory Challenges As expected, with growth comes challenges and Binance’s journey has not always been all growth and triumph. The platform has been the subject of various legal challenges across diverse jurisdictions.  The exchange was recently charged with “will evasion” and fraud by the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in June this year. In Europe, Binance is under probe by French regulators who accused the platform of engaging in money laundering. It has also been ordered to cease rendering crypto services by Belgium’s financial watchdog.  In China, the services of the platform are restricted and inaccessible to millions of users within the country. Binance has also withdrawn its license applications and canceled its registration bids in several countries.  Related Reading: Crypto Trading Volumes Fall To Lowest Level In 2023 Amid Bear Market Woes However, Binance has been able to make some gains in recent times. Earlier this month, it restored services in Japan, following the purchase of the local exchange Sakura Exchange BitCoin (SEBC) in November 2022. It has also been given a license to render cryptocurrency services in Dubai.  All these hurdles make the latest milestone not only remarkable but testamentary. The road to 150 million registered users has been paved with various challenges, but Binance has so far emerged victorious and triumphant.  Featured image from Reuters, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/binance/binance-zero-fee-bitcoin-ethereum/">the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange by trading volume</a>, has achieved another significant milestone. The firm, which recently turned six, keeps racking up several achievements despite the FUD that has surrounded it in recent times. </p>
<h2>A Worthy Feat For Binance</h2>
<p>The world’s largest crypto exchange by daily trading volume has recently disclosed that its registered users now stand at a whopping 150 million. This was revealed in a <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1687061963094814720?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1687061963094814720%7Ctwgr%5E2206280a29b0520b14a29ebd9dd2041f8c2c5cd1%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fnews.bitcoin.com%2Fbinance-users-reach-150-million-cz-reveals%2F" rel="nofollow">tweet</a> by its CEO, Changpeng “CZ” Zhao, on Thursday. </p>



<p>In the tweet, CZ noted his company’s milestone amidst growing regulatory scrutiny of its operations the world over. However, despite navigating through different challenges, Binance has managed to captivate the interest of several millions of users around the globe. So this is a testament to the platform’s quality service delivery and amazing features. </p>
<p>Just over a year ago, in July 2022, the exchange’s user base stood at about 120 million. The astonishing growth of 30 million users within the span of just 12 months tells of Binance’s undeniable hold in the constantly evolving cryptocurrency ecosystem. </p>
<p>A cursory look at the platform&#8217;s traffic data for the last three months shows that the top five nations contributing to this spike are Vietnam, India, Russia, Turkey, and Argentina. The increased expansion across various diverse geographies demonstrates the heightened acceptance and penetration of digital currencies. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/5Oa1w23u/" alt="Binance Coin (BNB) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2>Navigating Regulatory Challenges</h2>
<p>As expected, with growth comes challenges and Binance’s journey has not always been all growth and triumph. The platform has been the subject of various legal challenges across diverse jurisdictions. </p>
<p>The exchange was recently <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/doj-action-binance-hidden-blessing-bitcoin-crypto/">charged</a> with “will evasion” and fraud by the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in June this year. In <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/binance/binance-rescinds-decision-to-remove-privacy-coins-from-european-market/">Europe</a>, Binance is under probe by French regulators who accused the platform of engaging in money laundering. It has also been ordered to cease rendering crypto services by Belgium’s financial watchdog. </p>
<p>In China, the services of the platform are restricted and inaccessible to millions of users within the country. Binance has also withdrawn its license applications and canceled its registration bids in several countries. </p>



<p>However, Binance has been able to make some gains in recent times. Earlier this month, it restored services in Japan, following the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/binance/binance-to-enter-japan-with-a-bang/">purchase of the local exchange Sakura Exchange BitCoin (SEBC)</a> in November 2022. It has also been given a license to render cryptocurrency services in Dubai. </p>
<p>All these hurdles make the latest milestone not only remarkable but testamentary. The road to 150 million registered users has been paved with various challenges, but Binance has so far emerged victorious and triumphant. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Binance-users.jpeg?fit=460%2C319" width="460" height="319" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545886</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>These Are The Factors That Could Lead To Another Bitcoin Rally: ARK Invest</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/factors-could-lead-to-bitcoin-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 08:46:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ark invest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC Reversal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545863</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a report released on August 4, ARK Invest’s on-chain researcher David Puell reveals factors that could lead to another Bitcoin rally. The report, titled “The Bitcoin Monthly: July 2023,” provides an in-depth analysis and distinguishes between Bitcoin’s current situation and what the future holds for the largest cryptocurrency by market cap. Some Positives For Bitcoin Puell highlights how Bitcoin’s tepid 90-day volatility shares similarities with 2017 levels. According to the report, this prolonged low volatility usually represents the ‘calm before the storm,’ with Puell speculating that a significant price movement will likely happen soon. However, whether it will be a breakout or a breakdown remains uncertain.  Related Reading: Bank Of Canada Study Shows Crypto Ownership In The Country Fell In The Last 2 Years There is cause for optimism, though, as the decrease in hash rate on the blockchain provides an optimistic signal. The decrease could signify oversold conditions &#8211; whereby Bitcoin is currently trading below its actual worth, and considering that it has traded at an undervalued price for a long while now, we could see an upward trend, which would signify a price reversal.  Additionally, there has been an increase in “liveliness” as selling pressure has reduced and more holders are choosing to ‘HODL.’ The report states that liveliness fell below 60% in July, the lowest selling pressure since Q4 of 2020.  The short-term holders’ profit/loss ratio also coincides with historical trend reversals, signifying that a breakout is more likely to occur.  The report states: This breakeven level correlates both with local bottoms during primary bull markets and with local tops during bear market environments. Meanwhile, the Federal Reserve’s continued hike rate has been known to be a macro factor on Bitcoin and the crypto market. Puell believes that the Fed’s actions could significantly impact Bitcoin’s performance and the economy as a whole. A potential slowdown in CPI (consumer product index) inflation could see a surge in Bitcoin’s appeal as a non-inflammatory asset. BTC struggles to hold $29,000 support &#124; Source: BTCUSD on Tradingview.com Binance Could Have A Domino Effect On BTC The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (BTC) filed a lawsuit against Binance for trading unregistered securities, amongst other allegations. This ongoing legal tussle could affect Bitcoin’s performance and the crypto market.  According to the report, Binance’s BNB token ensures stability in the crypto market by providing significant liquidity for other cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin. If sentiments begin to tilt in favor of the SEC and DOJ, it could trigger a “bank run,” which would see BNB’s price plummet, causing a domino effect on the crypto market.  Related Reading: Crypto Trading Volumes Fall To Lowest Level In 2023 Amid Bear Market Woes While historical trends signify a bullish trajectory for Bitcoin’s price, the token might be marred by macroeconomic forces and regulatory concerns. It is believed that Bitcoin breaching the resistance level at $29,450 could shape its future outlook. As Bitcoin continues to witness a downward trajectory, that resistance level might be the key to a sustained breakout or further consolidation.  Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a <a href="https://ark-invest.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/The-Bitcoin-Monthly-July-2023.pdf" rel="nofollow">report</a> released on August 4, ARK Invest’s on-chain researcher David Puell reveals factors that could lead to another Bitcoin rally. The report, titled “The Bitcoin Monthly: July 2023,” provides an in-depth analysis and distinguishes between Bitcoin’s current situation and what the future holds for the largest cryptocurrency by market cap.</p>
<h2>Some Positives For Bitcoin</h2>
<p>Puell highlights how Bitcoin’s tepid 90-day volatility shares similarities with 2017 levels. According to the report, this prolonged low volatility usually represents the ‘calm before the storm,’ with Puell speculating that a significant price movement will likely happen soon. However, whether it will be a breakout or a breakdown remains uncertain. </p>

<p>There is cause for optimism, though, as the decrease in <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-hash-rate-retakes-all-time-high/">hash rate on the blockchain</a> provides an optimistic signal. The decrease could signify oversold conditions &#8211; whereby Bitcoin is currently trading below its actual worth, and considering that it has traded at an undervalued price for a long while now, we could see an upward trend, which would signify a price reversal. </p>
<p>Additionally, there has been an increase in “liveliness” as selling pressure has reduced and more holders are choosing to ‘HODL.’ The report states that liveliness fell below 60% in July, the lowest selling pressure since Q4 of 2020. </p>
<p>The short-term holders’ profit/loss ratio also coincides with historical trend reversals, signifying that a breakout is more likely to occur. </p>
<p>The report states:</p>
<blockquote><p>This breakeven level correlates both with local bottoms during primary bull markets and with local tops during bear market environments.</p></blockquote>
<p>Meanwhile, the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/federal-reserve-certifies-57-organizations-for-instant-payments-system-fednow/">Federal Reserve’s</a> continued hike rate has been known to be a macro factor on Bitcoin and the crypto market. Puell believes that the Fed’s actions could significantly impact Bitcoin’s performance and the economy as a whole. A potential slowdown in CPI (consumer product index) inflation could see a surge in Bitcoin’s appeal as a non-inflammatory asset.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/DEIkOT5l/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2>Binance Could Have A Domino Effect On BTC</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/sec-sues-binance-coinbase-blackrock-bitcoin-etf-inside-job/">United States Securities and Exchange Commission (BTC) filed a lawsuit against Binance</a> for trading unregistered securities, amongst other allegations. This ongoing legal tussle could affect Bitcoin’s performance and the crypto market. </p>
<p>According to the report, Binance’s BNB token ensures stability in the crypto market by providing significant liquidity for other cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin. If sentiments begin to tilt in favor of the SEC and DOJ, it could trigger a “<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/long-queues-seen-at-silicon-valley-bank-owned-boston-private-a-bank-run/">bank run</a>,” which would see BNB’s price plummet, causing a domino effect on the crypto market. </p>

<p>While historical trends signify a bullish trajectory for Bitcoin’s price, the token might be marred by macroeconomic forces and regulatory concerns. It is believed that Bitcoin breaching the resistance level at $29,450 could shape its future outlook. </p>
<p>As Bitcoin continues to witness a downward trajectory, that resistance level might be the key to a sustained breakout or further consolidation. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-877508718.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545863</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Research Expert Decodes Latest Crypto And Finance Market Trends</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/coinbase-research-expert-decodes-latest-crypto-and-finance-market-trends/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 23:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545856</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Coinbase’s Head of Research, David Duong, has shared his insights on the recent market movements in traditional finance and crypto.  He believes that current macro conditions suggest a temporary pause in the recent strong USD trend, which should support the crypto market.  Related Reading: Is SUI Price Stability Under Threat Due To Transactional Boom And Bust? Key Crypto &#38; Finance Movements Duong notes that the recent carry trades upset by the Bank of Japan’s decision to raise the hard cap on its 10-year bond yield have created instability across different pockets of the FX market.  Meanwhile, the surprise decision by Brazil’s central bank to cut its benchmark SELIC rate by 50bps (compared to expectations of 25bps) has led to higher interest rates in some price currencies coming down. In the US, the yield curve steepened significantly following the rally in Treasury bonds only two weeks ago, as the US Treasury Department announced an increase in the size of its debt issuance plans.  Although Fitch cut the US debt rating from AAA to AA+ due to concerns about the fiscal outlook, Duong believes this impact on bond yields was fairly limited. Duong emphasizes that the US dollar is more sensitive to front-end rates, and the 2y yield seems well anchored. This suggests a temporary pause in the recent strong USD trend, which should support the crypto market.  However, he expresses concern that crypto performance may recouple with US equities in the short term, which may cap the upside on digital assets due to stretched valuations. Duong also discusses the recent exploit of four liquidity pools on Curve, which didn&#8217;t help risk appetite in the crypto space but didn&#8217;t sustainably accelerate the downtrend that’s been ongoing since mid-July.  He believes the actual systemic risk associated with the exploit is limited by mitigating factors that offset some attack vulnerabilities. He also thinks this is not evidence of DeFi’s weakness but highlights the system’s antifragile properties. Related Reading: Crypto Trading Volumes Fall To Lowest Level In 2023 Amid Bear Market Woes Regarding market catalysts, Duong mentions the court decision in the Grayscale case (to convert its trust to an ETF), distributions from the Mt Gox Rehabilitation Trust to creditors, and any movement on the various Bitcoin spot Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF) applications in the US.  However, he notes that all those events are difficult to position for, so the market will have to wait for more information before pricing them in. Duong notes that flows on the desk have been balanced in the majors while altcoins have been net for sale. He also highlights Optimism’s OP token, which has traded better than expected, up 15% over the last 7 days, primarily attributed to the news around Base, Coinbase&#8217;s L2 on Ethereum. That chain, built on the OP stack, will broadly open on August 9. The total market capitalization of the cryptocurrency market stands at $1.13 trillion, which is consistent with its trading level since the start of August.  Additionally, Bitcoin&#8217;s dominance level is at 50.25%, while its price is currently trading at $29,216, showing a slight decline of 0.1% over the last 24 hours. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase’s Head of Research, David Duong, has shared his <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/institutional/research-insights/research/weekly-market-commentary/debt-serious-aug-04-2023?__cf_chl_f_tk=QA3R1OGlNFiZDWkplW4Z04cfk_pfwRG9Cte_KvtmjAo-1691168160-0-gaNycGzNDLs" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">insights </a>on the recent market movements in traditional finance and crypto. </p>
<p>He believes that current macro conditions suggest a temporary pause in the recent strong USD trend, which should support the crypto market. </p>

<h2>Key Crypto &amp; Finance Movements</h2>
<p>Duong notes that the recent carry trades upset by the Bank of Japan’s decision to raise the hard cap on its 10-year bond yield have created instability across different pockets of the FX market. </p>
<p>Meanwhile, the surprise decision by Brazil’s central bank to cut its benchmark SELIC rate by 50bps (compared to expectations of 25bps) has led to higher interest rates in some price currencies coming down.</p>
<p>In the US, the yield curve steepened significantly following the rally in Treasury bonds only two weeks ago, as the US Treasury Department announced an increase in the size of its debt issuance plans. </p>
<p>Although Fitch cut the US debt rating from AAA to AA+ due to concerns about the fiscal outlook, Duong believes this impact on bond yields was fairly limited.</p>
<p>Duong emphasizes that the US dollar is more sensitive to front-end rates, and the 2y yield seems well anchored. This suggests a temporary pause in the recent strong USD trend, which should support the crypto market. </p>
<p>However, he expresses concern that crypto performance may recouple with US equities in the short term, which may cap the upside on digital assets due to stretched valuations.</p>
<p>Duong also discusses the recent exploit of four liquidity pools on <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/curve-finance-fights-back-with-warning-and-unrefusable-offer-to-hacker/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Curve</a>, which didn&#8217;t help risk appetite in the crypto space but didn&#8217;t sustainably accelerate the downtrend that’s been ongoing since mid-July. </p>
<p>He believes the actual systemic risk associated with the exploit is limited by mitigating factors that offset some attack vulnerabilities. He also thinks this is not evidence of DeFi’s weakness but highlights the system’s antifragile properties.</p>

<p>Regarding market catalysts, Duong mentions the court decision in the Grayscale case (to convert its trust to an ETF), distributions from the Mt Gox Rehabilitation Trust to creditors, and any movement on the various Bitcoin spot Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF) applications in the US. </p>
<p>However, he notes that all those events are difficult to position for, so the market will have to wait for more information before pricing them in.</p>
<p>Duong notes that flows on the desk have been balanced in the majors while altcoins have been net for sale. He also highlights Optimism’s OP token, which has traded better than expected, up 15% over the last 7 days, primarily attributed to the news around Base, Coinbase&#8217;s L2 on Ethereum. That chain, built on the OP stack, will broadly open on August 9.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/J49W4LoC/" alt="Crypto" width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>The total market capitalization of the cryptocurrency market stands at $1.13 trillion, which is consistent with its trading level since the start of August. </p>
<p>Additionally, Bitcoin&#8217;s dominance level is at 50.25%, while its price is currently trading at $29,216, showing a slight decline of 0.1% over the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1310459406.jpg?fit=460%2C306" width="460" height="306" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545856</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
