<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 14:15:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Data Shows: Bitcoin Traders Going Long, Blast Above $30,000 Looming?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/data-shows-bitcoin-traders-going-long-blast-above-30000-looming/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 17:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544864</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin continues to trade sideways during today’s trading session, holding the line draw for the past few weeks. Recent data shows that the cryptocurrency has been recording “crab-like” price action in the short term, but operators favor the long side of their trades. Related Reading: Why This Billionaire Continues To Advocate For Bitcoin Amid Surging US Debt? As of this writing, Bitcoin trades at $29,700 with a 0.7% loss in the last 24 hours and a 2% loss in the previous week. The cryptocurrency’s implied volatility has been trending to the downside while BTC’s price holds still at its current levels. Low Volatility Set The Stage For A Bitcoin Price Explosion? Data from a report posted by crypto analytics firm Block Scholes via Deribit indicates that Bitcoin and Ethereum traders have been seeking long exposure to these cryptocurrencies. As mentioned above, this behavior coincides with a decline in delivered volatility. As a result, the BTC and ETH perpetual swap markets are experiencing a shift in funding rates. This measure determines the percentage paid by long to short positions at a given time. The chart below shows that funding rates have been trending to the upside since last September 2022. At that time, the price of Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies hit a multi-year low. Now, the BTC price experienced a 100% recovery from those levels leading to a change in the derivatives sector. The chart shows that funding rates across the BTC, ETH, and USDC trading pairs have been positive for the past three months. This data shows that traders are going long and willing to pay short positions for their exposure. A positive funding rate is often linked to the sentiment among operators and could hint at an upcoming bullish run when found on platforms like Deribit, where “smart money” trades. Why Are BTC Traders Going Long? Conversely, Block Scholes wonders: why are traders going long when implied volatility fell to new all-time lows? What’s driving operators for long exposure while the price trades sideways so much that they are willing to pay a premium? The report stated: We find it somewhat odd that traders are willing to pay such a consistently high rate for long exposure despite such low expectations of volatility. Related Reading: Bitcoin Set To Accelerate As A Store Of Value In Wake Of Bank Collapses, Cathie Wood The above is unclear; it could be traders hedging their positions on the options market could be traders getting ready for an upcoming move as the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) deliberates on the potential approval of a spot Bitcoin Exchange Traded Fund (ETF).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Bitcoin continues to trade sideways during today’s trading session, holding the line draw for the past few weeks. Recent data shows that the cryptocurrency has been recording “crab-like” price action in the short term, but operators favor the long side of their trades. </strong></p>

<p>As of this writing, Bitcoin trades at $29,700 with a 0.7% loss in the last 24 hours and a 2% loss in the previous week. The cryptocurrency’s implied volatility has been trending to the downside while BTC’s price holds still at its current levels.</p>
<img decoding="async" class="size-medium wp-image-544881" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-460x219.png" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT" width="460" height="219" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-460x219.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-860x410.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-768x366.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1536x732.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-750x358.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1140x543.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT.png 1758w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" loading="lazy"/>
<h2>Low Volatility Set The Stage For A Bitcoin Price Explosion?</h2>
<p>Data from a report <a href="https://insights.deribit.com/industry/weekly-commentary-whered-all-the-vol-go/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">posted</a> by crypto analytics firm Block Scholes via Deribit indicates that Bitcoin and Ethereum traders have been seeking long exposure to these cryptocurrencies. As mentioned above, this behavior coincides with a decline in delivered volatility.</p>
<p>As a result, the BTC and ETH perpetual swap markets are experiencing a shift in funding rates. This measure determines the percentage paid by long to short positions at a given time.</p>
<p>The chart below shows that funding rates have been trending to the upside since last September 2022. At that time, the price of Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies hit a multi-year low.</p>
<p>Now, the BTC price experienced a 100% recovery from those levels leading to a change in the derivatives sector. The chart shows that funding rates across the BTC, ETH, and USDC trading pairs have been positive for the past three months.</p>
<p>This data shows that traders are going long and willing to pay short positions for their exposure. A positive funding rate is often linked to the sentiment among operators and could hint at an upcoming bullish run when found on platforms like Deribit, where “smart money” trades.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-544877 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-860x386.jpg" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT Chart 2" width="860" height="386" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-860x386.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-460x207.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-768x345.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-1536x690.jpg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-750x337.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2-1140x512.jpg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Chart-2.jpg 1601w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px"/>
Why Are BTC Traders Going Long?
<p>Conversely, Block Scholes wonders: why are traders going long when implied volatility fell to new all-time lows? What’s driving operators for long exposure while the price trades sideways so much that they are willing to pay a premium? The report stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>We find it somewhat odd that traders are willing to pay such a consistently high rate for long exposure despite such low expectations of volatility.</p></blockquote>

<p>The above is unclear; it could be traders hedging their positions on the options market could be traders getting ready for an upcoming move as the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) deliberates on the potential approval of a spot Bitcoin Exchange Traded Fund (ETF).</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1-460x365.jpg" width="460" height="365" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Attorney Withdraws From SEC Lawsuit, Will It Affect XRP?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/ripple-attorney-withdraws-from-sec-lawsuit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 16:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple attorney]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple lawsuit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple v SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544879</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A recent development in the ongoing showdown between the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has seen the withdrawal of another Ripple attorney from the lawsuit, recent court filings reveal. This comes after a motion was filed earlier in the month for Anna R. Gressel to withdraw as attorney of defendant Ripple Labs. This recent withdrawal has cast a shadow of uncertainty as holders of XRP ponder on the likely impact of this development. Ripple Remains Upbeat Despite Attorney’s Withdrawal According to details in the filing made at the District Court for the Southern District of New York on July 27, Ripple is asking for the leave of the court to withdraw Lisa R. Zornberg as an attorney to the defendants in the ongoing XRP vs. SEC lawsuit.  Related Reading: VC Firm Sequoia Capital Slashes Crypto Fund By 65% Amid Bear Market Ripple is appealing to the court to grant Lisa R. Zornberg of the popular Debevoise &#38; Plimpton LLP permission to withdraw as an attorney in the lawsuit. This is in light of the fact that Lisa R. Zornberg will no longer be working with the law firm from July 31.  The foremost federal prosecutor was appointed by New York City Mayor Eric Adams as City Hall&#8217;s Chief Counsel earlier this week. However, this move does not in any way affect Ripple’s relationship with Debevoise &#38; Plimpton LLP as other attorneys of the firm will continue representing Ripple Labs in the case.  Ripple has also reiterated that the withdrawal of Lisa R. Zornberg does not in any way affect its interests, including those of CEO Brad Garlinghouse and co-founder Chris Larsen. It’s also important to note that the court had previously approved withdrawal motions for three attorneys Kylie Chiseul Kim, Clayton J. Masterman, and Anna R. Gressel to exit the lawsuit.   Attorney Withdraws As Case Grinds to a Close The withdrawal of Lisa R. Zornbergs comes in the wake of Judge Analisa Torres&#8217; referral of the lawsuit to Magistrate Judge Sarah Netburn. Magistrate Judge Netburn instructed the SEC and Ripple to reach an agreement on three mutually suitable dates to hold a settlement conference on issues like institutional sales of XRP. Related Reading: Bitcoin Set To Accelerate As A Store Of Value In Wake Of Bank Collapses, Cathie Wood XRP’s price witnessed a surge in the wake of the summary judgment entered in favor of Ripple. The plans unveiled by Ripple have also helped in bolstering investor confidence as the demand for XRP among institutional investors continues to surge. XRP is currently trading at $0.071, down 0.5% in the last 24 hours according to data from CoinGecko. However, its current price puts it 33% higher than its July opening price of $0.47. XRP price is 33% higher compared to July lows &#124; Source: XRPUSD on Tradingview.com Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A recent development in the ongoing showdown between the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has seen the withdrawal of another Ripple attorney from the lawsuit, recent court <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.551082/gov.uscourts.nysd.551082.880.0.pdf" rel="nofollow">filings</a> reveal. This comes after a motion was <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.551082/gov.uscourts.nysd.551082.873.0.pdf" rel="nofollow">filed</a> earlier in the month for Anna R. Gressel to withdraw as attorney of defendant Ripple Labs.</p>
<p>This recent withdrawal has cast a shadow of uncertainty as holders of XRP ponder on the likely impact of this development.</p>
<h2>Ripple Remains Upbeat Despite Attorney’s Withdrawal</h2>
<p>According to details in the <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.551082/gov.uscourts.nysd.551082.880.0.pdf" rel="nofollow">filing</a> made at the District Court for the Southern District of New York on July 27, Ripple is asking for the leave of the court to withdraw Lisa R. Zornberg as an attorney to the defendants in the ongoing XRP vs. SEC lawsuit. </p>

<p>Ripple is appealing to the court to grant Lisa R. Zornberg of the popular Debevoise &amp; Plimpton LLP permission to withdraw as an attorney in the lawsuit. This is in light of the fact that Lisa R. Zornberg will no longer be working with the law firm from July 31. </p>
<p>The foremost federal prosecutor was appointed by New York City Mayor Eric Adams as City Hall&#8217;s Chief Counsel earlier this week. However, this move does not in any way affect Ripple’s relationship with Debevoise &amp; Plimpton LLP as other attorneys of the firm will continue representing Ripple Labs in the case. </p>
<p>Ripple has also reiterated that the withdrawal of Lisa R. Zornberg does not in any way affect its interests, including those of CEO Brad Garlinghouse and co-founder Chris Larsen.</p>
<p>It’s also important to note that the court had previously approved <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/press-releases/why-did-ripple-attorney-exit-sec-lawsuit-defense-team-sleeping-whales-awaken-they-are-buying-this-altcoin/">withdrawal motions</a> for three attorneys Kylie Chiseul Kim, Clayton J. Masterman, and Anna R. Gressel to exit the lawsuit.  </p>
<h2>Attorney Withdraws As Case Grinds to a Close</h2>
<p>The withdrawal of Lisa R. Zornbergs comes in the wake of Judge Analisa Torres&#8217; referral of the lawsuit to Magistrate Judge Sarah Netburn. Magistrate Judge Netburn instructed the SEC and Ripple to reach an agreement on three mutually suitable dates to hold a <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-vs-sec-judge-orders-settlement-conference/" rel="nofollow">settlement conference</a> on issues like institutional sales of XRP.</p>

<p>XRP’s price witnessed a surge in the wake of the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-judge-deems-xrp-sale-non-investment-contract/" rel="nofollow">summary judgment</a> entered in favor of Ripple. The plans unveiled by Ripple have also helped in bolstering investor confidence as the demand for XRP among institutional investors continues to surge.</p>
<p>XRP is currently trading at $0.071, down 0.5% in the last 24 hours according to data from <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/xrp" rel="nofollow">CoinGecko</a>. However, its current price puts it 33% higher than its July opening price of $0.47.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/GtqNBi1w/" alt="Ripple (XRP) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1135927483-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Rally May Not Resume Until This Happens</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-rally-may-not-resume-until-this-happens/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 15:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin Supply]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544817</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin has continued to stagnate recently as another recovery move has failed to prosper. So here&#8217;s an indicator that may hint when a break could happen. Bitcoin Rally May Not Resume Until The Stablecoin Market Cap Goes Up Around the start of this week, Bitcoin observed a sharp plunge that had taken the asset&#8217;s price from the $30,000 level down to the $29,000 mark. A couple of days back, however, the coin had started surging again and had reclaimed the $26,600 level. This uplift in the price had come as the US Fed had announced a 25 bps interest rate hike, but before long, the recovery efforts had run out of steam, and now, the cryptocurrency has already retraced its gains from the rally. BTC has gone back towards the $29,000 level recently &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Earlier, Bitcoin had been stuck in a phase of stagnation above the $30,000 level for more than a month, but with the plunge in the price, this streak had been broken. Related Reading: PEPE Whales Load Up Their Bags As Memecoin Jumps 13% The asset now sticking near the $29,000 level may mean, however, that volatility hasn&#8217;t truly returned for the asset yet, as it still continues to consolidate, just around a different level. When a true break away from this stagnation may happen and the rally would return could possibly depend on the total supply of all the stablecoins. As explained by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, range-breaking price rises in Bitcoin this year have generally only come whenever the stablecoin supply has registered an increase. The value of the metric seems to have been heading down in recent days &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As the quant has marked in the chart, the major price increases in the past few months have generally preceded a sharp local increase in the supply of the stablecoins. Usually, an increase in the stablecoin supply can suggest two things. First, there may be a fresh injection of capital happening into the market, as investors ask for more of these fiat-tied tokens to be minted. And second, some holders of other coins like Bitcoin may be selling their coins to seek the relative safety that the stablecoins offer. Either way, such investors who hold their capital in the form of stables do so because they eventually plan to dip (back) into the volatile side of the market. Due to this reason, the total stablecoin supply may be looked at as a store of buying pressure that can be deployed into assets like Bitcoin. From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that it hasn&#8217;t exactly been the increase in the stablecoin supply that has fueled the price surges this year, but rather the decline in the metric that followed shortly after. Related Reading: Bitcoin At Decision Point As Investors Hold Neutral Sentiment These decreases in the supply suggested a transfer of capital into Bitcoin and others, which is why their prices observed a bullish boost. It&#8217;s also visible in the graph, however, that the stablecoin supply has been on a net decline in this period, meaning that the dry powder tied up in these tokens has been constantly running out. Based on this trend, if the stablecoin supply doesn&#8217;t see another major cash injection in the coming days, then the Bitcoin rally may not be able to resume. At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,200, down 1% in the last 24 hours. Featured image from iStock.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has continued to stagnate recently as another recovery move has failed to prosper. So here&#8217;s an indicator that may hint when a break could happen.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Rally May Not Resume Until The Stablecoin Market Cap Goes Up</h2>
<p>Around the start of this week, Bitcoin observed a sharp plunge that had taken the asset&#8217;s price from the $30,000 level down to the $29,000 mark. A couple of days back, however, the coin had started surging again and had reclaimed the $26,600 level.</p>
<p>This uplift in the price had come as the US Fed had announced a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/european-central-bank-25-bps-hike/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">25 bps interest rate hike</a>, but before long, the recovery efforts had run out of steam, and now, the cryptocurrency has already retraced its gains from the rally.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/NbFxGJoR/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>

<p>Earlier, Bitcoin had been stuck in a phase of stagnation above the $30,000 level for more than a month, but with the plunge in the price, this streak had been broken.</p>

<p>The asset now sticking near the $29,000 level may mean, however, that volatility hasn&#8217;t truly returned for the asset yet, as it still continues to consolidate, just around a different level. When a true break away from this stagnation may happen and the rally would return could possibly depend on the total supply of all the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/stablecoin/stablecoin-exchange-deposits-remain-low-mean-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">stablecoins</a>.</p>
<p>As explained by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/64c2ff380c84a11369407f96-No-change-in-All-Stablecoins-Supply" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, range-breaking price rises in Bitcoin this year have generally only come whenever the stablecoin supply has registered an increase.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/226984/quicktake/019f8_00beb5837aafb098964d28edb7db5c6a5b75a02de8f6990e4df62baef497f1a4.png" alt="Bitcoin Stablecoin Supply" width="1280" height="713"/></p>

<p>As the quant has marked in the chart, the major price increases in the past few months have generally preceded a sharp local increase in the supply of the stablecoins.</p>
<p>Usually, an increase in the stablecoin supply can suggest two things. First, there may be a fresh injection of capital happening into the market, as investors ask for more of these fiat-tied tokens to be minted.</p>
<p>And second, some holders of other coins like Bitcoin may be selling their coins to seek the relative safety that the stablecoins offer. Either way, such investors who hold their capital in the form of stables do so because they eventually plan to dip (back) into the volatile side of the market.</p>
<p>Due to this reason, the total stablecoin supply may be looked at as a store of buying pressure that can be deployed into assets like Bitcoin.</p>
<p>From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that it hasn&#8217;t exactly been the increase in the stablecoin supply that has fueled the price surges this year, but rather the decline in the metric that followed shortly after.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-decision-point-investors-hold-neutral-sentiment/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin At Decision Point As Investors Hold Neutral Sentiment</a></p>
<p>These decreases in the supply suggested a transfer of capital into Bitcoin and others, which is why their prices observed a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/stablecoin-cap-early-signs-of-reversal-why-goodr-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">bullish boost</a>. It&#8217;s also visible in the graph, however, that the stablecoin supply has been on a net decline in this period, meaning that the dry powder tied up in these tokens has been constantly running out.</p>
<p>Based on this trend, if the stablecoin supply doesn&#8217;t see another major cash injection in the coming days, then the Bitcoin rally may not be able to resume.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,200, down 1% in the last 24 hours.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-1367449613-1-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>VC Firm Sequoia Capital Slashes Crypto Fund By 65% Amid Bear Market</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/sequoia-capital-slashes-crypto-fund/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 14:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Fund]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto VC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sequoia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VC Funding]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544848</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Just over a year after launching its crypto fund, venture capital firm Sequoia is now rolling back its investments and taking more of a more careful approach. The firm was making some serious waves when it launched its crypto fund last year in February, signaling that crypto was ready for mainstream VC backing. But now the company has reportedly downsized its cryptocurrency fund by 65% as the crypto winter rages on.  Sequoia Pulls Back On Its Crypto Funding Sequoia Capital, one of Silicon Valley&#8217;s most prestigious VC firms, is scaling back its ambitions in the crypto space. After launching a dedicated $585 million crypto fund last year, Sequoia recently announced they’re slashing it by 65% to $200 million.  Related Reading: European Central Bank Follows US Fed’s Footsteps With 25 BPS Hike The firm has also reduced its ecosystem fund by 50%. The fund, which invests in other smaller venture funds and solo investors, is now at $450 million, down from $900 million. Insiders close to the situation said this is a result of the bear market, which has affected projects across the industry and pulled down prices significantly over the last year. Why Is Sequoia Taking This Step Now? Sequoia is known for making investments in crypto companies and had initially announced its funds as part of a larger restructuring effort to increase its investments in the crypto space. The crypto market, however, has seen most projects take a big hit over the last few months and Sequoia wasn&#8217;t left out, as it has seen a major part of its investment take drastic losses.  The company was particularly affected by the crash of FTX, as it had a $214 million investment in the failed crypto exchange. Rather than spray and pray with a large fund, Sequoia is now tightening its focus.  Total market cap at $1.14 trillion as VC investments slow down &#124; Source: Crypto Total Market Cap on Tradingview.com According to the report, the company&#8217;s new investment plan is to pivot toward smaller crypto players. The smaller cryptocurrency fund will now focus more on a select group of startup companies.  With the crypto market taking a major downturn since the announcement of its funds, it&#8217;s no surprise that Sequoia has decided to scale back. Crypto projects, in particular, haven&#8217;t done well in recent times. Related Reading: DeFi Protocol Sparks Speculation Of $16 Million Rug Pull After Severing Lines of Communication According to a recent report by Lattice, a crypto venture fund, only 5% of projects created during the 2021 crypto boom have been able to create Product-to-Market Fit (PMF). More data published by Cointelegraph also shows that the amount of money invested in cryptocurrency startups through venture capital fell by 29.73% in the month of June. While it shows a lack of faith and reflects the growing trend among venture capital firms, the pullback doesn&#8217;t mean Sequoia is abandoning the space altogether. The venture capital firm began its crypto journey in 2014 and has a history of backing innovative technologies early on. Featured image from CryptoPotato, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Just over a year after launching its crypto fund, venture capital firm <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/binance-founder-sued-over-venture-capital-funding-deals/">Sequoia</a> is now rolling back its investments and taking more of a more careful approach. The firm was making some serious waves when it launched its crypto fund last year in February, signaling that crypto was ready for mainstream VC backing. But now the company has reportedly downsized its cryptocurrency fund by 65% as the crypto winter rages on. </p>
<h2>Sequoia Pulls Back On Its Crypto Funding</h2>
<p>Sequoia Capital, one of Silicon Valley&#8217;s most prestigious VC firms, is <a href="https://chain.review/2023/07/27/sequoia-capital-trims-crypto-investment-by-65-strategic-shift-or-declining-faith/" rel="nofollow">scaling</a> back its ambitions in the crypto space. After launching a dedicated $585 million crypto fund last year, Sequoia recently announced they’re slashing it by 65% to $200 million. </p>

<p>The firm has also reduced its ecosystem fund by 50%. The fund, which invests in other smaller venture funds and solo investors, is now at $450 million, down from $900 million.</p>
<p>Insiders close to the situation said this is a result of the bear market, which has affected projects across the industry and pulled down prices significantly over the last year.</p>
<h2>Why Is Sequoia Taking This Step Now?</h2>
<p>Sequoia is known for making investments in crypto companies and had initially announced its funds as part of a larger restructuring effort to increase its investments in the crypto space. The crypto market, however, has seen most projects take a big hit over the last few months and Sequoia wasn&#8217;t left out, as it has seen a major part of its investment take drastic losses. </p>
<p>The company was particularly affected by the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/breaking-ftx-founder-sbf-on-the-brink-of-jail-judge-set-to-rule-on-bail/">crash of FTX</a>, as it had a $214 million investment in the failed crypto exchange. Rather than spray and pray with a large fund, Sequoia is now tightening its focus. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/KSAFm0LV/" alt="Crypto total market cap chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1758"/></p>

<p>According to the report, the company&#8217;s new investment plan is to pivot toward smaller crypto players. The smaller cryptocurrency fund will now focus more on a select group of startup companies. </p>
<p>With the crypto market taking a major downturn since the announcement of its funds, it&#8217;s no surprise that Sequoia has decided to scale back. Crypto projects, in particular, haven&#8217;t done well in recent times.</p>

<p>According to a recent report by <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-firms-market-fit-product/" rel="nofollow">Lattice</a>, a crypto venture fund, only 5% of projects created during the 2021 crypto boom have been able to create Product-to-Market Fit (PMF). More <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-venture-capital-funding-tumbles-economic-uncertainty-scares-investors" rel="nofollow">data </a>published by Cointelegraph also shows that the amount of money invested in cryptocurrency startups through venture capital fell by 29.73% in the month of June.</p>
<p>While it shows a lack of faith and reflects the growing trend among venture capital firms, the pullback doesn&#8217;t mean Sequoia is abandoning the space altogether. The venture capital firm began its crypto journey in 2014 and has a history of backing innovative technologies early on.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Sequoia-crypto-460x276.jpeg" width="460" height="276" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why This Billionaire Continues To Advocate For Bitcoin Amid Surging US Debt?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/why-this-billionaire-continues-to-advocate-for-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 13:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US debt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544849</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) has continued to occupy center stage, drawing varied reactions from different financial pundits. One of these voices is billionaire investor Mike Novogratz, who has yet again reiterated his support for the top cryptocurrency despite the unsettling dynamics in the United States economy. The Growing Concern: Skyrocketing Interest Payments The US is currently experiencing an unprecedented increase in debts as its interest payments reach $970 billion. This figure represents a leap of $41 billion in the second quarter alone. Observers anticipate that the rising trajectory could soon see the country&#8217;s debts surge resulting in the interest payments hitting the $1 trillion milestone, which has set off alarm bells in financial circles. Related Reading: Bitcoin Retreat Below $30,000: A Threat To Crypto’s 2023 Dominance Over Stocks? To clarify, interest payments are the actual payments that the borrower makes to the lender, typically on a regular schedule, to repay the interest on a loan or debt. The amount of each payment is determined by the interest rate and the terms of the loan. As such, the sustained upsurge of interest payments in the US economy has triggered growing unease among financial experts. Tax receipts are currently failing to keep pace with the ballooning sovereign debt. Consequently, the issuance of more debt to fund interest payments is becoming an increasingly common occurrence. This scenario has created a vicious cycle, causing concern about the potential repercussions on the nation&#8217;s fiscal health. In light of this, Mike Novogratz has once again expressed his firm support for Bitcoin. His latest advocacy came to the forefront recently when he urged investors to buy Bitcoin as the US national debt spiked by $1 trillion between June and July. Buy $BTC!!! https://t.co/UyGNaGXzyI — Mike Novogratz (@novogratz) July 27, 2023 Novogratz&#8217;s Stance: Bitcoin As A Safe Haven Despite expressing caution regarding the broader economy, Novogratz holds a sanguine view of Bitcoin&#8217;s prospects. He envisions that the cryptocurrency is on the cusp of another growth cycle, following a consolidation phase oscillating between the $28,000 to $32,000 range. However, Novogratz maintains that a significant shift in policy by the Federal Reserve, specifically a reduction in interest rates, is key for this expected surge to come to fruition. Related Reading: Galaxy Digital Founder Anticipates BTC Price Surge Due To This Reason Meanwhile, recent indicators suggest that the central bank may have different intentions. The Federal Reserve&#8217;s current stance seems to diverge from the conditions that Novogratz believes are necessary for a Bitcoin rally. Despite this, the experienced investor continues to champion Bitcoin, viewing it as a potential safe haven amid economic uncertainties. In the meantime, Bitcoin&#8217;s valuation is still persistently working to rise above the recent downward trend. The digital asset experienced a slight dip of 1% in the last day and now has a market cap of $567.5 billion. BTC&#8217;s market price currently stands at $29,309, at the time of writing. This price action follows the asset&#8217;s unsuccessful endeavor to reclaim the $30,000 mark earlier this week.  Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC) has continued to occupy center stage, drawing varied reactions from different financial pundits. One of these voices is billionaire investor Mike Novogratz, who has yet again reiterated his support for the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/standard-chartered-raises-bitcoin-forecast/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">top cryptocurrency</a> despite the unsettling dynamics in the United States economy.</p>
<h2>The Growing Concern: Skyrocketing Interest Payments</h2>
<p>The US is currently experiencing an unprecedented increase in debts as its interest payments reach $970 billion. This figure represents a leap of $41 billion in the second quarter alone. Observers anticipate that the rising trajectory could soon see the country&#8217;s debts surge resulting in the interest payments hitting the $1 trillion milestone, which has set off alarm bells in financial circles.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-retreat-below-30000-a-threat-to-cryptos-2023-dominance-over-stocks/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin Retreat Below $30,000: A Threat To Crypto’s 2023 Dominance Over Stocks?</a></p>
<p>To clarify, interest payments are the actual payments that the borrower makes to the lender, typically on a regular schedule, to repay the interest on a loan or debt. The amount of each payment is determined by the interest rate and the terms of the loan.</p>
<p>As such, the sustained upsurge of interest payments in the US economy has triggered growing unease among financial experts. Tax receipts are currently failing to keep pace with the ballooning sovereign debt.</p>
<p>Consequently, the issuance of more debt to fund interest payments is becoming an increasingly common occurrence. This scenario has created a vicious cycle, causing concern about the potential repercussions on the nation&#8217;s fiscal health.</p>
<p>In light of this, Mike Novogratz has once again expressed his firm support for <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/dormant-bitcoin-supply-peaks-as-institutional-investors/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a>. His latest advocacy came to the forefront recently when he urged investors to buy Bitcoin as the US national debt spiked by $1 trillion between June and July.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="und">Buy <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$BTC</a>!!! <a href="https://t.co/UyGNaGXzyI" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/UyGNaGXzyI</a></p>
<p>— Mike Novogratz (@novogratz) <a href="https://twitter.com/novogratz/status/1684694364679790592?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">July 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<h2>Novogratz&#8217;s Stance: Bitcoin As A Safe Haven</h2>
<p>Despite expressing caution regarding the broader economy, Novogratz holds a sanguine view of Bitcoin&#8217;s prospects. He <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/founder-anticipates-btc-price-surge-forecasts-bitcoin-etfs/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">envisions that the cryptocurrency is on the cusp of another growth cycle</a>, following a consolidation phase oscillating between the <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-12/novogratz-sees-bitcoin-rising-says-etfs-likely-to-be-approved#xj4y7vzkg" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">$28,000 to $32,000 range</a>. </p>
<p>However, Novogratz maintains that a significant shift in policy by the Federal Reserve, specifically a reduction in interest rates, is key for this expected surge to come to fruition.</p>

<p>Meanwhile, recent indicators suggest that the central bank may have <a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/business/federal-reserve-rate-decision-1.6918654" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">different intentions</a>. The Federal Reserve&#8217;s current stance seems to diverge from the conditions that Novogratz believes are necessary for a Bitcoin rally. Despite this, the experienced investor continues to champion Bitcoin, viewing it as a potential safe haven amid economic uncertainties.</p>
<p>In the meantime, Bitcoin&#8217;s valuation is still persistently working to rise above the recent downward trend. The digital asset experienced a slight dip of 1% in the last day and now has a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-realized-cap-nears-400b-price-reclaims/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">market cap</a> of $567.5 billion. </p>
<p>BTC&#8217;s market price currently stands at $29,309, at the time of writing. This price action follows the asset&#8217;s unsuccessful endeavor to reclaim the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-retreat-below-30000-a-threat-to-cryptos-2023-dominance-over-stocks/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$30,000 mark</a> earlier this week. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/lPaxSGRt/" alt="Bitcoin price chart on TradingView.com" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/andre-francois-mckenzie-iGYiBhdNTpE-unsplash-2-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Set To Accelerate As A Store Of Value In Wake Of Bank Collapses, Cathie Wood</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-set-to-accelerate-as-store-of-value/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 12:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ark invest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cathie Wood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544827</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ARK Invest CEO and crypto proponent Cathie Wood says that Bitcoin is set to grow massively as a store of value following the recent bank collapses. She believes that Bitcoin’s stability and a huge rally in the wake of US regional banks collapsing is a major testament to the fact that Bitcoin is the future of money. Cathie Wood Remains Bullish On Bitcoin In a recent interview with Barron&#8217;s, Wood maintained that she remains bullish on digital assets and highlighted three reasons she won’t be backing down on her investments. According to her, Bitcoin stood tall and rose by 60%, from $19,000 to $30,000, when regional banks like First Republic, SVB, and Signature Bank collapsed. She attributed this run to investors seeing the asset as a safe alternative for storing their wealth.  Related Reading: European Central Bank Follows US Fed’s Footsteps With 25 BPS Hike Wood explained: We see three revolutions taking place because of crypto. Bitcoin will dominate the first one, the money revolution. The biggest proof is that when regional-bank stocks were falling apart earlier this year, Bitcoin went from $19,000 to $30,000. That was a flight to safety, and we expect it to accelerate. The centralized monetary system we have today is an aberration. We could be going back to the future – before the Federal Reserve existed – under a digital, rules-based monetary system with no government oversight. The other reasons for her bullishness on digital assets relate to decentralized finance (DeFi) and digital property rights involving tokenizing several physical assets in real estate and other relevant industries.  “The second revolution is in financial services, or the so-called DeFi, which will be Ethereum-based. There are a number of infrastructure providers out there. It’s the survival of the fittest, and I’m excited to see who wins,” the CEO said. Last but not least, according to Woord, “is digital property rights, or what many call NFT or the metaverse. People are already buying real estate in virtual worlds. Our young research associates come into the office wearing jeans and T-shirts with no logos, but they are getting their status in the virtual world.” BTC bulls struggle to keep bears at bay &#124; Source: BTCUSD on Tradingview.com Weighing In On Coinbase’s Battle With SEC During the interview, Cathie Wood also discussed Coinbase’s ongoing battle with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Wood’s ARK holdings are one of the largest holders of Coinbase’s stock. She believes that the crypto exchange will ultimately get victory in the SEC’s lawsuit against it for the sale of unregistered securities.  According to her, the court will rule that the SEC has gone beyond its regulatory purview, and in the long run, the US Congress will pass crypto-friendly bills.  “Meanwhile, the legislative branch has awakened to the fact that crypto is a new asset class and we might need new legislatures to give the regulators some guidance,” the ARK Invest CEO added. Related Reading: Lacoste Unveils Exclusive Ethereum-Based Virtual Store For NFT Holders “Those two branches of government have given us great confidence that Coinbase will come out of this as a winner. Many Coinbase competitors either haven’t entered the US or moved out because of our regulatory system. Coinbase has stayed to fight. We think they’ll be rewarded accordingly.” Cathie Wood’s ARK had bought $21.6 million worth of Coinbase’s stock in early June, just immediately after the SEC filed a lawsuit against the crypto exchange. Featured image from ETF Stream, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ARK Invest CEO and crypto proponent <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/cathie-wood-bitcoin-to-1-million/" rel="nofollow">Cathie Wood</a> says that Bitcoin is set to grow massively as a store of value following the recent bank collapses. She believes that Bitcoin’s stability and a huge rally in the wake of US regional banks collapsing is a major testament to the fact that Bitcoin is the future of money.</p>
<h2>Cathie Wood Remains Bullish On Bitcoin</h2>
<p>In a recent <a href="https://www.barrons.com/amp/articles/ark-invest-cathie-wood-speaks-her-mind-tesla-nvidia-ai-meta-438bf0b7?siteid=yhoof2" rel="nofollow">interview</a> with Barron&#8217;s, Wood maintained that she remains bullish on digital assets and highlighted three reasons she won’t be backing down on her investments. According to her, Bitcoin stood tall and rose by 60%, from $19,000 to $30,000, when regional banks like First Republic, SVB, and Signature Bank collapsed. She attributed this run to investors seeing the asset as a safe alternative for storing their wealth. </p>

<p>Wood explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>We see three revolutions taking place because of crypto. Bitcoin will dominate the first one, the money revolution. The biggest proof is that when regional-bank stocks were falling apart earlier this year, Bitcoin went from $19,000 to $30,000. That was a flight to safety, and we expect it to accelerate. The centralized monetary system we have today is an aberration. We could be going back to the future – before the Federal Reserve existed – under a digital, rules-based monetary system with no government oversight.</p></blockquote>
<p>The other reasons for her bullishness on digital assets relate to <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-takes-step-towards-secure-defi/" rel="nofollow">decentralized finance (DeFi)</a> and digital property rights involving tokenizing several physical assets in real estate and other relevant industries. </p>
<p>“The second revolution is in financial services, or the so-called DeFi, which will be Ethereum-based. There are a number of infrastructure providers out there. It’s the survival of the fittest, and I’m excited to see who wins,” the CEO said.</p>
<p>Last but not least, according to Woord, “is digital property rights, or what many call NFT or the metaverse. People are already buying real estate in virtual worlds. Our young research associates come into the office wearing jeans and T-shirts with no logos, but they are getting their status in the virtual world.”</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/DMvABxzA/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1644"/></p>

<h2>Weighing In On Coinbase’s Battle With SEC</h2>
<p>During the interview, Cathie Wood also discussed Coinbase’s ongoing battle with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Wood’s ARK holdings are one of the largest holders of Coinbase’s stock. She believes that the crypto exchange will ultimately get victory in the SEC’s lawsuit against it for the sale of unregistered securities. </p>
<p>According to her, the court will rule that the SEC has gone beyond its regulatory purview, and in the long run, the US Congress will pass crypto-friendly bills. </p>
<p>“Meanwhile, the legislative branch has awakened to the fact that crypto is a new asset class and we might need new legislatures to give the regulators some guidance,” the ARK Invest CEO added.</p>

<p>“Those two branches of government have given us great confidence that Coinbase will come out of this as a winner. Many Coinbase competitors either haven’t entered the US or moved out because of our regulatory system. Coinbase has stayed to fight. We think they’ll be rewarded accordingly.”</p>
<p>Cathie Wood’s ARK had <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/coinbase/ark-invest-ceo-still-bullish-on-coinbase/">bought $21.6 million worth of Coinbase’s stock</a> in early June, just immediately after the SEC filed a lawsuit against the crypto exchange.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Cathie-Wood-Bitcoin-460x307.png" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>DeFi Protocol Sparks Speculation Of $16 Million Rug Pull After Severing Lines of Communication</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/defi/defi-protocol-sparks-speculation-of-rug-pull/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 11:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi protocol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Discord]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hector Network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rug Pull]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544826</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[DeFi protocol, Hector Network, has closed its official Discord server, leaving many investors in the dark. The move comes amidst growing suspicions of a $16 million rug pull engineered through a so-called hard rug, a process where funds are quickly moved, leaving investors with shitcoins. This comes after a controversial rage-quit vote organized by the project’s DAO.  DeFi Protocol Hector Network Leaves Investors In Limbo Hector Network investors woke up to the news that the DeFi protocol had cut off communications on its official Discord server. The Discord server was the only means of communication between the network’s team and its investors which was established after the Hector Network team censored them from the official server in April.  Related Reading: Lacoste Unveils Exclusive Ethereum-Based Virtual Store For NFT Holders The server was meant to run parallel to the official Discord, preserving data from the latter. Since then, it has become the only means of communication among DAO members. The move has left the network’s investors in a state of shock since they no longer have any means of communication with the network’s team. This has led to a lot of backlash, and according to Libagscientist, an investor and vocal critic of the platform, “there is no backchannel open anymore.”  In the absence of any official communication, dejected investors are accusing the network of siphoning the $16 million left in its treasury.  According to investors, the team embezzled the project’s funds over an 18-month period starting in 2021. According to records of DAO votes, the Hector team received over $51 million in salaries during this period without delivering on any meaningful milestone. An aggrieved investor identified as Jintu said, “..not one thing has actually moved forwards.” A Story of Sheer Incompetence and Greed The Hector Network is part of several Olympus DAO forks, a prominent cryptocurrency reserve currency project that peaked during the DeFi summer of 2021. The Hector Network, like other Olympus DAO forks, promised huge annualized yields of about 100,000% in the beginning, and the early successes of Olympus DAO attracted many investors hunting for massive returns.  During its hay days, Hector Network’s native token, HEC reached $357 in late 2021. However, the platform&#8217;s challenge lies in the fact that its inflationary yield needs to be supported with a steady influx of investor cash to keep the HEC token valuable and maintain its high yields.  Related Reading: European Central Bank Follows US Fed’s Footsteps With 25 BPS Hike Following the crypto winter that began in November 2021, the platform has been unable to recover. Aggrieved investors believe that the team should have applied the funds held in its treasury toward developing value for token holders.  Many have now accused the team of being greedy and unconcerned about meeting the targets of the network and the current saga might eventually end up in the courts. However, investors’ top priority remains to recoup their funds. Hector Network has declined requests for comments but has unequivocally rejected the allegations in a statement released on June 14. HEC token price trending low at $3.2 &#124; Source: HECBUSD on Tradingview.com Featured image from Bitcoinist, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DeFi protocol, Hector Network, has <a href="https://www.dlnews.com/articles/defi/hector-network-shuts-down-discord-server/" rel="nofollow">closed</a> its official Discord server, leaving many investors in the dark. The move comes amidst growing suspicions of a $16 million <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/encryption-a-l-rug-pulls-2-million-repay-300000-crypto-gambling-debt/" rel="nofollow">rug pul</a>l engineered through a so-called hard rug, a process where funds are quickly moved, leaving investors with shitcoins. This comes after a controversial rage-quit vote organized by the project’s DAO. </p>
<h2>DeFi Protocol Hector Network Leaves Investors In Limbo</h2>
<p>Hector Network investors woke up to the news that the DeFi protocol had cut off communications on its official Discord server. The Discord server was the only means of communication between the network’s team and its investors which was established after the Hector Network team censored them from the official server in April. </p>

<p>The server was meant to run parallel to the official Discord, preserving data from the latter. Since then, it has become the only means of communication among DAO members.</p>
<p>The move has left the network’s investors in a state of shock since they no longer have any means of communication with the network’s team. This has led to a lot of backlash, and according to Libagscientist, an investor and vocal critic of the platform, “there is no backchannel open anymore.” </p>
<p>In the absence of any official communication, dejected investors are accusing the network of siphoning the $16 million left in its treasury. </p>
<p>According to investors, the team embezzled the project’s funds over an 18-month period starting in 2021. According to records of DAO votes, the Hector team received over $51 million in salaries during this period without delivering on any meaningful milestone. An aggrieved investor identified as <a href="https://discord.com/channels/1116358879702417448/1116358880327385090/1132192275338907658" rel="nofollow">Jintu</a> said, “..not one thing has actually moved forwards.”</p>
<h2><b>A Story of Sheer Incompetence and Greed</b></h2>
<p>The Hector Network is part of several Olympus DAO forks, a prominent cryptocurrency reserve currency project that peaked during the DeFi summer of 2021. The Hector Network, like other Olympus DAO forks, promised huge annualized yields of about 100,000% in the beginning, and the early successes of Olympus DAO attracted many investors hunting for massive returns. </p>
<p>During its hay days, Hector Network’s native token, HEC reached $357 in late 2021. However, the platform&#8217;s challenge lies in the fact that its inflationary yield needs to be supported with a steady influx of investor cash to keep the HEC token valuable and maintain its high yields. </p>

<p>Following the crypto winter that began in November 2021, the platform has been unable to recover. Aggrieved investors believe that the team should have applied the funds held in its treasury toward developing value for token holders. </p>
<p>Many have now accused the team of being greedy and unconcerned about meeting the targets of the network and the current saga might eventually end up in the courts. However, investors’ top priority remains to recoup their funds. Hector Network has declined requests for comments but has unequivocally rejected the allegations in a <a href="https://medium.com/@Hector_Network/community-update-addressing-recent-security-incidents-at-hector-network-2fcf4d5c12a2" rel="nofollow">statement</a> released on June 14.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/4b9JE2xU/" alt="Hector Network (HEC) token price chart from Tradingview.com (DeFi)" width="2884" height="1644"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Hector-Network-460x259.png" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Will Skyrocket Due To AI-Driven DAO Revolution: Arthur Hayes</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-price-skyrocket-ai-dao-revolution/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 09:45:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arthur Hayes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DAO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544814</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a thought-provoking blog post titled &#8220;Moai,&#8221; Arthur Hayes, co-founder of the renowned crypto exchange BitMEX, delves into the potential impact of Artificial Intelligence (AI) on the future of economic organization and the role of Ethereum. Hayes argues that the rise of AI-driven Decentralized Autonomous Organizations (DAOs) will revolutionize the global economy and propel Ethereum to new heights. The Critical Role Of DAOs In The AI Era Hayes contends that the current economic progress and per capita wealth of global civilization can be attributed to the efficient self-organization of human societies. He emphasizes that traditional company structures, empowered and regulated by the state, have been the primary vehicles for economic development. However, he highlights the limitations of these structures when it comes to AI-driven entities. He states, &#8220;An AI has no reason to follow any laws. It cannot be coerced by the state, and therefore, exchanges that trade tokens issued by AI-powered DAOs will likely become natural monopolies.&#8221; Related Reading: Lacoste Unveils Exclusive Ethereum-Based Virtual Store For NFT Holders Hayes lays out a compelling argument for why DAOs, relying on smart contracts executed on public blockchains like Ethereum, are the ideal organizational structure for AI-driven entities. These smart contracts provide transparency, immutability, and cryptographic verification of transactions and agreements. Consequently, DAOs can operate efficiently and securely without the need for third-party intermediaries or costly auditing processes. He envisions a future where AI-powered DAOs will raise capital and trade their tokens on decentralized exchanges (DEXs) on Ethereum rather than traditional centralized exchanges. This will create truly global capital markets accessible to anyone with an internet connection. Hayes predicts that DEXs will become natural monopolies due to the advantages they offer in terms of trust, security, and ease of use. The BitMEX founder presents a hypothetical example of &#8220;PoetAI,&#8221; an AI-powered DAO that aims to fundraise and produce original poetry for profit. He envisions how PoetAI could issue its tokens, called &#8220;POET,&#8221; through a smart contract with specific attributes, such as revenue sharing and voting mechanisms. Investors can confidently invest in PoetAI DAO knowing that its financial statements are continuously available on the public blockchain, eliminating the need for traditional auditors. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Could Avoid More Downsides If It Closes Above One Key Level Moreover, Hayes explains that DAOs can raise capital by issuing debt, enabling economic time travel by borrowing from the future to stimulate present economic activity. The enforceability of contracts in DAOs can be facilitated through smart contracts on public blockchains, ensuring that investors are protected. Hayes’ Bull Case For Ethereum Hayes concludes, &#8220;Ethereum transactions will grow exponentially as DAOs proliferate. As a result, the price of ETH should skyrocket in anticipation if this AI DAO hypothesis is widely believed.&#8221; He also suggests that identifying and investing in Ethereum based governance tokens of DEXs facilitating AI-driven DAO trading will lead to significant profits. Furthermore, Ethereum middleware layers that enable visualization of AI DAO accounts will become essential for the smooth functioning of these capital markets. While these ideas represent bold predictions about the future of AI and the role of Ethereum, Hayes presents a compelling case for the potential disruptive power of AI-driven DAOs. Hayes is one of the great thinkers of crypto space and his thesis a narrative to watch. At press time, the Ether (ETH) price was at $1,863, just below the mid-range resistance. Featured image from rc.xyz NFT gallery / Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a thought-provoking blog post titled &#8220;Moai,&#8221; Arthur Hayes, co-founder of the renowned crypto exchange BitMEX, delves into the potential impact of Artificial Intelligence (AI) on the future of economic organization and the role of Ethereum. Hayes argues that the rise of AI-driven Decentralized Autonomous Organizations (DAOs) will revolutionize the global economy and propel Ethereum to new heights.</p>
<h2>The Critical Role Of DAOs In The AI Era</h2>
<p>Hayes contends that the current economic progress and per capita wealth of global civilization can be attributed to the efficient self-organization of human societies. He emphasizes that traditional company structures, empowered and regulated by the state, have been the primary vehicles for economic development. However, he highlights the limitations of these structures when it comes to AI-driven entities.</p>
<p>He states, &#8220;An AI has no reason to follow any laws. It cannot be coerced by the state, and therefore, exchanges that trade tokens issued by AI-powered DAOs will likely become natural monopolies.&#8221;</p>

<p>Hayes lays out a compelling argument for why DAOs, relying on smart contracts executed on public blockchains like Ethereum, are the ideal organizational structure for AI-driven entities. These smart contracts provide transparency, immutability, and cryptographic verification of transactions and agreements. Consequently, DAOs can operate efficiently and securely without the need for third-party intermediaries or costly auditing processes.</p>
<p>He envisions a future where AI-powered DAOs will raise capital and trade their tokens on decentralized exchanges (DEXs) on Ethereum rather than traditional centralized exchanges. This will create truly global capital markets accessible to anyone with an internet connection. Hayes predicts that DEXs will become natural monopolies due to the advantages they offer in terms of trust, security, and ease of use.</p>
<p>The BitMEX founder presents a hypothetical example of &#8220;PoetAI,&#8221; an AI-powered DAO that aims to fundraise and produce original poetry for profit. He envisions how PoetAI could issue its tokens, called &#8220;POET,&#8221; through a smart contract with specific attributes, such as revenue sharing and voting mechanisms. Investors can confidently invest in PoetAI DAO knowing that its financial statements are continuously available on the public blockchain, eliminating the need for traditional auditors.</p>

<p>Moreover, Hayes explains that DAOs can raise capital by issuing debt, enabling economic time travel by borrowing from the future to stimulate present economic activity. The enforceability of contracts in DAOs can be facilitated through smart contracts on public blockchains, ensuring that investors are protected.</p>
<h2>Hayes’ Bull Case For Ethereum</h2>
<p>Hayes concludes, &#8220;Ethereum transactions will grow exponentially as DAOs proliferate. As a result, the price of ETH should skyrocket in anticipation if this AI DAO hypothesis is widely believed.&#8221;</p>
<p>He also suggests that identifying and investing in Ethereum based governance tokens of DEXs facilitating AI-driven DAO trading will lead to significant profits. Furthermore, Ethereum middleware layers that enable visualization of AI DAO accounts will become essential for the smooth functioning of these capital markets.</p>
<p>While these ideas represent bold predictions about the future of AI and the role of Ethereum, Hayes presents a compelling case for the potential disruptive power of AI-driven DAOs. Hayes is one of the great thinkers of crypto space and his thesis a narrative to watch.</p>
<p>At press time, the Ether (ETH) price was at $1,863, just below the mid-range resistance.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-544821 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSD_2023-07-28_11-29-54.png" alt="Ethereum price" width="2830" height="1654" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSD_2023-07-28_11-29-54.png 2830w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSD_2023-07-28_11-29-54-460x269.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSD_2023-07-28_11-29-54-860x503.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSD_2023-07-28_11-29-54-768x449.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSD_2023-07-28_11-29-54-1536x898.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSD_2023-07-28_11-29-54-2048x1197.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSD_2023-07-28_11-29-54-750x438.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSD_2023-07-28_11-29-54-1140x666.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2830px) 100vw, 2830px"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/rc-xyz-nft-gallery-BStHRaoas6M-unsplash-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crunching The Data: Will Bitcoin Price Soar Or Slump In The Coming Days?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/data-bitcoin-price-soar-or-slump-coming-days/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 07:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[On-chain data]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PCE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544792</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin price is currently in an uncertain situation. After BTC broke below the one-month trading range between $29.800 and $31.500, the bulls have so far failed to recapture this area. A first attempt failed on Wednesday at $29.725, a second effort on Thursday at $29.600. On the other hand, the bears currently also fail to push the price below the critical support at $29.000. In which direction the next movement will go is, as always, pure speculation, but data can give indications. Bullish Signal 1: Decreasing BTC Supply On Exchanges Renowned crypto analyst Ali Martinez shared an intriguing bullish chart, revealing that only 2.25 million BTC are currently held in known crypto exchange wallets. This is the lowest Bitcoin supply on trading platforms since January 2018. The data suggests that investors and long-term holders are refraining from selling and are instead choosing to keep their BTC off exchanges. This &#8220;hodling&#8221; behavior indicates a positive sentiment BTC holders. Bullish Signal 2: Lack Of Inflows From Bitcoin Whales Head of Research at CryptoQuant, Julio Moreno, pointed out another bullish sign when he shared a chart showing a lack of inflows from large investors with 1,000 to 10,000 BTC (aka Bitcoin whales) into exchanges. Moreno stated, “&#8221;Not really seeing Bitcoin whale inflows into exchanges.&#8221; Additionally, the same trend is observed among smaller investors, indicating a reluctance to deposit BTC into centralized exchanges. Commenting on the exchange deposit transactions (7-day SMA) chart, Moreno added, “indeed, seems nobody wants to deposit into centralized exchanges.&#8221; Related Reading: Don’t Change The Channel! Why Bitcoin Could Target $42K If Uptrend Holds Such behavior suggests that significant holders and institutions are holding onto their BTC assets, potentially anticipating future price increases. Bearish Signal: Short-Term Holder (STH) MVRV Metric On-chain analyst Axel Adler Jr. addressed the short-term holder (STH) MVRV metric, saying: &#8220;STH MVRV is actively falling and we may see something similar to what happened in the two previous corrections.&#8221; The chart shown by Adler reveals that the STH MVRV fell either close to 0 or even below during the lows of the sharp Bitcoin price corrections in mid-March and mid-June. Currently, the STH MVRV is still somewhat elevated, so a last pullback in the Bitcoin price triggered by short term holder selling may be necessary for the MVRV to reset to 0. Adler also remarked that there isn&#8217;t a substantial Inflow to futures exchanges at the moment like there was in March and June. &#8220;Don&#8217;t expect a sharp breakthrough upwards or downwards,&#8221; added Adler. BTC Binance Spot Liquidity Analysis Analyst @52kskew shared a comprehensive analysis of BTC Binance spot liquidity, highlighting an interesting observation. The bid liquidity (bids &#62; asks) and spot asks moved lower towards price due to low volatility. He added, “note the difference in volume leading to previous selloff &#38; current falling volume &#38; minimal decline.” Related Reading: Fed’s No Recession Claim Boosts Bitcoin And Crypto, Historical Data Contradicts Given the bid liquidity between $29,000 and $28,500, this area could be the point for buyers to step in if BTC experiences a pullback. In a bullish scenario, spot buying would occur in this area, followed by a rotation out of shorts. New longs get opened and price migrates towards spot supply near $30,000. In a sell off scenario, price grinds through spot bid liquidity and forced selling occurs, says Skew. Potential Impact of Economic Data On Bitcoin In addition, it is crucial to keep an eye on macroeconomic factors that could influence Bitcoin&#8217;s price. The release of the Personal Consumption Expenditures Price Index (PCE) at 8:30 am EST today is of particular importance. During Wednesday&#8217;s FOMC press conference, Fed Chairman Jerome Powell stressed the importance of core inflation, which is proving sticky. Therefore, the Core PCE in particular, needs to continue falling to alleviate the Fed&#8217;s inflation concerns. If the 4.2% expectation for core PCE is exceeded, a bullish reaction from Bitcoin can be expected. At press time, the Bitcoin price stood at $29,210. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin price is currently in an uncertain situation. After BTC broke below the one-month trading range between $29.800 and $31.500, the bulls have so far failed to recapture this area. A first attempt failed on Wednesday at $29.725, a second effort on Thursday at $29.600.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the bears currently also fail to push the price below the critical support at $29.000. In which direction the next movement will go is, as always, pure speculation, but data can give indications.</p>
<h2>Bullish Signal 1: Decreasing BTC Supply On Exchanges</h2>
<p>Renowned crypto analyst Ali Martinez <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1684708495000551424" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shared</a> an intriguing bullish chart, revealing that only 2.25 million BTC are currently held in known crypto exchange wallets. This is the lowest Bitcoin supply on trading platforms since January 2018.</p>
<p>The data suggests that investors and long-term holders are refraining from selling and are instead choosing to keep their BTC off exchanges. This &#8220;hodling&#8221; behavior indicates a positive sentiment BTC holders.</p>
<h2>Bullish Signal 2: Lack Of Inflows From Bitcoin Whales</h2>
<p>Head of Research at CryptoQuant, Julio Moreno, pointed out another bullish sign when he shared a chart showing a lack of inflows from large investors with 1,000 to 10,000 BTC (aka Bitcoin whales) into exchanges. Moreno stated, “&#8221;Not really seeing Bitcoin whale inflows into exchanges.&#8221;</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-544804 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2EaFxiXkAA7oSq-scaled.jpg" alt="Bitcoin exchange inflows by whales" width="2560" height="1613" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2EaFxiXkAA7oSq-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2EaFxiXkAA7oSq-460x290.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2EaFxiXkAA7oSq-860x542.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2EaFxiXkAA7oSq-768x484.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2EaFxiXkAA7oSq-1536x968.jpg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2EaFxiXkAA7oSq-2048x1290.jpg 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2EaFxiXkAA7oSq-750x472.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/F2EaFxiXkAA7oSq-1140x718.jpg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px"/>
<p>Additionally, the same trend is observed among smaller investors, indicating a reluctance to deposit BTC into centralized exchanges. Commenting on the exchange deposit transactions (7-day SMA) chart, Moreno added, “indeed, seems nobody wants to deposit into centralized exchanges.&#8221;</p>

<p>Such behavior suggests that significant holders and institutions are holding onto their BTC assets, potentially anticipating future price increases.</p>
<h2>Bearish Signal: Short-Term Holder (STH) MVRV Metric</h2>
<p>On-chain analyst Axel Adler Jr. addressed the short-term holder (STH) MVRV metric, saying: &#8220;STH MVRV is actively falling and we may see something similar to what happened in the two previous corrections.&#8221; The chart shown by Adler reveals that the STH MVRV fell either close to 0 or even below during the lows of the sharp Bitcoin price corrections in mid-March and mid-June.</p>
<p>Currently, the STH MVRV is still somewhat elevated, so a last pullback in the Bitcoin price triggered by short term holder selling may be necessary for the MVRV to reset to 0.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-544801 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/STH-MVRV.jpg" alt="STH MVRV" width="1024" height="644" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/STH-MVRV.jpg 1024w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/STH-MVRV-460x289.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/STH-MVRV-860x541.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/STH-MVRV-768x483.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/STH-MVRV-750x472.jpg 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px"/>
<p>Adler also remarked that there isn&#8217;t a substantial Inflow to futures exchanges at the moment like there was in March and June. &#8220;Don&#8217;t expect a sharp breakthrough upwards or downwards,&#8221; added Adler.</p>
<h2>BTC Binance Spot Liquidity Analysis</h2>
<p>Analyst @52kskew shared a comprehensive analysis of BTC Binance spot liquidity, highlighting an interesting observation. The bid liquidity (bids &gt; asks) and spot asks moved lower towards price due to low volatility. He added, “note the difference in volume leading to previous selloff &amp; current falling volume &amp; minimal decline.”</p>

<p>Given the bid liquidity between $29,000 and $28,500, this area could be the point for buyers to step in if BTC experiences a pullback. In a bullish scenario, spot buying would occur in this area, followed by a rotation out of shorts. New longs get opened and price migrates towards spot supply near $30,000. In a sell off scenario, price grinds through spot bid liquidity and forced selling occurs, says Skew.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-544802 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/skew.jpg" alt="Binance bid asks" width="2516" height="1183" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/skew.jpg 2516w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/skew-460x216.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/skew-860x404.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/skew-768x361.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/skew-1536x722.jpg 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/skew-2048x963.jpg 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/skew-750x353.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/skew-1140x536.jpg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 2516px) 100vw, 2516px"/>
<h2>Potential Impact of Economic Data On Bitcoin</h2>
<p>In addition, it is crucial to keep an eye on macroeconomic factors that could influence Bitcoin&#8217;s price. The release of the Personal Consumption Expenditures Price Index (PCE) at 8:30 am EST today is of particular importance.</p>
<p>During Wednesday&#8217;s FOMC press conference, Fed Chairman Jerome Powell stressed the importance of core inflation, which is proving sticky. Therefore, the Core PCE in particular, needs to continue falling to alleviate the Fed&#8217;s inflation concerns. If the 4.2% expectation for core PCE is exceeded, a bullish reaction from Bitcoin can be expected.</p>
<p>At press time, the Bitcoin price stood at $29,210.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-544806 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-28_09-12-50.png" alt="Bitcoin price" width="3628" height="1672" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-28_09-12-50.png 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-28_09-12-50-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-28_09-12-50-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-28_09-12-50-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-28_09-12-50-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-28_09-12-50-2048x944.png 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-28_09-12-50-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-28_09-12-50-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3628px) 100vw, 3628px"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iStock-485863805-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BNB Price Consolidates Below $250: What Could Trigger A Fresh Increase</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/bnb/bnb-price-consolidates-below-250/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 04:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnbusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=544788</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[BNB price (Binance coin) is consolidating below $250 against the US Dollar. The price could start a strong increase if it clears the $245 and $250 resistance levels. Binance coin price is struggling to gain pace above the $250 zone against the US Dollar. The price is now trading below $245 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $240 on the 4-hour chart of the BNB/USD pair (data source from Binance). The pair might gain bullish momentum above $245 and $250. Binance Coin Price Eyes Fresh Increase In the past few days, BNB price saw a couple of swing moves from $245. The bulls struggled to push the price above the $250 resistance. The price reacted to the downside a couple of times and tested the $235 support zone. A low is formed near $253.6 and the price is attempting a fresh increase, unlike Bitcoin and Ethereum. There was a move above the $240 resistance. The price spiked above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $262 swing high to the $235 low. There was also a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $240 on the 4-hour chart of the BNB/USD pair. BNB price is now trading below $245 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours). On the upside, it is facing resistance near the $245 level. The next major resistance is near $250 or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $262 swing high to the $235 low. A close above the $250 resistance might increase the chances of a push above the $255 resistance. Source: BNBUSD on TradingView.com A clear move above the $255 resistance might start a steady increase. The next major resistance is near the $262 level, above which the price might rise toward the $270 resistance. Another Decline in BNB? If BNB fails to clear the $245 resistance, it could start another decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $236 level. The next major support is near the $232 level. If there is a downside break below the $232 support, the price could drop toward the $220 support. Any more losses could send the price toward the $212 support. Technical Indicators 4-Hours MACD – The MACD for BNB/USD is losing pace in the bullish zone. 4-Hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BNB/USD is currently above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $236, $232, and $220. Major Resistance Levels – $245, $250, and $255.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>BNB price (Binance coin) is consolidating below $250 against the US Dollar. The price could start a strong increase if it clears the $245 and $250 resistance levels.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Binance coin price is struggling to gain pace above the $250 zone against the US Dollar.</li>
<li>The price is now trading below $245 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours).</li>
<li>There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $240 on the 4-hour chart of the BNB/USD pair (data source from Binance).</li>
<li>The pair might gain bullish momentum above $245 and $250.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Binance Coin Price Eyes Fresh Increase</h2>
<p>In the past few days, BNB price saw a couple of swing moves from $245. The bulls struggled to push the price above the $250 resistance. The price reacted to the downside a couple of times and tested the $235 support zone.</p>
<p>A low is formed near $253.6 and the price is attempting a fresh increase, unlike <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-weekly-low-28880/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a> and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-downsides-1850/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum</a>. There was a move above the $240 resistance. The price spiked above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $262 swing high to the $235 low.</p>
<p>There was also a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $240 on the 4-hour chart of the BNB/USD pair. BNB price is now trading below $245 and the 100 simple moving average (4 hours).</p>
<p>On the upside, it is facing resistance near the $245 level. The next major resistance is near $250 or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $262 swing high to the $235 low. A close above the $250 resistance might increase the chances of a push above the $255 resistance.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-544789" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Coin-BNB-2.png" alt="BNB Price" width="1835" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Coin-BNB-2.png 1835w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Coin-BNB-2-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Coin-BNB-2-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Coin-BNB-2-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Coin-BNB-2-1536x707.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Coin-BNB-2-750x345.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-Coin-BNB-2-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px"/></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BNBUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BNBUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>A clear move above the $255 resistance might start a steady increase. The next major resistance is near the $262 level, above which the price might rise toward the $270 resistance.</p>
<h2>Another Decline in BNB?</h2>
<p>If BNB fails to clear the $245 resistance, it could start another decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $236 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $232 level. If there is a downside break below the $232 support, the price could drop toward the $220 support. Any more losses could send the price toward the $212 support.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>4-Hours MACD – The MACD for BNB/USD is losing pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4-Hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BNB/USD is currently above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $236, $232, and $220.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $245, $250, and $255.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Depositphotos_78872860_s-2019-460x293.jpg" width="460" height="293" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
