<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 20:55:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Cardano Whales Start 2023 With Accumulation Trend That Could Be Bullish For ADA</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/ada/cardano-whales-start-2023-with-accumulation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 23:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[adausd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano performance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515120</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) has seen some pretty tragic price action in the last couple of months, which has dragged its price down toward two-year lows. It still continues to maintain this downtrend and is barely moving, just like the rest of the crypto market, but some developments among large ADA investors could see some bullish momentum for the digital asset. Cardano Whales Begin Accumulating In New Year Toward the end of 2022 when momentum in the crypt market was dropping, there had been some selling from large ADA investors. This was not out of the ordinary as the holidays have historically triggered selling and profit-taking.  Related Reading: MATIC Holders Suffer Massive Losses, Here’s How Many Wallets Are In The Red Cardano whales had sold over 569 million ADA during this time. The result was more selling pressure on the digital asset that dragged its price down below $0.25, making its lowest price point since early 2021. As Santiment notes, this saw the total holdings of investors holding between 1 million and 100 million ADA on their balances drop drastically just as 2022 drew to a close. ADA whales increase holdings &#124; Source: Santiment However, this investor class seems to have entered the new year with renewed vigor as they have already begun buying back the tokens they had dumped. The report shows that in the first five days of 2023, these large investors have already added more than 217 million ADA to their stash. This brought the percentage of supply that they now hold back up to the 57.22% level, not the highest it’s ever been, but certainly an encouraging figure. ADA Enjoys The Spoils Of Accumulation The price of ADA is already reacting to the number of coins that these Cardano whales are buying. Over the last 24 hours, the cryptocurrency has jumped back into the green, and its price has already moved above $0.27 once more. Related Reading: Ethereum Could Jump 27% To Trade At $1,600, How Is This Possible? A continuation of the accumulation trend could possibly lead to a much larger break out for the digital asset, especially now that investor sentiment is doing much better. If this happens, a 10% upside that pushes ADA’s price above $0.3 will be easily achieved. ADA price trading at $0.26 &#124; Source: ADAUSD on TradingView.com Perhaps more important is the fact that the bulls are already mounting support at the $0.26 level. The successful switch from a resistance point to a support point also shows the determination of the bulls to continue the uptrend. However, there is still the threat of bears dragging down the price of the digital asset, especially with trading volume not growing as expected. Another fall below $0.25 will likely end up putting ADA’s price at pre-2021 levels. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from Forbes, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Cardano (ADA) has seen some pretty tragic price action in the last couple of months, which has dragged its price down toward two-year lows. It still continues to maintain this downtrend and is barely moving, just like the rest of the crypto market, but some developments among large ADA investors could see some bullish momentum for the digital asset.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Cardano Whales Begin Accumulating In New Year</h2>
<p class="p2">Toward the end of 2022 when momentum in the crypt market was dropping, there had been some selling from large ADA investors. This was not out of the ordinary as the holidays have historically triggered selling and profit-taking. </p>

<p class="p2">Cardano whales had sold over 569 million ADA during this time. The result was more selling pressure on the digital asset that dragged its price down below $0.25, making its lowest price point since early 2021. As <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1611168969301581824?s=20&amp;t=tgbZ4ZsPFqrAcTq5ksYzIA" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Santiment</a> notes, this saw the total holdings of investors holding between 1 million and 100 million ADA on their balances drop drastically just as 2022 drew to a close.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-515122 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-460x297.jpeg" alt="Cardano (ADA)" width="460" height="297" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-460x297.jpeg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-860x556.jpeg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-768x497.jpeg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-1536x993.jpeg 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-2048x1324.jpeg 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-750x485.jpeg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-ADA-1140x737.jpeg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p class="p2">However, this investor class seems to have entered the new year with renewed vigor as they have already begun buying back the tokens they had dumped. The report shows that in the first five days of 2023, these large investors have already added more than 217 million ADA to their stash. This brought the percentage of supply that they now hold back up to the 57.22% level, not the highest it’s ever been, but certainly an encouraging figure.</p>
<h2 class="p2">ADA Enjoys The Spoils Of Accumulation</h2>
<p class="p2">The price of ADA is already reacting to the number of coins that these Cardano whales are buying. Over the last 24 hours, the cryptocurrency has jumped back into the green, and its price has already moved above $0.27 once more.</p>

<p class="p2">A continuation of the accumulation trend could possibly lead to a much larger break out for the digital asset, especially now that investor sentiment is doing much better. If this happens, a 10% upside that pushes ADA’s price above $0.3 will be easily achieved.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/U19SfWVn/" alt="Cardano (ADA) price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1646" /></p>

<p class="p2">Perhaps more important is the fact that the bulls are already mounting support at the $0.26 level. The successful switch from a resistance point to a support point also shows the determination of the bulls to continue the uptrend.</p>
<p class="p2">However, there is still the threat of bears dragging down the price of the digital asset, especially with trading volume not growing as expected. Another fall below $0.25 will likely end up putting ADA’s price at pre-2021 levels.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>AVAX Value Drops By 2% Following Grayscale Removal of Avalanche From Large Cap Fund</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/altcoin/avax-drops-2-as-grayscale-rebalances-portfolio/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 23:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche (Avax)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAXUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grayscale]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515178</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In its latest quarterly update, Grayscale announced the rebalancing of funds for the fourth quarter of 2022. As part of the rebalancing, Grayscale sold off a certain amount of its Digital Large Cap Fund and dumped its held tokens, including Avalanche Network token AVAX.   AVAX has slipped by 2% following the sell-off in the past 24 hours. According to Grayscale, the sold-off AVAX tokens were replaced with the purchase of the existing fund components in proportion to their respective weightings. Grayscale Purchased And Existing Tokens The AVAX sell-off was only part of the CoinDesk Large Cap Select Index and Grayscale Digital Large Cap Fund. In its CoinDesk Smart Contract Platform Select Ex ETH Index and Grayscale Smart Contract Platform Ex-Ethereum Fund portfolio rebalancing, the company sold off Algorand native token ALGO. In its CoinDesk DeFi Select Index methodology, Grayscale adjusted its DeFi Fund’s portfolio and purchased Synthetix (SNX) after selling some existing assets.  Related Reading: Grayscale Says It May Return 20% Of Investor Capital, Bitcoin Refuses To Budge As of now, the Grayscale portfolio fund now includes 65% Bitcoin (BTC), 30% Ethereum (ETH), 1.86% Cardano (ADA), 1.39% Polygon (MATIC), and 1% Solana (SOL). Meanwhile, its DeFi Fund’s Fund Components include  65.05% Uniswap (UNI), 12.39% Aave (AAVE), 8.15% MakerDAO (MKR), 6.02% Synthetix (SNX), 4.58% Curve DAO Token (CRV), and 3.81% Compound (COMP).  Since July, Grayscale has been carefully monitoring the CoinDesk Large Cap Select Index. The index launched in April tracks the market capitalization-loaded performance of “the largest and most liquid digital assets.” During Grayscale usage of the Index, the quarterly scheduled rebalancing resulted in the dumping of Bitcoin Cash (BCH), Litecoin (LTC), Chainlink (LINK), Polkadot (DOT), and more Uniswap (UNI) purchases. AVAX Slips After Grayscale Dumped Before the sell-off, AVAX was still sitting at a $12 zone; however, after Grayscale dumped its holdings, the AVAX token dropped by 2% and traded at $11.39 Friday morning.  AVAX has appreciated over the past months. It has surged from around $9 to $13. Notably, Grayscale fund’s portfolio, which currently has $163 million in assets under management (AUM), only held a small portion of AVAX tokens. As of September 30, AVAX made up less than 1% of the company’s fund’s assets, according to its previous quarterly report. Related Reading: Avalanche: Will 2023 Bring A Fruitful Recovery For The AVAX Ecosystem? There was no significant move from ALGO, which was also removed from the Grayscale portfolio fund. It fell from a range of $0.17 to $0.15. As of the time of writing, ALGO currently trades at $11.73 with a 24-hour trading volume of $45 million.  On the other hand, AVAX seems to be gaining momentum to the upside at the time of writing as it has already formed a retracement; a reversal is likely to happen. AVAX currently trades at $11.73, down by 0.8% in the last 24 hours, with a trading volume of $125 million over the same period.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In its latest quarterly update, Grayscale announced the rebalancing of funds for the fourth quarter of 2022. As part of the rebalancing, Grayscale sold off a certain amount of its Digital Large Cap Fund and dumped its held tokens, including <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/avalanche-exits-2022-with-10-decline/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Avalanche</a> Network token AVAX.  </p>
<p>AVAX has slipped by 2% following the sell-off in the past 24 hours. According to Grayscale, the sold-off AVAX tokens were replaced with the purchase of the existing fund components in proportion to their respective weightings.</p>
<h2>Grayscale Purchased And Existing Tokens</h2>
<p>The AVAX <a href="https://twitter.com/grayscale/status/1611392521552252928?s=46&amp;t=zcoKrOKGfdFdEzvz_iTrWg" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">sell-off</a> was only part of the CoinDesk Large Cap Select Index and Grayscale Digital Large Cap Fund. In its CoinDesk Smart Contract Platform Select Ex ETH Index and Grayscale Smart Contract Platform Ex-Ethereum Fund portfolio rebalancing, the company sold off Algorand native token ALGO.</p>
<p>In its CoinDesk DeFi Select Index methodology, Grayscale adjusted its DeFi Fund’s portfolio and purchased Synthetix (SNX) after selling some existing assets. </p>

<p>As of now, the Grayscale portfolio fund now includes 65% <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-exchange-transaction-4-low-bottom/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> (BTC), 30% Ethereum (ETH), 1.86% Cardano (ADA), 1.39% Polygon (MATIC), and 1% Solana (SOL). Meanwhile, its DeFi Fund’s Fund Components include  65.05% Uniswap (UNI), 12.39% Aave (AAVE), 8.15% MakerDAO (MKR), 6.02% Synthetix (SNX), 4.58% Curve DAO Token (CRV), and 3.81% Compound (COMP). </p>
<p>Since July, Grayscale has been carefully monitoring the CoinDesk Large Cap Select Index. The index launched in April tracks the market capitalization-loaded performance of “the largest and most liquid digital assets.”</p>
<p>During Grayscale usage of the Index, the quarterly scheduled rebalancing resulted in the dumping of Bitcoin Cash (BCH), Litecoin (LTC), Chainlink (LINK), Polkadot (DOT), and more <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/uniswap/uniswap-saved-vulnerability-security-firm/">Uniswap</a> (UNI) purchases.</p>
<h2>AVAX Slips After Grayscale Dumped</h2>
<p>Before the sell-off, <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/avalanche-recovery-for-the-ecosystem/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">AVAX</a> was still sitting at a $12 zone; however, after Grayscale dumped its holdings, the AVAX token dropped by 2% and traded at $11.39 Friday morning. </p>
<p>AVAX has appreciated over the past months. It has surged from around $9 to $13. Notably, Grayscale fund’s portfolio, which currently has $163 million in assets under management (AUM), only held a small portion of AVAX tokens. As of September 30, AVAX made up less than 1% of the company’s fund’s assets, according to its previous quarterly report.</p>

<p>There was no significant move from ALGO, which was also removed from the Grayscale portfolio fund. It fell from a range of $0.17 to $0.15. As of the time of writing, ALGO currently trades at $11.73 with a 24-hour trading volume of $45 million. </p>
<img loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/YVOFy1sS/" alt="AVAX price chart on TradingView" width="1280" height="538" />
<p>On the other hand, AVAX seems to be gaining momentum to the upside at the time of writing as it has already formed a retracement; a reversal is likely to happen. AVAX currently trades at $11.73, down by 0.8% in the last 24 hours, with a trading volume of $125 million over the same period.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/AVALANCHE-AVAX-460x230.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Leads Gains Among Top Coins, Is It Set To $0.50?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardano-ada-leads-gains-among-top-coin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jammyhunts]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 22:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA Price Prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515147</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) is currently trading at $0.2752, with an increase of over 65% in its trading volume at $304.79 million. Its price change in 24 hours is +$0.006083 representing a 2.17% increase. Also, the 24-hour low of ADA is $0.2681, while its high is $0.27562. The market capitalization has risen by 2.25% to $9.51 billion. It is currently ranked among the top ten cryptocurrencies, according to CoinmarketCap, at number 9.  Related Reading: What To Expect As Bitcoin Pictures Bullish Divergence On Chart? The circulating supply is 34.52 billion ADA, with its maximum token supply pegged at 45 billion ADA tokens. ADA has performed well recently since the turn of the year, prompting optimism among holders. With the prolonged crypto winter in 2022, investors are hoping for more favorable market conditions moving forward. Cardano’s recovery has rekindled interest in the project and questions on how long it can sustain the rally. What Is Behind ADA’s Price Upsurge? ADA is enjoying increased adoption since its trading volume has increased. Investors and holders of the coin are more likely to buy into the project due to its utility. Cardano is one of the largest blockchains to use the energy-efficient proof-of-stake network. This proof-of-stake helps in energy saving and environmental protection. Cardano network also supports the creation of smart contracts. These smart contracts facilitate the creation of decentralized applications (DApps) on the Cardano network. It is also gaining more attention in Web3 and for gaming applications. With faster transaction times and regular upgrades, it is ideal for technological innovation. Cardano upgrades also undergo thorough research and scrutiny before being released to the public. ADA Price Prediction ADA is trading below its 50-day and 200-day Simple Moving Average (SMA). However, the candlestick formation on the chart shows a possible bullish run in the coming days. A thick green candle on the daily chart indicates sustained bullish pressure and will likely continue in the coming days. ADA&#8217;s closest resistance level is $0.329. Other resistance levels are $0.44, 0.595, and $0.777. If the bulls sustain the pressure, it will test the nearest resistance level of $0.329 in the coming days. The support levels of $0.260, $0.262, and $0.265 held and acted as a pivot for the price upsurge.  The Relative Strength Index (RSI) stands at 49.19, in the neutral zone above the oversold region of 40. However, the RSI will probably rise above 49 in the coming days. The Moving Average Convergence, Divergence (MACD) shows neutrality but indicates a possible uptrend. The MACD line falls under the signal line but is positioned upward. Related Reading: Why Bitcoin Will Come Out Ahead In A Recession, Top Analyst Claims The price of ADA will record a slight increase in the coming days. However, from the candlestick patterns, many red candles are present. It means that the trend can reverse at any time to a bearish pattern. Expect ADA to increase to $0.329, its nearest resistance level. Please note that this is not investment advice. The above price predictions are the analysis of the author. Always do proper research and technical analysis.  Invest the amount you can afford to lose. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cardano (ADA) is currently trading at $0.2752, with an increase of over 65% in its trading volume at $304.79 million. Its price change in 24 hours is +$0.006083 representing a 2.17% increase. Also, the 24-hour low of ADA is $0.2681, while its high is $0.27562. The market capitalization has risen by 2.25% to $9.51 billion. It is currently ranked among the top ten cryptocurrencies, according to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/curr" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinmarketCap</a>, at number 9. </p>

<p>The circulating supply is 34.52 billion ADA, with its maximum token supply pegged at 45 billion ADA tokens. ADA has performed well recently since the turn of the year, prompting optimism among holders. </p>
<p>With the prolonged crypto winter in 2022, investors are hoping for more favorable market conditions moving forward. Cardano’s recovery has rekindled interest in the project and questions on how long it can sustain the rally.</p>
<h2><b>What Is Behind ADA’s Price Upsurge?</b></h2>
<p>ADA is enjoying increased adoption since its trading volume has increased. Investors and holders of the coin are <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">more likely to buy</a> into the project due to its utility. Cardano is one of the largest blockchains to use the energy-efficient proof-of-stake network.</p>
<p>This proof-of-stake helps in energy saving and environmental protection. Cardano network also supports the creation of smart contracts. These smart contracts facilitate the creation of decentralized applications (DApps) on the Cardano network.</p>
<p>It is also gaining more attention in Web3 and for <a href="https://adapulse.io/a-look-into-the-cardano-gaming-ecosystem/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">gaming applications</a>. With faster transaction times and regular upgrades, it is ideal for technological innovation. Cardano upgrades also undergo thorough research and scrutiny before being released to the public.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-515158" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSD_2023-01-06_21-52-46.png" alt="ADAUSD" width="979" height="538" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSD_2023-01-06_21-52-46.png 979w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSD_2023-01-06_21-52-46-460x253.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSD_2023-01-06_21-52-46-860x473.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSD_2023-01-06_21-52-46-768x422.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSD_2023-01-06_21-52-46-750x412.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 979px) 100vw, 979px" />
<b>ADA Price Prediction</b>
<p>ADA is trading below its 50-day and 200-day Simple Moving Average (SMA). However, the candlestick formation on the chart shows a possible bullish run in the coming days. A thick green candle on the daily chart indicates sustained bullish pressure and will likely continue in the coming days.</p>
<p>ADA&#8217;s closest resistance level is $0.329. Other resistance levels are $0.44, 0.595, and $0.777. If the bulls sustain the pressure, it will test the nearest resistance level of $0.329 in the coming days. The support levels of $0.260, $0.262, and $0.265 held and acted as a pivot for the price upsurge. </p>
<p>The Relative Strength Index (RSI) stands at 49.19, in the neutral zone above the oversold region of 40. However, the RSI will probably rise above 49 in the coming days. The Moving Average Convergence, Divergence (MACD) shows neutrality but indicates a possible uptrend. The MACD line falls under the signal line but is positioned upward.</p>

<p>The price of ADA will record a slight increase in the coming days. However, from the candlestick patterns, many red candles are present. It means that the trend can reverse at any time to a bearish pattern. Expect ADA to increase to $0.329, its nearest resistance level.</p>
<p>Please note that this is not investment advice. The above price predictions are the analysis of the author. Always do proper research and technical analysis.  Invest the amount you can afford to lose.</p>
<p>Featured image from Pixabay and chart from TradingView.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cardano-2-460x307.png" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Whales Move Assets As Price Dips, What’s Next?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/ripple/xrp-whales-move-assets-as-price-dips-whats-next/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[David]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 21:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515142</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The crypto market is still recording the swings of the prevailing crypto winter, especially XRP. Most of the assets have not been impressive in their price movements. According to data from CoinMarketCap, the crypto market has pushed the cumulative market cap to around $812.00 billion. This indicated a drop of 0.88% over the past 24 hours. With the declining market trend, XRP stands among the assets that have lost value. The price dip has attracted crypto whales. They have moved millions of XRP tokens to different crypto exchanges. Related Reading: Dogecoin Price Falls, Is It A Wise Idea To Short? Whales Show Interest In XRP According to WhaleAlert, an on-chain data provider, there have been several transactions involving XRP. It recorded that crypto whales have transferred about 385 million XRP to crypto exchanges within 24 hours. The cumulative tokens are worth almost $131 million in the current market prices. The data provider noted that besides the most significant single transaction, many whales had moved about 70 million XRP tokens to several crypto exchanges. The value is worth about $25.6 million. The report indicated that most transfer transactions were on Bitstamp, costing $10.1 million. In addition, one of the whales moved XRP tokens worth about $11.8 million to the Bitso crypto exchange. Also, an unknown crypto whale is reported to have purchased up to 35.1 million XRP tokens. The transaction occurred during this present XRP price dip through the Bitso exchange. As a result, the whale accumulated Ripple tokens worth about $11.8 million. Notably, the largest single transaction from a whale, as recorded by the data provider, involved a transfer of over 280 million XRP tokens. The tokens are worth almost $95.4 million. Related Reading: Bitcoin Bearish Signal: Large Dormant Supply On The Move XRP Token Continues To Plummet Ripple&#8217;s native token has not made any unusual movement recently. Instead, XRP has dropped by almost 12% over the past 30 days. During today&#8217;s early trading hours, XRP dipped by 3%. At the time of writing, the token is trading at $0.3364. Also, XRP recorded about $691.2 million as its trading volume over the past 24 hours. Its market cap now sits at $16.93 billion, keeping the token at the 6th position in the CoinMarketCap ranking of crypto assets. The price trend for XRP still has some elements of instability and uncertainty. Recall that over the past three days, XRP indicated slight volatility as the price climbed to around $0.35. The coin showed a considerable presence of the bulls through its price movement. However, XRP still couldn&#8217;t sustain the reclaimed value as the token fell to the $0.33 level. A recent report disclosed that Ripple&#8217;s case with SEC might still last longer. Seven days ago, Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse estimated that the lawsuit might run for 3 to 4 months more but should end in Q1 of 2023. As the lawsuit is highly linked to XRP, analysts predict a change to a positive direction.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto market is still recording the swings of the prevailing crypto winter, especially XRP. Most of the assets have not been impressive in their price movements. According to data from CoinMarketCap, the crypto market has pushed the cumulative market cap to around $812.00 billion. This indicated a drop of 0.88% over the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>With the declining market trend, XRP stands among the assets that have lost value. The price dip has attracted crypto whales. They have moved millions of XRP tokens to different crypto exchanges.</p>

<h2>Whales Show Interest In XRP</h2>
<p>According to <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1611048312936726528" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">WhaleAlert</a>, an on-chain data provider, there have been several transactions involving XRP. It recorded that crypto whales have transferred about 385 million XRP to crypto exchanges within 24 hours. The cumulative tokens are worth almost $131 million in the current market prices.</p>
<p>The data provider noted that besides the most significant single transaction, many whales had moved about 70 million XRP tokens to several crypto exchanges. The value is worth about $25.6 million. The report indicated that most transfer transactions were on Bitstamp, costing $10.1 million. In addition, one of the whales moved XRP tokens worth about $11.8 million to the Bitso crypto exchange.</p>
<p>Also, an unknown crypto whale is reported to have purchased up to 35.1 million XRP tokens. The transaction occurred during this present XRP price dip through the Bitso exchange. As a result, the whale accumulated Ripple tokens worth about $11.8 million.</p>
<p>Notably, the largest single transaction from a whale, as recorded by the data provider, involved a transfer of over 280 million XRP tokens. The tokens are worth almost $95.4 million.</p>

<h2>XRP Token Continues To Plummet</h2>
<p>Ripple&#8217;s native token has not made any unusual movement recently. Instead, XRP has dropped by almost 12% over the past 30 days.</p>
<p>During today&#8217;s early trading hours, XRP dipped by 3%. At the time of writing, the token is trading at $0.3364. Also, XRP recorded about $691.2 million as its trading volume over the past 24 hours. Its market cap now sits at $16.93 billion, keeping the token at the 6th position in the CoinMarketCap ranking of crypto assets.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-515149 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT_2023-01-06_21-30-35-860x499.png" alt="XRP Whales Moves Assets As Price Dips, What’s Next?" width="860" height="499" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT_2023-01-06_21-30-35-860x499.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT_2023-01-06_21-30-35-460x267.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT_2023-01-06_21-30-35-768x446.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT_2023-01-06_21-30-35-750x435.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT_2023-01-06_21-30-35.png 1116w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>The price trend for XRP still has some elements of instability and uncertainty. Recall that over the past three days, XRP indicated slight volatility as the price climbed to around $0.35. The coin showed a considerable presence of the bulls through its price movement. However, XRP still couldn&#8217;t sustain the reclaimed value as the token fell to the $0.33 level.</p>
<p>A recent report disclosed that Ripple&#8217;s case with SEC might still last longer. Seven days ago, Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse estimated that the lawsuit might run for 3 to 4 months more but should end in Q1 of 2023. As the lawsuit is highly linked to XRP, analysts predict a change to a positive direction.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/pexels-worldspectrum-1108313-460x294.jpg" width="460" height="294" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Exchange Depositing Transactions At 4-Year Low, Bottom Signal?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-exchange-transaction-4-low-bottom/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 19:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bottom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Exchange Depositing Transactions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515097</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Bitcoin exchange depositing transactions are now at a 4-year low, indicating that the bottom may be here. Bitcoin 30-Day MA Exchange Depositing Transactions Have Declined As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, the metric&#8217;s current levels are the same as in Q1 2019. The &#8220;exchange depositing transactions&#8221; is an indicator that measures the total number of Bitcoin transfers that are headed toward centralized exchanges. The difference between this metric and the more popular exchange inflow is that the latter indicator tells us the total amount of BTC being deposited to exchanges, that is, the combined sum of the value of each transaction going to exchanges (rather than their total number), which is a value that can be inflated by a few whales and are thus not representative of the trend being followed by the entire market (especially the retail investors). But since the exchange depositing transactions only focus on the pure number of individual transfers taking place rather than their amounts, the metric could give a more accurate picture regarding whether the average investor is sending coins to exchanges or not at the moment. Related Reading: Bitcoin Bearish Signal: Large Dormant Supply On The Move Since one of the main reasons holders deposit to exchanges is for selling purposes, a high value of this indicator can have bearish implications for the price of the crypto. On the other hand, low values imply not many investors are applying selling pressure right now. The below chart shows the trend in the 30-day moving average (MA) Bitcoin exchange depositing transactions over the last several years: The 30-day MA value of the metric seems to have been pretty low in recent days &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As shown in the graph, the 30-day MA Bitcoin exchange depositing transactions have declined for quite a while and have recently hit pretty low values. The current levels are the lowest the indicator has observed since Q1 2019, four years ago. Related Reading: Why Bitcoin Will Come Out Ahead In A Recession, Top Analyst Claims Back then, the bear market of that cycle was at its final stages as the asset price was at cyclical lows. This means that the appetite for depositing coins to exchanges, and thus for selling BTC, is at historically low levels. This could suggest that the selling pressure may have become exhausted in the market now, and the bottom could be near, if not already, for the current BTC cycle. However, the quant in the post also notes that the bottoming process being possibly here doesn&#8217;t discount the possibility that there could still be a final downward push left for Bitcoin. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $16,700, up 1% in the last week. Looks like the value of the crypto has been consolidating sideways in the last few days &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Thought Catalog on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows the Bitcoin exchange depositing transactions are now at a 4-year low, indicating that the bottom may be here.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin 30-Day MA Exchange Depositing Transactions Have Declined</h2>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/quicktake/63b7061fa401864fc8dda539-Exchange-depositing-transactions-30d-MA-have-just-hit-their-4-year-low-Boll-band" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, the metric&#8217;s current levels are the same as in Q1 2019. The &#8220;exchange depositing transactions&#8221; is an indicator that measures the total number of Bitcoin transfers that are headed toward centralized exchanges.</p>
<p>The difference between this metric and the more popular <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-bullish-whale-exchange-inflows-down/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">exchange inflow</a> is that the latter indicator tells us the total amount of BTC being deposited to exchanges, that is, the combined sum of the value of each transaction going to exchanges (rather than their total number), which is a value that can be inflated by a few <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-surges-whales-elevated-activity/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">whales</a> and are thus not representative of the trend being followed by the entire market (especially the retail investors).</p>
<p>But since the exchange depositing transactions only focus on the pure number of individual transfers taking place rather than their amounts, the metric could give a more accurate picture regarding whether the average investor is sending coins to exchanges or not at the moment.</p>

<p>Since one of the main reasons holders deposit to exchanges is for selling purposes, a high value of this indicator can have bearish implications for the price of the crypto. On the other hand, low values imply not many investors are applying selling pressure right now.</p>
<p>The below chart shows the trend in the 30-day moving average (MA) Bitcoin exchange depositing transactions over the last several years:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/327489/quicktake/djmPb5xBO_212edaa0adb1e59bc16531e759791da1b262361cba2cab192810bbc9066c033b.png" alt="Bitcoin Exchange Depositing Transactions" width="1280" height="484" /></p>

<p>As shown in the graph, the 30-day MA Bitcoin exchange depositing transactions have declined for quite a while and have recently hit pretty low values. The current levels are the lowest the indicator has observed since Q1 2019, four years ago.</p>

<p>Back then, the bear market of that cycle was at its final stages as the asset price was at cyclical lows. This means that the appetite for depositing coins to exchanges, and thus for selling BTC, is at historically low levels.</p>
<p>This could suggest that the selling pressure may have become exhausted in the market now, and the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-mvrv-ratio-falls-to-3-year-lows/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bottom</a> could be near, if not already, for the current BTC cycle. However, the quant in the post also notes that the bottoming process being possibly here doesn&#8217;t discount the possibility that there could still be a final downward push left for Bitcoin.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $16,700, up 1% in the last week.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-515136 size-large aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-9-860x475.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="860" height="475" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-9-860x475.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-9-460x254.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-9-768x424.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-9-750x414.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/chart-9.png 976w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/thought-catalog-I0TDRP0fj6Y-unsplash-460x345.jpg" width="460" height="345" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Bearish Below $16,900 But Indicators Point Otherwise</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-price-bearish-16900-otherwise/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 18:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515093</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin price has struggled below $17,000 for multiple weeks now, and it recently dipped below the $16,900 mark. This downward move on the Bitcoin chart could be attributed to the recent Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) minutes. The minutes of the meetings revealed that the Federal Reserve System would stick with higher interest rates for the foreseeable future. This has evidently sent ripples through the market, causing participants to react negatively. The technical outlook of the asset has reflected a fall in accumulation, but indicators are still positive about the Bitcoin price over the upcoming trading sessions. From the daily chart, it can be inferred that BTC will make a recovery in the next trading sessions. Bitcoin continues to hold itself steady above the $16,600 price mark. Currently, the price of the asset is consolidated, with major altcoins following the same price trajectory. Over the last 24 hours, BTC slipped 0.6%. The Bitcoin price at the moment is trading at a 76% discount from its all-time high of 2021. The market capitalization of Bitcoin decreased slightly, indicating that sellers outnumbered buyers at press time. Related Reading: Binance Acquisition Moves See BNB Riding A Wave of Enthusiasm Bitcoin Price Analysis: One-Day Chart BTC was trading at $16,700 at the time of writing. The coin recently lost the $16,800 support level; however, this is extremely short-term as BTC will soon initiate recovery on the chart. A slight push from the buyers will help BTC propel itself above the $16,800 mark, which indicates that the overhead resistance for the coin stood at $16,900. Clearing the $16,900 price mark will pave the way up to $17,000. On the other hand, if demand doesn&#8217;t show up immediately, BTC could retrace further to sit at $16,600 before it starts to move northward again. The amount of BTC traded in the last session declined to indicate slight bearishness. Technical Analysis Despite a fall in the number of buyers, the technical outlook has managed to remain positive for Bitcoin price. The Relative Strength Index noted a downtick, which indicated that buyers were slowly exiting the market. On the other hand, however, Bitcoin has displayed a positive sign on the daily chart. The price of the asset was above the 20-Simple Moving Average line (SMA), which meant that buyers still had the upper hand in driving the price momentum in the market. Additionally, the 50-SMA (yellow) was below the 20-SMA (red) line; this is a golden cross, a pattern that is formed before the coin starts a rally. In accordance with incoming bullish strength, Bitcoin price depicted a buy signal on the daily chart. The price momentum is indicated by the Moving Average Convergence Divergence, which showed green signal bars. Related Reading: Ethereum Gains 4.5% in Weekly Timescale As Shanghai Upgrade Nears These bars were buy signals, which also aligned with the idea that the price of the asset was about to go up. Bollinger Bands illustrate volatility and future fluctuations in price. The bands were heavily constricted, in a squeeze, indicating a sharp turn in price and possible trading opportunities for traders. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin price has struggled below $17,000 for multiple weeks now, and it recently dipped below the $16,900 mark. This downward move on the Bitcoin chart could be attributed to the recent Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) minutes.</p>
<p>The minutes of the meetings revealed that the Federal Reserve System would stick with higher interest rates for the foreseeable future.</p>
<p>This has evidently sent ripples through the market, causing participants to react negatively. The technical outlook of the asset has reflected a fall in accumulation, but indicators are still positive about the Bitcoin price over the upcoming trading sessions. From the daily chart, it can be inferred that BTC will make a recovery in the next trading sessions.</p>
<p>Bitcoin continues to hold itself steady above the $16,600 price mark. Currently, the price of the asset is consolidated, with major altcoins following the same price trajectory. Over the last 24 hours, BTC slipped 0.6%. The Bitcoin price at the moment is trading at a 76% discount from its all-time high of 2021. The market capitalization of Bitcoin decreased slightly, indicating that sellers outnumbered buyers at press time.</p>

<h2>Bitcoin Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-515099 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-06_18-28-49.png" alt="Bitcoin" width="1817" height="830" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-06_18-28-49.png 1817w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-06_18-28-49-460x210.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-06_18-28-49-860x393.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-06_18-28-49-768x351.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-06_18-28-49-1536x702.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-06_18-28-49-750x343.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-06_18-28-49-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px" />
<p>BTC was trading at $16,700 at the time of writing. The coin recently lost the $16,800 support level; however, this is extremely short-term as BTC will soon initiate recovery on the chart.</p>
<p>A slight push from the buyers will help BTC propel itself above the $16,800 mark, which indicates that the overhead resistance for the coin stood at $16,900.</p>
<p>Clearing the $16,900 price mark will pave the way up to $17,000. On the other hand, if demand doesn&#8217;t show up immediately, BTC could retrace further to sit at $16,600 before it starts to move northward again. The amount of BTC traded in the last session declined to indicate slight bearishness.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-515101 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-06_18-29-33.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-06_18-29-33.png 1817w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-06_18-29-33-460x188.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-06_18-29-33-860x352.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-06_18-29-33-768x314.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-06_18-29-33-1536x628.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-06_18-29-33-750x307.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-06_18-29-33-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px" />
<p>Despite a fall in the number of buyers, the technical outlook has managed to remain positive for Bitcoin price. The Relative Strength Index noted a downtick, which indicated that buyers were slowly exiting the market. On the other hand, however, Bitcoin has displayed a positive sign on the daily chart.</p>
<p>The price of the asset was above the 20-Simple Moving Average line (SMA), which meant that buyers still had the upper hand in driving the price momentum in the market. Additionally, the 50-SMA (yellow) was below the 20-SMA (red) line; this is a golden cross, a pattern that is formed before the coin starts a rally.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-515104 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-06_18-30-00.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-06_18-30-00.png 1817w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-06_18-30-00-460x188.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-06_18-30-00-860x352.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-06_18-30-00-768x314.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-06_18-30-00-1536x628.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-06_18-30-00-750x307.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-06_18-30-00-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px" />
<p>In accordance with incoming bullish strength, Bitcoin price depicted a buy signal on the daily chart. The price momentum is indicated by the Moving Average Convergence Divergence, which showed green signal bars.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum-investors-gain-4-5/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum Gains 4.5% in Weekly Timescale As Shanghai Upgrade Nears</a></p>
<p>These bars were buy signals, which also aligned with the idea that the price of the asset was about to go up. Bollinger Bands illustrate volatility and future fluctuations in price. The bands were heavily constricted, in a squeeze, indicating a sharp turn in price and possible trading opportunities for traders.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/kanchanara-SXAmI2f4uvA-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana’s BONK Crashes 50% In 24 Hours, Is It Time To Get Out?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/altcoin/bonk-crashes-50-in-24-hours/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 17:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BONK]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BONK INU]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BONK price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BONK Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BONKUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515119</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Solana-based BONK has been all the craze since the start of the new year. The meme coin had risen from obscurity to the largest meme coin on the Solana ecosystem in less than two weeks, recording massive gains for investors during this time. However, the hype seems to have reached its peak and BONK has begun the dreaded downward correction. BONK Falls 50% In 24 Hours In the last day, the price of BONK  has rapidly declined, losing more than 50% of its value during this time. It hit its all-time high price of $0.0000049 on Thursday when the hype was at its peak but since then, has fallen to $0.000002. Related Reading: Ethereum Could Jump 27% To Trade At $1,600, How Is This Possible? This was after recording a more than 4,000% return rate in a 10-day period and reaching a market cap of over $200 million. However, as is the case with meme coins, holding on to such gains becomes impossible with no real utility and eventually, the sell-offs dragged its price back down. Being a digital currency driven by purely social sentiment, this was expected to happen, just like it did with predecessors such as Dogecoin and Shiba Inu. This drawdown in price has also seen the price surge recorded in Solana over the last week slow down significantly. However, while BONK is seeing over 53% losses in the past day, SOL recorded small gains of 0.17%. BONK falls over 50% in 24 hours &#124; Source: BONKUSDT on TradingView.com Is It Time To Sell The Tokens? With a downturn such as this, BONK could be seeing the start of the end just like Shiba Inu had done in October 2021. As such, it could be wise to get out of the cryptocurrency now if the losses were to continue for the next few days. But it is also important to take into account the growth of the meme coin, as well as the attention it is receiving in the market. For example, BONK remains one of the most visited pages on Coinmarketcap. It is second only to RichQUACK, another meme coin that has not done well in the last week. What this shows is that there are still a lot of eyes on the cryptocurrency, which could give it a leg up. Related Reading: MATIC Holders Suffer Massive Losses, Here’s How Many Wallets Are In The Red Another important tidbit is that BONK transactions had reportedly surpassed that of Ethereum in the last three days, according to data from Dune Analytics. Now, this is only at the peak of the hype and does not mean that the meme coin would be able to sustain such levels but is important to note nonetheless. Transactions surpass Ethereum &#124; Source: Twitter However, it is essential to remember that when a digital asset falls 50%, it would need to see a 100% increase to get back to its previous price, which can be a hard feat to accomplish for a meme coin. In the end, investors should keep in mind that meme coins are more volatile than the average large-cap cryptocurrency. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from CryptoPotato, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Solana-based BONK has been all the craze since the start of the new year. The meme coin had risen from obscurity to the largest meme coin on the Solana ecosystem in less than two weeks, recording massive gains for investors during this time. However, the hype seems to have reached its peak and BONK has begun the dreaded downward correction.</p>
<h2 class="p2">BONK Falls 50% In 24 Hours</h2>
<p class="p2">In the last day, the price of BONK  has rapidly declined, losing more than 50% of its value during this time. It hit its all-time high price of $0.0000049 on Thursday when the hype was at its peak but since then, has fallen to $0.000002.</p>

<p class="p2">This was after recording a more than 4,000% return rate in a 10-day period and reaching a market cap of over $200 million. However, as is the case with meme coins, holding on to such gains becomes impossible with no real utility and eventually, the sell-offs dragged its price back down. Being a digital currency driven by purely social sentiment, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bonk-joins-the-rank-of-shib-and-doge/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">this was expected to happen</a>, just like it did with predecessors such as Dogecoin and Shiba Inu.</p>
<p class="p2">This drawdown in price has also seen the price surge recorded in Solana over the last week slow down significantly. However, while BONK is seeing over 53% losses in the past day, SOL recorded small gains of 0.17%.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/gH30JCSK/" alt="BONK price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1646" /></p>

<h2 class="p2">Is It Time To Sell The Tokens?</h2>
<p class="p2">With a downturn such as this, BONK could be seeing the start of the end just like Shiba Inu had done in October 2021. As such, it could be wise to get out of the cryptocurrency now if the losses were to continue for the next few days. But it is also important to take into account the growth of the meme coin, as well as the attention it is receiving in the market.</p>
<p class="p2">For example, BONK remains one of the most visited pages on Coinmarketcap. It is second only to RichQUACK, another meme coin that has not done well in the last week. What this shows is that there are still a lot of eyes on the cryptocurrency, which could give it a leg up.</p>

<p class="p2">Another important tidbit is that BONK transactions had reportedly surpassed that of Ethereum in the last three days, according to data from <a href="https://dune.com/wagg/bonk-stats" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Dune Analytics</a>. Now, this is only at the peak of the hype and does not mean that the meme coin would be able to sustain such levels but is important to note nonetheless.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-515128 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BONK-transactions-460x195.jpeg" alt="BONK transactions" width="460" height="195" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BONK-transactions-460x195.jpeg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BONK-transactions-860x364.jpeg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BONK-transactions-768x325.jpeg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BONK-transactions-1536x650.jpeg 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BONK-transactions-750x317.jpeg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BONK-transactions-1140x482.jpeg 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BONK-transactions.jpeg 1920w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p class="p2">However, it is essential to remember that when a digital asset falls 50%, it would need to see a 100% increase to get back to its previous price, which can be a hard feat to accomplish for a meme coin. In the end, investors should keep in mind that meme coins are more volatile than the average large-cap cryptocurrency.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BONK-transactions-1-460x195.jpeg" width="460" height="195" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Bitcoin Will Come Out Ahead In A Recession, Top Analyst Claims</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/bitcoin-recession-analyst-claims/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 15:27:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Breaking News Ticker]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515112</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin keeps moving with no clear direction in the first week of 2023. Following a rejection from a critical resistance zone, the cryptocurrency returned to its range and could be gearing up for a re-test of support.  Related Reading: Dogecoin Price Falls, Is It A Wise Idea To Short? In the meantime, altcoins are blooming, with many recording profits on high timeframes. As of this writing, Bitcoin (BTC) trades at $16,700 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. In the previous seven days, BTC records similar price action.  BTC In The Short Term, What&#8217;s Driving The Price Action? Bitcoin is reacting to macroeconomic developments and the U.S. Federal Reserve (Fed) monetary policy in the short term. As NewsBTC reported yesterday, investors are hesitant to trade in any direction due to uncertainty around global markets. The situation is likely to persist during January. Today the U.S. released new economic data, but with &#8220;mixed&#8221; results, according to a pseudonym analyst:  Economic Data a bit mixed. More jobs than expected but lower hourly earnings which is the second most important number I&#8217;d say. The matter in which the market will digest this is the most telling factor in my opinion. The unemployment rate in the United States printed 3.5% for December 2022, which came much lower than the market expected. The Fed uses this metric to gauge the efficacy of its monetary policy.  The higher unemployment, the more they can tame inflation, but the U.S. job market has been resilient and has remained strong despite the Fed&#8217;s intentions. In that sense, Bitcoin and risk-on assets reacted with small losses.  The lower-than-expected results in unemployment provide room for the Fed to continue tightening. However, the risk of an economic recession increases as the financial institution pushes on to bring down inflation.  Bitcoin Will Make It During A Recession? In a recessionary economic scenario, Bloomberg Intelligence Senior Macro Strategy, Mike McGlone, believes Bitcoin will thrive. The analyst is bullish on BTC for the long term but shared some reservations about its immediate future.  McGlone expects Bitcoin to revisit critical support at around $10,000 to $12,000 in an economic recession. This massive crash will ripple across the nascent industry and operate as the final catalyzer for another rally. The analyst said: The rising potential for a severe global economic slowdown may be a top crypto performance factor in 20222. Out bias is that Bitcoin is more likely to come out ahead in most scenarios (…). Related Reading: Bitcoin Bearish Signal: Large Dormant Supply On The Move If this scenario continues, the cryptocurrency could start trading as Gold and a store of value assets, similar to its performance from 2020 to 2021. Right now, BTC trades as a risk asset, but the status quo is poised for a change as the global economy enters a critical stage. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Bitcoin keeps moving with no clear direction in the first week of 2023. Following a rejection from a critical resistance zone, the cryptocurrency returned to its range and could be gearing up for a re-test of support. </strong></p>

<p>In the meantime, altcoins are blooming, with many recording profits on high timeframes. As of this writing, Bitcoin (BTC) trades at $16,700 with sideways movement in the last 24 hours. In the previous seven days, BTC records similar price action. </p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-515132 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSD-860x376.png" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT" width="860" height="376" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSD-860x376.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSD-460x201.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSD-768x336.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSD-1536x672.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSD-750x328.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSD-1140x499.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSD.png 1813w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<h2>BTC In The Short Term, What&#8217;s Driving The Price Action?</h2>
<p>Bitcoin is reacting to macroeconomic developments and the U.S. Federal Reserve (Fed) monetary policy in the short term. As NewsBTC <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-price-catch-up-28000-is-key-level/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> yesterday, investors are hesitant to trade in any direction due to uncertainty around global markets.</p>
<p>The situation is likely to persist during January. Today the U.S. released new economic data, but with &#8220;mixed&#8221; results, <a href="https://twitter.com/DaanCrypto/status/1611355568647671810" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">according to a pseudonym analyst</a>: </p>
<blockquote><p>Economic Data a bit mixed. More jobs than expected but lower hourly earnings which is the second most important number I&#8217;d say. The matter in which the market will digest this is the most telling factor in my opinion.</p></blockquote>
<p>The unemployment rate in the United States printed 3.5% for December 2022, which came much lower than the market expected. The Fed uses this metric to gauge the efficacy of its monetary policy. </p>
<p>The higher unemployment, the more they can tame inflation, but the U.S. job market has been resilient and has remained strong despite the Fed&#8217;s intentions. In that sense, Bitcoin and risk-on assets reacted with small losses. </p>
<p>The lower-than-expected results in unemployment provide room for the Fed to continue tightening. However, the risk of an economic recession increases as the financial institution pushes on to bring down inflation. </p>
Bitcoin Will Make It During A Recession?
<p>In a recessionary economic scenario, Bloomberg Intelligence Senior Macro Strategy, Mike McGlone, <a href="https://twitter.com/mikemcglone11/status/1611063638684536860" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">believes</a> Bitcoin will thrive. The analyst is bullish on BTC for the long term but shared some reservations about its immediate future. </p>
<p>McGlone expects Bitcoin to revisit critical support at around $10,000 to $12,000 in an economic recession. This massive crash will ripple across the nascent industry and operate as the final catalyzer for another rally. The analyst said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The rising potential for a severe global economic slowdown may be a top crypto performance factor in 20222. Out bias is that Bitcoin is more likely to come out ahead in most scenarios (…).</p></blockquote>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-515129 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-860x594.jpg" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT" width="860" height="594" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-860x594.jpg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-460x318.jpg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-768x530.jpg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-750x518.jpg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT.jpg 962w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />

<p>If this scenario continues, the cryptocurrency could start trading as Gold and a store of value assets, similar to its performance from 2020 to 2021. Right now, BTC trades as a risk asset, but the status quo is poised for a change as the global economy enters a critical stage. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-460x306.jpeg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>What To Expect As Bitcoin Pictures Bullish Divergence On Chart?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/expect-bitcoin-bullish-divergence/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 15:06:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=514777</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin price has been making a slight recovery on its chart. Although the coin has been consolidating over the past few weeks, BTC has been attempting to make an upward movement. Over the last 24 hours, the coin has registered a 0.6% appreciation. Looking at the weekly progress, BTC has been stuck between two price levels of $16,400 and $16,900, respectively. Going by the technical outlook, the coin has depicted positive sentiments, with buyers slowly returning to the market. It also formed a bullish pattern on the daily chart, which meant that the price might encounter a recovery over the upcoming trading sessions. The accumulation showed up on the chart, which meant that the coin was experiencing demand over the past trading sessions. BTC has also formed a double bottom pattern, which is a charting pattern that resonates with an upcoming major move for the king coin. At the moment, Bitcoin is trading 76% below its all-time high, which was secured in the past year. The market capitalization of BTC also noted an increase, signifying bullish strength building up. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Plays Catch-Up With Altcoins, Why $28,000 Is A Key Level Bitcoin Price Analysis: One-Day Chart BTC was trading at $16,800 at the time of writing. The coin crossed the $16,800 mark as demand surged. Overhead resistance for Bitcoin stood at $17,000. The double bottom formed by Bitcoin might cause the coin to rally and move above $17,000. On the other hand, if Bitcoin slips from its current price level, then the support zone for the coin stands at $16,400. A fall from $16,400 will drag the price down to $16,100. The amount of BTC traded in the last session was green, which meant that the coin was entering a bullish zone. Technical Analysis Bitcoin demand has been increasing in recent trading sessions. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) moved up closer to the half-line and touched it, recording an increase in buyers. The RSI also formed a bullish divergence (white), which is a sign of positive price action. Similarly, Bitcoin price travelled above the 20-Simple Moving Average line, which meant buyers were driving the price action in the market. A move above the 50-SMA will ensure the BTC price trades above the $17,400 mark. In relation to bullishness, other technical indicators have also sided with the incoming bullish force. The Chaikin Money Flow (CMF), which indicates capital inflows and outflows at a given time, registered positive movement. CMF was positive and above the half-line, which portrayed an increase in capital inflows. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) is responsible for reading price momentum and reversals of the same. MACD demonstrated green histograms, which were buy signals for the coin. This meant that Bitcoin could anticipate an increase in price. Related Reading: Ethereum Stakers In Massive Loss As 80% of Staked ETH Is In The Red Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin price has been making a slight recovery on its chart. Although the coin has been consolidating over the past few weeks, BTC has been attempting to make an upward movement. Over the last 24 hours, the coin has registered a 0.6% appreciation.</p>
<p>Looking at the weekly progress, BTC has been stuck between two price levels of $16,400 and $16,900, respectively. Going by the technical outlook, the coin has depicted positive sentiments, with buyers slowly returning to the market.</p>
<p>It also formed a bullish pattern on the daily chart, which meant that the price might encounter a recovery over the upcoming trading sessions. The accumulation showed up on the chart, which meant that the coin was experiencing demand over the past trading sessions.</p>
<p>BTC has also formed a double bottom pattern, which is a charting pattern that resonates with an upcoming major move for the king coin. At the moment, Bitcoin is trading 76% below its all-time high, which was secured in the past year. The market capitalization of BTC also noted an increase, signifying bullish strength building up.</p>

<h2>Bitcoin Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514794 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-04_19-48-21.png" alt="Bitcoin" width="1817" height="830" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-04_19-48-21.png 1817w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-04_19-48-21-460x210.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-04_19-48-21-860x393.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-04_19-48-21-768x351.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-04_19-48-21-1536x702.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-04_19-48-21-750x343.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-04_19-48-21-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px" />
<p>BTC was trading at $16,800 at the time of writing. The coin crossed the $16,800 mark as demand surged. Overhead resistance for Bitcoin stood at $17,000. The double bottom formed by Bitcoin might cause the coin to rally and move above $17,000.</p>
<p>On the other hand, if Bitcoin slips from its current price level, then the support zone for the coin stands at $16,400. A fall from $16,400 will drag the price down to $16,100. The amount of BTC traded in the last session was green, which meant that the coin was entering a bullish zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514798 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-04_19-49-43.png" alt="Bitcoin" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-04_19-49-43.png 1817w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-04_19-49-43-460x188.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-04_19-49-43-860x352.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-04_19-49-43-768x314.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-04_19-49-43-1536x628.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-04_19-49-43-750x307.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-04_19-49-43-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px" />
<p>Bitcoin demand has been increasing in recent trading sessions. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) moved up closer to the half-line and touched it, recording an increase in buyers. The RSI also formed a bullish divergence (white), which is a sign of positive price action.</p>
<p>Similarly, Bitcoin price travelled above the 20-Simple Moving Average line, which meant buyers were driving the price action in the market. A move above the 50-SMA will ensure the BTC price trades above the $17,400 mark.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-514799 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-04_19-55-17.png" alt="Bitcoin" width="1817" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-04_19-55-17.png 1817w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-04_19-55-17-460x188.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-04_19-55-17-860x352.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-04_19-55-17-768x314.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-04_19-55-17-1536x628.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-04_19-55-17-750x307.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD_2023-01-04_19-55-17-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1817px) 100vw, 1817px" />
<p>In relation to bullishness, other technical indicators have also sided with the incoming bullish force. The Chaikin Money Flow (CMF), which indicates capital inflows and outflows at a given time, registered positive movement.</p>
<p>CMF was positive and above the half-line, which portrayed an increase in capital inflows. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) is responsible for reading price momentum and reversals of the same. MACD demonstrated green histograms, which were buy signals for the coin. This meant that Bitcoin could anticipate an increase in price.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum-stakers-in-massive-loss/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum Stakers In Massive Loss As 80% of Staked ETH Is In The Red</a></p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/kanchanara-pCMWBd6UfYo-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Price Falls, Is It A Wise Idea To Short?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/dogecoin-2/dogecoin-price-falls-wise-to-short/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 15:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515115</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Dogecoin price has remained motionless over the past several weeks. In recent times, due to constant lateral trading, DOGE lost the $0.072 support line. Over the past 24 hours, the coin has dipped nearly 3% on its chart. The meme coin has only moved 0.7% in the last week. As Bitcoin started to act wobbly on its chart, many altcoins that had made gains started to retrace on their respective charts. Technical indicators, however, suggest that the asset might register gains over the next trading session. The coin has registered a fall in demand on the chart, but that is not supposed to last for long. Although DOGE had pierced through several support lines, the coin could soon make up for the loss. The crucial resistance mark for Dogecoin stood at $0.078. Buying pressure has to return to the market for Dogecoin price to target a move above $0.078 and attempt to trade near $0.080. Touching the $0.080 mark will invalidate the bearish thesis for a significant period of time. The market capitalization of Dogecoin did not indicate that bears were crawling back into the market. Related Reading: XRP Price Primed For Future Rally Following Ripple’s MENA Expansion Dogecoin Price Analysis: One-Day Chart DOGE was selling at $0.070 at press time. The coin was secured on top of its $0.066 support line, but a fall from the $0.066 level will ensure that the bears are completely back. Overhead resistance for the coin stood at $0.072 and then at $0.078. As far as the indicators are concerned, the Dogecoin price shall not have too much difficulty moving above the $0.072 level, but the $0.078 price mark will prove to be a tough resistance level for Dogecoin, causing the coin to fall in value. In regard to the shorting opportunity, it is better to wait as the Dogecoin price is eyeing the next resistance level. Shorting at the moment will cause further losses for traders. The amount of Dogecoin traded in the last session fell, indicating a bearish bias. Technical Analysis A fall in accumulation on the daily chart has caused Dogecoin buyers to fade from the market. The Relative Strength Index was below the 40 mark, indicating that sellers were stronger than buyers in the market. Dogecoin&#8217;s price was below the 20-Simple Moving Average line, which again reiterated that sellers were driving the price momentum in the market. Despite that, an increase in demand will push the meme coin to rise above the 200-SMA (green) line, which is considered extremely bullish. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Consolidates Gains, Why ETH Could Start Another Increase Over the past trading sessions, whenever the Dogecoin price rose above the 200-SMA line, the coin rallied. This is why shorting the asset right now would not be a wise idea. In view of the price rising over the next few trading sessions, the technical indicators have displayed buy signals. Contrary to shorting, the asset has presented an entry point for traders. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence shows the price momentum; it formed green signal bars, indicating a buy signal for the coin. Similarly, the Awesome Oscillator suggests the price trend and direction, while the indicator also displayed green histograms tied to buy signals. The buy signals translate to the price going up in the upcoming sessions. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Dogecoin price has remained motionless over the past several weeks. In recent times, due to constant lateral trading, DOGE lost the $0.072 support line. Over the past 24 hours, the coin has dipped nearly 3% on its chart.</p>
<p>The meme coin has only moved 0.7% in the last week. As Bitcoin started to act wobbly on its chart, many altcoins that had made gains started to retrace on their respective charts. Technical indicators, however, suggest that the asset might register gains over the next trading session.</p>
<p>The coin has registered a fall in demand on the chart, but that is not supposed to last for long. Although DOGE had pierced through several support lines, the coin could soon make up for the loss. The crucial resistance mark for Dogecoin stood at $0.078.</p>
<p>Buying pressure has to return to the market for Dogecoin price to target a move above $0.078 and attempt to trade near $0.080. Touching the $0.080 mark will invalidate the bearish thesis for a significant period of time. The market capitalization of Dogecoin did not indicate that bears were crawling back into the market.</p>

<h2>Dogecoin Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-515117 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-06_19-41-44.png" alt="Dogecoin Price" width="1816" height="830" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-06_19-41-44.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-06_19-41-44-460x210.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-06_19-41-44-860x393.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-06_19-41-44-768x351.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-06_19-41-44-1536x702.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-06_19-41-44-750x343.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-06_19-41-44-1140x521.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>DOGE was selling at $0.070 at press time. The coin was secured on top of its $0.066 support line, but a fall from the $0.066 level will ensure that the bears are completely back. Overhead resistance for the coin stood at $0.072 and then at $0.078.</p>
<p>As far as the indicators are concerned, the Dogecoin price shall not have too much difficulty moving above the $0.072 level, but the $0.078 price mark will prove to be a tough resistance level for Dogecoin, causing the coin to fall in value.</p>
<p>In regard to the shorting opportunity, it is better to wait as the Dogecoin price is eyeing the next resistance level. Shorting at the moment will cause further losses for traders. The amount of Dogecoin traded in the last session fell, indicating a bearish bias.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-515118 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-06_19-42-33.png" alt="Dogecoin Price" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-06_19-42-33.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-06_19-42-33-460x188.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-06_19-42-33-860x352.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-06_19-42-33-768x314.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-06_19-42-33-1536x628.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-06_19-42-33-750x307.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-06_19-42-33-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>A fall in accumulation on the daily chart has caused Dogecoin buyers to fade from the market. The Relative Strength Index was below the 40 mark, indicating that sellers were stronger than buyers in the market.</p>
<p>Dogecoin&#8217;s price was below the 20-Simple Moving Average line, which again reiterated that sellers were driving the price momentum in the market. Despite that, an increase in demand will push the meme coin to rise above the 200-SMA (green) line, which is considered extremely bullish.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-consolidates-1200/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum Price Consolidates Gains, Why ETH Could Start Another Increase</a></p>
<p>Over the past trading sessions, whenever the Dogecoin price rose above the 200-SMA line, the coin rallied. This is why shorting the asset right now would not be a wise idea.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-515121 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-06_19-43-09.png" alt="Dogecoin Price" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-06_19-43-09.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-06_19-43-09-460x188.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-06_19-43-09-860x352.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-06_19-43-09-768x314.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-06_19-43-09-1536x628.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-06_19-43-09-750x307.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOGEUSD_2023-01-06_19-43-09-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>In view of the price rising over the next few trading sessions, the technical indicators have displayed buy signals. Contrary to shorting, the asset has presented an entry point for traders. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence shows the price momentum; it formed green signal bars, indicating a buy signal for the coin.</p>
<p>Similarly, the Awesome Oscillator suggests the price trend and direction, while the indicator also displayed green histograms tied to buy signals. The buy signals translate to the price going up in the upcoming sessions.</p>




]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/kanchanara-ds7OD7n8XDQ-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
