<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 15:33:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ethereum Stalls At $1,200, Why Bears Still Have The Upper Hand</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-stalls-at-1200/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 23:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH performance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513564</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum is still closely mirroring the price of bitcoin through the bear market and that has seen its price basically stall in the last day in tandem with BTC. ETH’s price is presently resting just above $1,200, and while this would have served as a good bounce-off point for the digital asset, it shows no signs of doing so. Ethereum Price Stuck At $1,200 Given the current market circumstances, Ethereum at $1,200 presents one of the best prices that the market will see for the digital asset before 2022 runs out. The momentum in the market was already on a decline but the 49% jump in Ethereum’s trading volume in the last day put a perhaps temporary stop to that decline. Short-term indicators pointing towards sell points to this being temporary. Now, for the lull in price, it can be explained by ETH’s price sitting so close to the 20-day moving average of $1,247. Since there isn’t much movement in the market, it makes sense that the digital asset would only try to maintain its price at just above $1,200 at this time. Related Reading: Ethereum Classic Hashrate Dumps Almost 50% In 3 Months, What About ETC? Bitcoin’s tight correlation to the stock market has also impacted Ethereum. Although cryptocurrencies did not fall like the stock market following the release of the US GDP data on Thursday, it definitely hindered any growth from taking place in the market. ETH price struggling at $1,200 &#124; Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com Why Is ETH Struggling? Ethereum has received some bad press over the last couple of days. One of the most prominent was when the Paxful peer-to-peer exchange announced that it was delisting Ethereum. CEO Ray Youssef presented the reason as “Integrity over revenue” as the exchange believes that the network was not decentralized. This stoked fears that had previously subsided following the move to proof of stake. For many, this move made Ethereum much easier to control and Youssef said, “One day you will need permission to use it.” Related Reading: Exchange Inflows, Outflows At A Stalemate As Bitcoin Refuses To Budge Given this, the price of ETH has buckled under the pressure of the FUD it created. If bulls are unable to hold the $1,200 support, then it could send the digital asset into free fall, with no significant support until $1,140. The cryptocurrency is already headed for a close below its year-to-date peak but a close below $1,200 would see it start the new year with a very bearish outlook. ETH is trading at $1,224 at the time of this writing, according to data from Coinmarketcap. It is up 0.64% in the last 24 hours and boasts a market cap of $149.8 billion. Featured image from Ledger Insights, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Ethereum is still closely mirroring the price of bitcoin through the bear market and that has seen its price basically stall in the last day in tandem with BTC. ETH’s price is presently resting just above $1,200, and while this would have served as a good bounce-off point for the digital asset, it shows no signs of doing so.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Ethereum Price Stuck At $1,200</h2>
<p class="p2">Given the current market circumstances, Ethereum at $1,200 presents one of the best prices that the market will see for the digital asset before 2022 runs out. The momentum in the market was already on a decline but the 49% jump in Ethereum’s trading volume in the last day put a perhaps temporary stop to that decline. Short-term indicators pointing towards sell points to this being temporary.</p>
<p class="p2">Now, for the lull in price, it can be explained by ETH’s price sitting so close to the 20-day moving average of $1,247. Since there isn’t much movement in the market, it makes sense that the digital asset would only try to maintain its price at just above $1,200 at this time.</p>

<p class="p2">Bitcoin’s tight correlation to the stock market has also impacted Ethereum. Although cryptocurrencies did not fall like the stock market following the release of the US GDP data on Thursday, it definitely hindered any growth from taking place in the market.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/zA8Jgp8N/" alt="Ethereum price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1646" /></p>

<h2 class="p2">Why Is ETH Struggling?</h2>
<p class="p2">Ethereum has received some bad press over the last couple of days. One of the most prominent was when the Paxful peer-to-peer exchange <a href="https://twitter.com/raypaxful/status/1605529289054527488?s=20&amp;t=FoVWLKR7msdnjKOfZTUB4Q" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">announced</a> that it was delisting Ethereum. CEO Ray Youssef presented the reason as “Integrity over revenue” as the exchange believes that the network was not decentralized.</p>
<p class="p2">This stoked fears that had previously subsided following the move to proof of stake. For many, this move made Ethereum much easier to control and Youssef said, “One day you will need permission to use it.”</p>

<p class="p2">Given this, the price of ETH has buckled under the pressure of the FUD it created. If bulls are unable to hold the $1,200 support, then it could send the digital asset into free fall, with no significant support until $1,140. The cryptocurrency is already headed for a close below its year-to-date peak but a close below $1,200 would see it start the new year with a very bearish outlook.</p>
<p class="p2">ETH is trading at $1,224 at the time of this writing, according to data from Coinmarketcap. It is up 0.64% in the last 24 hours and boasts a market cap of $149.8 billion.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-460x298.jpeg" width="460" height="298" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Token Jumps 65% As SBF Returns Home, Can FTT Hold The Gains?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/ftx/can-ftt-hold-the-gains/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 17:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTT token]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Token]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513563</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[FTX Token (FTT) saw massive gains on Thursday as news of former CEO Sam Bankman-Fried making bail spread across the space. The rapid uptick in the price of the token showed the positivity, albeit brief, that had spread across investors in the token. However, as the dust settles on the disgraced founder, the question now becomes whether the digital asset can hold the gains from yesterday. FTT Jumps 65%  On Thursday, Bankman-Fried’s parents had put their home up to raise money for the $250 million bond put on the former CEO, with friends and associates speculated to have helped come up with the 10% collateral required for his release. However this was achieved, Sam was released under house arrest. Related Reading: Exchange Inflows, Outflows At A Stalemate As Bitcoin Refuses To Budge Soon after the news broke, the price of FTX’s native token FTT made a significant jump. After trending just below $1 for the better part of the week, the 65% push had brought it above $1.1. This brought renewed vigor to the market and momentum rightfully picked up. FTT price spikes following SBF making bail &#124; Source: FTTUSD on TradingView.com The problem now is that FTT has not done a good job of holding onto these gains. Naturally, the brief surge in price had triggered sell-offs among investors looking to take out some profit, triggering another fall below $1. In the early hours of Friday, there had been a 9% jump that brought FTT’s price above $1 once more, but even this would not hold. Support remains weak at $1 and it is now a battle between the bears and the bulls to turn this critical level in their favor. Right now, the bears remain in control of the digital asset with the price sitting at $0.96, and FTT has struggled to break the resistance mounting at $1. What About FTX? For many in the space who lost money when the FTX crypto exchange collapsed, this is just the beginning of the battle. Charges have already been brought against Bankman-Fried and his associates in what is being called the ‘largest fraud of the generation’ but there is still a long way to go. On Thursday, it was reported that Paul Hastings LLP had been appointed by a committee to represent the interests of creditors in the FTX bankruptcy case. So far, the new FTX CEO John J. Ray III said he and his team had been able to recover around $1 billion worth of assets. Related Reading: Ethereum Classic Hashrate Dumps Almost 50% In 3 Months, What About ETC? Former Alameda Research executive Caroline Ellison and FTX co-founder Gary Wang have already pled guilty to fraud charges and agreed to work with authorities. Both have been released on $250,000 bonds with travel restrictions. As the FTX case develops, it is expectedly going to have a big impact on the price movements of FTT tokens. Given this, investors should exercise caution when investing and trading the cryptocurrency. Featured image from Bitcoinist, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">FTX Token (FTT) saw massive gains on Thursday as news of former CEO Sam Bankman-Fried making bail spread across the space. The rapid uptick in the price of the token showed the positivity, albeit brief, that had spread across investors in the token. However, as the dust settles on the disgraced founder, the question now becomes whether the digital asset can hold the gains from yesterday.</p>
<h2 class="p2">FTT Jumps 65% </h2>
<p class="p2">On Thursday, Bankman-Fried’s parents had put their home up to raise money for the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-sam-bankman-fried-released-on-250-million-bail/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$250 million bond put on the former CEO</a>, with friends and associates speculated to have helped come up with the 10% collateral required for his release. However this was achieved, Sam was released under house arrest.</p>

<p class="p2">Soon after the news broke, the price of FTX’s native token FTT made a significant jump. After trending just below $1 for the better part of the week, the 65% push had brought it above $1.1. This brought renewed vigor to the market and momentum rightfully picked up.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/EG8TFcMt/" alt="FTX Token (FTT) price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1646" /></p>

<p class="p2">The problem now is that FTT has not done a good job of holding onto these gains. Naturally, the brief surge in price had triggered sell-offs among investors looking to take out some profit, triggering another fall below $1. In the early hours of Friday, there had been a 9% jump that brought FTT’s price above $1 once more, but even this would not hold.</p>
<p class="p2">Support remains weak at $1 and it is now a battle between the bears and the bulls to turn this critical level in their favor. Right now, the bears remain in control of the digital asset with the price sitting at $0.96, and FTT has struggled to break the resistance mounting at $1.</p>
<h2 class="p2">What About FTX?</h2>
<p class="p2">For many in the space who lost money when the FTX crypto exchange collapsed, this is just the beginning of the battle. Charges have already been brought against Bankman-Fried and his associates in what is being called the ‘largest fraud of the generation’ but there is still a long way to go.</p>
<p class="p2">On Thursday, it was reported that Paul Hastings LLP had been appointed by a committee to represent the interests of creditors in the FTX bankruptcy case. So far, the new FTX CEO John J. Ray III said he and his team had been able to recover around $1 billion worth of assets.</p>

<p class="p2">Former Alameda Research executive Caroline Ellison and FTX co-founder Gary Wang have already pled guilty to fraud charges and agreed to work with authorities. Both have been released on $250,000 bonds with travel restrictions.</p>
<p class="p2">As the FTX case develops, it is expectedly going to have a big impact on the price movements of FTT tokens. Given this, investors should exercise caution when investing and trading the cryptocurrency.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/FTX-FTT-Token-460x306.jpeg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>MATIC Price Enters Recovery Mode But Can It Touch $0.90?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/matic/matic-price-recovery-mode-but-can-it-touch-0-90/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 15:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATICUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[maticusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513556</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The MATIC price has remained bearish for most of this month. Presently, MATIC is attempting to correct its price. Over the last 24 hours, the coin is up by 2%. In the past week, however, the coin has depreciated by over 8%. Although, securing daily gains has helped the altcoin reverse some of its weekly losses. With Bitcoin consolidating at the moment, many altcoins are unable to break past their immediate resistance. The technical outlook for MATIC was bearish, but certain indicators pointed towards a potential rally in the upcoming trading sessions. The buying strength remained low, which means that accumulation was also lower on the chart. For prices to propel above the immediate price ceiling, buyers have to surpass sellers. As the altcoin logged gains over the last 48 hours, MATIC now has a strong support region extending from $0.70 to $0.63. As MATIC traded laterally between different price zones for weeks of this month, investors have remained worried. This caused sellers to short the asset, resulting in increased selling pressure. The altcoin currently presents an entry opportunity as the bulls are slowly making a comeback in the market. The amount of altcoin traded in the last session fell, which still points to a bearish presence. Related Reading: Bitcoin Volatility Will Spike By End 2022, Which Way Will It Push BTC? MATIC Price Analysis: One-Day Chart The altcoin was exchanging hands at $0.80 at the time of writing. After a period of consolidation, it has finally started to register gains. The coin&#8217;s overhead price ceiling was $0.82; if that was breached, MATIC could attempt to return to or even exceed the $0.90 mark. The $0.82 level has previously acted as a platform for a rally in the altcoin&#8217;s case. On the flip side, if unable to rest above the $0.77 mark, the price will first fall to $0.70 and then to $0.67. The amount of MATIC traded in the last session was in red, indicating that sellers were still active on the daily chart. Technical Analysis Buying strength has remained low due to increased shorting over the past few weeks. The Relative Strength (RSI) Index stood at 40, which indicated that even though buyers were making a comeback, sellers remained strong. However, there has been an uptick in the RSI over the last few days. MATIC&#8217;s price was below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, which demonstrates that sellers were driving the price momentum. On the other hand, MATIC&#8217;s price was attempting to move above the 200-SMA line (green below) which paints an extremely bullish picture. This meant that the altcoin could soon move above the $0.82 resistance mark and rally up. In accordance with the entry point for buyers, the Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) painted fading red signal bars. These declining red signal bars are tied to the decline in the sell signal for the altcoin, which also means shorting currently might not be a good idea. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Key Trend is Forming and Swift Recovery Could Occur The MACD depicts the change in price momentum, and these bars portray that the indicator could reflect bullish signals over the next trading sessions. The Bollinger Bands indicate the volatility in the market. The bands were wide, meaning that the price could touch the upper band at $0.84. Featured Image From UnSplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The MATIC price has remained bearish for most of this month. Presently, MATIC is attempting to correct its price. Over the last 24 hours, the coin is up by 2%. In the past week, however, the coin has depreciated by over 8%. Although, securing daily gains has helped the altcoin reverse some of its weekly losses.</p>
<p>With Bitcoin consolidating at the moment, many altcoins are unable to break past their immediate resistance. The technical outlook for MATIC was bearish, but certain indicators pointed towards a potential rally in the upcoming trading sessions.</p>
<p>The buying strength remained low, which means that accumulation was also lower on the chart. For prices to propel above the immediate price ceiling, buyers have to surpass sellers. As the altcoin logged gains over the last 48 hours, MATIC now has a strong support region extending from $0.70 to $0.63.</p>
<p>As MATIC traded laterally between different price zones for weeks of this month, investors have remained worried. This caused sellers to short the asset, resulting in increased selling pressure. The altcoin currently presents an entry opportunity as the bulls are slowly making a comeback in the market. The amount of altcoin traded in the last session fell, which still points to a bearish presence.</p>

<h2>MATIC Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-513569 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-23_20-14-45.png" alt="MATIC Price" width="1816" height="782" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-23_20-14-45.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-23_20-14-45-460x198.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-23_20-14-45-860x370.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-23_20-14-45-768x331.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-23_20-14-45-1536x661.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-23_20-14-45-750x323.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-23_20-14-45-1140x491.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>The altcoin was exchanging hands at $0.80 at the time of writing. After a period of consolidation, it has finally started to register gains. The coin&#8217;s overhead price ceiling was $0.82; if that was breached, MATIC could attempt to return to or even exceed the $0.90 mark.</p>
<p>The $0.82 level has previously acted as a platform for a rally in the altcoin&#8217;s case. On the flip side, if unable to rest above the $0.77 mark, the price will first fall to $0.70 and then to $0.67. The amount of MATIC traded in the last session was in red, indicating that sellers were still active on the daily chart.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-513570 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-23_20-15-27.png" alt="MATIC Price" width="1816" height="695" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-23_20-15-27.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-23_20-15-27-460x176.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-23_20-15-27-860x329.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-23_20-15-27-768x294.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-23_20-15-27-1536x588.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-23_20-15-27-750x287.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-23_20-15-27-1140x436.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>Buying strength has remained low due to increased shorting over the past few weeks. The Relative Strength (RSI) Index stood at 40, which indicated that even though buyers were making a comeback, sellers remained strong. However, there has been an uptick in the RSI over the last few days.</p>
<p>MATIC&#8217;s price was below the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA) line, which demonstrates that sellers were driving the price momentum.</p>
<p>On the other hand, MATIC&#8217;s price was attempting to move above the 200-SMA line (green below) which paints an extremely bullish picture. This meant that the altcoin could soon move above the $0.82 resistance mark and rally up.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-513571 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-23_20-15-56.png" alt="MATIC Price" width="1816" height="695" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-23_20-15-56.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-23_20-15-56-460x176.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-23_20-15-56-860x329.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-23_20-15-56-768x294.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-23_20-15-56-1536x588.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-23_20-15-56-750x287.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSD_2022-12-23_20-15-56-1140x436.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>In accordance with the entry point for buyers, the Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) painted fading red signal bars. These declining red signal bars are tied to the decline in the sell signal for the altcoin, which also means shorting currently might not be a good idea.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-key-trend-1250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum Price Key Trend is Forming and Swift Recovery Could Occur</a></p>
<p>The MACD depicts the change in price momentum, and these bars portray that the indicator could reflect bullish signals over the next trading sessions. The Bollinger Bands indicate the volatility in the market. The bands were wide, meaning that the price could touch the upper band at $0.84.</p>



]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/gabriel-mihalcea-Hx26miJmS1Y-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin (DOGE) Price Is Up 5% On This News</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/dogecoin-doge-price-is-up-5-on-this-news/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 14:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitstamp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Musk]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513532</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[After a tough week for Dogecoin (DOGE) investors, there was at least a small Christmas present from the European crypto exchange Bitstamp yesterday. The fifth-largest exchange by spot trading volume, according to recent data from CoinMarketCap, announced that it will list Dogecoin. Bitstamp, which is based in Luxembourg, allows trading between fiat currencies and Bitcoin, as well as other cryptocurrencies. As of yesterday, Dogecoin (DOGE) can now be exchanged for euros and USD. &#8220;We&#8217;ve launched Dogecoin, the cryptocurrency inspired by the popular Shiba Inu meme, for our customers. Buy and trade DOGE on Bitstamp today!&#8221; the exchange wrote. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Poised To Rally Big-Time On Today’s PCE Release Dogecoin Price Shows Slight Recovery Driven by the news, DOGE recorded a slight upward move today, causing the Dogecoin price to rise by 5% temporarily. At press time, DOGE was trading at $0.776. Thus, DOGE had already lost some of its profits again and is only 2% above the previous day&#8217;s price as of press time. The news has also caused Dogecoin to see a brisk increase in 24-hour trading volume. Compared to the previous period, DOGE&#8217;s trading volume spiked by 76%, totaling $590 million. Still, the DOGE army has failed to push the price above the key resistance at $0.0791. A look at the 4-hour chart reveals that the price is still in strong bearish territory. If DOGE fails to break through the aforementioned resistance, a retest of the support at $0.0700 seems likely to happen. A look at the 1-day chart also reveals that Dogecoin has been in a descending trend channel since the beginning of the month. After trading as high as $0.114 on December 5, DOGE is currently trapped in this descending trend. A close significantly above the $0.0776 level would mark a breakout from the trend channel and could bring new hope. As NewsBTC reported, DOGE investors can hope for a positive boost from today&#8217;s release of the core Personal Consumption Expenditures Price Index (PCE). If the data comes in significantly below expectations, what seems very like to some analysts, the US dollar could weaken and boost risk assets such as DOGE. Related Reading: Dogecoin (DOGE) Climbs 2.58% In 24 Hours, Can It Reach $0.1 Before The Week Runs Out? Is The DOGE Community Losing Faith? The current downward trajectory comes after Dogecoin&#8217;s biggest and most influential fan, Elon Musk, has gone relatively quiet. After the Twitter acquisition, Musk was still very active in promoting DOGE. The Tesla CEO hinted several times that Dogecoin could play a role in Twitter&#8217;s future path. However, in the past week, there were two harsh dampers for the DOGE army. On the one hand, a vote ended with Musk stepping down as Twitter CEO in the coming weeks, and on the other, the platform introduced a new chart feature for Bitcoin and Ethereum, but not for the meme coin. Featured image from Kanchanara / Unsplash, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After a tough week for Dogecoin (DOGE) investors, there was at least a small Christmas present from the European crypto exchange Bitstamp yesterday. The fifth-largest exchange by spot trading volume, according to recent data from CoinMarketCap, announced that it will list Dogecoin.</p>
<p>Bitstamp, which is based in Luxembourg, allows trading between fiat currencies and Bitcoin, as well as other cryptocurrencies. As of yesterday, Dogecoin (DOGE) can now be exchanged for euros and USD.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;ve launched Dogecoin, the cryptocurrency inspired by the popular Shiba Inu meme, for our customers. Buy and trade DOGE on Bitstamp today!&#8221; the exchange <a href="https://blog.bitstamp.net/post/were-listing-dogecoin-doge/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">wrote</a>.</p>

<h2>Dogecoin Price Shows Slight Recovery</h2>
<p>Driven by the news, DOGE recorded a slight upward move today, causing the Dogecoin price to rise by 5% temporarily. At press time, DOGE was trading at $0.776. Thus, DOGE had already lost some of its profits again and is only 2% above the previous day&#8217;s price as of press time.</p>
<p>The news has also caused Dogecoin to see a brisk increase in 24-hour trading volume. Compared to the previous period, DOGE&#8217;s trading volume spiked by 76%, totaling $590 million. Still, the DOGE army has failed to push the price above the key resistance at $0.0791.</p>
<p>A look at the 4-hour chart reveals that the price is still in strong bearish territory. If DOGE fails to break through the aforementioned resistance, a retest of the support at $0.0700 seems likely to happen.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-513534 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD_2022-12-23_12-47-30.png" alt="Dogecoin DOGE USD 2022-12-23" width="3612" height="1617" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD_2022-12-23_12-47-30.png 3612w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD_2022-12-23_12-47-30-460x206.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD_2022-12-23_12-47-30-860x385.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD_2022-12-23_12-47-30-768x344.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD_2022-12-23_12-47-30-1536x688.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD_2022-12-23_12-47-30-2048x917.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD_2022-12-23_12-47-30-750x336.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD_2022-12-23_12-47-30-1140x510.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3612px) 100vw, 3612px" />
<p>A look at the 1-day chart also reveals that Dogecoin has been in a descending trend channel since the beginning of the month. After trading as high as $0.114 on December 5, DOGE is currently trapped in this descending trend. A close significantly above the $0.0776 level would mark a breakout from the trend channel and could bring new hope.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-513537 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD_2022-12-23_13-25-36.png" alt="DOGE USD_2022-12-23" width="3625" height="1672" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD_2022-12-23_13-25-36.png 3625w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD_2022-12-23_13-25-36-460x212.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD_2022-12-23_13-25-36-860x397.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD_2022-12-23_13-25-36-768x354.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD_2022-12-23_13-25-36-1536x708.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD_2022-12-23_13-25-36-2048x945.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD_2022-12-23_13-25-36-750x346.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOGEUSD_2022-12-23_13-25-36-1140x526.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3625px) 100vw, 3625px" />
<p>As NewsBTC <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-poised-to-rally-big-time-on-pce/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a>, DOGE investors can hope for a positive boost from today&#8217;s release of the core Personal Consumption Expenditures Price Index (PCE). If the data comes in significantly below expectations, what seems very like to some analysts, the US dollar could weaken and boost risk assets such as DOGE.</p>

<h2>Is The DOGE Community Losing Faith?</h2>
<p>The current <a href="https://newsbtc.com/dogecoin-2/dogecoin-doge-climbs-2-58-in-24-hours-can-it-reach-0-1-before-the-week-runs-out/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">downward trajectory</a> comes after Dogecoin&#8217;s biggest and most influential fan, Elon Musk, has gone relatively quiet. After the Twitter acquisition, Musk was still very active in promoting DOGE. The Tesla CEO hinted several times that Dogecoin could play a role in Twitter&#8217;s future path.</p>
<p>However, in the past week, there were two harsh dampers for the DOGE army. On the one hand, a vote ended with Musk stepping down as Twitter CEO in the coming weeks, and on the other, the platform introduced a new <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/musk-integrates-bitcoin-ethereum-charts-twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">chart feature</a> for Bitcoin and Ethereum, but not for the meme coin.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/kanchanara-eUw1S8c6oF8-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>WAVES Gets Dragged Down By USDN, Despite Pumping Investor Distribution</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/waves-dragged-down-by-usdn/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 14:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDN]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Waves]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Waves blockchain]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513551</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There is enormous negative sentiment surrounding USDN. And with USDN continuously falling off its track, it’s also pulling WAVES down. WAVES is the native token of the Waves blockchain. According to CoinMarketCap, the token is up by 0.23% or trading at $1.57 as of this writing. There is very little improvement with its current figures. Token up by 0.23% or trading at $1.57 USDN extremely volatile Crypto down by 45% in the past couple of weeks Waves blockchain confirmed the plunge of the Neutrino USD (USDN) stablecoin but insisted that the USDN, while built on top of the ecosystem, is completely detached from WAVES.  Related Reading: VeChain Jumps By 4% As VET Investors Look To Profit Before Christmas Nevertheless, as the value of USDN declined, it seems to be pulling WAVES further down as well. Stablecoins are digital currencies whose value is anchored to that of a stable value asset, such as a fiat currency or a commodity price. The excessive volatility of Bitcoin (BTC) and other major cryptocurrencies has made crypto investments less appropriate for everyday transactions; stablecoins try to address this problem by providing a more &#8220;stable&#8221; alternative. Image: Altcoin Buzz WAVES Down By 99% Off Its April 2022 ATH Blockchain founder Sasha Ivanov has urged different crypto exchanges on Wednesday to cut off the futures markets that are connected to the crypto as she insists that it’s doing more harm than good. The crypto exchanges included Kraken, Bybit, Binance, and OKX. Ivanov on a Twitter post said: “They are a breeding ground for FUD and making money off short positions, profitable because of it. I kindly ask all centralized exchanges to disable Waves future markets.” Evidently, the blockchain native currency has nosedived by more than 45% as seen in the past couple of weeks. In fact, its numbers now are completely off-track as it’s down by as much as 99% from its ATH as seen in April 2022. Stablecoin Acting Erratic Lately USDN has been extremely volatile.  The token&#8217;s most recent de-peg came following South Korea’s digital asset exchange association issuing a warning. Related Reading: MATIC Seen Breaking Present Support With Sustained Momentum Crypto total market cap at nearly $774 billion on the daily chart &#124; Chart: TradingView.com According to Wu Blockchain, the Korean Federation of Exchanges (KFE) has issued an &#8220;investment warning&#8221; for WAVES. The reason for this is because of the erratic price movements of the USDN stablecoin, which is intended to keep its $1 peg at all times. WAVES was flagged as an &#8220;investment warning&#8221; by the Korea Federation of Exchanges. The reason is that the USDN stablecoin has been fluctuating rapidly. Upbit will decide whether to terminate the transaction within two weeks. https://t.co/wiB5gSfm7f — Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) December 8, 2022]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There is enormous negative sentiment surrounding USDN. And with USDN continuously falling off its track, it’s also pulling WAVES down.</p>
<p>WAVES is the native token of the Waves blockchain. According to<a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/waves/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> CoinMarketCap</a>, the token is up by 0.23% or trading at $1.57 as of this writing. </p>
<p>There is very little improvement with its current figures.</p>
<ul>
<li>Token up by 0.23% or trading at $1.57</li>
<li>USDN extremely volatile</li>
<li>Crypto down by 45% in the past couple of weeks</li>
</ul>
<p>Waves blockchain confirmed the plunge of the Neutrino USD (USDN) <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/terms/s/stablecoin.asp" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">stablecoin</a> but insisted that the USDN, while built on top of the ecosystem, is completely detached from WAVES. </p>

<p>Nevertheless, as the value of USDN declined, it seems to be pulling WAVES further down as well.</p>
<p>Stablecoins are digital currencies whose value is anchored to that of a stable value asset, such as a fiat currency or a commodity price.</p>
<p>The excessive volatility of Bitcoin (BTC) and other major cryptocurrencies has made crypto investments less appropriate for everyday transactions; stablecoins try to address this problem by providing a more &#8220;stable&#8221; alternative.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-513561 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/a-13-460x240.png" alt="" width="460" height="240" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/a-13-460x240.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/a-13-750x391.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/a-13.png 765w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<h2><b>WAVES Down By 99% Off Its April 2022 ATH</b></h2>
<p>Blockchain founder Sasha Ivanov has urged different crypto exchanges on Wednesday to cut off the futures markets that are connected to the crypto as she insists that it’s doing more harm than good. </p>
<p>The crypto exchanges included Kraken, Bybit, Binance, and OKX.</p>
<p>Ivanov on a<a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2022/12/21/waves-blockchain-founder-asks-exchanges-to-delist-waves-token-derivative-trading/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> Twitter post</a> said:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>“They are a breeding ground for FUD and making money off short positions, profitable because of it. I kindly ask all centralized exchanges to disable Waves future markets.”</strong></p></blockquote>
<p>Evidently, the blockchain native currency has nosedived by more than 45% as seen in the past couple of weeks. </p>
<p>In fact, its numbers now are completely off-track as it’s down by as much as 99% from its ATH as seen in April 2022.</p>
<h2><b>Stablecoin Acting Erratic Lately</b></h2>
<p>USDN has been extremely volatile. </p>
<p>The token&#8217;s most recent de-peg came following South Korea’s digital asset exchange association issuing a warning.</p>

<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/cdrFd9fL/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>

<p>According to Wu Blockchain, the Korean Federation of Exchanges (KFE) has issued an<a href="https://u.today/waves-usdn-stablecoin-depegs-korean-regulator-issues-warning" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> &#8220;investment warning&#8221;</a> for WAVES.</p>
<p>The reason for this is because of the erratic price movements of the USDN stablecoin, which is intended to keep its $1 peg at all times.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">WAVES was flagged as an &#8220;investment warning&#8221; by the Korea Federation of Exchanges. The reason is that the USDN stablecoin has been fluctuating rapidly. Upbit will decide whether to terminate the transaction within two weeks. <a href="https://t.co/wiB5gSfm7f" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">https://t.co/wiB5gSfm7f</a></p>
<p>— Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1600818943861870594?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">December 8, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/WAVES-460x308.png" width="460" height="308" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Poised To Rally Big-Time On Today&#8217;s PCE Release</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-poised-to-rally-big-time-on-pce/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 10:11:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CPI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FOMC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PCE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Powell]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513505</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin price could see a significant uptick today Friday, December 23 at 8:30 am (EST) if the Core Personal Consumption Expenditures Price Index (PCE) comes in better than expected. And the chances are high! Bitcoin price has been heavily dependent on macro data and the decisions of the U.S. Federal Reserve (FED) lately. The last FOMC meeting of the year on December 13 provided a bearish surprise, even though the consumer price index (CPI) came in better than expected. However, there was a catch. After the FOMC meeting, rumors emerged that chairman Jerome Powell ignored the CPI data that arrived a few hours before the meeting, although he claimed the opposite in the press conference. Within Wall Street, several analysts spoke out, accusing Powell of hoaxes. Why Today&#8217;s Core PCE Is Of Paramount Importance The problem is that the Fed&#8217;s forecast for core PCE inflation seems far too high after the surprisingly weak CPI data, as Tomas Lee, an analyst at Fundstrat, writes. As the economic forecast overview shows, the FED raised the core PCE inflation target for 2022 from 4.5% to 4.8%. With that, Powell added to the &#8220;higher for longer&#8221; narrative. But there is something &#8220;odd,&#8221; as Lee explained. The month-to-month percentage change in inflation would have to be staggeringly high to reach the FED&#8217;s 4.8% target. Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Shows Signs of Life and Could Soon Clear This Hurdle Lee wonders how the FED can forecast 4.8% core PCE inflation in 2022 when inflation is moving toward 4.1-4.2%. &#8220;How can Fed forecast be so far??&#8221; Lee wrote. The analyst points to a ransomware attack on Haver Analytics as a possible reason for this large divergence. Due to the attack, Haver Analytics may not have been able to update the data, which is why Jerome Powell and the FOMC committee ignored the positive data. Therefore, according to the Fundstrat analyst, today&#8217;s PCE release is of massive importance. Lee writes: We think core PCE inflation will be 0.10% compared to Cleveland Fed inflation NOW forecast of 0.26%. Any figure below 0.40% would make #FOMC figure of 4.8% too high. Remarkably, the PCE is also the key data point for the U.S. central bank. The FED&#8217;s forecasts and its 2% target are not based on CPI, but on the PCE. Twitter user ZeroHedge estimated based on this fact: If tomorrow&#8217;s core PCE is 4.5% or lower (~75% chance), the entire hawkish FOMC repricing is blown out &#8211; no way 4.8% core PCE in December, SEP/Dots repriced and terminal rate tumbles. The Impact On The Bitcoin Price If the PCE is significantly below the FED&#8217;s expectations, the theory would find confirmation today and could completely wipe out the bearish sentiment. The FED would possibly be forced to revise its forecasts as the PCE shows that inflation is under control. This could prompt the FED to take a more dovish stance at the next meeting, with markets front-running this as early as today. Ultimately, the PCE release could lead to a weaker dollar, spurring risk assets like Bitcoin. Related Reading: Bitcoin Volatility Will Spike By End 2022, Which Way Will It Push BTC? At press time, the Bitcoin price stood at $16,827. Today, like the last few days, the $16,900 level will be of key importance as the most crucial resistance at the moment. If there is a strong push above this resistance, the next target would be the $17,400 region. Otherwise, Bitcoin investors should keep an eye on the support at $16,400. Featured image from Traxer / Unsplash, Chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin price could see a significant uptick today Friday, December 23 at 8:30 am (EST) if the Core Personal Consumption Expenditures Price Index (PCE) comes in better than expected. And the chances are high!</p>
<p>Bitcoin price has been heavily dependent on macro data and the decisions of the U.S. Federal Reserve (FED) lately. The last <a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/upcoming-fomc-meeting-is-the-most-important-ever-for-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FOMC meeting</a> of the year on December 13 provided a bearish surprise, even though the consumer price index (CPI) came in better than expected.</p>
<p>However, there was a catch. After the FOMC meeting, rumors emerged that chairman Jerome Powell ignored the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/bitcoin-price-breaks-above-18200-cpi-data-comes-in-better-than-expected/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CPI data</a> that arrived a few hours before the meeting, although he claimed the opposite in the press conference. Within Wall Street, several analysts spoke out, accusing Powell of hoaxes.</p>
<h2>Why Today&#8217;s Core PCE Is Of Paramount Importance</h2>
<p>The problem is that the Fed&#8217;s forecast for core PCE inflation seems far too high after the surprisingly weak CPI data, as Tomas Lee, an analyst at Fundstrat, <a href="https://twitter.com/fundstrat/status/1606090045269544963" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">writes</a>.</p>
<p>As the economic forecast overview shows, the FED raised the core PCE inflation target for 2022 from 4.5% to 4.8%. With that, Powell added to the &#8220;higher for longer&#8221; narrative. But there is something &#8220;odd,&#8221; as Lee explained. The month-to-month percentage change in inflation would have to be staggeringly high to reach the FED&#8217;s 4.8% target.</p>

<p>Lee wonders how the FED can forecast 4.8% core PCE inflation in 2022 when inflation is moving toward 4.1-4.2%. &#8220;How can Fed forecast be so far??&#8221; Lee wrote.</p>
<p>The analyst points to a ransomware attack on Haver Analytics as a possible reason for this large divergence. Due to the attack, Haver Analytics may not have been able to update the data, which is why Jerome Powell and the FOMC committee ignored the positive data.</p>
<p>Therefore, according to the Fundstrat analyst, today&#8217;s PCE release is of massive importance. Lee writes:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>We think core PCE inflation will be 0.10% compared to Cleveland Fed inflation NOW forecast of 0.26%. Any figure below 0.40% would make #FOMC figure of 4.8% too high.</strong></p></blockquote>
<p>Remarkably, the PCE is also the key data point for the U.S. central bank. The FED&#8217;s forecasts and its 2% target are not based on CPI, but on the PCE. Twitter user ZeroHedge <a href="https://twitter.com/zerohedge/status/1606112936300142592" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">estimated</a> based on this fact:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>If tomorrow&#8217;s core PCE is 4.5% or lower (~75% chance), the entire hawkish FOMC repricing is blown out &#8211; no way 4.8% core PCE in December, SEP/Dots repriced and terminal rate tumbles.</strong></p></blockquote>
<h2>The Impact On The Bitcoin Price</h2>
<p>If the PCE is significantly below the FED&#8217;s expectations, the theory would find confirmation today and could completely wipe out the bearish sentiment. The FED would possibly be forced to revise its forecasts as the PCE shows that inflation is under control.</p>
<p>This could prompt the FED to take a more dovish stance at the next meeting, with markets front-running this as early as today. Ultimately, the PCE release could lead to a weaker dollar, spurring risk assets like Bitcoin.</p>

<p>At press time, the Bitcoin price stood at $16,827. Today, like the last few days, the $16,900 level will be of <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-shows-life-17k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">key importance</a> as the most crucial resistance at the moment.</p>
<p>If there is a strong push above this resistance, the next target would be the $17,400 region. Otherwise, Bitcoin investors should keep an eye on the support at $16,400.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-513515 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-23_10-10-05.png" alt="Bitcoin BTC USD 2022-12-23" width="3620" height="1613" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-23_10-10-05.png 3620w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-23_10-10-05-460x205.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-23_10-10-05-860x383.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-23_10-10-05-768x342.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-23_10-10-05-1536x684.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-23_10-10-05-2048x913.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-23_10-10-05-750x334.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD_2022-12-23_10-10-05-1140x508.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 3620px) 100vw, 3620px" />

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/traxer-i8aBzmIcXpU-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>MATIC Seen Breaking Present Support With Sustained Momentum</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/matic-seen-breaking-support/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 09:58:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATIC Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATIC Price Pullback]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513510</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MATIC has shown rapid accumulation or increase in the supply since the final days of November. More so, there was also an increased demand seen in the derivatives market which could be the outcome of positive Binance Funding Rate on the MATIC/USDT pair. CoinMarketCap data shows that MATIC price is now up by 1.48% or trading at $0.8019 at the time of writing. With the rate it’s going, Polygon could further retest of even breach the present support level with sustained momentum. Price still could potentially slide further towards $0.7736 or even lower Polygon token price spikes by 1.48% Shows rapid accumulation since November 21 Related Reading: VeChain Jumps By 4% As VET Investors Look To Profit Before Christmas The overall market sentiment for Polygon has been positive all throughout. Despite its recent hiccups in price, the development activity was observed to have spiked, which pushed the coin enter bearish turf for the most parts of December. After its release in 2017, Polygon quickly became a popular alternative to the Ethereum blockchain due to its faster transaction times and lower transaction fees. Meanwhile, a stop loss is seen hovering above $0.8155, which means a spike going above this range could further invalidate the bearish forecast for the crypto. This uptrend could trigger the MATIC bulls to barrel past the resistance seen at $0.8154. Chart: TradingView MATIC is seen sliced in between the $0.8911 and $0.9492 in the first few weeks of the month. On the other hand, by December 15, the crypto sang a different tune, as the price retreated and found support at the $0.7736 level. MATIC Technical Indicators: Price Pullback MATIC technical indicators suggest a price pullback might settle at the range of $0.7735. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) shows a moderate slope on the charts which means that it’s near the oversold zone. Over the past week, Polygon&#8217;s stock has dropped 6.31%. And in the past 24 hours, the price has risen by 1.10%. Price increased by 0.45% in the last hour alone, according to data by Coinbase. Related Reading: Tron Shows Bullish Energy And Attracts Investors To Buy TRX MATIC total market cap at nearly $7 billion on the daily chart &#124; Chart: TradingView.com Polygon Target: $2.26 In 2023 In the meantime, it looks like the market is leaning towards the bears as the crypto&#8217;s price could retreat to $0.7392, which traders can treat as short-selling targets especially with increased risk appetite. Notably, famous crypto expert and trader Jason Pizzino also shared his forecast on Polygon with his 279,000 YouTube subscribers, stating that MATIC could potentially dip by more than 30% from the current price of $0.8019, which could be seen as an opportunity to buy low and sell high for many traders. However, with Polygon&#8217;s resilience, MATIC price for 2023 could shoot towards a maximum of $2.26, with the average price hovering around $2.00. With a bear market, MATIC’s minimum price could potentially dip to $1.75 come 2023.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MATIC has shown rapid accumulation or increase in the supply since the final days of November. More so, there was also an increased demand seen in the derivatives market which could be the outcome of positive Binance Funding Rate on the MATIC/USDT pair.</p>
<p><a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/polygon/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">CoinMarketCap</a> data shows that MATIC price is now up by 1.48% or trading at $0.8019 at the time of writing. With the rate it’s going, Polygon could further retest of even breach the present support level with sustained momentum.</p>
<ul>
<li>Price still could potentially slide further towards $0.7736 or even lower</li>
<li>Polygon token price spikes by 1.48%</li>
<li>Shows rapid accumulation since November 21</li>
</ul>

<p>The overall market sentiment for Polygon has been positive all throughout. Despite its recent hiccups in price, the development activity was observed to have spiked, which pushed the coin enter bearish turf for the most parts of December.</p>
<p>After its release in 2017, Polygon quickly became a popular alternative to the Ethereum blockchain due to its <a href="https://www.analyticsinsight.net/polygon-matic-and-solana-sol-nosedive-snowfall-protocol-snw-investors-hit-gold/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">faster transaction</a> times and lower transaction fees.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, a stop loss is seen hovering above $0.8155, which means a spike going above this range could further invalidate the bearish forecast for the crypto. This uptrend could trigger the MATIC bulls to barrel past the resistance seen at $0.8154.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-513514 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/a-12.png" alt="" width="593" height="330" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/a-12.png 593w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/a-12-460x256.png 460w" sizes="(max-width: 593px) 100vw, 593px" /></p>

<p>MATIC is seen sliced in between the $0.8911 and $0.9492 in the first few weeks of the month. On the other hand, by December 15, the crypto sang a different tune, as the price retreated and found support at the $0.7736 level.</p>
<h2><b>MATIC Technical Indicators: Price Pullback</b></h2>
<p>MATIC technical indicators suggest a price pullback might settle at the range of $0.7735. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) shows a moderate slope on the charts which means that it’s near the oversold zone. </p>
<p>Over the past week, Polygon&#8217;s stock has dropped 6.31%. And in the past 24 hours, the price has risen by 1.10%. Price increased by 0.45% in the last hour alone, according to <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/price/polygon" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a> by Coinbase.</p>

<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/KEPQzLkf/" width="2047" height="979" /></p>

<h2><b>Polygon Target: $2.26 In 2023</b></h2>
<p>In the meantime, it looks like the market is leaning towards the bears as the crypto&#8217;s price could retreat to $0.7392, which traders can treat as short-selling targets especially with increased risk appetite.</p>
<p>Notably, famous crypto expert and trader<a href="https://dailyhodl.com/2022/12/21/heres-whats-in-store-for-polygon-matic-solana-sol-and-cardano-ada-according-to-top-analyst/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> Jason Pizzino</a> also shared his forecast on Polygon with his 279,000 YouTube subscribers, stating that MATIC could potentially dip by more than 30% from the current price of $0.8019, which could be seen as an opportunity to buy low and sell high for many traders.</p>
<p>However, with Polygon&#8217;s resilience, <a href="https://bitnation.co/forecast/polygon-price-prediction/#:~:text=Polygon%20has%20amazing%20potential%20over,all%2Dtime%20high%20of%20%247.80." rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">MATIC price for 2023</a> could shoot towards a maximum of $2.26, with the average price hovering around $2.00. With a bear market, MATIC’s minimum price could potentially dip to $1.75 come 2023.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATIC-1-460x233.png" width="460" height="233" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Key Trend is Forming and Swift Recovery Could Occur</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-key-trend-1250/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 04:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513491</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum is attempting an upside break above the $1,230 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH could start a strong increase if it settles above the $1,230 and $1,250 resistance levels. Ethereum tested the $1,180 level and climbed higher sharply. The price is now trading above $1,200 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There was a break above a key contracting triangle with resistance near $1,215 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could gain bullish momentum if there is a clear move above $1,230 and $1,250. Ethereum Price Eyes Fresh Rally Ethereum price started a downside correction from the $1,230 resistance zone. ETH spiked below the $1,200 support zone and the 100 hourly simple moving average. However, the bulls were active above the $1,160 support zone. A low was formed near $1,180 and the price climbed higher sharply, similar to bitcoin. There was a strong move above the $1,200 level. Besides, there was a break above a key contracting triangle with resistance near $1,215 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. Ether price is now trading above $1,200 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. It is now trading just below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent wave from the $1,180 swing low to $1,237 high. An immediate resistance is near the $1,230 level. The next major resistance is near the $1,250 level. A clear upside break above the $1,250 resistance could start a strong upward move. In the stated case, the price may perhaps rise towards the $1,300 resistance. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com The next major resistance could be $1,350. If the bulls clear the $1,350 resistance, the price might rise towards $1,400. Any more gains might send the price towards the $1,500 resistance zone. Fresh Drop in ETH? If ethereum fails to climb above the $1,250 resistance, it could start another drop. An initial support on the downside is near the $1,210 level and the 100 hourly simple moving average. The next major support is near the $1,200 level. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent wave from the $1,180 swing low to $1,237 high. A downside break below $1,200 might spark a move towards the $1,150 support. Any more losses could lead the price towards the $1,100 zone. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now losing momentum in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,200 Major Resistance Level – $1,230]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum is attempting an upside break above the $1,230 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH could start a strong increase if it settles above the $1,230 and $1,250 resistance levels.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum tested the $1,180 level and climbed higher sharply.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $1,200 and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</li>
<li>There was a break above a key contracting triangle with resistance near $1,215 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could gain bullish momentum if there is a clear move above $1,230 and $1,250.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Eyes Fresh Rally</h2>
<p>Ethereum price started a downside correction from the $1,230 resistance zone. ETH spiked below the $1,200 support zone and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</p>
<p>However, the bulls were active above the $1,160 support zone. A low was formed near $1,180 and the price climbed higher sharply, similar to <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-shows-life-17k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bitcoin</a>. There was a strong move above the $1,200 level. Besides, there was a break above a key contracting triangle with resistance near $1,215 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD.</p>
<p>Ether price is now trading above $1,200 and the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-consolidates-1250/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">100 hourly simple moving average</a>. It is now trading just below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent wave from the $1,180 swing low to $1,237 high.</p>
<p>An immediate resistance is near the $1,230 level. The next major resistance is near the $1,250 level. A clear upside break above the $1,250 resistance could start a strong upward move. In the stated case, the price may perhaps rise towards the $1,300 resistance.</p>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-17.png"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-513492" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-17.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-17.png 1834w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-17-460x212.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-17-860x396.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-17-768x354.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-17-1536x708.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-17-750x346.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-17-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The next major resistance could be $1,350. If the bulls clear the $1,350 resistance, the price might rise towards $1,400. Any more gains might send the price towards the $1,500 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Fresh Drop in ETH?</h2>
<p>If ethereum fails to climb above the $1,250 resistance, it could start another drop. An initial support on the downside is near the $1,210 level and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $1,200 level. It is close to the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the recent wave from the $1,180 swing low to $1,237 high. A downside break below $1,200 might spark a move towards the $1,150 support. Any more losses could lead the price towards the $1,100 zone.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is now losing momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,200</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,230</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Depositphotos_103793088_s-2019-460x251.jpg" width="460" height="251" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Shows Signs of Life and Could Soon Clear This Hurdle</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-shows-life-17k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 02:45:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513487</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is attempting an upside break above $16,800. BTC could start a decent increase if it clears the $16,800 and $17,000 resistance levels. Bitcoin is still facing a strong resistance near $17,000 and $17,200. The price is trading above $16,700 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $16,800 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could attempt a fresh increase if there is a clear move above the $17,000 resistance zone. Bitcoin Price Eyes Recovery Bitcoin price remained stable above the $16,500 zone. BTC attempted an upside break above the $17,000 resistance, but it faced sellers. A high was formed near $17,067 and the price started a downside correction. There was a move below the $16,800 level and the 100 hourly simple moving average. The price declined below the 50% Fib retracement level of the up move from the $16,260 swing low to $17,067 high. Bitcoin price tested the $16,550 level, where it found support. It remained stable above the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the up move from the $16,260 swing low to $17,067 high. The price recovered losses and climbed above $16,700. It is now trading above $16,700 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $16,800 zone. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $16,800 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The first major resistance is near the $17,000 zone. A clear move above the $17,000 resistance might encourage the bulls to pump the price above the $17,200 resistance. If they succeed, the price could even surpass the $17,500 level. The next major resistance is near $18,000, above which the price climb towards the $18,500 resistance zone. Fresh Drop in BTC? If bitcoin fails to clear the $17,000 resistance, there could be a fresh drop. An immediate support on the downside is near the $16,750 level and the 100 hourly SMA The next major support is near the $16,550 level. A downside break below the $16,550 support might call for a move towards the $16,350 level. Any more losses might send the price towards $16,000. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $16,700, followed by $16,550. Major Resistance Levels – $16,800, $17,000 and $17,500.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is attempting an upside break above $16,800. BTC could start a decent increase if it clears the $16,800 and $17,000 resistance levels.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is still facing a strong resistance near $17,000 and $17,200.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $16,700 and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $16,800 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could attempt a fresh increase if there is a clear move above the $17,000 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Eyes Recovery</h2>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-recovery-fade-17-2k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin price remained stable above the $16,500 zone</a>. BTC attempted an upside break above the $17,000 resistance, but it faced sellers.</p>
<p>A high was formed near $17,067 and the price started a downside correction. There was a move below the $16,800 level and the 100 hourly simple moving average. The price declined below the 50% Fib retracement level of the up move from the $16,260 swing low to $17,067 high.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price tested the $16,550 level, where it found support. It remained stable above the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the up move from the $16,260 swing low to $17,067 high.</p>
<p>The price recovered losses and climbed above $16,700. It is now trading above $16,700 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $16,800 zone. There is also a key bearish trend line forming with resistance near $16,800 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-21.png"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-513488" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-21.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-21.png 1834w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-21-460x212.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-21-860x396.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-21-768x354.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-21-1536x708.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-21-750x346.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-21-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $17,000 zone. A clear move above the $17,000 resistance might encourage the bulls to pump the price above the $17,200 resistance. If they succeed, the price could even surpass the $17,500 level. The next major resistance is near $18,000, above which the price climb towards the $18,500 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Fresh Drop in BTC?</h2>
<p>If bitcoin fails to clear the $17,000 resistance, there could be a <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-signals-rejection-17k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">fresh drop</a>. An immediate support on the downside is near the $16,750 level and the 100 hourly SMA</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $16,550 level. A downside break below the $16,550 support might call for a move towards the $16,350 level. Any more losses might send the price towards $16,000.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $16,700, followed by $16,550.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $16,800, $17,000 and $17,500.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/Depositphotos_179514440_s-2019-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Classic Hashrate Dumps Almost 50% In 3 Months, What About ETC?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/etc/ethereum-classic-hashrate-dumps-almost-50/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 23:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETC hashrate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[etc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hashrate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ravencoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=513410</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum Classic saw its hashrate balloon when Ethereum finally moved to a proof of stake mechanism. The miners who were being kicked out of the network and could no longer use their machines had switched to others such as Ethereum Classic and Ravencoin to put their very specific machines to use. At the time, ETC’s hashrate had grown more than 200%, but now the network is seeing its hashrate fall once more. Ethereum Classic Hashrate Down By Almost 50% On Sep. 16, the mining hashrate of the Ethereum Classic network reached a new all-time high of 199.4 terahashes per second (TH/s) after climbing steadily for more than a week. With this growth had come more usage on the network, triggering staggering growth in its price. Related Reading: Bitcoin Retail Investors Now Hold 17% Of Total BTC Supply, But Is It Good News? However, as the Ethereum network has settled into its proof of stake (POS) consensus mechanism, the Ethereum Classic hashrate is correcting downwards. Hashrate is now down almost 50% in the last 3 months to be sitting at 109.3 TH/s on Dec. 22. ETC hashrate down almost 50% in 3 months &#124; Source: Coinwarz The decline can also be attributed to the bear market and the muted interest from investors. Since bitcoin’s price touched below $20,000, all of the cryptocurrencies in the space have seen a similar decline. Ravencoin, another proof of work network that got massive attention following Ethereum’s move to proof of stake, has also seen its hashrate plummet in the last 3 months. Ravencoin’s hashrate now sits at 9.49 TH/s compared to its Sep. 22, 2022 peak of 17.59 TH/s. Meanwhile, other leading proof of work networks including Litecoin and Dogecoin has seen an increase in mining hashrate, whereas bitcoin remains mostly around 250 exahashes per second (EH/s). What About ETC Price? ETC, the native cryptocurrency of the Ethereum Classic network, was basically on a rollercoaster in the three months since Ethereum moved to proof of stake. At first, as the network began to get more attention, ETC’s price had risen drastically. It eventually peaked above $42 before starting another downtrend. Related Reading: https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/microstrategy-bought-bitcoin/ At current prices, the digital asset has lost over 68% of its value from September 2022 and is still very bearish. A lot of attention had also moved on to Dogecoin, a proof-of-work cryptocurrency that saw a surge in price following Elon Musk’s takeover of Twitter. ETC price down 68% in 3 months &#124; Source: ETCUSD on TradingView.com Obviously, this increase in the price of DOGE had incentivized miners to move over to Dogecoin, eventually taking share from Ethereum Classic. As interest fell, so did the mining hashrate and price naturally followed the same trend. ETC now sits below its 100-day moving average, which means that investors are expecting lower prices to come. It is trading at $16.41 at the time of this writing, down 11% in the last 7 days. Featured image from Crypto News Flash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Ethereum Classic saw its hashrate balloon when Ethereum finally moved to a proof of stake mechanism. The miners who were being kicked out of the network and could no longer use their machines had switched to others such as Ethereum Classic and Ravencoin to put their very specific machines to use. At the time, ETC’s hashrate had grown more than 200%, but now the network is seeing its hashrate fall once more.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Ethereum Classic Hashrate Down By Almost 50%</h2>
<p class="p2">On Sep. 16, the mining hashrate of the Ethereum Classic network reached a new all-time high of 199.4 terahashes per second (TH/s) after climbing steadily for more than a week. With this growth had come more usage on the network, triggering staggering growth in its price.</p>

<p class="p2">However, as the Ethereum network has settled into its proof of stake (POS) consensus mechanism, the Ethereum Classic hashrate is correcting downwards. <a href="https://www.coinwarz.com/mining/ethereum-classic/hashrate-chart" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Hashrate is now down almost 50% in the last 3 months</a> to be sitting at 109.3 TH/s on Dec. 22.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-513412 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-22-at-11.43.23-460x208.png" alt="Ethereum Classic hashrate" width="460" height="208" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-22-at-11.43.23-460x208.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-22-at-11.43.23-860x389.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-22-at-11.43.23-768x347.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-22-at-11.43.23-1536x695.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-22-at-11.43.23-2048x926.png 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-22-at-11.43.23-750x339.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Screen-Shot-2022-12-22-at-11.43.23-1140x516.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p class="p2">The decline can also be attributed to the bear market and the muted interest from investors. Since bitcoin’s price touched below $20,000, all of the cryptocurrencies in the space have seen a similar decline. Ravencoin, another proof of work network that got massive attention following Ethereum’s move to proof of stake, has also seen its hashrate plummet in the last 3 months.</p>
<p class="p2">Ravencoin’s hashrate now sits at 9.49 TH/s compared to its Sep. 22, 2022 peak of 17.59 TH/s. Meanwhile, other leading proof of work networks including Litecoin and Dogecoin has seen an increase in mining hashrate, whereas bitcoin remains mostly around 250 exahashes per second (EH/s).</p>
<h2 class="p2">What About ETC Price?</h2>
<p class="p2">ETC, the native cryptocurrency of the Ethereum Classic network, was basically on a rollercoaster in the three months since Ethereum moved to proof of stake. At first, as the network began to get more attention, ETC’s price had risen drastically. It eventually peaked above $42 before starting another downtrend.</p>

<p class="p2">At current prices, the digital asset has lost over 68% of its value from September 2022 and is still very bearish. A lot of attention had also moved on to Dogecoin, a proof-of-work cryptocurrency that saw a surge in price following Elon Musk’s takeover of Twitter.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/aprkK5EA/" alt="Ethereum Classic (ETC) price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1760" /></p>

<p class="p2">Obviously, this increase in the price of DOGE had incentivized miners to move over to Dogecoin, eventually taking share from Ethereum Classic. As interest fell, so did the mining hashrate and price naturally followed the same trend.</p>
<p class="p2">ETC now sits below its 100-day moving average, which means that investors are expecting lower prices to come. It is trading at $16.41 at the time of this writing, down 11% in the last 7 days.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-Classic-hashrate-460x276.jpeg" width="460" height="276" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
