<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"

	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 08:52:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">221170450</site>	<item>
		<title>These Are The Factors That Could Lead To Another Bitcoin Rally: ARK Invest</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/factors-could-lead-to-bitcoin-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 08:46:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ark invest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC Reversal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545863</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a report released on August 4, ARK Invest’s on-chain researcher David Puell reveals factors that could lead to another Bitcoin rally. The report, titled “The Bitcoin Monthly: July 2023,” provides an in-depth analysis and distinguishes between Bitcoin’s current situation and what the future holds for the largest cryptocurrency by market cap. Some Positives For Bitcoin Puell highlights how Bitcoin’s tepid 90-day volatility shares similarities with 2017 levels. According to the report, this prolonged low volatility usually represents the ‘calm before the storm,’ with Puell speculating that a significant price movement will likely happen soon. However, whether it will be a breakout or a breakdown remains uncertain.  Related Reading: Bank Of Canada Study Shows Crypto Ownership In The Country Fell In The Last 2 Years There is cause for optimism, though, as the decrease in hash rate on the blockchain provides an optimistic signal. The decrease could signify oversold conditions &#8211; whereby Bitcoin is currently trading below its actual worth, and considering that it has traded at an undervalued price for a long while now, we could see an upward trend, which would signify a price reversal.  Additionally, there has been an increase in “liveliness” as selling pressure has reduced and more holders are choosing to ‘HODL.’ The report states that liveliness fell below 60% in July, the lowest selling pressure since Q4 of 2020.  The short-term holders’ profit/loss ratio also coincides with historical trend reversals, signifying that a breakout is more likely to occur.  The report states: This breakeven level correlates both with local bottoms during primary bull markets and with local tops during bear market environments. Meanwhile, the Federal Reserve’s continued hike rate has been known to be a macro factor on Bitcoin and the crypto market. Puell believes that the Fed’s actions could significantly impact Bitcoin’s performance and the economy as a whole. A potential slowdown in CPI (consumer product index) inflation could see a surge in Bitcoin’s appeal as a non-inflammatory asset. BTC struggles to hold $29,000 support &#124; Source: BTCUSD on Tradingview.com Binance Could Have A Domino Effect On BTC The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (BTC) filed a lawsuit against Binance for trading unregistered securities, amongst other allegations. This ongoing legal tussle could affect Bitcoin’s performance and the crypto market.  According to the report, Binance’s BNB token ensures stability in the crypto market by providing significant liquidity for other cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin. If sentiments begin to tilt in favor of the SEC and DOJ, it could trigger a “bank run,” which would see BNB’s price plummet, causing a domino effect on the crypto market.  Related Reading: Crypto Trading Volumes Fall To Lowest Level In 2023 Amid Bear Market Woes While historical trends signify a bullish trajectory for Bitcoin’s price, the token might be marred by macroeconomic forces and regulatory concerns. It is believed that Bitcoin breaching the resistance level at $29,450 could shape its future outlook. As Bitcoin continues to witness a downward trajectory, that resistance level might be the key to a sustained breakout or further consolidation.  Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a <a href="https://ark-invest.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/The-Bitcoin-Monthly-July-2023.pdf" rel="nofollow">report</a> released on August 4, ARK Invest’s on-chain researcher David Puell reveals factors that could lead to another Bitcoin rally. The report, titled “The Bitcoin Monthly: July 2023,” provides an in-depth analysis and distinguishes between Bitcoin’s current situation and what the future holds for the largest cryptocurrency by market cap.</p>
<h2>Some Positives For Bitcoin</h2>
<p>Puell highlights how Bitcoin’s tepid 90-day volatility shares similarities with 2017 levels. According to the report, this prolonged low volatility usually represents the ‘calm before the storm,’ with Puell speculating that a significant price movement will likely happen soon. However, whether it will be a breakout or a breakdown remains uncertain. </p>

<p>There is cause for optimism, though, as the decrease in <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-hash-rate-retakes-all-time-high/">hash rate on the blockchain</a> provides an optimistic signal. The decrease could signify oversold conditions &#8211; whereby Bitcoin is currently trading below its actual worth, and considering that it has traded at an undervalued price for a long while now, we could see an upward trend, which would signify a price reversal. </p>
<p>Additionally, there has been an increase in “liveliness” as selling pressure has reduced and more holders are choosing to ‘HODL.’ The report states that liveliness fell below 60% in July, the lowest selling pressure since Q4 of 2020. </p>
<p>The short-term holders’ profit/loss ratio also coincides with historical trend reversals, signifying that a breakout is more likely to occur. </p>
<p>The report states:</p>
<blockquote><p>This breakeven level correlates both with local bottoms during primary bull markets and with local tops during bear market environments.</p></blockquote>
<p>Meanwhile, the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/federal-reserve-certifies-57-organizations-for-instant-payments-system-fednow/">Federal Reserve’s</a> continued hike rate has been known to be a macro factor on Bitcoin and the crypto market. Puell believes that the Fed’s actions could significantly impact Bitcoin’s performance and the economy as a whole. A potential slowdown in CPI (consumer product index) inflation could see a surge in Bitcoin’s appeal as a non-inflammatory asset.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/DEIkOT5l/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2>Binance Could Have A Domino Effect On BTC</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/sec-sues-binance-coinbase-blackrock-bitcoin-etf-inside-job/">United States Securities and Exchange Commission (BTC) filed a lawsuit against Binance</a> for trading unregistered securities, amongst other allegations. This ongoing legal tussle could affect Bitcoin’s performance and the crypto market. </p>
<p>According to the report, Binance’s BNB token ensures stability in the crypto market by providing significant liquidity for other cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin. If sentiments begin to tilt in favor of the SEC and DOJ, it could trigger a “<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/long-queues-seen-at-silicon-valley-bank-owned-boston-private-a-bank-run/">bank run</a>,” which would see BNB’s price plummet, causing a domino effect on the crypto market. </p>

<p>While historical trends signify a bullish trajectory for Bitcoin’s price, the token might be marred by macroeconomic forces and regulatory concerns. It is believed that Bitcoin breaching the resistance level at $29,450 could shape its future outlook. </p>
<p>As Bitcoin continues to witness a downward trajectory, that resistance level might be the key to a sustained breakout or further consolidation. </p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-877508718.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545863</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Research Expert Decodes Latest Crypto And Finance Market Trends</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/coinbase-research-expert-decodes-latest-crypto-and-finance-market-trends/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 23:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545856</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Coinbase’s Head of Research, David Duong, has shared his insights on the recent market movements in traditional finance and crypto.  He believes that current macro conditions suggest a temporary pause in the recent strong USD trend, which should support the crypto market.  Related Reading: Is SUI Price Stability Under Threat Due To Transactional Boom And Bust? Key Crypto &#38; Finance Movements Duong notes that the recent carry trades upset by the Bank of Japan’s decision to raise the hard cap on its 10-year bond yield have created instability across different pockets of the FX market.  Meanwhile, the surprise decision by Brazil’s central bank to cut its benchmark SELIC rate by 50bps (compared to expectations of 25bps) has led to higher interest rates in some price currencies coming down. In the US, the yield curve steepened significantly following the rally in Treasury bonds only two weeks ago, as the US Treasury Department announced an increase in the size of its debt issuance plans.  Although Fitch cut the US debt rating from AAA to AA+ due to concerns about the fiscal outlook, Duong believes this impact on bond yields was fairly limited. Duong emphasizes that the US dollar is more sensitive to front-end rates, and the 2y yield seems well anchored. This suggests a temporary pause in the recent strong USD trend, which should support the crypto market.  However, he expresses concern that crypto performance may recouple with US equities in the short term, which may cap the upside on digital assets due to stretched valuations. Duong also discusses the recent exploit of four liquidity pools on Curve, which didn&#8217;t help risk appetite in the crypto space but didn&#8217;t sustainably accelerate the downtrend that’s been ongoing since mid-July.  He believes the actual systemic risk associated with the exploit is limited by mitigating factors that offset some attack vulnerabilities. He also thinks this is not evidence of DeFi’s weakness but highlights the system’s antifragile properties. Related Reading: Crypto Trading Volumes Fall To Lowest Level In 2023 Amid Bear Market Woes Regarding market catalysts, Duong mentions the court decision in the Grayscale case (to convert its trust to an ETF), distributions from the Mt Gox Rehabilitation Trust to creditors, and any movement on the various Bitcoin spot Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF) applications in the US.  However, he notes that all those events are difficult to position for, so the market will have to wait for more information before pricing them in. Duong notes that flows on the desk have been balanced in the majors while altcoins have been net for sale. He also highlights Optimism’s OP token, which has traded better than expected, up 15% over the last 7 days, primarily attributed to the news around Base, Coinbase&#8217;s L2 on Ethereum. That chain, built on the OP stack, will broadly open on August 9. The total market capitalization of the cryptocurrency market stands at $1.13 trillion, which is consistent with its trading level since the start of August.  Additionally, Bitcoin&#8217;s dominance level is at 50.25%, while its price is currently trading at $29,216, showing a slight decline of 0.1% over the last 24 hours. Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase’s Head of Research, David Duong, has shared his <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/institutional/research-insights/research/weekly-market-commentary/debt-serious-aug-04-2023?__cf_chl_f_tk=QA3R1OGlNFiZDWkplW4Z04cfk_pfwRG9Cte_KvtmjAo-1691168160-0-gaNycGzNDLs" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">insights </a>on the recent market movements in traditional finance and crypto. </p>
<p>He believes that current macro conditions suggest a temporary pause in the recent strong USD trend, which should support the crypto market. </p>

<h2>Key Crypto &amp; Finance Movements</h2>
<p>Duong notes that the recent carry trades upset by the Bank of Japan’s decision to raise the hard cap on its 10-year bond yield have created instability across different pockets of the FX market. </p>
<p>Meanwhile, the surprise decision by Brazil’s central bank to cut its benchmark SELIC rate by 50bps (compared to expectations of 25bps) has led to higher interest rates in some price currencies coming down.</p>
<p>In the US, the yield curve steepened significantly following the rally in Treasury bonds only two weeks ago, as the US Treasury Department announced an increase in the size of its debt issuance plans. </p>
<p>Although Fitch cut the US debt rating from AAA to AA+ due to concerns about the fiscal outlook, Duong believes this impact on bond yields was fairly limited.</p>
<p>Duong emphasizes that the US dollar is more sensitive to front-end rates, and the 2y yield seems well anchored. This suggests a temporary pause in the recent strong USD trend, which should support the crypto market. </p>
<p>However, he expresses concern that crypto performance may recouple with US equities in the short term, which may cap the upside on digital assets due to stretched valuations.</p>
<p>Duong also discusses the recent exploit of four liquidity pools on <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/curve-finance-fights-back-with-warning-and-unrefusable-offer-to-hacker/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Curve</a>, which didn&#8217;t help risk appetite in the crypto space but didn&#8217;t sustainably accelerate the downtrend that’s been ongoing since mid-July. </p>
<p>He believes the actual systemic risk associated with the exploit is limited by mitigating factors that offset some attack vulnerabilities. He also thinks this is not evidence of DeFi’s weakness but highlights the system’s antifragile properties.</p>

<p>Regarding market catalysts, Duong mentions the court decision in the Grayscale case (to convert its trust to an ETF), distributions from the Mt Gox Rehabilitation Trust to creditors, and any movement on the various Bitcoin spot Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF) applications in the US. </p>
<p>However, he notes that all those events are difficult to position for, so the market will have to wait for more information before pricing them in.</p>
<p>Duong notes that flows on the desk have been balanced in the majors while altcoins have been net for sale. He also highlights Optimism’s OP token, which has traded better than expected, up 15% over the last 7 days, primarily attributed to the news around Base, Coinbase&#8217;s L2 on Ethereum. That chain, built on the OP stack, will broadly open on August 9.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/J49W4LoC/" alt="Crypto" width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>The total market capitalization of the cryptocurrency market stands at $1.13 trillion, which is consistent with its trading level since the start of August. </p>
<p>Additionally, Bitcoin&#8217;s dominance level is at 50.25%, while its price is currently trading at $29,216, showing a slight decline of 0.1% over the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1310459406.jpg?fit=460%2C306" width="460" height="306" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545856</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Curve Finance Exploiter Returns 61,000 ETH After Protocol&#8217;s Stern Warning</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/curve-finance-exploiter-returns-61000-eth-after-protocols-stern-warning/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 22:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CRV Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CRVUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curve Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545848</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a surprising turn of events, the hacker known as the &#8220;Alchemix/Curve Finance Exploiter&#8221; has returned a total of 4,819.55 alteth and 6106 Ethereum (ETH) to Alchemix Finance, as reported by the journalist Colin Wu.   The hacker, who had gained unauthorized access to the protocol, had earlier demanded that the Alchemix Finance team confirm the address to which they wanted the stolen funds returned. Curve Finance Breach Ends On Positive Note Curve Finance has announced the return of stolen funds worth over $60 million, which were taken in a recent exploit.  As reported by NewsBTC, the protocol had issued a statement on Etherscan, urging the hackers to return the funds, and offered a 10% reward for their return. The hackers have agreed to return the funds, keeping 10% of the stolen amount. Related Reading: Will Bitcoin Rebound Anytime Soon? Here’s What On-Chain Data Says The attack on Curve Finance, which took place on July 30th, significantly impacted the decentralized finance (DeFi) sector and raised concerns about its security.  The hack targeted several pools on Curve Finance, withdrawing more than $47 million from various DeFi projects. This led to a drop in the value of Curve DAO (CRV), prompting its founder, Michael Egorov, to sell off the asset to save it. Following the attack, Curve Finance has taken measures to improve its security, including updating its contracts and implementing stricter security protocols. The protocol has also called on the hacker to return the stolen funds and offered a reward for their cooperation. The hack had caused significant concern among the cryptocurrency community. Still, the Alchemix Finance team&#8217;s swift response and the hacker&#8217;s decision to return the stolen funds demonstrate the importance of protocols taking swift action to protect their users and assets. CRV Sees Strong Trading Volume Despite Recent Hack Curve Finance is one of the largest decentralized exchanges (DEXs) in the cryptocurrency market, with a total value locked (TVL) of $2.349 billion, according to data from DeFiLlama.  The exchange has a market capitalization of $540.35 million and a fully diluted valuation of $2.035 billion, making it a significant player in the DeFi ecosystem. Related Reading: Bitstamp Makes Highly Anticipated XRP Announcement, But Does It Live Up To The Hype? The Curve Finance token (CRV) price currently stands at $0.62, with a 24-hour trading volume of $177.09 million. The staked amount of CRV is $432.64 million, representing approximately 80.07% of the market capitalization of the protocol. The data from DeFiLlama highlights the significant role that Curve Finance plays in the DeFi sector, with a substantial TVL and a high level of staked tokens. The liquidity available for trading on the exchange is also significant, with a high annualized trading volume and fees. The revenue generated by Curve Finance demonstrates the potential for decentralized exchanges to become profitable businesses, offering a viable alternative to centralized exchanges.  Overall, the data from DeFiLlama highlights the significant role that Curve Finance plays in the DeFi ecosystem and the potential for decentralized exchanges to become profitable businesses. With its high TVL, staked tokens, and liquidity, Curve Finance is well-positioned to continue its growth and become a leader in the DeFi sector. Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a surprising turn of events, the hacker known as the &#8220;Alchemix/Curve Finance Exploiter&#8221; has returned a total of 4,819.55 alteth and 6106 Ethereum (ETH) to Alchemix Finance, as <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1687472385241608192?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reported </a>by the journalist Colin Wu.  </p>
<p>The hacker, who had gained unauthorized access to the protocol, had earlier demanded that the Alchemix Finance team confirm the address to which they wanted the stolen funds returned.</p>
<h2>Curve Finance Breach Ends On Positive Note</h2>
<p>Curve Finance has <a href="https://twitter.com/AlchemixFi/status/1687469467196928000?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced </a>the return of stolen funds worth over $60 million, which were taken in a recent exploit. </p>
<p>As <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/curve-finance-fights-back-with-warning-and-unrefusable-offer-to-hacker/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">reported </a>by NewsBTC, the protocol had issued a statement on Etherscan, urging the hackers to return the funds, and offered a 10% reward for their return. The hackers have agreed to return the funds, keeping 10% of the stolen amount.</p>

<p>The attack on Curve Finance, which took place on July 30th, significantly impacted the decentralized finance (DeFi) sector and raised concerns about its security. </p>
<p>The hack targeted several pools on Curve Finance, withdrawing more than $47 million from various DeFi projects. This led to a drop in the value of Curve DAO (CRV), prompting its founder, Michael Egorov, to sell off the asset to save it.</p>
<p>Following the attack, Curve Finance has taken measures to improve its security, including updating its contracts and implementing stricter security protocols. The protocol has also called on the hacker to return the stolen funds and offered a reward for their cooperation.</p>
<p>The hack had caused significant concern among the cryptocurrency community. Still, the Alchemix Finance team&#8217;s swift response and the hacker&#8217;s decision to return the stolen funds demonstrate the importance of protocols taking swift action to protect their users and assets.</p>
CRV Sees Strong Trading Volume Despite Recent Hack
<p>Curve Finance is one of the largest decentralized exchanges (DEXs) in the cryptocurrency market, with a total value locked (TVL) of $2.349 billion, according to <a href="https://defillama.com/protocol/curve-finance" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data </a>from DeFiLlama. </p>
<p>The exchange has a market capitalization of $540.35 million and a fully diluted valuation of $2.035 billion, making it a significant player in the DeFi ecosystem.</p>

<p>The Curve Finance token (CRV) price currently stands at $0.62, with a 24-hour trading volume of $177.09 million. The staked amount of CRV is $432.64 million, representing approximately 80.07% of the market capitalization of the protocol.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/cx6tINEo/" alt="Curve Finance" width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>The data from DeFiLlama highlights the significant role that Curve Finance plays in the DeFi sector, with a substantial TVL and a high level of staked tokens. The liquidity available for trading on the exchange is also significant, with a high annualized trading volume and fees.</p>
<p>The revenue generated by Curve Finance demonstrates the potential for decentralized exchanges to become profitable businesses, offering a viable alternative to centralized exchanges. </p>
<p>Overall, the data from DeFiLlama highlights the significant role that Curve Finance plays in the DeFi ecosystem and the potential for decentralized exchanges to become profitable businesses. With its high TVL, staked tokens, and liquidity, Curve Finance is well-positioned to continue its growth and become a leader in the DeFi sector.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/sasun-bughdaryan-GQ5uX_BlfmY-unsplash.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545848</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XDC Token Continues To Record Higher Gains Daily, Can It Achieve $0.1 Mark?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/xdc-token-continues-to-record-higher-gains-daily-can-it-achieve-0-1-mark/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kent Glory]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 21:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XDC analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XDC Network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XDC price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XDC token]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XDCUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545802</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[XDC Network is now on its way to the $0.1 target price after encouraging price movements over the past weeks. The token is now among the most searched cryptos ranking fourth on CoinMarketCap’s list of trending cryptocurrencies. However, the question remains: How long can XDC sustain these rallies? Are the bulls energetic enough to exceed the anticipated $0.1 price mark? Let&#8217;s see XDC Soars Amid Market Downturn, What’s Fueling Its Price Movements? XDC Network is soaring today, August 4, as the broader market slightly improved. With a bullish momentum, the token rose by 16.7% on Friday morning. Also, it emerged as the biggest gainer with over 45% seven-day gain and 162% 30-day value growth. Related Reading: Bitcoin And Crypto Alert: The Implications Of Bill Ackman’s 30-Year T-Bills Short As of July 6, XDC traded at $0.03238 but later climbed to a monthly peak of $0.09092 on August 3, over 180% in the last 30 days. XDC reached a week high of $0.09134 on August 4, a nearly 50% increase from $0.05896 recorded on July 29.  These impressive moves have positioned the token as the best-performing cryptocurrency in the 30-day and seven-day timeframe. Although the momentum is still bullish, it has stalled slightly since the asset has shed a few gains and shifted from the day peak of $0.09146 to $0.081. These gains could result from other ecosystem developments, including the partnership between XDC Network and Infocomm Media Development Authority (IMDA) Singapore.  According to July 28 Bloomberg report, the crypto project integrated with IMDA’s TradeTrust &#8211; a Singaporean framework enables trusted interoperability of electronic trade documents across digital platforms.  This collaborative effort will allow IMDA’s TradeTrust to verify and transfer documents. Such capability can enhance trade visibility, proof of authenticity, and origins of documents. The collaboration is expected to enable a seamless and efficient flow of goods between digital trading partners. According to the report, the partnership marks a milestone for the XDC Network, as it could expand its reach and user base. Such growth will likely lead to a significant spike in active transactions and trading activities and it could be among the primary factors fueling XDC&#8217;s rallies in the past few days. XDC Market Outlook, More Rallies Possible? The XDC/USD chart shows the token trades below the Moving Average Convergence/Divergence signal line. This indicates a bearish momentum as XDC sheds previous gains.  Also, the RSI at 46.75 suggests the asset is approaching the oversold region. Moreover, the bears have formed stiff resistance at the $0.0851 level. They’re ready to push XDC down to lower lows if the bulls fail to regain momentum. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Price Poised To Reach $0.01 With Shibarium Upgrade, These CEOs Say  However, if the bulls rally enough to push the price above $0.851, the next target zone will be the $0.09166 level, from where XDC will likely shoot to $0.1 if momentum is sustained. Featured image from Pixabay and chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>XDC Network is now on its way to the $0.1 target price after encouraging price movements over the past weeks. The token is now among the most searched cryptos ranking fourth on CoinMarketCap’s list of <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/trending-cryptocurrencies/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">trending cryptocurrencies</a>.</p>
<p>However, the question remains: How long can XDC sustain these rallies? Are the bulls energetic enough to exceed the anticipated $0.1 price mark? Let&#8217;s see</p>
<h2>XDC Soars Amid Market Downturn, What’s Fueling Its Price Movements?</h2>
<p>XDC Network is soaring today, August 4, as the broader market slightly improved. With a bullish momentum, the token rose by 16.7% on Friday morning. Also, it emerged as the biggest gainer with over 45% seven-day gain and 162% 30-day value growth.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-crypto-implications-bill-ackman-30-y-t-bills-short/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin And Crypto Alert: The Implications Of Bill Ackman’s 30-Year T-Bills Short</a></p>
<p>As of July 6, XDC traded at $0.03238 but later climbed to a monthly peak of $0.09092 on August 3, over 180% in the last 30 days. XDC reached a week high of $0.09134 on August 4, a nearly 50% increase from $0.05896 recorded on July 29. </p>
<p>These impressive moves have positioned the token as the best-performing cryptocurrency in the 30-day and seven-day timeframe. Although the momentum is still bullish, it has stalled slightly since the asset has shed a few gains and shifted from the day peak of $0.09146 to $0.081. </p>
<p>These gains could result from other ecosystem developments, including the partnership between XDC Network and Infocomm Media Development Authority (IMDA) Singapore. </p>
<p>According to July 28 Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/press-releases/2023-07-28/xdc-network-has-partnered-with-the-infocomm-media-development-authority-imda-singapore-by-completing-their-integration-with" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a>, the crypto project integrated with IMDA’s TradeTrust &#8211; a Singaporean framework enables trusted interoperability of electronic trade documents across digital platforms. </p>
<p>This collaborative effort will allow IMDA’s TradeTrust to verify and transfer documents. Such capability can enhance trade visibility, proof of authenticity, and origins of documents. The collaboration is expected to enable a seamless and efficient flow of goods between digital trading partners.</p>
<p>According to the report, the partnership marks a milestone for the XDC Network, as it could expand its reach and user base. Such growth will likely lead to a significant spike in active transactions and trading activities and it could be among the primary factors fueling XDC&#8217;s rallies in the past few days.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Ttfecfk2/" alt="XDCUSD price chart" width="980" height="589"/>
<h2>XDC Market Outlook, More Rallies Possible?</h2>
<p>The XDC/USD <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/DxC8Rqny/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">chart</a> shows the token trades below the Moving Average Convergence/Divergence signal line. This indicates a bearish momentum as XDC sheds previous gains. </p>
<p>Also, the RSI at 46.75 suggests the asset is approaching the oversold region. Moreover, the bears have formed stiff resistance at the $0.0851 level. They’re ready to push XDC down to lower lows if the bulls fail to regain momentum. </p>

<p>However, if the bulls rally enough to push the price above $0.851, the next target zone will be the $0.09166 level, from where XDC will likely shoot to $0.1 if momentum is sustained.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/XDC.jpg?fit=460%2C276" width="460" height="276" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545802</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin NVT Shows Bearish Crossover, Price Drop Incoming?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-nvt-shows-bearish-crossover-price-drop-incoming/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 20:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin bearish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin NVT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin NVT Golden Cross]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545827</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Bitcoin Network Value To Transactions (NVT) ratio has formed a bearish crossover, a sign that a decline may be imminent. Bitcoin NVT Ratio Has Formed A Historical Bearish Crossover The &#8220;NVT ratio&#8221; is an indicator that measures the ratio between the Bitcoin market cap and transaction volume. In simple terms, what this metric tells us is whether the asset&#8217;s price (the market cap) is fairly valued compared to the network&#8217;s ability to transact coins (the transaction volume). When the ratio has a value above 1, it means that the price may be overinflated right now, as the blockchain isn&#8217;t observing the shift of any significant amount of capital. The risk of a correction taking place generally goes up the higher the metric trends above this mark. On the other hand, the indicator being below the threshold can imply that the market cap may be undervalued currently, and thus, a price surge may be due for the asset. In the context of the current discussion, the NVT ratio itself isn&#8217;t of interest, but rather a modified form called the &#8220;NVT golden cross&#8221; is. This metric compares the short-term moving average (MA) of the NVT ratio (10-day) to its long-term MA (30-day). As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, this NVT golden cross may be forming a pattern currently that could lead to a correction in the asset&#8217;s price. The below chart shows the trend in the Bitcoin NVT golden cross and the 30-day exponential moving average (EMA) of the same over the past year: The two metrics seem to have crossed each other in recent days &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As displayed in the above graph, the Bitcoin NVT golden cross has been going down recently and has just crossed under its 30-day EMA. This line appears to have historically been significant for the asset, as the instances marked by the analyst shows. Related Reading: Crypto Storm Brewing: Bitcoin Vortex Indicator Flashes Buy Alert Generally, whenever the indicator has crossed below this EMA line, the cryptocurrency&#8217;s value has taken a hit. From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that this pattern has already held up a few times during this rally so far. Naturally, if this historical precedence is anything to go by, then the current bearish crossover might also lead to Bitcoin registering a drawdown in the near future. It should be noted, though, that the crossover may not be fully confirmed yet, as the NVT golden cross has only slightly gone below the 30-day EMA so far. So it&#8217;s possible that the indicator could turn itself around in the coming days and cancel out the cross. Related Reading: Will Binance’s Zero-Fee Trading Help Bitcoin And Ethereum Prices It now remains to be seen, whether the Bitcoin NVT golden cross and the 30-day EMA would keep going in the same trajectories and solidify the cross, or if the pattern would retrace. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,200, down 1% in the last week. BTC has continued to show stagnation recently &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from mana5280 on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows the Bitcoin Network Value To Transactions (NVT) ratio has formed a bearish crossover, a sign that a decline may be imminent.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin NVT Ratio Has Formed A Historical Bearish Crossover</h2>
<p>The &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-overvalued-according-nvt-ratio/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">NVT ratio</a>&#8221; is an indicator that measures the ratio between the Bitcoin market cap and transaction volume. In simple terms, what this metric tells us is whether the asset&#8217;s price (the market cap) is fairly valued compared to the network&#8217;s ability to transact coins (the transaction volume).</p>
<p>When the ratio has a value above 1, it means that the price may be overinflated right now, as the blockchain isn&#8217;t observing the shift of any significant amount of capital. The risk of a correction taking place generally goes up the higher the metric trends above this mark.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the indicator being below the threshold can imply that the market cap may be undervalued currently, and thus, a price surge may be due for the asset.</p>
<p>In the context of the current discussion, the NVT ratio itself isn&#8217;t of interest, but rather a modified form called the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-nvt-golden-cross-says-btc-is-overpriced-decline-soon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">NVT golden cross</a>&#8221; is. This metric compares the short-term moving average (MA) of the NVT ratio (10-day) to its long-term MA (30-day).</p>
<p>As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/64ccc5ae4909d367ef29214f-EMA30-crossed-over-NVT-Golden-Cross-line-a-possible-impact-on-Bitcoin-price" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a>, this NVT golden cross may be forming a pattern currently that could lead to a correction in the asset&#8217;s price.</p>
<p>The below chart shows the trend in the Bitcoin NVT golden cross and the 30-day exponential moving average (EMA) of the same over the past year:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://i0.wp.com/img.cryptoquant.com/312101/quicktake/Sk2cMuWZ_ae7cebd6483d98353c055970e48fe053daaf28dc74d75e064a3730d013f6a7f5.png?resize=1280%2C806&#038;ssl=1" alt="Bitcoin NVT Golden Cross" width="1280" height="806"  data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the Bitcoin NVT golden cross has been going down recently and has just crossed under its 30-day EMA. This line appears to have historically been significant for the asset, as the instances marked by the analyst shows.</p>

<p>Generally, whenever the indicator has crossed below this EMA line, the cryptocurrency&#8217;s value has taken a hit. From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that this pattern has already held up a few times during this <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/is-another-bitcoin-rally-coming-soon-this-pattern-may-say-so/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">rally</a> so far.</p>
<p>Naturally, if this historical precedence is anything to go by, then the current bearish crossover might also lead to Bitcoin registering a drawdown in the near future.</p>
<p>It should be noted, though, that the crossover may not be fully confirmed yet, as the NVT golden cross has only slightly gone below the 30-day EMA so far. So it&#8217;s possible that the indicator could turn itself around in the coming days and cancel out the cross.</p>

<p>It now remains to be seen, whether the Bitcoin NVT golden cross and the 30-day EMA would keep going in the same trajectories and solidify the cross, or if the pattern would retrace.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,200, down 1% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/evx27NuA/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/mana5280-rGPDLlMNFF4-unsplash.jpg?fit=460%2C341" width="460" height="341" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545827</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bank Of Canada Study Shows Crypto Ownership In The Country Fell In The Last 2 Years</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/canada-crypto-ownership-in-the-country-fell-in-2-years/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 19:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bank of Canada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[boc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[canada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto investors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545826</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A recent study by the Bank of Canada (BoC) has shown a decline in the ownership of cryptocurrencies over the two years. The BoC has attributed this decline in crypto ownership to ecosystem collapses, regulatory hurdles, and price depreciation. Bitcoin’s Decline Most Notable According to the Bitcoin Omnibus Survey, Bitcoin’s ownership across the country dipped to 10% at the end of last year. This decline has been attributed to various factors, including the significant drop from its all-time high due to the current market conditions, especially since Bitcoin’s price crashed over 50% from its all-time high of $69,044.77 last year.  Related Reading: Will Binance’s Zero-Fee Trading Help Bitcoin And Ethereum Prices The survey also cited FTX’s unexpected collapse as contributing to the decline, as it prompted enhanced scrutiny from regulators while also creating doubts in the hearts of crypto investors. The decline in Bitcoin ownership wasn’t a result of investors moving their money to other crypto assets given that altcoins also suffered a similar fate to Bitcoin, as ownership in these digital assets also experienced a downward trend last year. The report read: Investors did not appear to shift out of Bitcoin and into other cryptoassets, as we observe decreased ownership of altcoins. There are some positives for Bitcoin and the crypto ecosystem, as Bitcoin’s ownership is still higher than the 8% recorded between 2018 and 2020. Another silver lining is that many locals are aware of Bitcoin (meaning they could invest in it in the near future), as general awareness of the token has been at an impressive 90%. However, despite being aware of the term Bitcoin, many Canadians still don’t understand how the cryptocurrency operates. According to the BoC&#8217;s research methodology, 61% of non-bitcoin owners showed low crypto literacy. Meanwhile, a meager 30% of Bitcoin owners exhibited high-level crypto literacy.  Market remains highly volatile &#124; Source: Crypto Total Market Cap on Tradingview.com Financial Literacy Doesn’t Equate To Crypto Enthusiasm Many would have predicted that persons with higher financial literacy would be more bullish on Bitcoin and other crypto assets. However, that isn’t the case in Canada, according to the survey. Interestingly, respondents with a high financial literacy were the ones who were quick to exit the crypto market. In contrast, those with a lower financial literacy remained bullish despite the market conditions and regulatory concerns.  Related Reading: CRV Price Recovers From 6-Month Lows, What’s Driving The Price? While these figures may not be so encouraging, there is enough reason to believe that the growing adoption of cryptocurrencies worldwide will impact the future of crypto ownership in the country as more locals gain crypto literacy.  Furthermore, efforts from the authorities to provide regulatory clarity could also help as it will boost investors’ confidence in the country and consequently increase crypto ownership in the country. Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A recent <a href="https://www.bankofcanada.ca/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/sdp2023-14.pdf" rel="nofollow">study</a> by the Bank of Canada (BoC) has shown a decline in the ownership of cryptocurrencies over the two years. The BoC has attributed this decline in crypto ownership to ecosystem collapses, regulatory hurdles, and price depreciation.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin’s Decline Most Notable</h2>
<p>According to the Bitcoin Omnibus Survey, Bitcoin’s ownership across the country dipped to 10% at the end of last year. This decline has been attributed to various factors, including the significant drop from its all-time high due to the current market conditions, especially since Bitcoin’s price crashed over 50% from its all-time high of $69,044.77 last year. </p>

<p>The survey also cited FTX’s unexpected collapse as contributing to the decline, as it prompted enhanced scrutiny from regulators while also creating doubts in the hearts of crypto investors.</p>
<p>The decline in Bitcoin ownership wasn’t a result of investors moving their money to other crypto assets given that altcoins also suffered a similar fate to Bitcoin, as ownership in these digital assets also experienced a downward trend last year.</p>
<p>The report read:</p>
<blockquote><p>Investors did not appear to shift out of Bitcoin and into other cryptoassets, as we observe decreased ownership of altcoins.</p></blockquote>
<p>There are some positives for Bitcoin and the crypto ecosystem, as Bitcoin’s ownership is still higher than the 8% recorded between 2018 and 2020. Another silver lining is that many locals are aware of Bitcoin (meaning they could invest in it in the near future), as general awareness of the token has been at an impressive 90%.</p>
<p>However, despite being aware of the term Bitcoin, many Canadians still don’t understand how the cryptocurrency operates. According to the BoC&#8217;s research methodology, 61% of non-bitcoin owners showed low crypto literacy. Meanwhile, a meager 30% of Bitcoin owners exhibited high-level crypto literacy. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/w5AtaN5o/" alt="Crypto total market cap chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2>Financial Literacy Doesn’t Equate To Crypto Enthusiasm</h2>
<p>Many would have predicted that persons with higher financial literacy would be more bullish on Bitcoin and other crypto assets. However, that isn’t the case in Canada, according to the survey. Interestingly, respondents with a high financial literacy were the ones who were quick to exit the crypto market. In contrast, those with a lower financial literacy remained bullish despite the market conditions and regulatory concerns. </p>

<p>While these figures may not be so encouraging, there is enough reason to believe that the growing adoption of cryptocurrencies worldwide will impact the future of crypto ownership in the country as more locals gain crypto literacy. </p>
<p>Furthermore, efforts from the authorities to provide regulatory clarity could also help as it will boost investors’ confidence in the country and consequently increase crypto ownership in the country.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1430765691.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545826</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Performance Woes: How Might Its Price Respond To Current Market Realities?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/all/xrp-performance-woes-how-might-its-price-respond-to-current-market-realities/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 18:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545813</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[XRP experienced a surge after Ripple Labs&#8217; recent legal win against the US Securities and Exchange Commission, marking a partial victory. Nonetheless, the pace of this upswing has moderated in recent weeks, encountering notable resistance and initiating a downward trajectory. With the latest data from CoinGecko, the XRP value registers at $0.658512. This shows a 1.1% contraction over the preceding 24 hours and a notable seven-day decline of 7.4%. Related Reading: All Hype? BALD Meme Coin’s Volume Shaved By 96% During the height of its price surge after Ripple Labs&#8217; legal breakthrough, its coin encountered a rejection near the $0.95 threshold. This particular zone mirrors the level it reached back in March 2022 during its bearish decline. This prompts the question of whether XRP is retracing its steps into a former range or if this constitutes a mere temporary retreat within an ongoing upward trend. XRP Dampening Sentiment Further impacting the prevailing sentiment around XRP, US District Judge Jed Rakoff has invalidated the approach taken in last month&#8217;s ruling concerning the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Ripple Labs. According to an XRP price analysis, the cryptocurrency has reached its zenith and is now poised to revisit its previous resistance level. Nonetheless, several crucial factors necessitate consideration beforehand. XRP is currently trading at the upper threshold of the expansive Bollinger Bands. While this signifies the potential for a retracement, it also signifies amplified volatility, indicating that any forthcoming pullback might manifest as notably severe. XRP price at $0.65 on the daily chart: TradingView.com Furthermore, the Stochastic RSI illustrates that XRP has surged to the overbought threshold at 80. This suggests a corrective pullback is probable, given that the market&#8217;s buying strength is waning. Traders Turn To New Coin As Alternative Amid the recent challenges faced by XRP, numerous traders have shifted their focus toward an emerging alternative &#8211; XRP20. This new option has garnered attention due to its modest market capitalization and unique advantages that set it apart from the original XRP coin. According to insights shared by analyst Jacob Bury, XRP20 holds significant potential for a price surge, leveraging the ongoing situation with XRP. The conventional XRP project has faced criticism for its centralized nature and the over-the-counter sales of XRP conducted by its founders. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Price Poised To Reach $0.01 With Shibarium Upgrade, These CEOs Say In contrast, XRP20 stands out as a fully community-owned venture. It has allotted 40% of its tokens for presale, another 40% for staking rewards, earmarked 10% for DEX liquidity and plans to burn the remaining 10%. The coin is not affiliated with Ripple, XRP or their ecosystem, its website says. One of the distinctive features of XRP20 lies in its extensive marketing achievements. The project has gained notable coverage from various prominent media outlets, contributing to a successful presale round that raised a substantial $300K in two days. This rapid fundraising underscores the growing interest and enthusiasm surrounding the coin within the trading community. (This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk). Featured image from iStock]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>XRP experienced a surge after Ripple Labs&#8217; recent legal win against the US Securities and Exchange Commission, marking a partial victory. Nonetheless, the pace of this upswing has moderated in recent weeks, encountering notable resistance and initiating a downward trajectory.</p>
<p>With the latest data from <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/xrp" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGecko</a>, the XRP value registers at $0.658512. This shows a 1.1% contraction over the preceding 24 hours and a notable seven-day decline of 7.4%.</p>

<p>During the height of its price surge after Ripple Labs&#8217; legal breakthrough, its coin encountered a rejection near the $0.95 threshold. This particular zone mirrors the level it reached back in March 2022 during its bearish decline. </p>
<p>This prompts the question of whether XRP is retracing its steps into a former range or if this constitutes a mere temporary retreat within an ongoing upward trend.</p>
<h2><strong>XRP Dampening Sentiment</strong></h2>
<p>Further impacting the prevailing sentiment around XRP, US District Judge Jed Rakoff has invalidated the approach taken in last month&#8217;s ruling concerning the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Ripple Labs.</p>
<p>According to an <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://finbold.com/xrp-price-prediction-as-crypto-prices-tank-will-it-drop-to-0-5-traders-are-turning-to-xrp20-instead/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">XRP price analysis</a>, the cryptocurrency has reached its zenith and is now poised to revisit its previous resistance level. Nonetheless, several crucial factors necessitate consideration beforehand.</p>
<p>XRP is currently trading at the upper threshold of the expansive Bollinger Bands. While this signifies the potential for a retracement, it also signifies amplified volatility, indicating that any forthcoming pullback might manifest as notably severe.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/8lkPwSGB/" width="1835" height="893"/></p>

<p>Furthermore, the Stochastic RSI illustrates that XRP has surged to the overbought threshold at 80. This suggests a corrective pullback is probable, given that the market&#8217;s buying strength is waning.</p>
<h2><strong>Traders Turn To New Coin As Alternative</strong></h2>
<p>Amid the recent challenges faced by XRP, numerous traders have shifted their focus toward an emerging alternative &#8211; XRP20. This new option has garnered attention due to its modest market capitalization and unique advantages that set it apart from the original XRP coin.</p>
<p>According to <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r4A-L0V3sxU" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">insights shared by analyst Jacob Bury</a>, XRP20 holds significant potential for a price surge, leveraging the ongoing situation with XRP. The conventional XRP project has faced criticism for its centralized nature and the over-the-counter sales of XRP conducted by its founders.</p>

<p>In contrast, XRP20 stands out as a fully community-owned venture. It has allotted 40% of its tokens for presale, another 40% for staking rewards, earmarked 10% for DEX liquidity and plans to burn the remaining 10%. The coin is not affiliated with Ripple, XRP or their ecosystem, its website says.</p>
<p>One of the distinctive features of XRP20 lies in its extensive marketing achievements. The project has gained notable coverage from various prominent media outlets, contributing to a successful presale round that raised a substantial $300K in two days. This rapid fundraising underscores the growing interest and enthusiasm surrounding the coin within the trading community.</p>
<p><em>(This site&#8217;s content should not be construed as investment advice. Investing involves risk. When you invest, your capital is subject to risk).</em></p>
<p><em>Featured image from iStock</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/a-15.png?fit=460%2C261" width="460" height="261" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545813</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Trading Volumes Fall To Lowest Level In 2023 Amid Bear Market Woes</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/crypto-trading-volumes-fall-to-lowest-level-in-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 17:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange volumes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto exchanges]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto trading volumes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto volumes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Upbit]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545785</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[According to a report by CCData, a digital assets data provider, crypto trading volumes on centralized exchanges in July fell to their lowest this year as the bear market lingers. Spot trading volumes dipped by 10.5% to $515 billion, while derivatives volume dipped by 12.7% to $1.85 trillion.  This slump has been attributed to the low volatility in the price action of the two leading crypto tokens &#8211; bitcoin and ether. Both tokens have continued to experience sideways price movement since the beginning of July, thus keeping the market players out as they await a breakout.  Binance Continues To Lead The Pack Despite Regulatory Concerns According to the latest exchange review report, Binance remains the largest crypto exchange by spot trading volume, recording $208 billion in trading volume for July. However, it wasn’t all good news for the exchange as its market share declined for the fifth consecutive month in July, dipping to 40.4% &#8211; its lowest since August 2022. Related Reading: Buying Pressure Incoming? MicroStrategy Files Notice With SEC To Sell $750 Million In Stocks The decline in Binance’s market share has been attributed largely to the firm’s ongoing legal battle with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). In July, the SEC accused Binance and its CEO Changpeng Zhao, of offering different tokens, which the regulator has tagged as “unregistered securities,” to the public.  Binance’s regulatory battles might have forced traders to seek alternatives as they fear the worst might happen to the crypto exchange. &#8220;The recent concerns over possible regulatory action against Binance seem to have adversely affected the trading activity on the exchange, with users likely to prefer other alternatives,&#8221; said Joseph, a research analyst at CCData, in a note to CoinDesk. Total market cap struggles at $1.127 trillion &#124; Source: Crypto Total Market Cap on Tradingview.com Crypto Industry In South Korea Thriving South Korea’s Upbit, meanwhile, outperformed the general market trend as the crypto exchange as it rose to become the second-largest crypto exchange by trading volume, ranking only behind Binance.  In July, the crypto exchange saw its spot trading volume rise by 42.3% to $29.8 billion. This figure put Upbit ahead of rivals OKX and Coinbase (the first time this is happening), with both crypto exchanges’ volumes dropping 11.6% and 5.75%, respectively. Related Reading: Ethereum ETFs Heat Up As Filings With SEC Climbs To Six “Compared to last month, Upbit saw the largest increase in market share, with the exchange now accounting for 5.78% of the trading volumes on centralized exchanges,” the report elaborated.  Upbit wasn’t the only South Korean crypto exchange that enjoyed a remarkable uptrend last month. According to the report, other South Korean exchanges like Bithumb and CoinOne also saw an increase in their trading volume. Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to a <a href="https://ccdata.io/reports/exchange-review-july-2023" rel="nofollow">report</a> by CCData, a digital assets data provider, crypto trading volumes on centralized exchanges in July fell to their lowest this year as the bear market lingers. Spot trading volumes dipped by 10.5% to $515 billion, while derivatives volume dipped by 12.7% to $1.85 trillion. </p>
<p>This slump has been attributed to the low volatility in the price action of the two leading crypto tokens &#8211; bitcoin and ether. Both tokens have continued to experience sideways price movement since the beginning of July, thus keeping the market players out as they await a breakout. </p>
<h2>Binance Continues To Lead The Pack Despite Regulatory Concerns</h2>
<p>According to the latest exchange review report, Binance remains the largest crypto exchange by spot trading volume, recording $208 billion in trading volume for July. However, it wasn’t all good news for the exchange as its market share declined for the fifth consecutive month in July, dipping to 40.4% &#8211; its lowest since August 2022.</p>

<p>The decline in Binance’s market share has been attributed largely to the firm’s ongoing legal battle with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). In July, the SEC accused Binance and its CEO Changpeng Zhao, of offering different tokens, which the regulator has tagged as “unregistered securities,” to the public. </p>
<p>Binance’s regulatory battles might have forced traders to seek alternatives as they fear the worst might happen to the crypto exchange.</p>
<p>&#8220;The recent concerns over possible regulatory action against Binance seem to have adversely affected the trading activity on the exchange, with users likely to prefer other alternatives,&#8221; said Joseph, a research analyst at CCData, in a note to CoinDesk.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Dp6EQH7a/" alt="Crypto total market cap chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2>Crypto Industry In South Korea Thriving</h2>
<p>South Korea’s Upbit, meanwhile, outperformed the general market trend as the crypto exchange as it rose to become the second-largest crypto exchange by trading volume, ranking only behind Binance. </p>
<p>In July, the crypto exchange saw its spot trading volume rise by 42.3% to $29.8 billion. This figure put Upbit ahead of rivals OKX and Coinbase (the first time this is happening), with both crypto exchanges’ volumes dropping 11.6% and 5.75%, respectively.</p>

<p>“Compared to last month, Upbit saw the largest increase in market share, with the exchange now accounting for 5.78% of the trading volumes on centralized exchanges,” the report elaborated. </p>
<p>Upbit wasn’t the only South Korean crypto exchange that enjoyed a remarkable uptrend last month. According to the report, other South Korean exchanges like Bithumb and CoinOne also saw an increase in their trading volume.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1398694810.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545785</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will Bitcoin Rebound Anytime Soon? Here&#8217;s What On-Chain Data Says</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-rebound-anytime-soon-on-chain-data-says/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 16:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Rebound]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545767</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin has continued to struggle recently as its price is still in the low $29,000 level. Here&#8217;s what on-chain data says about if a rebound is likely or not. What Does Bitcoin On-Chain Data Say About The Asset&#8217;s Near-Term Outlook? Bitcoin has stagnated recently as the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price has failed to keep any significant moves going. Even the latest decline in the asset has been indecisive, as the price didn&#8217;t take long to fall back to a sideways movement. Under these conditions, it&#8217;s natural that investors may be wondering when the asset might break out of this consolidation. Related Reading: Quant Explains How These Indicators Affect Ethereum Price Recent on-chain data from Santiment sheds light on the underlying metrics related to the asset, which may contain hints about where the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price could be heading next. First, here is a chart that shows the data for two of the Bitcoin indicators that are of interest here: The trend in the active addresses and ratio of volume in profit to loss &#124; Source: Santiment on X As you can see in the above graph, there are two indicators of relevance here: the &#8220;daily active addresses&#8221; and the &#8220;ratio of on-chain transaction volume in profit to loss.&#8221; The former of these naturally keeps track of the total number of unique addresses on the Bitcoin blockchain that are taking part in some kind of transaction activity on the network. From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that this metric has observed a large spike recently, suggesting that a high number of addresses have become active. Generally, a large number of addresses making transfers on the chain implies that a high amount of users are making use of the chain right now. The current value of the metric suggests that more than a million addresses have been active recently, which is the highest that the indicator has been since the middle of April. Such an increase in utility suggests that there is a large amount of interest in the coin at the moment. Now, the other metric here measures the difference between the profit-taking and loss-taking volumes on the Bitcoin network. As is visible in the graph, this indicator has a negative value currently, which means that the majority of the selling in the market is happening at some loss. These negative levels of the metric are similar in scale to those observed back during the March plunge. Historically, bottoms in the price have become more probable to form when investors are capitulating like this, as the coins of the weak hands are picked up by the strong hands in such periods. Related Reading: Bitcoin And Crypto Alert: The Implications Of Bill Ackman’s 30-Year T-Bills Short If a rebound move does arise from this capitulation, then its timing may be ideal, as a high amount of active addresses can mean the presence of a large number of traders who can help fuel the move. Additionally, the Bitcoin millionaire and billionaire addresses have also been behind the asset recently, as they have added 27,755 BTC to their holdings since May. The value of the metric has been trending up recently &#124; Source: Santiment on X Based on these factors, it&#8217;s not hard to believe that a rebound in the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price might take place in the near future, although it may only be a short-term move. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,100, down 1% in the last week. BTC has continued to move sideways &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from iStock.com, charts from TradingView.com, Santiment.net]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has continued to struggle recently as its price is still in the low $29,000 level. Here&#8217;s what on-chain data says about if a rebound is likely or not.</p>
<h2>What Does Bitcoin On-Chain Data Say About The Asset&#8217;s Near-Term Outlook?</h2>
<p>Bitcoin has stagnated recently as the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price has failed to keep any significant moves going. Even the latest decline in the asset has been indecisive, as the price didn&#8217;t take long to fall back to a sideways movement. Under these conditions, it&#8217;s natural that investors may be wondering when the asset might break out of this consolidation.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/quant-explains-how-these-indicators-affect-ethereum-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Quant Explains How These Indicators Affect Ethereum Price</a></p>
<p>Recent on-chain data from <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Santiment</a> sheds light on the underlying metrics related to the asset, which may contain hints about where the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price could be heading next.</p>
<p>First, here is a chart that shows the data for two of the Bitcoin indicators that are of interest here:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/F2nkXdeakAAS7cd?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Bitcoin Active Addresses &amp; Profit To Loss" width="2774" height="1766"/></p>

<p>As you can see in the above graph, there are two indicators of relevance here: the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-addresses-decline-transaction-demand-why/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">daily active addresses</a>&#8221; and the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-loss-taking-spikes-why-could-bullish/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">ratio of on-chain transaction volume in profit to loss</a>.&#8221;</p>
<p>The former of these naturally keeps track of the total number of unique addresses on the Bitcoin blockchain that are taking part in some kind of transaction activity on the network.</p>
<p>From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that this metric has observed a large spike recently, suggesting that a high number of addresses have become active. Generally, a large number of addresses making transfers on the chain implies that a high amount of users are making use of the chain right now.</p>
<p>The current value of the metric suggests that more than a million addresses have been active recently, which is the highest that the indicator has been since the middle of April. Such an increase in utility suggests that there is a large amount of interest in the coin at the moment.</p>
<p>Now, the other metric here measures the difference between the profit-taking and loss-taking volumes on the Bitcoin network. As is visible in the graph, this indicator has a negative value currently, which means that the majority of the selling in the market is happening at some loss.</p>
<p>These negative levels of the metric are similar in scale to those observed back during the March plunge. Historically, bottoms in the price have become more probable to form when investors are capitulating like this, as the coins of the weak hands are picked up by the strong hands in such periods.</p>

<p>If a rebound move does arise from this <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/xrp-traders-show-capitulation-why-could-bullish/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">capitulation</a>, then its timing may be ideal, as a high amount of active addresses can mean the presence of a large number of traders who can help fuel the move.</p>
<p>Additionally, the Bitcoin millionaire and billionaire addresses have also been behind the asset recently, as they have added 27,755 BTC to their holdings since May.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/F2lYERmagAAoFT-?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Bitcoin sharks &amp; whales" width="2851" height="1810"/></p>

<p>Based on these factors, it&#8217;s not hard to believe that a rebound in the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price might take place in the near future, although it may only be a short-term move.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $29,100, down 1% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/uoZoEtCZ/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="877"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1384277890.jpg?fit=460%2C239" width="460" height="239" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545767</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitstamp Makes Highly Anticipated XRP Announcement, But Does It Live Up To The Hype?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/bitstamp-makes-anticipated-xrp-announcement/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 15:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitstamp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=545783</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On Wednesday, August, 2, crypto exchange Bitstamp made a cryptic tweet teasing a new announcement and development for XRP. The exchange kept its promise and made the announcement. However, did it live up to the expectations and hype? The Big Announcement Popular digital asset exchange platform Bitstamp has recently unveiled its highly anticipated XRP announcement. The new feature allows users to stake their XRP holdings and earn long-term 2% APY in rewards. This offering is part of the platform’s creative Bitstamp Earn Lending Program, which offers users a reliable and secure means to lend their XRP holdings and earn rewards in return.  Related Reading: CRV Price Recovers From 6-Month Lows, What’s Driving The Price? Bistamp’s lending service stands out because of its numerous benefits that provide participants with confidence in the whole lending procedure. Bitstamp will also not convert or lend users’ assets without explicit consent and instructions. To partake in XRP staking, users of the platform can easily navigate to the Earn Lending column on Bitstamp. While on the section, they will be offered an option to stake their XRP and earn the mouth-watering 2% APY rewards.  To bolster trust and entrench transparency, Bitstamp has partnered with Tesseract, a renowned firm that is specialized in exclusive lending to trusted borrowers. Tesseract will conduct thorough credit and risk evaluations on all prospective borrowers, thereby augmenting the general safety and reliability of the lending service.  Bitstamp will also render monthly performance reports to enhance transparency. The reports will cover key metrics, such as the risk profile of borrowers, portfolio concentration, and collateral levels.  XRP price shakes off Bistamp announcement &#124; Source: XRPUSD on Tradingview.com Members of XRP React The recent announcement has sparked a wave of expectations and reactions within the XRP community. The announcement of the 2% APY on XRP lending has been met with disappointment as community members expected a more groundbreaking revelation.  Community members had previously speculated on the nature of the announcement, with some XRP proponents speculating that Bitstamp may consider a full integration with the XRP Ledger (XRPL) decentralized exchange (DEX).  Related Reading: Ukraine Government Reveals Crypto Firms Have Cost The Country $81 Million In Lost Taxes Popular XRP community members like Dig Perspective emphasized that while the 2% APY looks good, the community expected something more remarkable. No offense @Bitstamp. 2% is great but we were looking for a bit more,if you have it to share? https://t.co/0iinJWFYi6 — Digital PerspectivesPermaBull🪝 (@DigPerspectives) August 3, 2023 Whichever way it goes, it remains to be seen if Bitstamp will live up to its promises.  XRP’s price is currently trading at $0.66, representing a 0.65% and 7.17% decline on the daily and weekly charts, respectively. Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On Wednesday, August, 2, crypto exchange Bitstamp made a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/bitstamp-major-xrp-announcement-market-hesitates/">cryptic tweet</a> teasing a new announcement and development for XRP. The exchange kept its promise and made the announcement. However, did it live up to the expectations and hype?</p>
<h2>The Big Announcement</h2>
<p>Popular digital asset exchange platform Bitstamp has recently <a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1687103461379481602" rel="nofollow">unveiled</a> its highly anticipated XRP announcement. The new feature allows users to stake their XRP holdings and earn long-term 2% APY in rewards. This offering is part of the platform’s creative Bitstamp Earn Lending Program, which offers users a reliable and secure means to lend their XRP holdings and earn rewards in return. </p>

<p>Bistamp’s lending service stands out because of its numerous benefits that provide participants with confidence in the whole lending procedure. Bitstamp will also not convert or lend users’ assets without explicit consent and instructions. To partake in XRP staking, users of the platform can easily navigate to the Earn Lending column on Bitstamp. While on the section, they will be offered an option to stake their XRP and earn the mouth-watering 2% APY rewards. </p>
<p>To bolster trust and entrench transparency, Bitstamp has partnered with Tesseract, a renowned firm that is specialized in exclusive lending to trusted borrowers. Tesseract will conduct thorough credit and risk evaluations on all prospective borrowers, thereby augmenting the general safety and reliability of the lending service. </p>
<p>Bitstamp will also render monthly performance reports to enhance transparency. The reports will cover key metrics, such as the risk profile of borrowers, portfolio concentration, and collateral levels. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/gIFErGf3/" alt="Ripple (XRP) price chart from Tradingview.com" width="2884" height="1746"/></p>

<h2>Members of XRP React</h2>
<p>The recent announcement has sparked a wave of expectations and reactions within the XRP community. The announcement of the 2% APY on XRP lending has been met with disappointment as community members expected a more groundbreaking revelation. </p>
<p>Community members had previously speculated on the nature of the announcement, with some XRP proponents speculating that Bitstamp may consider a full integration with the XRP Ledger (XRPL) decentralized exchange (DEX). </p>

<p>Popular XRP community members like <a href="https://twitter.com/digperspectives/status/1687101624932790275?s=46&amp;t=ONaoR5h_f0U0CUzEjMETuQ" rel="nofollow">Dig Perspective</a> emphasized that while the 2% APY looks good, the community expected something more remarkable.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">No offense <a href="https://twitter.com/Bitstamp?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@Bitstamp</a>. 2% is great but we were looking for a bit more,if you have it to share? <a href="https://t.co/0iinJWFYi6" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/0iinJWFYi6</a></p>
<p>— Digital PerspectivesPermaBull<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1fa9d.png" alt="🪝" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@DigPerspectives) <a href="https://twitter.com/DigPerspectives/status/1687101624932790275?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">August 3, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Whichever way it goes, it remains to be seen if Bitstamp will live up to its promises. </p>
<p>XRP’s price is currently trading at $0.66, representing a 0.65% and 7.17% decline on the daily and weekly charts, respectively.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/iStock-1436037805.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545783</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
