<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 03:55:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://newsbtc.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Spikes To $19K, Why BTC Could Correct Lower In Short Term</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-spikes-to-19k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 02:58:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515878</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price climbed further higher above $18,500. BTC tested the $19,000 resistance zone and is currently consolidating gains. Bitcoin climbed further higher above the $18,000 and $18,500 resistance levels. The price is trading above $18,200 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There is a connecting bullish trend line forming with support near $18,600 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could correct lower towards the $18,500 and $18,350 support levels. Bitcoin Price Tests $19K Bitcoin price remained well bid above the $18,000 zone. BTC formed another bullish breakout and was able to surge above the $18,500 resistance zone, unlike ethereum. The price cleared the $18,800 resistance zone and even spiked above the $19,000 level. A high is formed near $19,098 and the price is now consolidating gains. There was a minor decline below the $18,900 level. The price declined below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $17,927 swing low to $19,098 high. Bitcoin price is trading above $18,200 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There is also a connecting bullish trend line forming with support near $18,600 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $19,000 level. The next major resistance is near the $19,200 zone, above which the price might start another steady increase. In the stated case, the price may perhaps rise towards the $19,500 level. Any more gains might send btc price towards the $20,000 level. Downside Correction in BTC? If bitcoin price fails to clear the $19,000 resistance, it could start a downside correction. An immediate support on the downside is near the $18,650 level. The next major support is near the $18,500 level and the trend line. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $17,927 swing low to $19,098 high. The main support is now forming near the $17,800 level, below which the price might retest $17,000. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $18,650, followed by $18,500. Major Resistance Levels – $19,000, $19,200 and $20,000.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price climbed further higher above $18,500. BTC tested the $19,000 resistance zone and is currently consolidating gains.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin climbed further higher above the $18,000 and $18,500 resistance levels.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $18,200 and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a connecting bullish trend line forming with support near $18,600 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could correct lower towards the $18,500 and $18,350 support levels.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Tests $19K</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-surges-past-18k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">remained well bid above the $18,000 zone</a>. BTC formed another bullish breakout and was able to surge above the $18,500 resistance zone, unlike <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-climbs-5-pc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ethereum</a>.</p>
<p>The price cleared the $18,800 resistance zone and even spiked above the $19,000 level. A high is formed near $19,098 and the price is now consolidating gains. There was a minor decline below the $18,900 level. The price declined below the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $17,927 swing low to $19,098 high.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is trading above $18,200 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There is also a connecting bullish trend line forming with support near $18,600 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-10.png"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-515879" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-10.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Spikes To $19K" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-10.png 1834w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-10-460x212.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-10-860x396.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-10-768x354.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-10-1536x708.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-10-750x346.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-10-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $19,000 level. The next major resistance is near the $19,200 zone, above which the price might start another steady increase. In the stated case, the price may perhaps rise towards the $19,500 level. Any more gains might send btc price towards the $20,000 level.</p>
<h2>Downside Correction in BTC?</h2>
<p>If bitcoin price fails to clear the $19,000 resistance, it could start a downside correction. An immediate support on the downside is near the $18,650 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $18,500 level and the trend line. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $17,927 swing low to $19,098 high. The main support is now forming near the $17,800 level, below which the price might retest $17,000.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $18,650, followed by $18,500.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $19,000, $19,200 and $20,000.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/Depositphotos_179514440_s-2019-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Rallies Above $1,400 As Sharks Accumulate</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-rallies-above-1400-as-sharks-accumulate/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515872</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum has rallied above $1,400 today as on-chain data shows ETH sharks have been busy accumulating recently. Related Reading: Altcoin Volume Dominance At Highest Since Jan 2021, Trouble For Bitcoin? Ethereum Shark Addresses Have Grown By 3,000 In the Last Two Months As per data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, the current number of shark addresses in the market is the highest since February 2021. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;ETH Supply Distribution,&#8221; which tells us which coin groups have how many wallets. These coin groups are ranges that define the number of coins the addresses currently hold in a particular group. For example, the 1-10 coins cohort includes all wallets holding at least one and at most 10 ETH. The Supply Distribution metric for this group would then track the total number of addresses falling inside this range. In the context of the current topic, the coin group of interest is the 100-10,000 coins cohort (which is made up of two separate groups, 100-1,000 coins, and 1,000-10,000 coins; they have just been merged). Now, here is a chart that shows the Supply Distribution data for this Ethereum coin group: It looks like the value of this metric has observed some uptrend in recent weeks &#124; Source: Santiment on Twitter This coin group&#8217;s lower and upper bounds convert to around $140,000 and $14 million. The Ethereum investors who hold amounts in this range are called the sharks, and although they aren&#8217;t as crucial as the whales, movements from these holders can still have significant implications on the market. As shown in the above graph, the Ethereum sharks were taking profits during September and October last year as their total number of addresses declined to a low. However, over the past few months, accumulation has rapidly taken place in the market as 3,000 new shark addresses have been created on the network. ETH has been rallying in recent days as these sharks have been accumulating, and for now, these investors aren&#8217;t showing any signs of stopping either. The total number of addresses belonging to this cohort is 48,556, the highest level the indicator has seen since February 2021, almost two years ago. If these sharks budge here and take some profits while the prices are high, the rally might lose steam and end. However, if these investors keep this accumulation up instead, it would be a bullish sign for Ethereum, and the rally may continue. Related Reading: Bitcoin Currently More Stable Than Gold, DXY, Nasdaq, Here’s What Could Happen Next ETH Price At the time of writing, Ethereum is trading around $1,400, up 12% in the last week. The value of the crypto seems to have sharply surged in the last few days &#124; Source: ETHUSDT on TradingView Featured image from Gerald Schömbs on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Santiment.net]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum has rallied above $1,400 today as on-chain data shows ETH sharks have been busy accumulating recently.</p>

<h2><b>Ethereum Shark Addresses Have Grown By 3,000 In the Last Two Months</b></h2>
<p>As per data from the on-chain analytics firm<a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1613359474710048768" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> Santiment</a>, the current number of shark addresses in the market is the highest since February 2021. The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;ETH Supply Distribution,&#8221; which tells us which coin groups have how many wallets.</p>
<p>These coin groups are ranges that define the number of coins the addresses currently hold in a particular group. For example, the 1-10 coins cohort includes all wallets holding at least one and at most 10 ETH. The Supply Distribution metric for this group would then track the total number of addresses falling inside this range.</p>
<p>In the context of the current topic, the coin group of interest is the 100-10,000 coins cohort (which is made up of two separate groups, 100-1,000 coins, and 1,000-10,000 coins; they have just been merged). Now, here is a chart that shows the Supply Distribution data for this Ethereum coin group:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-515873 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-860x552.jpeg" alt="Ethereum ETH ETHUSDT" width="860" height="552" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-860x552.jpeg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-460x295.jpeg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-768x493.jpeg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-1536x987.jpeg 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-2048x1316.jpeg 2048w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-750x482.jpeg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-1140x732.jpeg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>
<p>It looks like the value of this metric has observed some uptrend in recent weeks | Source:<a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1613359474710048768/photo/1" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> Santiment on Twitter</a></p>
<p>This coin group&#8217;s lower and upper bounds convert to around $140,000 and $14 million. The Ethereum investors who hold amounts in this range are called the<a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/litecoin-bullish-shark-whale-2-year-high/"> sharks</a>, and although they aren&#8217;t as crucial as the<a href="https://newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-bullish-whale-34-7m-shib-binance/"> whales</a>, movements from these holders can still have significant implications on the market.</p>
<p>As shown in the above graph, the Ethereum sharks were taking profits during September and October last year as their total number of addresses declined to a low. However, over the past few months, accumulation has rapidly taken place in the market as 3,000 new shark addresses have been created on the network.</p>
<p>ETH has been<a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-climbs-5-pc/"> rallying</a> in recent days as these sharks have been accumulating, and for now, these investors aren&#8217;t showing any signs of stopping either. The total number of addresses belonging to this cohort is 48,556, the highest level the indicator has seen since February 2021, almost two years ago.</p>
<p>If these sharks budge here and take some profits while the prices are high, the rally might lose steam and end. However, if these investors keep this accumulation up instead, it would be a bullish sign for Ethereum, and the rally may continue.</p>

<h2><b>ETH Price</b></h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Ethereum is trading around $1,400, up 12% in the last week.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-515874 size-large" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-CHART-1-860x394.png" alt="Ethereum ETH ETHUSDT CHART 1" width="860" height="394" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-CHART-1-860x394.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-CHART-1-460x211.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-CHART-1-768x352.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-CHART-1-1536x704.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-CHART-1-750x344.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-CHART-1-1140x522.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-ETH-ETHUSDT-CHART-1.png 1814w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>
<p>The value of the crypto seems to have sharply surged in the last few days | Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/chart/hstM8J8q/?symbol=BINANCE%3AETHUSDT" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"><strong>ETHUSDT on TradingView</strong></a></p>
<p>Featured image from Gerald Schömbs on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Santiment.net</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/iStock-1329407939-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>“Parabolic” Signal That Triggered Past Bitcoin Bull Runs Reappears</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-parabolic-sar-btcusdt/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tony Spilotro]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 23:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[j. welles wilder]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[parabolic sar]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515865</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price made a 5% move today, poking above $19,000 momentarily. It is currently the largest daily climb of 2023 and since the FTX collapse.  More significantly, the sharp rally tagged a level that triggered a possible trend change according to the weekly Parabolic SAR. In the past, the technical indicator has lived up to its name. What could it mean this time? Bitcoin Makes Biggest Move Of 2023 The start of 2023 has been positive for altcoins. But up until today, Bitcoin has been mild by comparison.  Following today’s CPI data release coming in at 6.5% and Biden’s victory lap on inflation, Bitcoin price soared by $1,000, taking the top cryptocurrency above $19,000 briefly.  Related Reading: Bitcoin Price Prediction: What Elliott Wave Theory Suggests Is Next For BTC More importantly than what happened today, was what occurred on the weekly timeframe. BTCUSDT (Binance) weekly tagged the Parabolic SAR for the first time since May 2022. The LUNA collapse pulled Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies lower, beginning the second, more aggressive phase of the recent downtrend.  The same Parabolic SAR signal was also triggered prior to the 2019 crypto rally, and the 2020 to 2021 bull run (pictured below). Both rallies also blossomed from the same exact trend line previously. The Parabolic SAR has produced profitable results &#124; BTCUSDT on TradingView.com BTCUSDT Weekly Triggers Parabolic SAR Buy Signal  The Parabolic SAR is a technical indicator designed by J. Wells Wilder, Jr. and is used to detect changes in trend direction. The tool consists of a visual overlay of SAR dots that hover above or below price action, determining the direction of the trend.  When the SAR dots are tagged, it suggests that a trend might “stop and reverse” — which is precisely what SAR stands for. Therefore, it’s especially effective in timing entire and exits. Because the SAR dots travel higher or lower alongside the trend, they can be used reliably to set trailing stop losses.  Related Reading: Currency Expert Explains Why Altcoins Experience More Carnage Than Bitcoin And Ethereum On weekly timeframes, BTCUSDT (Binance) touched the Parabolic SAR, essentially telling short traders to get out of the position. If bears had used the PSAR for trailing stop losses, they’ve now been stopped out — purposely — in profit.   While the signal isn’t a guarantee of continued upside, considering that the possible signal of a trend change has appeared alongside the coincidental timing of a long-term trend line touch, the recovery from this level could be more sustainable than many are ready for. Follow @TonySpilotroBTC on Twitter or join the TonyTradesBTC Telegram for exclusive daily market insights and technical analysis education. Please note: Content is educational and should not be considered investment advice. Featured image from iStockPhoto, Charts from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-price-prediction-elliott-wave-theory-btc/">Bitcoin price</a> made a 5% move today, poking above $19,000 momentarily. It is currently the largest daily climb of 2023 and since the FTX collapse. </p>
<p>More significantly, the sharp rally tagged a level that triggered a possible trend change according to the weekly Parabolic SAR. In the past, the technical indicator has lived up to its name. What could it mean this time?</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Makes Biggest Move Of 2023</h2>
<p>The start of 2023 has been <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/the-january-effect-crypto-altcoins-2023/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">positive for altcoins</a>. But up until today, Bitcoin has been mild by comparison. </p>
<p>Following today’s CPI data release coming in at 6.5% and Biden’s victory lap on inflation, Bitcoin price soared by $1,000, taking the top cryptocurrency above $19,000 briefly. </p>

<p>More importantly than what happened today, was what occurred on the weekly timeframe. BTCUSDT (Binance) weekly tagged the Parabolic SAR for the first time since May 2022. The LUNA collapse pulled Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies lower, beginning the second, more aggressive phase of the recent downtrend. </p>
<p>The same Parabolic SAR signal was also triggered prior to the 2019 crypto rally, and the 2020 to 2021 bull run (pictured below). Both rallies also blossomed from the same exact trend line previously.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-515866 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/2023-01-12-18.14.30-860x600.jpg" alt="BTCUST Bitcoin price" width="860" height="600" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/2023-01-12-18.14.30-860x600.jpg 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/2023-01-12-18.14.30-460x321.jpg 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/2023-01-12-18.14.30-768x536.jpg 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/2023-01-12-18.14.30-1536x1073.jpg 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/2023-01-12-18.14.30-750x524.jpg 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/2023-01-12-18.14.30-1140x796.jpg 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/2023-01-12-18.14.30.jpg 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" /></p>

<h2>BTCUSDT Weekly Triggers Parabolic SAR Buy Signal </h2>
<p>The <a href="https://newsbtc.com/topic/parabolic-sar/">Parabolic SAR</a> is a technical indicator designed by J. Wells Wilder, Jr. and is used to detect changes in trend direction. The tool consists of a visual overlay of SAR dots that hover above or below price action, determining the direction of the trend. </p>
<p>When the SAR dots are tagged, it suggests that a trend might “stop and reverse” — which is precisely what SAR stands for. Therefore, it’s especially effective in timing entire and exits. Because the SAR dots travel higher or lower alongside the trend, they can be used reliably to set trailing stop losses. </p>

<p>On weekly timeframes, BTCUSDT (Binance) touched the Parabolic SAR, essentially telling short traders to get out of the position. If bears had used the PSAR for trailing stop losses, they’ve now been stopped out — purposely — in profit.  </p>
<p>While the signal isn’t a guarantee of continued upside, considering that the possible signal of a trend change has appeared alongside the coincidental timing of a long-term trend line touch, the recovery from this level could be more sustainable than many are ready for.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/iStock-988233854-460x276.jpg" width="460" height="276" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polkadot Breaches $5 But These Levels Remain Crucial For DOT</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/polkadot-breaches-5-levels-remain-crucial-for-dot/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 21:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOTUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polkadot]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515859</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Polkadot has finally managed to break past the rigid price resistance mark of $5. Over the last 24 hours, DOT increased by more than 6%. In the past week, the coin has secured double-digit gains. Related Reading: Ethereum Price Climbs 5% To Take Out Hurdles, Is Bottom Really In? Bitcoin moved into its daily chart&#8217;s $18,000 price zone, pushing altcoins on their respective charts. Although DOT rallied in the last 24 hours, the altcoin is still not out of the woods. The altcoin must remain above two price levels. The technical outlook still sided with the bulls, but there was a fall in the accumulation on the daily chart, indicating that there has been a fall in demand. The demand, however, secured by DOT reached a multi-month high. Usually, after being overvalued, the coin starts to retrace on its chart. Indicators showed that if buyers do not remain consistent, DOT will depreciate on its chart over the subsequent few trading sessions. The altcoin market capitalization fell slightly in the last 24 hours, which meant demand for the altcoin dipped. At the moment, DOT was trading 90% below its all-time high of 2021. Polkadot Price Analysis: One-Day Chart DOT was trading at $5.09 at the time of writing. The coin was trading within an ascending parallel channel (blue). The ascending parallel channel marked a bullish force in the market. At the time of writing, Polkadot broke above the ascending parallel channel, indicating that DOT might consolidate over the subsequent trading sessions before it starts to retrace. Immediate resistance for the coin stood at $5.30; if it managed to breach that level, it could rally to $5.40. On the other hand, if Polkadot loses its momentum, it will fall to $4.80. The altcoin has to remain above the $4.80 mark, or the bears will take over completely. Technical Analysis The altcoin was still in the bullish zone despite a slight fall in demand. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) was above the 60 mark with a minor downtick; this indicated that although demand fell, the price was under bullish control. Similarly, the asset price was seen above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA), which indicated that the bulls were driving the price momentum in the market. As RSI secured a multi-month high, the altcoin traveled above the 50-SMA (yellow) line. With increased demand, technical indicators pointed out traders could have a buying opportunity. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence suggests price momentum and reversals. Related Reading: Avalanche Impresses With 32% Rally – Will AVAX Sustain This Ascent? The indicator formed green signal bars tied to buy signals. The Bollinger bands also grew apart in anticipation of a substantial price movement over the next trading session. Featured Image From Unsplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Polkadot has finally managed to break past the rigid price resistance mark of $5. Over the last 24 hours, DOT increased by more than 6%. In the past week, the coin has secured double-digit gains.</p>

<p>Bitcoin moved into its daily chart&#8217;s $18,000 price zone, pushing altcoins on their respective charts. Although DOT rallied in the last 24 hours, the altcoin is still not out of the woods. The altcoin must remain above two price levels.</p>
<p>The technical outlook still sided with the bulls, but there was a fall in the accumulation on the daily chart, indicating that there has been a fall in demand. The demand, however, secured by DOT reached a multi-month high. Usually, after being overvalued, the coin starts to retrace on its chart.</p>
<p>Indicators showed that if buyers do not remain consistent, DOT will depreciate on its chart over the subsequent few trading sessions. The altcoin market capitalization fell slightly in the last 24 hours, which meant demand for the altcoin dipped. At the moment, DOT was trading 90% below its all-time high of 2021.</p>
<h2>Polkadot Price Analysis: One-Day Chart</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-213153 size-full" src="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOTUSD_2023-01-12_21-06-03.png" alt="Polkadot" width="1816" height="830" />
<p>DOT was trading at $5.09 at the time of writing. The coin was trading within an ascending parallel channel (blue). The ascending parallel channel marked a bullish force in the market.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, Polkadot broke above the ascending parallel channel, indicating that DOT might consolidate over the subsequent trading sessions before it starts to retrace.</p>
<p>Immediate resistance for the coin stood at $5.30; if it managed to breach that level, it could rally to $5.40. On the other hand, if Polkadot loses its momentum, it will fall to $4.80. The altcoin has to remain above the $4.80 mark, or the bears will take over completely.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-213154 size-full" src="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOTUSD_2023-01-12_21-07-12.png" alt="Polkadot" width="1816" height="743" />
<p>The altcoin was still in the bullish zone despite a slight fall in demand. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) was above the 60 mark with a minor downtick; this indicated that although demand fell, the price was under bullish control.</p>
<p>Similarly, the asset price was seen above the 20-Simple Moving Average (SMA), which indicated that the bulls were driving the price momentum in the market. As RSI secured a multi-month high, the altcoin traveled above the 50-SMA (yellow) line.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-213155 size-full" src="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DOTUSD_2023-01-12_21-07-43.png" alt="Polkadot" width="1816" height="743" />
<p>With increased demand, technical indicators pointed out traders could have a buying opportunity. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence suggests price momentum and reversals.</p>

<p>The indicator formed green signal bars tied to buy signals. The Bollinger bands also grew apart in anticipation of a substantial price movement over the next trading session.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ee705c26cee74f3b962238e36ef563be-1-460x259.png" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Price Prints Bullish Pattern, Why Close Above $0.08 Is Critical</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/dogecoin-price-close-0-08-critical/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 05:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technical analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE/USDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515847</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dogecoin formed a base near $0.066 and started a fresh increase against the US Dollar. DOGE could rise further if there is a close above the $0.080 resistance. DOGE gained pace and traded above the $0.075 resistance against the US dollar. The price is trading above the $0.0750 zone and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours). There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.0740 on the 4-hours chart of the DOGE/USD pair (data source from Kraken). The pair could rise further if there is a clear close above the $0.080 resistance. Dogecoin Price Signals Bullish After a strong decline, dogecoin price found support near the $0.066 zone. DOGE remained well bid and started a steady increase above the $0.068 resistance. There was a clear move above the $0.070 resistance zone to set the pace for a decent increase. The price cleared the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the key decline from the $0.1402 swing high to $0.0658 low. The price is now trading above the $0.0750 zone and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours). There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.0740 on the 4-hours chart of the DOGE/USD pair. In the past few sessions, doge saw bullish moves above $0.075, similar to bitcoin and ethereum. On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $0.080 level. The first major resistance is near the $0.0820 level. A clear move above the $0.082 resistance might send the price towards the $0.088 resistance. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the key decline from the $0.1402 swing high to $0.0658 low. Source: DOGEUSD on TradingView.com Any more gains might send the price towards the $0.090 level. A clear move above the $0.090 resistance could open the gates for a rally towards the $0.100 level. Dips Limited in DOGE? If DOGE price fails to gain pace above the $0.082 level, it could started a downside correction. An initial support on the downside is near the $0.0765 level. The next major support is near the $0.074 level and the trend line. If there is a downside break below the $0.074 support, the price could decline further. In the stated case, the price might decline towards the $0.070 level. Technical Indicators 4-Hours MACD – The MACD for DOGE/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone. 4-Hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for DOGE/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $0.0765, $0.0740 and $0.0700. Major Resistance Levels – $0.080, $0.0850 and $0.088.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Dogecoin formed a base near $0.066 and started a fresh increase against the US Dollar. DOGE could rise further if there is a close above the $0.080 resistance.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>DOGE gained pace and traded above the $0.075 resistance against the US dollar.</li>
<li>The price is trading above the $0.0750 zone and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours).</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.0740 on the 4-hours chart of the DOGE/USD pair (data source from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could rise further if there is a clear close above the $0.080 resistance.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Dogecoin Price Signals Bullish</h2>
<p>After a strong decline, dogecoin price found support near the $0.066 zone. DOGE remained well bid and started a steady increase above the $0.068 resistance.</p>
<p>There was a clear move above the $0.070 resistance zone to set the pace for a decent increase. The price cleared the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the key decline from the $0.1402 swing high to $0.0658 low. The price is now trading above the $0.0750 zone and the 100 simple moving average (4-hours).</p>
<p>There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $0.0740 on the 4-hours chart of the DOGE/USD pair. In the past few sessions, doge saw bullish moves above $0.075, similar to <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-surges-past-18k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bitcoin</a> and <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-climbs-5-pc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ethereum</a>.</p>
<p>On the upside, the price is facing resistance near the $0.080 level. The first major resistance is near the $0.0820 level. A clear move above the $0.082 resistance might send the price towards the $0.088 resistance. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the key decline from the $0.1402 swing high to $0.0658 low.</p>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Doegcoin-DOGE.png"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-515848" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Doegcoin-DOGE.png" alt="Dogecoin Price Signals Bullish" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Doegcoin-DOGE.png 1834w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Doegcoin-DOGE-460x212.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Doegcoin-DOGE-860x396.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Doegcoin-DOGE-768x354.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Doegcoin-DOGE-1536x708.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Doegcoin-DOGE-750x346.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Doegcoin-DOGE-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/DOGEUSD/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">DOGEUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>Any more gains might send the price towards the $0.090 level. A clear move above the $0.090 resistance could open the gates for a rally towards the $0.100 level.</p>
<h2>Dips Limited in DOGE?</h2>
<p>If DOGE price fails to gain pace above the $0.082 level, it could started a downside correction. An initial support on the downside is near the $0.0765 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $0.074 level and the trend line. If there is a downside break below the $0.074 support, the price could decline further. In the stated case, the price might decline towards the $0.070 level.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>4-Hours MACD – The MACD for DOGE/USD is now gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>4-Hours RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for DOGE/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $0.0765, $0.0740 and $0.0700.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $0.080, $0.0850 and $0.088.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/shutterstock_1100038610-460x272.jpg" width="460" height="272" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Climbs 5% To Take Out Hurdles, Is Bottom Really In?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-climbs-5-pc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 04:48:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515844</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum climbed higher above the $1,350 resistance zone against the US Dollar. ETH tested the $1,420 zone and is currently consolidating gains. Ethereum started a steady increase above the $1,320 and $1,350 resistance levels. The price is now trading above $1,350 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There is a connecting bullish trend line forming with support near $1,345 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could start another increase if it stays above the $1,320 support zone. Ethereum Price Breaks $1,400 Ethereum price remained well bid above the $1,300 resistance. ETH settled above the $1,320 resistance zone and started another increase, similar to bitcoin above $17,500. There was a strong upward move above the $1,350 resistance zone. The price gained over 5% and even broke the $1,400 resistance zone. A high is formed near $1,419 and the price is now consolidating gains. Ether price is now trading above $1,350 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There is also a connecting bullish trend line forming with support near $1,345 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. The pair seems to be trading just above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent rally from the $1,322 swing low to $1,419 high. An immediate resistance is near the $1,420 level. The next major resistance is near the $1,450 level. An upside break above the $1,450 resistance zone could set the pace for a larger increase. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com In the stated case, the price may perhaps climb higher towards the $1,500 resistance. Any more gains might send the price towards $1,550, above which the price could rise towards the $1,600 resistance zone. Losses Limited in ETH? If ethereum fails to clear the $1,420 resistance, it could start a downside correction. An initial support on the downside is near the $1,395 level. The next major support is near the $1,370 level. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent rally from the $1,322 swing low to $1,419 high. If there is a move below $1,350, the price might test the trend line and $1,350. Any more losses might call for a test of the $1,320 zone. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now losing momentum in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is now below the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,370 Major Resistance Level – $1,420]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum climbed higher above the $1,350 resistance zone against the US Dollar. ETH tested the $1,420 zone and is currently consolidating gains.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum started a steady increase above the $1,320 and $1,350 resistance levels.</li>
<li>The price is now trading above $1,350 and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a connecting bullish trend line forming with support near $1,345 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start another increase if it stays above the $1,320 support zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Breaks $1,400</h2>
<p>Ethereum price remained well bid above the $1,300 resistance. ETH settled above the $1,320 resistance zone and started another increase, similar to <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-surges-past-18k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bitcoin</a> above $17,500.</p>
<p>There was a strong upward move above the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-consolidate-gains-1350/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$1,350 resistance zone</a>. The price gained over 5% and even broke the $1,400 resistance zone. A high is formed near $1,419 and the price is now consolidating gains. Ether price is now trading above $1,350 and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</p>
<p>There is also a connecting bullish trend line forming with support near $1,345 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. The pair seems to be trading just above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent rally from the $1,322 swing low to $1,419 high.</p>
<p>An immediate resistance is near the $1,420 level. The next major resistance is near the $1,450 level. An upside break above the $1,450 resistance zone could set the pace for a larger increase.</p>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-7.png"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-515845" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-7.png" alt="Ethereum Price Climbs 5%" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-7.png 1834w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-7-460x212.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-7-860x396.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-7-768x354.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-7-1536x708.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-7-750x346.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-7-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>In the stated case, the price may perhaps climb higher towards the $1,500 resistance. Any more gains might send the price towards $1,550, above which the price could rise towards the $1,600 resistance zone.</p>
<h2>Losses Limited in ETH?</h2>
<p>If ethereum fails to clear the $1,420 resistance, it could start a downside correction. An initial support on the downside is near the $1,395 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $1,370 level. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent rally from the $1,322 swing low to $1,419 high. If there is a move below $1,350, the price might test the trend line and $1,350. Any more losses might call for a test of the $1,320 zone.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is now losing momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is now below the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,370</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,420</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/shutterstock_1249579717-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Avalanche Impresses With 32% Rally &#8211; Will AVAX Sustain This Ascent?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/news/avalanche-makes-32-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 04:22:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CPI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515833</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The crypto rally that greeted the new year has definitely brought gains to the world of altcoins. According to CoinMarketCap data, most huge gains were made by altcoins in the past 30 days. AVAX, native token of the Avalanche blockchain, is one of them with gains of up to 32% in the seven days.  The rally came as major cryptos like Bitcoin and Ethereum all registered gains and increased investor sentiment. Although the fear, uncertainty, and doubt of the last year’s bear market is still present, the increasing chance of a recession still gives investors some worry. As of writing, AVAX is trading at $15.96, up 28% in the last 24 hours, data from Coingecko show. What Supported The Avalanche Rally?  The Avalanche ecosystem has been bullish. Recently, Shopify partnered with Avalanche to allow Shopify merchants to sell their NFTs. According to public information, users don’t need to handle any cryptocurrencies to buy NFTs.  Venly, one of the numerous blockchain partners of Shopify, created a no-code tool for sellers to create NFTs. In a recent interview, Venly co-founder Tom Dierckxens said that this evolution in NFT technology is an evolution which can be adopted in the mass market. This is only the most previous on-chain development for the ecosystem. On a previous tweet by Axaholic, a Twitter account dedicated to Avalanche updates, the ecosystem partnered up with Re Protocol which tokenizes the reinsurance industry, empowering business through blockchain solutions.  On-chain developments also led to Avalanche experiencing a strong uptick in development activity and price as seen on data provided by Santiment.  Also, the world&#8217;s largest cloud provider, Amazon Web Services (AWS), has joined forces with blockchain technology firm Ava Labs to speed up and broaden the use of blockchain across different types of industries. Related Reading: ApeCoin Climbs 21% In Last 7 Days As Sentiment Remains Bullish With this collaboration, Avalanche, Ava Labs&#8217; layer-1 blockchain, will be more accessible to individuals and businesses, and node administrators will have more control over the network&#8217;s performance and functionality. Image: Phemex Will AVAX Maintain Its Momentum? The current momentum seems to be profit-taking behavior before another bullish leg up. With the markets anticipating lower Consumer Price Index levels, AVAX might have a needed boost in the coming release on Thursday.   However, with its high correlation with Bitcoin, it could follow the top crypto in any direction. Bitcoin, as of writing, has broken past the $18,000 mark and trading at $18,229, up 8.2% in the last seven days, based on data by Coingecko. Chart: Benzinga Related Reading: Polkadot Records New Achievements In Dev’t Activity, Pushes DOT Price Up Meanwhile, the chart above contrasts the token&#8217;s price adjustment and volatility over the past 24 hours (left) with that during the last seven days (right). The Bollinger Bands in the middle of the chart are a measure of the volatility of the price swings over a given time period (daily or weekly) and are shown in gray. Volatility goes up when the space between the bands (or the amount of gray area) extends. -Featured Image: Cointribune]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto rally that greeted the new year has definitely brought gains to the world of altcoins. According to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/gainers-losers/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinMarketCap data</a>, most huge gains were made by altcoins in the past 30 days. AVAX, native token of the Avalanche blockchain, is one of them with <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/avalanche" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">gains</a> of up to 32% in the seven days. </p>
<p>The rally came as major cryptos like Bitcoin and Ethereum all registered gains and increased investor sentiment. Although the fear, uncertainty, and doubt of the last year’s bear market is still present, the <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/news/earnings/23/01/30366957/market-volatility-decreases-ahead-of-cpi-data" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">increasing chance</a> of a recession still gives investors some worry.</p>
<p>As of writing, AVAX is trading at $15.96, up 28% in the last 24 hours, data from Coingecko show.</p>
<h2><strong>What Supported The Avalanche Rally? </strong></h2>
<p>The Avalanche ecosystem has been bullish. Recently, Shopify <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/finance/news/shopify-merchants-now-sell-avalanche-155902118.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">partnered</a> with Avalanche to allow Shopify merchants to sell their NFTs. According to public information, users don’t need to handle any cryptocurrencies to buy NFTs. </p>
<p>Venly, one of the <a href="https://help.shopify.com/en/manual/products/digital-service-product/nfts/blockchain-app-partners" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">numerous</a> blockchain partners of Shopify, created a no-code tool for sellers to create NFTs. In a recent interview, Venly co-founder Tom Dierckxens said that this evolution in NFT technology is an evolution which can be adopted in the mass market. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-515841 size-full aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-33.png" alt="" width="601" height="571" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-33.png 601w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-33-460x437.png 460w" sizes="(max-width: 601px) 100vw, 601px" /></p>
<p>This is only the most previous on-chain development for the ecosystem. On a previous <a href="https://twitter.com/avaxholic/status/1610124275327078401?s=20&amp;t=6BL_oNwC5cRjy9ywIYMijA" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">tweet</a> by <a href="https://twitter.com/avaxholic" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Axaholic</a>, a Twitter account dedicated to Avalanche updates, the ecosystem partnered up with Re Protocol which tokenizes the reinsurance industry, empowering business through blockchain solutions. </p>
<p>On-chain developments also led to Avalanche experiencing a strong uptick in development activity and price as seen on data provided by <a href="https://app.santiment.net/s/xHE24U_N" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Santiment</a>. </p>
<p>Also, the world&#8217;s largest cloud provider, Amazon Web Services (AWS), has joined forces with blockchain technology firm Ava Labs to speed up and broaden the use of blockchain across different types of industries.</p>

<p>With this collaboration, Avalanche, Ava Labs&#8217; layer-1 blockchain, will be more accessible to individuals and businesses, and node administrators will have more control over the network&#8217;s performance and functionality.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-515839 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-32-460x258.png" alt="AVAX" width="460" height="258" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-32-460x258.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-32.png 643w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<h2><strong>Will AVAX Maintain Its Momentum?</strong></h2>
<p>The current momentum seems to be profit-taking behavior before another bullish leg up. With the markets anticipating lower Consumer Price Index levels, AVAX might have a needed boost in the coming release on Thursday.  </p>
<p>However, with its high correlation with Bitcoin, it could follow the top crypto in any direction. Bitcoin, as of writing, has broken past the $18,000 mark and trading at $18,229, up 8.2% in the last seven days, based on data by Coingecko.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter wp-image-515835 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-31.png" alt="AVAX" width="577" height="309" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-31.png 577w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/a-31-460x246.png 460w" sizes="(max-width: 577px) 100vw, 577px" /></p>


<p>Meanwhile, the chart above contrasts the token&#8217;s price adjustment and volatility over the past 24 hours (left) with that during the last seven days (right).</p>
<p>The Bollinger Bands in the middle of the chart are a measure of the volatility of the price swings over a given time period (daily or weekly) and are shown in gray.</p>
<p>Volatility goes up when the space between the bands (or the amount of gray area) extends.</p>
<p><em>-Featured Image: Cointribune</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Avalanche-1-460x307.png" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Surges Past $18K and Now The Bulls Could Aim $19K</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-surges-past-18k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 03:18:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515830</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price extended its increase and surged above $18,000. BTC is gaining pace and might rise towards the $19,000 resistance zone. Bitcoin extended its rise above the $17,500 and $18,000 resistance levels. The price is trading above $18,000 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $17,400 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could continue to move up towards the $19,000 resistance zone. Bitcoin Price Rallies 5% Bitcoin price gained pace after there was a close above the $17,000 pivot zone. BTC accelerated higher above the $17,250 resistance zone to move into a positive zone, similar to ethereum. The price climbed above the $17,500 resistance zone to start a strong increase. The bulls even pumped the price above the $18,000 resistance zone. A high was formed near $18,367 and the price is now consolidating gains. Bitcoin price is trading above $18,000 and the 100 hourly simple moving average. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $17,400 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. It is also well above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent surge from the $17,308 swing low to $18,367 high. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $18,350 level. The next major resistance is near the $18,500 zone, above which the price might continue to move up. In the stated case, the price may perhaps rise towards the $19,200 level. Any more gains might send btc price towards the $20,000 level. Dips Attractive in BTC? If bitcoin price fails to clear the $18,350 resistance, it could start a downside correction. An immediate support on the downside is near the $18,120 level. The next major support is near the $17,800 level. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent surge from the $17,308 swing low to $18,367 high. The main support is now forming near the $17,400 level and the trend line, below which the price might retest $17,000. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $18,120, followed by $17,800. Major Resistance Levels – $18,350, $18,500 and $19,200.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price extended its increase and surged above $18,000. BTC is gaining pace and might rise towards the $19,000 resistance zone.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin extended its rise above the $17,500 and $18,000 resistance levels.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $18,000 and the 100 hourly simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support near $17,400 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move up towards the $19,000 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Rallies 5%</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price gained pace after there was a close above the $17,000 pivot zone. BTC accelerated higher above the $17,250 resistance zone to move into a positive zone, similar to <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-consolidate-gains-1350/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ethereum</a>.</p>
<p>The price climbed above the $17,500 resistance zone to start a strong increase. The bulls even pumped the price above the $18,000 resistance zone. A high was formed near $18,367 and the price is now consolidating gains.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is trading above $18,000 and the <a href="https://newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-resumes-increase-17k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">100 hourly simple moving average</a>. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support near $17,400 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. It is also well above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent surge from the $17,308 swing low to $18,367 high.</p>
<p><a href="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-9.png"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-515831" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-9.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Rallies 5%" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-9.png 1834w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-9-460x212.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-9-860x396.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-9-768x354.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-9-1536x708.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-9-750x346.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-9-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>On the upside, an immediate resistance is near the $18,350 level. The next major resistance is near the $18,500 zone, above which the price might continue to move up. In the stated case, the price may perhaps rise towards the $19,200 level. Any more gains might send btc price towards the $20,000 level.</p>
<h2>Dips Attractive in BTC?</h2>
<p>If bitcoin price fails to clear the $18,350 resistance, it could start a downside correction. An immediate support on the downside is near the $18,120 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $17,800 level. It is near the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent surge from the $17,308 swing low to $18,367 high. The main support is now forming near the $17,400 level and the trend line, below which the price might retest $17,000.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $18,120, followed by $17,800.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $18,350, $18,500 and $19,200.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/shutterstock_1069524017-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Tops List Of Gainers As Whale Interest Spikes</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-tops-list-of-gainers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Best Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 23:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP performance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515759</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[XRP has been on the front lines of crypto news for the past couple of weeks as Ripple’s lawsuit with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) heats up. The increased attention has translated to more market movement, and whales are looking to take advantage of this. Whales Move Into XRP XRP’s trading volume saw a spike on Tuesday following the upward rally in the crypto market. This saw an increase in the price of the digital asset but perhaps most important for the day was the fact that Binance Smart Chain whales were actually more interested in the coin. Related Reading: Bullish Signal: Bitcoin Whales Go On 20,000 BTC Buying Spree Whale tracking website WhaleStats reported that XRP had become the most traded token among the top 100 BSC whales for the day. It dethroned AAVE which had previously dominated the attention of these large whales to achieve this feat. 📰 JUST IN: $XRP @Ripple flipped $AAVE for MOST TRADED token among top 100 #BSC whales Check the top 100 whales here: https://t.co/0SYnjw0xQs (and hodl $BBW to see data for the top 4000!)#XRP #AAVE #whalestats #babywhale #BBW pic.twitter.com/MhK4A1ATd3 &#8212; WhaleStats &#8211; the top 1000 BSC richlist (@WhaleStatsBSC) January 10, 2023 Now, the increased interest from these whales has not died down yet because while XRP is not currently the most traded token, it is still a top 10 token for them. It features in the fourth spot of most purchased tokens for the largest BSC whales. Additionally, the XRP smart contract is one of the top 10 most used smart contracts among the top 100 BSC whales. Price sitting at $0.37 &#124; Source: XRPUSD on TradingView.com Jumping In Front Of Crypto Market Gains There are still residual market gains from the Monday price surge in the crypto market and XRP is one of the tokens soaking up the gains. It is currently one of the top gainers over the last 24 hours, placing third on the Coinmarketcap list of gainers with a 4.34% increase in the last day. XRP in the top five gainers &#124; Source: Coinmarketcap This increase in price has now pushed the price of XRP above its 20-day moving average. The breakpoints to a short-term bull trend for the digital asset, at least for the week. The most important now is for the digital asset to break the resistance at $0.037, as this will propel it above its 50-day moving average of $0.379. Once this is achieved, then a rally above $0.4 will be locked in for the cryptocurrency. Related Reading: Why Are Liquid Staking Cryptocurrencies Seeing Double-Digit Gains? An event that could likely prove volatile for the XRP price is another hearing set for January 19 in the Ripple v. SEC case. Both parties involved are required to file any objections to the non-parties&#8217; motions by January 18.  As for the final verdict for the case, Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse and lawyer Stuart Alderoty both expect a decision from Judge Analisa Torres sometime in the second quarter of 2023. Follow Best Owie on Twitter for market insights, updates, and the occasional funny tweet… Featured image from The Coin Republic, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">XRP has been on the front lines of crypto news for the past couple of weeks as Ripple’s lawsuit with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) heats up. The increased attention has translated to more market movement, and whales are looking to take advantage of this.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Whales Move Into XRP</h2>
<p class="p2">XRP’s trading volume saw a spike on Tuesday following the upward rally in the crypto market. This saw an increase in the price of the digital asset but perhaps most important for the day was the fact that Binance Smart Chain whales were actually more interested in the coin.</p>

<p class="p2">Whale tracking website WhaleStats reported that XRP had become the most traded token among the top 100 BSC whales for the day. It dethroned AAVE which had previously dominated the attention of these large whales to achieve this feat.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4f0.png" alt="📰" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> JUST IN: <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24XRP&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$XRP</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/Ripple?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@Ripple</a> flipped <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24AAVE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$AAVE</a> for MOST TRADED token among top 100 <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BSC?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#BSC</a> whales</p>
<p>Check the top 100 whales here: <a href="https://t.co/0SYnjw0xQs" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">https://t.co/0SYnjw0xQs</a></p>
<p>(and hodl <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BBW&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$BBW</a> to see data for the top 4000!)<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/XRP?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#XRP</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/AAVE?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#AAVE</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/whalestats?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#whalestats</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/babywhale?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#babywhale</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BBW?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#BBW</a> <a href="https://t.co/MhK4A1ATd3" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/MhK4A1ATd3</a></p>
<p>&mdash; WhaleStats &#8211; the top 1000 BSC richlist (@WhaleStatsBSC) <a href="https://twitter.com/WhaleStatsBSC/status/1612758748648325121?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p class="p2">Now, the increased interest from these whales has not died down yet because while XRP is not currently the most traded token, it is still a top 10 token for them. It features in the fourth spot of most purchased tokens for the largest BSC whales.</p>
<p class="p2">Additionally, the XRP smart contract is one of the top 10 most used smart contracts among the top 100 BSC whales.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/5q3TTsWM/" alt="XRP price chart from TradingView.com" width="3284" height="1646" /></p>

<h2 class="p2">Jumping In Front Of Crypto Market Gains</h2>
<p class="p2">There are still residual market gains from the Monday price surge in the crypto market and XRP is one of the tokens soaking up the gains. It is currently one of the top gainers over the last 24 hours, placing third on the Coinmarketcap list of gainers with a 4.34% increase in the last day.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-515760 aligncenter" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-gainers-460x247.png" alt="XRP gainers" width="460" height="247" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-gainers-460x247.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-gainers-860x461.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-gainers-768x412.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-gainers-750x402.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-gainers-1140x611.png 1140w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-gainers.png 1466w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" /></p>

<p class="p2">This increase in price has now pushed the price of XRP above its 20-day moving average. The breakpoints to a short-term bull trend for the digital asset, at least for the week. The most important now is for the digital asset to break the resistance at $0.037, as this will propel it above its 50-day moving average of $0.379. Once this is achieved, then a rally above $0.4 will be locked in for the cryptocurrency.</p>

<p class="p2">An event that could likely prove volatile for the XRP price is another hearing set for January 19 in the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-execs-predict-utility-key-driver-2023/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Ripple v. SEC case</a>. Both parties involved are required to file any objections to the non-parties&#8217; motions by January 18. </p>
<p class="p2">As for the final verdict for the case, Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse and lawyer Stuart Alderoty both expect a decision from Judge Analisa Torres sometime in the second quarter of 2023.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRP-1-460x259.jpeg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Avalanche Partners With Amazon, What’s Next For The Price?</title>
		<link>https://newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/avalanche-partners-amazon-next-for-the-price/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[anushsamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 20:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Breaking News Ticker]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAXUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAXUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[aws]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://newsbtc.com/?p=515815</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Avalanche and its dApp ecosystem shall now be supported by Amazon Web Services (AWS), which also comprises one-click node deployment through the AWS marketplace. With this partnership with AWS, Ava Labs can help customers deploy custom offerings linked to over 100,000 partners spread across 150 countries. Related Reading: Bitcoin Currently More Stable Than Gold, DXY, Nasdaq, Here’s What Could Happen Next Technically, the Avalanche node operators can operate in AWS GovCloud for the FedRAMP compliance use case, which is an essential pre-requisite for many enterprises and governments. This partnership will help scale blockchain adoption among many enterprises, government organizations, and other institutions. Howard Wright, the VP and Global Head of startups at AWS, stated: Looking forward, web3 and blockchain are inevitable. No one can call the time or date or quarter that it’s going to happen and it’ll be mainstream, but we’ve seen the cycles of growth before. The velocity of this one seems like it’s accelerating and we’re just excited to be a part of this. Through the partnership, individuals will find it much easier to launch and manage nodes on Avalanche; additionally, it will strengthen and make the network more flexible for developers to work on. This new development has positively affected the altcoin&#8217;s price, but it is yet to be seen if the coin can sustain this price sentiment. Avalanche Technical Analysis The news of AWS being incorporated into the Avalanche ecosystem has instantly spiked investor interest. The daily chart of AVAX displays a 6.6% gain, which can be termed a rally. This has made the coin break past the $13.60 resistance level, and now AVAX is valued at $14.40. It is yet to be seen if the coin manages to breach the $15 mark, acting as a resistance mark for the coin. A fall from the current price will bring the altcoin down to $13.70. The Relative Strength Index was overbought, which means the asset was overvalued. The overvalued condition can be attributed to the newest development. Usually, once the asset is overbought, the price corrects itself. Due to bullish sentiment, AVAX shot past the 20-Simple Moving Average line (SMA), indicating that buyers have been driving the price momentum in the market. Not just the 20-SMA, the altcoin was parked above the 50-SMA due to excessive demand. The Moving Average Convergence Divergence suggests price momentum and a trend reversal. The indicator formed a few green histograms, which are buy signals for the coin. The most recent histogram increased in size, anticipating the rise in the price of the asset. Investors could quickly take this as a signal for entry as the price would increase over the next few trading sessions before it started to retrace. Related Reading: Polkadot Records New Achievements In Dev’t Activity, Pushes DOT Price Up The Directional Movement Index reads the price direction, and it was bullish. The +DI line (blue) was above the -DI line (orange). The Average Directional Index (red) was near 20 with a slight uptick, confirming that although the price witnessed a northbound movement, the price direction lacks substantial strength. Featured Image From Unsplash, Charts From TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Avalanche and its dApp ecosystem shall now be supported by <a href="https://twitter.com/TechCrunch/status/1613234600884461583?t=7aI3bbo9HfDYJU8yUXiePQ&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Amazon Web Services</a> (AWS), which also comprises one-click node deployment through the AWS marketplace.</p>
<p>With this partnership with AWS, Ava Labs can help customers deploy custom offerings linked to over 100,000 partners spread across 150 countries.</p>

<p>Technically, the Avalanche node operators can operate in AWS GovCloud for the FedRAMP compliance use case, which is an essential pre-requisite for many enterprises and governments.</p>
<p>This partnership will help scale blockchain adoption among many enterprises, government organizations, and other institutions.</p>
Howard Wright, the VP and Global Head of startups at AWS, stated:

<blockquote><p>Looking forward, web3 and blockchain are inevitable. No one can call the time or date or quarter that it’s going to happen and it’ll be mainstream, but we’ve seen the cycles of growth before. The velocity of this one seems like it’s accelerating and we’re just excited to be a part of this.</p></blockquote>
<p>Through the partnership, individuals will find it much easier to launch and manage nodes on Avalanche; additionally, it will strengthen and make the network more flexible for developers to work on. This new development has positively affected the altcoin&#8217;s price, but it is yet to be seen if the coin can sustain this price sentiment.</p>

<h2>Avalanche Technical Analysis</h2>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-515816 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/AVAXUSD_2023-01-12_01-06-25.png" alt="Avalanche" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/AVAXUSD_2023-01-12_01-06-25.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/AVAXUSD_2023-01-12_01-06-25-460x188.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/AVAXUSD_2023-01-12_01-06-25-860x352.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/AVAXUSD_2023-01-12_01-06-25-768x314.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/AVAXUSD_2023-01-12_01-06-25-1536x628.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/AVAXUSD_2023-01-12_01-06-25-750x307.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/AVAXUSD_2023-01-12_01-06-25-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>The news of AWS being incorporated into the Avalanche ecosystem has instantly spiked investor interest. The daily chart of AVAX displays a 6.6% gain, which can be termed a rally.</p>
<p>This has made the coin break past the $13.60 resistance level, and now AVAX is valued at $14.40. It is yet to be seen if the coin manages to breach the $15 mark, acting as a resistance mark for the coin. A fall from the current price will bring the altcoin down to $13.70.</p>
<p>The Relative Strength Index was overbought, which means the asset was overvalued. The overvalued condition can be attributed to the newest development. Usually, once the asset is overbought, the price corrects itself.</p>
<p>Due to bullish sentiment, AVAX shot past the 20-Simple Moving Average line (SMA), indicating that buyers have been driving the price momentum in the market. Not just the 20-SMA, the altcoin was parked above the 50-SMA due to excessive demand.</p>
<img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-515817 size-full" src="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/AVAXUSD_2023-01-12_01-06-50.png" alt="Avalanche" width="1816" height="743" srcset="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/AVAXUSD_2023-01-12_01-06-50.png 1816w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/AVAXUSD_2023-01-12_01-06-50-460x188.png 460w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/AVAXUSD_2023-01-12_01-06-50-860x352.png 860w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/AVAXUSD_2023-01-12_01-06-50-768x314.png 768w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/AVAXUSD_2023-01-12_01-06-50-1536x628.png 1536w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/AVAXUSD_2023-01-12_01-06-50-750x307.png 750w, https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/AVAXUSD_2023-01-12_01-06-50-1140x466.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1816px) 100vw, 1816px" />
<p>The Moving Average Convergence Divergence suggests price momentum and a trend reversal. The indicator formed a few green histograms, which are buy signals for the coin. The most recent histogram increased in size, anticipating the rise in the price of the asset.</p>
<p>Investors could quickly take this as a signal for entry as the price would increase over the next few trading sessions before it started to retrace.</p>

<p>The Directional Movement Index reads the price direction, and it was bullish. The +DI line (blue) was above the -DI line (orange).</p>
<p>The Average Directional Index (red) was near 20 with a slight uptick, confirming that although the price witnessed a northbound movement, the price direction lacks substantial strength.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/christian-wiediger-rymh7EZPqRs-unsplash-1-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/

Object Caching 214/220 objects using apc
Page Caching using disk: enhanced (Page is feed) 
Database Caching 36/45 queries in 0.031 seconds using memcached

Served from: newsbtc.com @ 2023-01-12 22:56:45 by W3 Total Cache
-->