<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; cryptocurrency news today, price &#38; technical analysis</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 03:14:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Just Reversed And Signals Fresh Run To $2,000</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-reversed-1915/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 03:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=529800</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum price started a fresh increase above the $1,880 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH is rising and might soon aim for a move toward $2,000. Ethereum is attempting a fresh increase above $1,880. The price is trading above $1,880 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $1,860 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could continue to move up if it clears the $1,920 resistance zone. Ethereum Price Recovers Ground Ethereum’s price remained well-bid above the $1,800 support zone. ETH started a decent upward move and was able to clear the $1,850 resistance, similar to Bitcoin at $28,800. There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $1,860 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. The pair even climbed above $1,900. A high is formed near $1,915 and the price is now consolidating gains. It is trading above $1,880 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. Ether is trading nicely above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $1,843 swing low to the $1,915 high. Immediate resistance is near the $1,915 level. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com The next major resistance seems to be forming near $1,940. An upside break above the $1,940 resistance might send Ethereum toward the $2,000 resistance. Any more gains could send Ether toward the $2,050 resistance. In the stated case, Ether could even attempt a move toward the $2,120 resistance. Are Dips Limited in ETH? If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,915 resistance, it could start a downside correction. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,890 level. The next major support is near the $1,880 zone or the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $1,843 swing low to the $1,915 high, below which ether price might drop toward the 100 hourly SMA. Any more losses may perhaps take the price toward the $1,840 level in the near term. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is now losing momentum in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is above the 50 level. Major Support Level – $1,870 Major Resistance Level – $1,915]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum price started a fresh increase above the $1,880 resistance against the US Dollar. ETH is rising and might soon aim for a move toward $2,000.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum is attempting a fresh increase above $1,880.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $1,880 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</li>
<li>There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance near $1,860 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to move up if it clears the $1,920 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Recovers Ground</h2>
<p>Ethereum’s price remained well-bid above the $1,800 support zone. ETH started a decent upward move and was able to clear the $1,850 resistance, similar to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-regains-strength-30k-2/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> at $28,800.</p>
<p>There was a break above a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-vulnerable-1900/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">key bearish trend line</a> with resistance near $1,860 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. The pair even climbed above $1,900. A high is formed near $1,915 and the price is now consolidating gains. It is trading above $1,880 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</p>
<p>Ether is trading nicely above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $1,843 swing low to the $1,915 high. Immediate resistance is near the $1,915 level.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-3.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-529801" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-3.png" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-3.png 1834w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-3-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-3-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-3-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-3-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-3-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-3-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The next major resistance seems to be forming near $1,940. An upside break above the $1,940 resistance might send Ethereum toward the $2,000 resistance. Any more gains could send Ether toward the $2,050 resistance. In the stated case, Ether could even attempt a move toward the $2,120 resistance.</p>
<h2>Are Dips Limited in ETH?</h2>
<p>If Ethereum fails to clear the $1,915 resistance, it could start a downside correction. Initial support on the downside is near the $1,890 level.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $1,880 zone or the 50% Fib retracement level of the recent increase from the $1,843 swing low to the $1,915 high, below which ether price might drop toward the 100 hourly SMA. Any more losses may perhaps take the price toward the $1,840 level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is now losing momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $1,870</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $1,915</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/iStock-952510084-460x220.jpg" width="460" height="220" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Regains Strength Post Fed Hike, $30K Could Be Next</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-regains-strength-30k-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 02:21:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=529796</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is recovering and trading above $29,000. BTC is slowly moving higher and the bulls might soon aim for a move toward the $30,000 resistance. Bitcoin is attempting a recovery wave above the $28,800 resistance zone. The price is trading above $28,800 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There was a break above a key contracting triangle with resistance near $28,700 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could rise further and revisit the $30,000 resistance zone. Bitcoin Price Recovers Losses Bitcoin price remained well-bid above the $28,000 support zone. BTC started a decent recovery wave above the $28,500 resistance zone. It even broke the $28,800 resistance after the Fed announced another rate hike from 5% to 5.25%. There was a break above a key contracting triangle with resistance near $28,700 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. The pair is now trading above $28,800 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. Bitcoin price is currently consolidating near the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the main decline from the $29,975 swing high to the $27,664 low. Immediate resistance is near the $29,200 level. The next major resistance sits near the $29,420 zone. It is close to the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the main decline from the $29,975 swing high to the $27,664 low. A proper move above the $29,420 resistance zone might send the price toward the $30,000 resistance zone. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com Any more gains could open the doors for a test of the $30,500 resistance. In the stated case, the price may perhaps rise toward the $31,200 level. Are Dips Supported in BTC? If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $29,200 resistance, it could start a downside correction. Immediate support on the downside is near the $28,800 level and the triangle trend line. The next major support is near the $28,650 zone or the 100 hourly Simple moving average, below which the price might drop toward the $28,400 support zone. Any more losses might take Bitcoin toward the $28,000 level in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $28,800, followed by $28,650. Major Resistance Levels – $29,200, $29,420, and $30,000.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is recovering and trading above $29,000. BTC is slowly moving higher and the bulls might soon aim for a move toward the $30,000 resistance.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin is attempting a recovery wave above the $28,800 resistance zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $28,800 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There was a break above a key contracting triangle with resistance near $28,700 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could rise further and revisit the $30,000 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Recovers Losses</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price remained <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-faces-hurdle-28800/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">well-bid above the $28,000 support zone</a>. BTC started a decent recovery wave above the $28,500 resistance zone. It even broke the $28,800 resistance after the Fed announced another rate hike from 5% to 5.25%.</p>
<p>There was a break above a key contracting triangle with resistance near $28,700 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. The pair is now trading above $28,800 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price is currently consolidating near the 61.8% Fib retracement level of the main decline from the $29,975 swing high to the $27,664 low. <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-slide-27650/?swcfpc=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Immediate resistance is near the $29,200 level</a>.</p>
<p>The next major resistance sits near the $29,420 zone. It is close to the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the main decline from the $29,975 swing high to the $27,664 low. A proper move above the $29,420 resistance zone might send the price toward the $30,000 resistance zone.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-3.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-529797" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-3.png" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1834" height="845" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-3.png 1834w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-3-460x212.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-3-860x396.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-3-768x354.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-3-1536x708.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-3-750x346.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-3-1140x525.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>Any more gains could open the doors for a test of the $30,500 resistance. In the stated case, the price may perhaps rise toward the $31,200 level.</p>
<h2>Are Dips Supported in BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin’s price fails to clear the $29,200 resistance, it could start a downside correction. Immediate support on the downside is near the $28,800 level and the triangle trend line.</p>
<p>The next major support is near the $28,650 zone or the 100 hourly Simple moving average, below which the price might drop toward the $28,400 support zone. Any more losses might take Bitcoin toward the $28,000 level in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now gaining pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $28,800, followed by $28,650.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $29,200, $29,420, and $30,000.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/shutterstock_456228007-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Meme Coin Mania Sweeps The Globe: Top 10 Countries Leading The Craze In 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/meme-coin-mania-sweeps-the-globe-top-10-countries-leading-the-craze-in-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memecoin Mania]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shib Inu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=529786</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The rise of the meme coin mania in 2023 has taken the cryptocurrency world by storm, and a new report by CoinGecko shows that the trend is most popular in the United States, India, and the United Kingdom. These countries account for over 50% of all meme coin fans this year, indicating a strong interest in these assets. But the appeal of meme coins continues beyond there. The report also highlights the popularity of these coins in other regions, including Southeast Asia&#8217;s Philippines and Malaysia, Nigeria and Morocco in Africa, Oceania&#8217;s Australia and New Zealand, and Canada. This diverse mix of countries suggests that meme coins have a global appeal. Related Reading: More Dip To Come: Bitcoin Liquidity On The Move Ahead Of Major Event From the US to India, The Global Phenomenon Of Meme Coins Takes Hold The top 10 countries leading the meme coin craze in 2023 make up the majority of interest in these assets, representing 82.9% of all fans. This indicates that even though meme coins may have started as a niche trend, they have quickly gained a following worldwide. According to the report, the United States is at the forefront of the meme coin craze in 2023, accounting for a whopping 23.6% of the global interest in these speculative assets. With over 2 million views on the top meme coin pages, it is clear that Americans are embracing this new type of cryptocurrency. The report shows that the most popular meme coin in the US this year is Shiba Inu, which generated 60.7% of all US interest in meme coins. This is not surprising given the coin&#8217;s recent surge in popularity due to celebrity endorsements and high-profile listings on major cryptocurrency exchanges. Following closely behind Shiba Inu is Pepe, a trending crypto that recently drove 11.8% of meme coin interest in the US. Other popular meme coins in the country include Bonk and Volt Inu, which generated 5.7% and 4.9% of US interest, respectively. Moreover, India will be the second-largest driver of the meme coin hype in 2023, accounting for 20.3% of all interest across the countries. Shiba Inu is the most popular coin in India, generating 55.8% of the country&#8217;s interest in these speculative assets. Baby Doge Coin also received a relatively high share of interest, with 29.9% of India&#8217;s meme coin interest. Floki is the most popular meme coin in the Philippines, generating 26.7% of the country&#8217;s interest in these assets. Shiba Inu and Bonk also received similar interest levels at 18.3% and 17.8%, respectively. Baby Doge Coin and Pepe were close behind, with 12.7% and 10.2% share of Philippines meme coin interest, respectively. Shiba Inu Reigns Supreme According to the report,  Shiba Inu is the most popular meme coin among investors in 2023, driving 46.7% of interest among the top meme coins.  Baby DogeCoin is the second most popular, generating 12.3% of investor interest. This is followed by more recent coins, Pepe (9.4%), Floki (8.6%), and Bonk (8.2%). Furthermore, Pepe captured the most interest in Canada, accounting for 26.9% of all interest in the country. Interestingly, while Dogecoin pioneered the meme coin space, it generated only 61.1% of interest in Morocco and received only minor interest in the other countries surveyed.  Overall, the report by CoinGecko shows that meme coins continue to gain popularity and are a force to be reckoned with in the cryptocurrency market. As new coins emerge and gain traction, it will be interesting to see how this market evolves and whether meme coins will continue to be a dominant trend in the cryptocurrency world. Related Reading: SUI Plummets Over 30% As Trading Goes Live On Exchanges, What Went Wrong? Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The rise of the meme coin mania in 2023 has taken the cryptocurrency world by storm, and a new <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/research/publications/top-meme-coin-countries" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report </a>by CoinGecko shows that the trend is most popular in the United States, India, and the United Kingdom. These countries account for over 50% of all meme coin fans this year, indicating a strong interest in these assets.</p>
<p>But the appeal of meme coins continues beyond there. The report also highlights the popularity of these coins in other regions, including Southeast Asia&#8217;s Philippines and Malaysia, Nigeria and Morocco in Africa, Oceania&#8217;s Australia and New Zealand, and Canada. This diverse mix of countries suggests that meme coins have a global appeal.</p>





<h2><b>From the US to India, The Global Phenomenon Of Meme Coins Takes Hold</b></h2>
<p><b>The top 10 countries leading the meme coin craze in 2023 make up the majority of interest in these assets, representing 82.9% of all fans. This indicates that even though meme coins may have started as a niche trend, they have quickly gained a following worldwide.</b></p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-529788 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_32.jpg" alt="Meme Coins" width="569" height="522" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_32.jpg 569w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_32-460x422.jpg 460w" sizes="(max-width: 569px) 100vw, 569px" />
<p>According to the report, the United States is at the forefront of the meme coin craze in 2023, accounting for a whopping 23.6% of the global interest in these speculative assets. With over 2 million views on the top meme coin pages, it is clear that Americans are embracing this new type of cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>The report shows that the most popular meme coin in the US this year is Shiba Inu, which generated 60.7% of all US interest in meme coins. This is not surprising given the coin&#8217;s recent surge in popularity due to celebrity endorsements and high-profile listings on major cryptocurrency exchanges.</p>
<p>Following closely behind Shiba Inu is Pepe, a trending crypto that recently drove 11.8% of meme coin interest in the US. Other popular meme coins in the country include Bonk and Volt Inu, which generated 5.7% and 4.9% of US interest, respectively.</p>
<p>Moreover, India will be the second-largest driver of the meme coin hype in 2023, accounting for 20.3% of all interest across the countries. Shiba Inu is the most popular coin in India, generating 55.8% of the country&#8217;s interest in these speculative assets. Baby Doge Coin also received a relatively high share of interest, with 29.9% of India&#8217;s meme coin interest.</p>
<p>Floki is the most popular meme coin in the Philippines, generating 26.7% of the country&#8217;s interest in these assets. Shiba Inu and Bonk also received similar interest levels at 18.3% and 17.8%, respectively. Baby Doge Coin and Pepe were close behind, with 12.7% and 10.2% share of Philippines meme coin interest, respectively.</p>
<b>Shiba Inu Reigns Supreme</b>
<p>According to the report,  Shiba Inu is the most popular meme coin among investors in 2023, driving 46.7% of interest among the top meme coins. </p>
<p>Baby DogeCoin is the second most popular, generating 12.3% of investor interest. This is followed by more recent coins, Pepe (9.4%), Floki (8.6%), and Bonk (8.2%). Furthermore, Pepe captured the most interest in Canada, accounting for 26.9% of all interest in the country.</p>
<p>Interestingly, while Dogecoin pioneered the meme coin space, it generated only 61.1% of interest in Morocco and received only minor interest in the other countries surveyed. </p>
<p>Overall, the report by CoinGecko shows that meme coins continue to gain popularity and are a force to be reckoned with in the cryptocurrency market. As new coins emerge and gain traction, it will be interesting to see how this market evolves and whether meme coins will continue to be a dominant trend in the cryptocurrency world.</p>

<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/6Brs5OiU/" alt="Meme coins" width="1814" height="858" />
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/traxer-rpKxtylphc4-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Market in Disarray, But Optimism Prevails With Two Narratives</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-market-in-disarray-but-optimism-prevails-with-two-narratives/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reynaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 21:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=529762</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The price of Bitcoin has seen a small uptick during today’s trading session, but the cryptocurrency has been unable to break the sideways trend. Today, the U.S. Federal Reserve (Fed) announced a 25 basis points (bps) rate hike, but uncertainty in the financial world remains king. Related Reading: More Dip To Come: Bitcoin Liquidity On The Move Ahead Of Major Event As of this writing, Bitcoin (BTC) trades at $28,600 with sideways movement across the board. Other major cryptocurrencies in the top 10 by market capitalization have experienced similar price action except for XRP and Cardano (ADA), which record small losses in the past 24 hours. Bitcoin Stun By Economic Uncertainty, But Bulls Could Take The Upper Hand According to a report from the trading desk QCP Capital, Bitcoin, and the crypto market have been in an 8 week long confusion phase. As a result, the nascent industry experienced a decline in its Implied Volatility (IV), leading to the current sideways price action. Volatility, as measured by the VIX Index, is crashing to levels last seen during the 2022 bearish phase. This dynamic might trigger an aggressive move in the coming weeks, but the direction of such price action is unclear. However, two key events could support Bitcoin in reclaiming higher levels. Both scenarios will operate on the macroeconomic board, which keeps exercising a strong influence over BTC and other financial assets. First, QCP Capital argues that in the next two months, the U.S. banking crisis will still be relevant, along with the debt ceiling in the country. These narratives create the perception that the fiat system is weak, which could lead to further bank runs. BTC Bull Run Imminent?  Thus, the Fed must continue bailing out banking institutions and injecting liquidity into the financial markets. The debt ceiling presents a similar issue; the federal government might be forced to intervene because the U.S. is unlikely to default on its debt. As a result, more and more liquidity could enter financial markets allowing Bitcoin to breathe and resume its bullish momentum. According to QCP Capital, this phenomenon is already happening. Due to the banking crisis in the U.S., the Fed has been forced to intervene, increasing the side of its balance sheet by almost $500 billion over the past two weeks, as seen in the chart below. The Fed last injected this much liquidity during the COVID-19 crisis. At that time, the price of Bitcoin recorded a massive profit and entered price discovery for at least 12 months. The trading firm stated the following about BTC’s potential to see similar profits: The analog compares BTC price action now (red line) vs. BTC during the 2020 cycle (yellow line) by lining up the March 2020 and March 2022 lows. It shows that while we are likely in for a period of consolidation here, the underlying trend ahead is still strongly to the upside. Related Reading: Polygon (MATIC) Price Shows Vigor, Are Bulls Up To Something? Charts from QCP Capital and Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>The price of Bitcoin has seen a small uptick during today’s trading session, but the cryptocurrency has been unable to break the sideways trend. Today, the U.S. Federal Reserve (Fed) announced a 25 basis points (bps) rate hike, but uncertainty in the financial world remains king. </strong></p>

<p>As of this writing, Bitcoin (BTC) trades at $28,600 with sideways movement across the board. Other major cryptocurrencies in the top 10 by market capitalization have experienced similar price action except for XRP and Cardano (ADA), which record small losses in the past 24 hours.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-529793 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-860x394.png" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT" width="860" height="394" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-860x394.png 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-460x211.png 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-768x352.png 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1536x704.png 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-750x344.png 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-1140x523.png 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT.png 1813w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<h2>Bitcoin Stun By Economic Uncertainty, But Bulls Could Take The Upper Hand</h2>
<p>According to a <a href="https://qcp.capital/market-updates/market-update-3-may-23/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a> from the trading desk QCP Capital, Bitcoin, and the crypto market have been in an 8 week long confusion phase. As a result, the nascent industry experienced a decline in its Implied Volatility (IV), leading to the current sideways price action.</p>
<p>Volatility, as measured by the VIX Index, is crashing to levels last seen during the 2022 bearish phase. This dynamic might trigger an aggressive move in the coming weeks, but the direction of such price action is unclear.</p>
<p>However, two key events could support Bitcoin in reclaiming higher levels. Both scenarios will operate on the macroeconomic board, which keeps exercising a strong influence over BTC and other financial assets.</p>
<p>First, QCP Capital argues that in the next two months, the U.S. banking crisis will still be relevant, along with the debt ceiling in the country. <a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/us-banking-crisis-first-republic-jpmorgan-pacwest-2023-5" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">These narratives create the perception that the fiat system is weak, which could lead to further bank runs</a>.</p>
<strong>BTC Bull Run Imminent? </strong>
<p>Thus, the Fed must continue bailing out banking institutions and injecting liquidity into the financial markets. The debt ceiling presents a similar issue; the<a href="https://newrepublic.com/article/172376/debt-ceiling-deadline-default-negotiations" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> federal government might be forced to intervene because the U.S. is unlikely to default on its debt</a>.</p>
<p>As a result, more and more liquidity could enter financial markets allowing Bitcoin to breathe and resume its bullish momentum. According to QCP Capital, this phenomenon is already happening.</p>
<p>Due to the banking crisis in the U.S., the Fed has been forced to intervene, increasing the side of its balance sheet by almost $500 billion over the past two weeks, as seen in the chart below.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-529792 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Balance-sheet-1-860x402.jpg" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT Balance sheet 1" width="860" height="402" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Balance-sheet-1-860x402.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Balance-sheet-1-460x215.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Balance-sheet-1-768x359.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Balance-sheet-1-750x350.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Balance-sheet-1-1140x532.jpg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-Balance-sheet-1.jpg 1229w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>The Fed last injected this much liquidity during the COVID-19 crisis. At that time, the price of Bitcoin recorded a massive profit and entered price discovery for at least 12 months. The trading firm stated the following about BTC’s potential to see similar profits:</p>
<blockquote><p>The analog compares BTC price action now (red line) vs. BTC during the 2020 cycle (yellow line) by lining up the March 2020 and March 2022 lows. It shows that while we are likely in for a period of consolidation here, the underlying trend ahead is still strongly to the upside.</p></blockquote>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-529791 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-QCP-Capital-Chart-3-860x375.jpg" alt="Bitcoin BTC BTCUSDT QCP Capital Chart 3" width="860" height="375" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-QCP-Capital-Chart-3-860x375.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-QCP-Capital-Chart-3-460x201.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-QCP-Capital-Chart-3-768x335.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-QCP-Capital-Chart-3-750x327.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-QCP-Capital-Chart-3-1140x497.jpg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-BTC-BTCUSDT-QCP-Capital-Chart-3.jpg 1383w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />

<p>Charts from QCP Capital and Tradingview</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/iStock-1409541251-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Bold Move: Sells SUI For $100 Million, Tokens Now Worth $1 Billion</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/ftx/ftx-bold-move-sells-sui-for-100-million-tokens-now-worth-1-billion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 20:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX (FTT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SUI]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=529780</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[According to the trader and analyst of the crypto market under the pseudonym “Googly,” the fallen crypto exchange FTX sold warrants for $884 million SUI tokens to Mysten Labs and preferred stock for less than $100 million in March. The paper valuation for the tokens is now worth $1 billion. The sale of the warrants and preferred stock is significant for FTX, providing additional funding to support its operations and expansion. FTX has been gaining traction in the cryptocurrency market, and the additional funding will undoubtedly help the company continue to grow and innovate. However, It is worth noting that the value of the tokens and preferred stock can only be realized if FTX relaunches.  Related Reading: More Dip To Come: Bitcoin Liquidity On The Move Ahead Of Major Event FTX Laughing All The Way To The Bank? Not Quite FTX filed a court document on March 22, 2023, outlining its sale of interests in SUI Foundation and the Purchaser-Subject Company. According to the document, FTX Ventures Ltd. acquired 560,045 Series B Preferred Stock shares in the Purchaser-Subject Company and a warrant to purchase 363,636,305 SUI Tokens for a total of $99,999,843.06.  Additionally, Cottonwood Grove Limited acquired a warrant to purchase 173,333,333 SUI Tokens, and FTX Trading Ltd. acquired a warrant to purchase 346,666,667 SUI Tokens. These warrants are only exercisable upon achieving certain milestones and events concerning the implementation of SUI protocols and trading SUI tokens on the FTX.com platform. On August 31, 2022, FTX Ventures Ltd. acquired an additional 7,000 shares of Preferred Stock in the Purchaser-Subject Company and a warrant to purchase 4,114,898 SUI Tokens. All of the SUI Token Warrants are only exercisable after the SUI Tokens are minted, generated, or created, if ever. The Preferred Stock and the SUI Token Warrants held by the sellers are referred to collectively as the &#8220;Interests.&#8221; FTX has now filed a court document outlining the sale of these Interests for cash consideration. The document states that the Interests are easily separated from the Debtors&#8217; core operations. The sale of the Interests will not affect the Debtors&#8217; ability to operate any of their businesses. In addition, any income that the Preferred Stock might generate in the form of dividends or distributions is uncertain and would only be received at the discretion of the Purchaser-Subject Company&#8217;s board of directors. What You Need To Know About SUI SUI Tokens are a digital asset created by Sui Foundation, a blockchain-based platform that aims to provide secure, transparent, and decentralized data management and storage solutions. The SUI Tokens are designed to be used within the Sui ecosystem, allowing users to access various services and applications. Furthermore, the SUI Tokens are based on the Ethereum blockchain and are ERC-20 compliant, meaning they can be easily integrated with other Ethereum-based applications. The tokens can be used to pay for services within the Sui ecosystem, such as data storage and data management, and can also be traded on various cryptocurrency exchanges. As reported by NewsBTC, the highly anticipated launch of SUI, a blockchain-based platform for secure and decentralized data management, is finally here. Dubbed the next &#8220;Ethereum killer,&#8221; SUI is expected to shake up the cryptocurrency market with its unique technical approach. Related Reading: XRP Loses Previous Gains; Bulls Seek To Shift Momentum Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://twitter.com/0xG00gly/status/1653751790456676352?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to the trader and analyst of the crypto market under the pseudonym “Googly,” the fallen crypto exchange FTX sold warrants for $884 million SUI tokens to Mysten Labs and preferred stock for less than $100 million in March. The paper valuation for the tokens is now worth $1 billion.</p>
<p>The sale of the warrants and preferred stock is significant for FTX, providing additional funding to support its operations and expansion. FTX has been gaining traction in the cryptocurrency market, and the additional funding will undoubtedly help the company continue to grow and innovate.</p>
<p>However, It is worth noting that the value of the tokens and preferred stock can only be realized if FTX relaunches. </p>

<h2><b>FTX Laughing All The Way To The Bank? Not Quite</b></h2>
<p>FTX filed a court <a href="https://t.co/kkmfCmnEV1" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">document </a>on March 22, 2023, outlining its sale of interests in SUI Foundation and the Purchaser-Subject Company. According to the document, FTX Ventures Ltd. acquired 560,045 Series B Preferred Stock shares in the Purchaser-Subject Company and a warrant to purchase 363,636,305 SUI Tokens for a total of $99,999,843.06. </p>
<p>Additionally, Cottonwood Grove Limited acquired a warrant to purchase 173,333,333 SUI Tokens, and FTX Trading Ltd. acquired a warrant to purchase 346,666,667 SUI Tokens. These warrants are only exercisable upon achieving certain milestones and events concerning the implementation of SUI protocols and trading SUI tokens on the FTX.com platform.</p>
<p>On August 31, 2022, FTX Ventures Ltd. acquired an additional 7,000 shares of Preferred Stock in the Purchaser-Subject Company and a warrant to purchase 4,114,898 SUI Tokens. All of the SUI Token Warrants are only exercisable after the SUI Tokens are minted, generated, or created, if ever. The Preferred Stock and the SUI Token Warrants held by the sellers are referred to collectively as the &#8220;Interests.&#8221;</p>
<p>FTX has now filed a court document outlining the sale of these Interests for cash consideration. The document states that the Interests are easily separated from the Debtors&#8217; core operations. The sale of the Interests will not affect the Debtors&#8217; ability to operate any of their businesses.</p>
<p>In addition, any income that the Preferred Stock might generate in the form of dividends or distributions is uncertain and would only be received at the discretion of the Purchaser-Subject Company&#8217;s board of directors.</p>
<b>What You Need To Know About SUI</b>
<p>SUI Tokens are a digital asset created by Sui Foundation, a blockchain-based platform that aims to provide secure, transparent, and decentralized data management and storage solutions. The SUI Tokens are designed to be used within the Sui ecosystem, allowing users to access various services and applications.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the SUI Tokens are based on the Ethereum blockchain and are ERC-20 compliant, meaning they can be easily integrated with other Ethereum-based applications. The tokens can be used to pay for services within the Sui ecosystem, such as data storage and data management, and can also be traded on various cryptocurrency exchanges.</p>
<p>As reported by <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/ethereum-killer-sui-launched-today/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NewsBTC</a>, the highly anticipated launch of SUI, a blockchain-based platform for secure and decentralized data management, is finally here. Dubbed the next &#8220;Ethereum killer,&#8221; SUI is expected to shake up the cryptocurrency market with its unique technical approach.</p>

<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/R87Lklmi/" alt="FTX" width="1814" height="858" />
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/brano-heYdDdq0cbE-unsplash-460x259.jpg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Rally May Not Have Hit Top Yet, Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-rally-may-not-have-hit-top-heres-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 19:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cycles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin long-term holders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin top]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=529730</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The historical pattern in this Bitcoin on-chain indicator may suggest that the ongoing rally hasn&#8217;t reached its top yet. Bitcoin 1-Year Inactive Supply Has Continued To Go Up Recently According to a post from the on-chain analytics firm CryptoQuant, the 1-year inactive supply hit a high back in March of this year. The &#8220;1-year inactive supply&#8221; is an indicator that measures the total percentage of the Bitcoin supply that hasn&#8217;t moved on the blockchain since at least one year ago. This supply belongs to one of the two major cohorts in the BTC market: the &#8220;long-term holders&#8221; (LTHs). This group includes all investors who bought their coins more than six months ago, so the 1-year inactive supply metric doesn&#8217;t measure their entire supply, only a segment of it (although a rather large one). The LTHs hold a special place in the Bitcoin economy as they comprise the most resolute investors in the market. The selling and buying behavior of this cohort can, therefore, have long-term implications for the sector. Related Reading: Ethereum Sees Inflows Of $505M Into Binance, Sign Of Selling? Here is a chart that shows how the 1-year inactive BTC supply has changed over the lifetime of the cryptocurrency and how it has seemingly taken its place in the different price cycles: Looks like the value of the metric has been on the rise in recent days &#124; Source: CryptoQuant As the above graph shows, the Bitcoin 1-year inactive supply has historically trended up during the bear markets. This means these investors generally participate in accumulation in the leadup to and during the bear markets. The LTHs then continue to hold onto their filled-up bags and expand as they transition toward a bullish period. These investors show this behavior throughout the bull market buildup phase; when the rally starts reaching its last stages, these holders start selling to take their profits. This pattern has repeated throughout the different cycles, showing that the LTHs&#8217; behavior hasn&#8217;t changed too much. However, one thing that differs between the cycles is that their supply has been going up overall. This would partly be attributed to all the Bitcoin that has been getting lost due to wallet keys becoming inaccessible. Related Reading: $24,400 May Be Next Major Level Of Support For Bitcoin, Here’s Why The percentage of the circulating supply held by this Bitcoin investor segment hit an all-time high just back in March of this year, reaching a value north of 67%. These investors have shed some coins since then, but the difference in their supplies between then and now is negligible (13.1 million BTC vs. 13 million BTC). The April 2019 rally, which resembles the current one, also saw the LTHs holding tight until midway through the rally, when they started selling, and the cryptocurrency reached the top just a while later. Suppose the Bitcoin price and the 1-year inactive supply will follow the same pattern in this current rally as during all these past bullish periods. In that case, it seems likely that the top hasn&#8217;t been hit since the LTHs haven&#8217;t started participating in any significant distribution yet. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $28,300, down 4% in the last week. BTC has gone stale in the past day &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, CryptoQuant.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The historical pattern in this Bitcoin on-chain indicator may suggest that the ongoing rally hasn&#8217;t reached its top yet.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin 1-Year Inactive Supply Has Continued To Go Up Recently</h2>
<p>According to a post from the on-chain analytics firm <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/6452594312ca611e264b21f9-Understanding-the-Interplay-Between-Bitcoin-Holders-and-Market-Cycles" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CryptoQuant</a>, the 1-year inactive supply hit a high back in March of this year. The &#8220;1-year inactive supply&#8221; is an indicator that measures the total percentage of the Bitcoin supply that hasn&#8217;t moved on the blockchain since at least one year ago.</p>
<p>This supply belongs to one of the two major cohorts in the BTC market: the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-long-term-holders-holding-price-decline/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">long-term holders</a>&#8221; (LTHs). This group includes all investors who bought their coins more than six months ago, so the 1-year inactive supply metric doesn&#8217;t measure their entire supply, only a segment of it (although a rather large one).</p>
<p>The LTHs hold a special place in the Bitcoin economy as they comprise the most resolute investors in the market. The selling and buying behavior of this cohort can, therefore, have long-term implications for the sector.</p>

<p>Here is a chart that shows how the 1-year inactive BTC supply has changed over the lifetime of the cryptocurrency and how it has seemingly taken its place in the different price cycles:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://img.cryptoquant.com/4/quicktake/6ZA7hzZM9_eda6982a7ec1dac58bc047d0fa77f8fbac8ab18fb2025db76d9087ce853ffb35.png" alt="Bitcoin 1-Year Inactive Supply" width="1120" height="591" /></p>

<p>As the above graph shows, the Bitcoin 1-year inactive supply has historically trended up during the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-bear-market-historic-on-chain-signal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bear markets</a>. This means these investors generally participate in accumulation in the leadup to and during the bear markets.</p>
<p>The LTHs then continue to hold onto their filled-up bags and expand as they transition toward a bullish period. These investors show this behavior throughout the bull market buildup phase; when the rally starts reaching its last stages, these holders start selling to take their profits.</p>
<p>This pattern has repeated throughout the different cycles, showing that the LTHs&#8217; behavior hasn&#8217;t changed too much. However, one thing that differs between the cycles is that their supply has been going up overall. This would partly be attributed to all the Bitcoin that has been getting lost due to wallet keys becoming inaccessible.</p>

<p>The percentage of the circulating supply held by this Bitcoin investor segment hit an all-time high just back in March of this year, reaching a value north of 67%. These investors have shed some coins since then, but the difference in their supplies between then and now is negligible (13.1 million BTC vs. 13 million BTC).</p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/repeat-april-2019-bitcoin-rally-levels/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">April 2019 rally</a>, which resembles the current one, also saw the LTHs holding tight until midway through the rally, when they started selling, and the cryptocurrency reached the top just a while later.</p>
<p>Suppose the Bitcoin price and the 1-year inactive supply will follow the same pattern in this current rally as during all these past bullish periods. In that case, it seems likely that the top hasn&#8217;t been hit since the LTHs haven&#8217;t started participating in any significant distribution yet.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $28,300, down 4% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/6bpDmy1w/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1533" height="911" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/kanchanara-rhm7H8X5J98-unsplash-460x306.jpg" width="460" height="306" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SUI Plummets Over 30% As Trading Goes Live On Exchanges, What Went Wrong?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/sui-plummets-30-as-trading-goes-live-on-exchanges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 18:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchanges]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SUI]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=529754</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SUI, one of the long-awaited blockchain token projects in the crypto community, finally launched earlier today. However, contrary to expectations, SUI has recorded a significant plunge in price as the trading went live on multiple exchanges.  Over the past 4 hours since its launch, the token has declined by more than 30%. This price action disappointed traders who expected the token to only record a continuous upward trend following its launch, as often happens during these events. Trading Goes Live On Exchanges The token is now live on major exchanges in the crypto market, such as Binance, KuCoin, ByBit, and so on. The token can now be bought and sold against other cryptocurrencies and fiat currencies, including Bitcoin, USDT, TUSD, EUR, BNB, and TRY.  Related Reading: New “Ethereum Killer” SUI Launches Today, What You Need To Know According to a Binance blog post about the SUI listing, traders will not pay maker fees on SUI/USDT until further announcements. Chinese crypto journalist Colin Wu reported that the official team behind the SUI coin has demanded that exchanges should not launch SUI-based perpetual futures contracts. However, exchanges, including, Bybit, OKX, and KuCoin, launched several SUI trading pairs. SUI Plunges Over 30% Interestingly, the token has declined by over 30% following its trading launch on various crypto exchanges after its initial surge of over 1,000% at launch. The newborn asset currently trades for $1.53 at the time of writing down by 35%. SUI currently has a 24-low of $1.33 and a 24-high of $3.34, according to data from CoinMarketCap. Regardless of the market decline, the asset’s trading volume is still up and at a value of nearly $1 million, according to CoinMarketCap.  SUI is a blockchain project that aims to create a decentralized platform for secure and efficient data storage and management. It was launched in 2020 by a team of blockchain experts who sought to address the limitations of traditional data storage systems, such as high costs, centralization, and vulnerability to cyber threats. The blockchain is based on a Proof-of-Stake (PoS) consensus mechanism, which allows users to stake their tokens to participate in the network&#8217;s validation process and earn rewards for their contributions.  Though several factors could be tied to the plummet in SUI following its launch on exchanges. However, a few reasons could be the supply and demand dynamics and traders&#8217; and investors&#8217; disappointment. Related Reading: SuiPad – MystenLabs Official Launchpad Partner, secured $1.155 million in funding When a new crypto launches on an exchange, there may be an influx of sell orders as early investors and traders try to take profits. In SUI&#8217;s case, those who bought at presale for a low price and public sale may have sold to take a profit. And if the buying pressure is not strong enough to absorb these sell orders, the price is bound to drop. In addition, some traders and investors may have speculated on the token&#8217;s price before its launch on exchanges. This may have led to inflated and expanded expectations. When the price of SUI failed to meet those expectations, some may have sold off their holdings, contributing to the downward pressure on the price. Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUI, one of the long-awaited blockchain token projects in the crypto community, finally <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/ethereum-killer-sui-launched-today/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launched earlier today</a>. However, contrary to expectations, SUI has recorded a significant plunge in price as the trading went live on multiple exchanges. </p>
<p>Over the past 4 hours since its launch, the token has declined by more than 30%. This price action disappointed traders who expected the token to only record a continuous upward trend following its launch, as often happens during these events.</p>
<h2>Trading Goes Live On Exchanges</h2>
<p>The token is now live on major exchanges in the crypto market, such as Binance, KuCoin, ByBit, and so on. The token can now be bought and sold against other cryptocurrencies and fiat currencies, including Bitcoin, USDT, TUSD, EUR, BNB, and TRY. </p>

<p>According to a Binance <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/binance-will-open-trading-for-sui-0c5cae80f4ea42a79e9c92c1f7a25d6f" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">blog post</a> about the SUI listing, traders will not pay maker fees on SUI/USDT until further announcements.</p>
<p>Chinese crypto journalist Colin Wu <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1653722900661407744?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reported</a> that the official team behind the SUI coin has demanded that exchanges should not launch SUI-based perpetual futures contracts. However, exchanges, including, Bybit, OKX, and KuCoin, launched several SUI trading pairs.</p>
<h2>SUI Plunges Over 30%</h2>
<p>Interestingly, the token has declined by over 30% following its trading launch on various crypto exchanges after its initial surge of over 1,000% at launch. The newborn asset currently trades for $1.53 at the time of writing down by 35%.</p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/BtoK4WzS/" alt="SUI price chart on TradingView.com" width="2768" height="1556" />
<p>SUI currently has a 24-low of $1.33 and a 24-high of $3.34, according to data from CoinMarketCap. Regardless of the market decline, the asset’s trading volume is still up and at a value of nearly $1 million, according to CoinMarketCap. </p>
<p>SUI is a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/press-releases/suipad-mystenlabs-official-launchpad-partner-secured-1-155-million-in-funding/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">blockchain project</a> that aims to create a decentralized platform for secure and efficient data storage and management. It was launched in 2020 by a team of blockchain experts who sought to address the limitations of traditional data storage systems, such as high costs, centralization, and vulnerability to cyber threats.</p>
<p>The blockchain is based on a Proof-of-Stake (PoS) consensus mechanism, which allows users to stake their tokens to participate in the network&#8217;s validation process and earn rewards for their contributions. </p>
<p>Though several factors could be tied to the plummet in SUI following its launch on exchanges. However, a few reasons could be the supply and demand dynamics and traders&#8217; and investors&#8217; disappointment.</p>

<p>When a new crypto launches on an exchange, there may be an influx of sell orders as early investors and traders try to take profits. In SUI&#8217;s case, those who bought at presale for a low price and public sale may have sold to take a profit.</p>
<p>And if the buying pressure is not strong enough to absorb these sell orders, the price is bound to drop. In addition, some traders and investors may have speculated on the token&#8217;s price before its launch on exchanges.</p>
<p>This may have led to inflated and expanded expectations. When the price of SUI failed to meet those expectations, some may have sold off their holdings, contributing to the downward pressure on the price.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Optimism-460x259.jpeg" width="460" height="259" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>More Dip To Come: Bitcoin Liquidity On The Move Ahead Of Major Event</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/more-dip-to-come-bitcoin-liquidity-on-the-move-ahead-of-major-event/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 17:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=529752</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As the Federal Reserve (Fed) prepares to announce its decision on interest rates, Material Indicators, a research and analysis firm in the cryptocurrency market, is keeping a close eye on the Bitcoin (BTC) liquidity movements. FireCharts, a popular charting platform, has tracked liquidity movements on the BTC/USDT Binance order book. Their observations have led them to believe that the recent dip in Bitcoin&#8217;s price may extend. Liquidity refers to the amount of Bitcoin available for trading at a given price level. When there is a large amount of liquidity at a particular price level, traders can easily buy or sell Bitcoin at that price without significantly affecting the market. However, low liquidity at a certain price level can lead to volatility spikes as traders scramble to buy or sell the asset.  Related Reading: Polygon (MATIC) Price Shows Vigor, Are Bulls Up To Something? Will Bitcoin Face Another Dip Material Indicator’s FireCharts analysis shows that liquidity in the Bitcoin order book has been moving ahead of the Federal Reserve&#8217;s decision, indicating that traders are preparing for potential volatility in the market. This could lead to further price drops if liquidity to the upside declines.  Added to the above, according to Kaiko, a leading cryptocurrency market data provider, liquidity in Bitcoin and Ethereum continues to deteriorate, with market depth for both cryptocurrencies approaching one-year lows, which could have significant implications for bulls, as low liquidity can lead to increased volatility and price instability. As of writing, the price of Bitcoin stands at $28,300, representing a 1.4% decline over the past 24 hours. Despite the recent news of more bank failures, which briefly pushed the price above $29,000, Bitcoin has remained within its established trading range of $27,800 to $28,600. The attempt to exceed the $29,000 mark was unsuccessful, and the price has since retraced to its current level.  The market remains in flux as investors monitor the ongoing price movements, waiting for a clear direction to emerge after the Federal Open Market Committee meeting. But will this lead to more retracement, or will the market react positively to the news? BTC Braces For Potential Impact Of Federal Reserve&#8217;s Rate Hike The Federal Reserve&#8217;s latest measures on employment and wages suggest that more rate hikes may be on the horizon. This comes after the key labor costs metric for the first quarter came in higher than expected. One of the Fed&#8217;s preferred inflation gauges, the Personal Consumption Expenditure (PCE) index, remains persistently high.  Furthermore, according to the latest report by Bitfinex, a leading cryptocurrency exchange, the labor costs metric for the first quarter came in hotter than expected, indicating that wages are rising faster than anticipated. This could lead to higher inflation, as companies may pass higher labor costs to consumers through higher prices. This suggests that the Federal Reserve may need to raise interest rates to manage inflation and maintain price stability. The Fed has already signaled that it may raise rates in May, and these latest measures on employment and wages reinforce that decision. The implications of a rate hike are significant for the financial markets, including the cryptocurrency market. A rate hike could increase volatility and uncertainty as investors adjust their expectations for future economic growth and earnings. However, it could also lead to a stronger dollar and increased demand for safe-haven assets like gold and Bitcoin. Related Reading: $24,400 May Be Next Major Level Of Support For Bitcoin, Here’s Why Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As the Federal Reserve (Fed) prepares to announce its decision on interest rates, Material Indicators, a research and analysis firm in the cryptocurrency market, is keeping a close eye on the Bitcoin (BTC) liquidity movements. FireCharts, a popular charting platform, has tracked liquidity movements on the BTC/USDT Binance order book. Their observations have led them to believe that the recent dip in Bitcoin&#8217;s price may extend.</p>
<p>Liquidity refers to the amount of Bitcoin available for trading at a given price level. When there is a large amount of liquidity at a particular price level, traders can easily buy or sell Bitcoin at that price without significantly affecting the market. However, low liquidity at a certain price level can lead to volatility spikes as traders scramble to buy or sell the asset. </p>

<h2><b>Will Bitcoin Face Another Dip</b></h2>
<p>Material Indicator’s FireCharts <a href="https://twitter.com/MI_Algos/status/1653779144612642816?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">analysis </a>shows that liquidity in the Bitcoin order book has been moving ahead of the Federal Reserve&#8217;s decision, indicating that traders are preparing for potential volatility in the market. This could lead to further price drops if liquidity to the upside declines. </p>
<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large wp-image-529753" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FvNnRgNXoAA-1H3-860x527.jpg" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="527" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FvNnRgNXoAA-1H3-860x527.jpg 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FvNnRgNXoAA-1H3-460x282.jpg 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FvNnRgNXoAA-1H3-768x471.jpg 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FvNnRgNXoAA-1H3-750x460.jpg 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FvNnRgNXoAA-1H3-1140x699.jpg 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FvNnRgNXoAA-1H3.jpg 1352w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" />
<p>Added to the above, <a href="https://twitter.com/KaikoData/status/1653696007194984451?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">according </a>to Kaiko, a leading cryptocurrency market data provider, liquidity in Bitcoin and Ethereum continues to deteriorate, with market depth for both cryptocurrencies approaching one-year lows, which could have significant implications for bulls, as low liquidity can lead to increased volatility and price instability.</p>
<p>As of writing, the price of Bitcoin stands at $28,300, representing a 1.4% decline over the past 24 hours. Despite the recent <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/us-banking-crisis-worsens-with-half-of-americas-banks-on-the-verge-of-failure/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">news</a> of more bank failures, which briefly pushed the price above $29,000, Bitcoin has remained within its established trading range of $27,800 to $28,600. The attempt to exceed the $29,000 mark was unsuccessful, and the price has since retraced to its current level. </p>
<p>The market remains in flux as investors monitor the ongoing price movements, waiting for a clear direction to emerge after the Federal Open Market Committee meeting. But will this lead to more retracement, or will the market react positively to the news?</p>
<b>BTC Braces For Potential Impact Of Federal Reserve&#8217;s Rate Hike</b>
<p>The Federal Reserve&#8217;s latest measures on employment and wages suggest that more rate hikes may be on the horizon. This comes after the key labor costs metric for the first quarter came in higher than expected. One of the Fed&#8217;s preferred inflation gauges, the Personal Consumption Expenditure (PCE) index, remains persistently high. </p>
<p>Furthermore, according to the latest <a href="https://blog.bitfinex.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitfinex-Alpha-52.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report </a>by Bitfinex, a leading cryptocurrency exchange, the labor costs metric for the first quarter came in hotter than expected, indicating that wages are rising faster than anticipated. This could lead to higher inflation, as companies may pass higher labor costs to consumers through higher prices.</p>
<p>This suggests that the Federal Reserve may need to raise interest rates to manage inflation and maintain price stability. The Fed has already signaled that it may raise rates in May, and these latest measures on employment and wages reinforce that decision.</p>
<p>The implications of a rate hike are significant for the financial markets, including the cryptocurrency market. A rate hike could increase volatility and uncertainty as investors adjust their expectations for future economic growth and earnings. However, it could also lead to a stronger dollar and increased demand for safe-haven assets like gold and Bitcoin.</p>

<img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/WVGOBnUb/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1813" height="858" />
<p>Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/iStock-924153254-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polygon (MATIC) Price Shows Vigor, Are Bulls Up To Something?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/matic-analysis/polygon-matic-price-shows-vigor-are-bulls-up-to-something/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mudiaga Iritare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 15:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon (MATIC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon Bull]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=529695</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[May is looking up for Polygon (MATIC) price as it is seen to be in the green zone for two consecutive days. Polygon bulls have picked up steam and momentum in the new month after bears held the prices down since mid-February. Despite Polygon&#8217;s countless innovative partnerships and bullish news events, its native token remained bearish for most of the 2023 first quarter. And BTC&#8217;s impressive price movements in April were still not enough to awaken Polygon bulls, as bears remained adamant and unmoved. However, Polygon (MATIC) bulls remain resilient in their new show of strength in May. MATIC Price Gets Relief From Bulls Polygon (MATIC) bulls have shown resilience and pushed back prices after a major retracement that shook most cryptocurrencies due to a change in market sentiments of investors on the first day of May. The cryptocurrency markets, which experienced a major rally in BTC price and some altcoins in April, were met with bearish sentiments as the &#8220;Sell in May&#8221; narrative trooped in. Related Reading: This Meme Coin Created By GPT-4 Is Now Worth $40 Million, Here’s Why Polygon (MATIC), which closed April bearish at $0.97, was seen to decline further as it traded at a price low of $0.94 on the first day. However, yesterday&#8217;s trading session witnessed Polygon (MATIC) recovering as bulls stepped in and pushed back prices. According to Coinmarketcap data, Polygon (MATIC) is seen to continue from its previous day&#8217;s price recovery in today&#8217;s trading session. When writing, Polygon bulls are up 3% at a trading price of $0.98. The trading volume of the layer 2 blockchain token has also seen a near 14% increase in the last 24 hours, which may indicate buying activity from Polygon investors. MATIC&#8217;s price is currently seen to trade below the 200-day Exponential Moving Average, with bulls moving to test that area acting as immediate resistance. A break above the 200-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA), currently trending at $1.052, may see Polygon bulls pushing the price to the next available resistance. Polygon MATIC seen trading below its 200 EMA on the daily timeframe &#124; Source: MATICUSD on TradingView.com Polygon Onchain Analysis A close look into Polygon&#8217;s on-chain activity and metrics gives insights into the reasons behind its native token&#8217;s recent bullish price movements. Onchain data reports from CryptoQuant reveal that the MATIC exchange reserve in the last 24 hours is on a negative 0.46%. Related Reading: Prominent Analysts Vouch For Crypto As The Banking Stocks Nosedive A low or negative exchange reserve indicates reduced selling pressure of a digital asset, while a positive indicates increased selling pressure of an asset from holders and traders. Polygon&#8217;s exchange netflow today is low when compared to its 7-day average, which is also an indicator of the low selling pressure of MATIC on exchanges. Featured Image from Economic Times, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>May is looking up for Polygon (MATIC) price as it is seen to be in the green zone for two consecutive days. Polygon bulls have picked up steam and momentum in the new month after bears held the prices down since mid-February.</p>
<p>Despite Polygon&#8217;s countless innovative partnerships and bullish news events, its native token remained bearish for most of the 2023 first quarter. And BTC&#8217;s impressive price movements in April were still not enough to awaken Polygon bulls, as bears remained adamant and unmoved. However, Polygon (MATIC) bulls remain resilient in their new show of strength in May.</p>
<h2>MATIC Price Gets Relief From Bulls</h2>
<p>Polygon (MATIC) bulls have shown resilience and pushed back prices after a major retracement that shook most cryptocurrencies due to a change in market sentiments of investors on the first day of May.</p>
<p>The cryptocurrency markets, which experienced a major rally in BTC price and some altcoins in April, were met with bearish sentiments as the &#8220;Sell in May&#8221; narrative trooped in.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/this-meme-coin-created-by-gpt-4-is-now-worth-40-million-heres-why/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">This Meme Coin Created By GPT-4 Is Now Worth $40 Million, Here’s Why</a></p>
<p>Polygon (MATIC), which closed April bearish at $0.97, was seen to decline further as it traded at a price low of $0.94 on the first day.</p>
<p>However, yesterday&#8217;s trading session witnessed Polygon (MATIC) recovering as bulls stepped in and pushed back prices.</p>
<p>According to Coinmarketcap <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/polygon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a>, Polygon (MATIC) is seen to continue from its previous day&#8217;s price recovery in today&#8217;s trading session. When writing, Polygon bulls are up 3% at a trading price of $0.98.</p>
<p>The trading volume of the layer 2 blockchain token has also seen a near 14% increase in the last 24 hours, which may indicate buying activity from Polygon investors.</p>
<p>MATIC&#8217;s price is currently seen to trade below the 200-day Exponential Moving Average, with bulls moving to test that area acting as immediate resistance.</p>
<p>A break above the 200-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA), currently trending at $1.052, may see Polygon bulls pushing the price to the next available resistance.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/3BYTWoTA/" alt="MATIC" width="1280" height="595" /></p>

<h2>Polygon Onchain Analysis</h2>
<p>A close look into Polygon&#8217;s on-chain activity and metrics gives insights into the reasons behind its native token&#8217;s recent bullish price movements. Onchain data <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptoquant.com/asset/matic/summary" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reports</a> from CryptoQuant reveal that the MATIC exchange reserve in the last 24 hours is on a negative 0.46%.</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/prominent-analysts-vouch-for-crypto-as-the-banking-stocks-nosedive/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Prominent Analysts Vouch For Crypto As The Banking Stocks Nosedive</a></p>
<p>A low or negative exchange reserve indicates reduced selling pressure of a digital asset, while a positive indicates increased selling pressure of an asset from holders and traders.</p>
<p>Polygon&#8217;s exchange<a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptoquant.com/asset/matic/summary" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> netflow</a> today is low when compared to its 7-day average, which is also an indicator of the low selling pressure of MATIC on exchanges.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MATIC...jpg" width="350" height="250" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>$24,400 May Be Next Major Level Of Support For Bitcoin, Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/24400-next-major-level-support-bitcoin-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hououin Kyouma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 14:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin MVRV]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin short-term holders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin support]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=529633</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Historical data of an on-chain indicator may suggest that the $24,400 level could be a major level of support for Bitcoin right now. Bitcoin STH MVRV Would Hit 1.0 If Price Declines To $24,400 According to this week&#8217;s edition of the Glassnode report, the 1.0 level of the Bitcoin STH MVRV has been a point of support for the market during uptrends in the past. The &#8220;STH&#8221; here refers to the  &#8220;short-term holder group,&#8221; which is a Bitcoin cohort that includes all investors who have been holding onto their coins since less than 155 days ago. The &#8220;market value to realized value&#8221; (MVRV) is an indicator that measures the ratio between the Bitcoin market cap and its realized cap. The &#8220;realized cap&#8221; here is a BTC capitalization model that aims to find the &#8220;real&#8221; value of the asset by assuming that the value of each coin in circulation is not the current price, but the price at which it was last moved on the blockchain. Since the realized cap accounts for the price at which the investors bought (which is the price at which their coins last moved), its comparison with the market cap (that is, the current price) can tell us about the degree of profitability or loss among the overall market. When the MVRV is greater than 1, it means the average investor is holding an unrealized profit with their BTC right now. On the other hand, values below this threshold imply the market as a whole is holding some amount of unrealized loss currently. Now, the &#8220;STH MVRV,&#8221; the actual indicator of interest in the current discussion, naturally measures the value of the ratio specifically for the coins owned by the Bitcoin short-term holders. The below chart shows the trend in the 7-day average value of this metric over the last few years: The 7-day average value of the metric seems to have been above the 1.0 level in recent months &#124; Source: Glassnode's The Week Onchain - Week 18, 2023 In the graph, Glassnode has marked the lines of the 7-day average Bitcoin STH MVRV that have been relevant to the price of the cryptocurrency during the last few years. Related Reading: Ethereum Sees Inflows Of $505M Into Binance, Sign Of Selling? It looks like short-term corrections for the asset have generally become more probable when this indicator has crossed a value of 1.2. At this level, the STHs hold unrealized profits of 20%. The recent drawdown in the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price from the $30,000 mark also took place when the metric was above this level. To be more specific, the indicator had a value of 1.33 when the asset was rejected, implying that the STHs had 33% profits. The reason that high MVRV values of this cohort have usually made a decline more probable for the price is that the higher the amount of profits that the STHs hold, the more likely they become to sell and harvest their gains. From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that the on-chain analytics firm has also marked the relevance of the 1.0 level (that is, the threshold line between profit and loss) to the cryptocurrency. Interestingly, this level has generally provided support to the price during periods of uptrend. The likely explanation behind this trend is that the 1.0 level serves as the cost basis of the majority of the STHs in the market, so when the price hits this mark, these investors look at this point as a profitable zone to accumulate more of the asset. Obviously, this behavior is only seen during rallies, as holders would only find it worthful to buy more if they think the price has the potential to grow. Related Reading: Check Out This Shocking Pepe Coin Versus Bitcoin Comparison As the market is right now, the price would need to decline to $24,400 in order to hit this 1.0 level. This implies that if Bitcoin observes a deep decline in the near future, $24,400 could be the level that can provide support to it, considering the pattern that has held during the last few years. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $28,500, down 1% in the last week. Looks like BTC has seen some volatility recently &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, charts from TradingView.com, Glassnode.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Historical data of an on-chain indicator may suggest that the $24,400 level could be a major level of support for Bitcoin right now.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin STH MVRV Would Hit 1.0 If Price Declines To $24,400</h2>
<p>According to this week&#8217;s edition of the Glassnode <a href="https://insights.glassnode.com/the-week-onchain-week-18-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a>, the 1.0 level of the Bitcoin STH MVRV has been a point of support for the market during uptrends in the past. The &#8220;STH&#8221; here refers to the  &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-short-term-holder-profit-nov-2021/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">short-term holder group</a>,&#8221; which is a Bitcoin cohort that includes all investors who have been holding onto their coins since less than 155 days ago.</p>
<p>The &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-mvrv-ratio-approaches-1-5-break-happen/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">market value to realized value</a>&#8221; (MVRV) is an indicator that measures the ratio between the Bitcoin market cap and its realized cap. The &#8220;realized cap&#8221; here is a BTC capitalization model that aims to find the &#8220;real&#8221; value of the asset by assuming that the value of each coin in circulation is not the current price, but the price at which it was last moved on the blockchain.</p>
<p>Since the realized cap accounts for the price at which the investors bought (which is the price at which their coins last moved), its comparison with the market cap (that is, the current price) can tell us about the degree of profitability or loss among the overall market.</p>
<p>When the MVRV is greater than 1, it means the average investor is holding an unrealized profit with their BTC right now. On the other hand, values below this threshold imply the market as a whole is holding some amount of unrealized loss currently.</p>
<p>Now, the &#8220;STH MVRV,&#8221; the actual indicator of interest in the current discussion, naturally measures the value of the ratio specifically for the coins owned by the Bitcoin short-term holders.</p>
<p>The below chart shows the trend in the 7-day average value of this metric over the last few years:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://insights.glassnode.com/content/images/2023/05/woc-18-09-1-.png" alt="Bitcoin Short-Term Holder MVRV" width="2000" height="1152" /></p>

<p>In the graph, Glassnode has marked the lines of the 7-day average Bitcoin STH MVRV that have been relevant to the price of the cryptocurrency during the last few years.</p>

<p>It looks like short-term corrections for the asset have generally become more probable when this indicator has crossed a value of 1.2. At this level, the STHs hold unrealized profits of 20%.</p>
<p>The recent drawdown in the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price from the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-takes-a-dive-below-30000-whats-next-for-btc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$30,000 mark</a> also took place when the metric was above this level. To be more specific, the indicator had a value of 1.33 when the asset was rejected, implying that the STHs had 33% profits.</p>
<p>The reason that high MVRV values of this cohort have usually made a decline more probable for the price is that the higher the amount of profits that the STHs hold, the more likely they become to sell and harvest their gains.</p>
<p>From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that the on-chain analytics firm has also marked the relevance of the 1.0 level (that is, the threshold line between profit and loss) to the cryptocurrency. Interestingly, this level has generally provided support to the price during periods of uptrend.</p>
<p>The likely explanation behind this trend is that the 1.0 level serves as the cost basis of the majority of the STHs in the market, so when the price hits this mark, these investors look at this point as a profitable zone to accumulate more of the asset. Obviously, this behavior is only seen during rallies, as holders would only find it worthful to buy more if they think the price has the potential to grow.</p>

<p>As the market is right now, the price would need to decline to $24,400 in order to hit this 1.0 level. This implies that if Bitcoin observes a deep decline in the near future, $24,400 could be the level that can provide support to it, considering the pattern that has held during the last few years.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading around $28,500, down 1% in the last week.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/F1Uh9sQt/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1533" height="911" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/kanchanara-9pCV2MB65y8-unsplash-460x307.jpg" width="460" height="307" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
